Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Having too much free time and money can be tough, but having free time without any money is even worse.
Abare Inu / Rampaging Dog (1965)
(Inu/Dog Series #4)
I want to introduce the woman in this window
But I won't.
She is not so beautiful.
People who have free time do careless things
so please forgive me
I'll have no free time soon
No,G
G?
What's that?
it's going to be something naughty, right? Naughty...
just a little more naughty, huh?
That's a clever way to say it.
Well, after sex comes love, right?
After H comes love.
it's 'ai', isn't it? That's right,
it's 'ai', as in affection.
oh I see
I wonder if I'll have some free time soon
You know, I have a little something to consult with you about
Could you become my guarantor?
A guarantor?
What will you do?
I'm thinking of becoming a singer at that high-end club, you know?
And I need one guarantor
Is it okay if I write it as Daisuke Kamoi?
just use my name when you need it,
and my current address is...
It's the place called Rakuraku,
just after you turn at Yokochi over there
Thanks.
Oh you are here
What's wrong?
Something went wrong
Has someone started a fight with you?
No.
You were easily kicked out from RakuRaku apartment.
What do you mean ?I was kicked out?
The address I gave you earlier will be changed.
See you.
He is unreliable.
Dad, what are you doing?
Wake up.
Come on, come on,
what are you complaining about?
If you keep doing that, I'll stick the iron on your face
Please don't be so angry
This is my bed, and the blanket is mine,
so what are you talking about?
If you're going to complain,
Pay your rent! You can say after paying 750 yen for 5 days
750 yen? You can't say that after I told you to pay;
it clearly says 100 yen per day on the front
I'm going to give you 500 yen for 5 days
Stop complaining and just do it
Sleep over there?
Here?
Stay back.
Is this okay?
Look, you can see, right?
You're sticking out half your foot like that.
Is that so? If my foot is sticking out halfway, does that mean an extra 50 yen?
Of course,
if you mess around, your foot will stick out, right?
You're funny.
My long legs are not my fault
Are you really not going to pay?
I won't.
Are you not going to pay?
When you see someone's face, you should pay up
I can't pay.
Alright, can you stretch out your leg
a bit?
stretch out your leg,
Show me.
I'm going to cut off your long legs.
Don't be reckless, okay?
It's better to cut ties with you.
Come on, pay up the money
You don't need to worry about the change
I pay for him.
You should thank him
Ah, thank you for this
You're annoying.
but I'm sorry about that.
I'll pay you back when I have the money,
but you can't even work because your health is bad
How do you have any money?
Maybe you should go to the hospital?
I have a wife.
but I haven't seen her since I came to visit
She's just a woman from a family that has been drifting along
She's in Osaka for 15 days in 3 months.
She's paying you?
Can you sell this well for me?
I want to escape with her this money
Please.
It's my last hope
This is a very good pistol.
This is very pleasant to touch.
It would be great if you could sell this for around 30,000 yen.
Hey, I've become to want this ! I fell in love at first sight,
Leave it to me.
Good evening.
Oh Daisuke Kamoi.
What?
How do you know my name?
What are you, looking like a cat? I've heard about you from Detective Kimura
I am Doi who work with Kimura.
Kimura? Huh, that kid.
I gave him a raise, but he didn't thank me.
That's because I don't know your address,
can you tell me?
I can't do that,
Do you know about this pistol?
Recently, this has been smuggled.
I heard you were misbehaving.
I have no idea.
So why did you come here?
You appear by the scent of the pistol.
No way.
What are you doing
Let me read your palm.
you're quite a strange one.
it seems you're going to raise my salary again
Don't say bullshit.
If you want to raise your salary, you have to work for it yourself, you foolish person
I'd like to see your face too.
You know, I came to this shop because I need a beautiful my wife
I wonder if there's someone like that.
You will be able to get a wife soon
It really seems to be coming out like that
Don't act like that.
I'm going to sit down and come back again
You are scum.
Get out of here.
See you.
It seems pistols are widely available.
what do you want?
Hayashi-san was taken out!
What?
He was so terrible.
He is such a ruthless person.
What's wrong?
Get a grip! Get a grip!
Miyuki...
What?
Miyuki... Shima Miyuki...
Shima Miyuki?
she's the stripper from Jujo Music
Is she your lover?
She's nice woman.
whatever, call police.
Take care of him.
It's so cold.
Oh she is
Are you Miyuki-chan, right?
You know, Hayashi got shot,
Yoshio?
Why you dead?
Why?
He get taken out in one shot?
That's how it was.
The heart was slightly displaced,
but the person was already quite weakened
The bullet is still in his body?
I took it out.
Based on the bullet's residual situation in the body, the police believe there is a distance of more than 15 meters.
A bullet cut at 15 meters?
He must be pro.
We're heading to the autopsy room.
Just wait a moment.
An autopsy is not something
you should be watching
Yoshio.
Cry for me as if I were him.
He was good man.
He was not good enough for his looks.
but he was kind.
I also have a debt of gratitude of a thousand yen to him.
No way, it's not just a thousand yen
That guy left me something of much greater value, right?
If that's the case, Miyuki-chan,
It's about you.
Leave it to me.
See, no matter what happens, I'll protect you, you know
I will avenge him
Are you seducing her?
Just as my fortune-telling said,
it seems like you will have a wife.
You're quite the amusing one, aren't you?
Hayashi said he gave a pistol to you.
Don't doubt me.
It's the same type with this.
So give me.
Your face tells that.
You are annoying.
If I were to hold onto something like that,
I would return it to you in your stomach.
You get it?
He is on the criminal list for smuggling handguns.
I can't believe it.
Yoshio-san wouldn't do something like that
I will inspect your belongings.
Wait a minute,Lady first.
Well, it's a bit too much.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Wait.
Hmm, this area is nice, right?
Here.
we go, hey, go over there,
What?
it's fine, just go
Ah, raise your hand
Don't move.
Just stay still for now.
From here.
Ugh, that's tough!
It's way better than what I made
what are you doing?
Come on
Take it.
I was so scary.
Hey, everyone,are you moving out?
Hey, brother, is Miyuki doing well?
She has no family.
please take good care of her
Where has Miyuki gone?
I heard that Yuri and you are taking care of Miyuki
Yuri?
Who?
So, do you not know anything about it?
No.
In the northern nightclub tower, there is a girl named Yuri
She's a bit of a fixer-upper in this world
She's relying on her
Yuri and she takes care of Miyuki with you.
In the northern nightclub tower
Ok.
Are you going there?
Yes.
They are expensive club.
Whatever it is, I'll use my name.
Everyone, take care not to catch a cold and live happily. Goodbye.
Welcome.
Please
Please.
Thanks.
who is your favorite woman?
I want to meet Miyuki
Yes, what would you like to drink?
Water.
Water with whiskey?
No, just dilute the ice with water.
Are you kidding?
I'm serious.
Dilute the ice with water.
This is quite old-fashioned, isn't it?
There is a table charge,
What is a table charge?
When you take a seat, we will charge you
So I'm standing.
No matter it is, we will charge you
Don't say like that.
Humans are emotional creatures.
Wait a min.
Oh you are here.
Oh you are Tamachan, from the social club?
Here, I am called Miyuki
Nice to meet you
So Miyuki is you.
You're using a weird voice.
In the shop, we can only use words like this,
How are you?
What's with the 'ho ho ho'? I'm just feeling down over here
But you know, somehow you've become
prettier since you got this nice dress.
I'm taking a milk bath
Are you in a milk bath?
If the egg isn't in the milk, then you're a milkshake
Welcome!
This is Deputy Manager Onuki from our club
Regarding the charge,
it is automatically required
to be paid by anyone who enters
but I will take care of it
Sorry for the trouble.
but I'll borrow this
Don't be so distant.
Ah, Brandy
but you know...I'm going to become your guarantor
You were saying that you wanted to become a singer here,
but now you're a hostess?
That's right.
You see, the manager told me to sing, so I sang
He can't understand that.
Of course, your singing is just too good
Yes.
Anyway, just take it easy
By the way, is there another girl
named Miyuki?
I'm the only one here
Hey come on.
Is there new comer?
Yes there is but I worry if you seduce her.
Hey,come on.
Women always seduce me.
So I can't introduce you.
Sorry for making you wait.
What?
She is the boss of the Shishido group
The Shishido group,
huh? I'll remember that
That earlier one was a bit of a nuisance,
Is she?
She's just my type, you know.
Hey, your lover is right here
If you seduce her
If you get caught by the Shishido.
Shishido...
Wait a minute
I've seem That kid next to her
Please take care of this for a few days.
This is my handmade revolver, you know
If you take care of this automatic,
I can let it go for a cheap price
Hey brother, where did you get this PPK?
Is this a PPK?
It's got some special grooves cut into it.
and the steel is pretty good too
Where did you get it?
Are you going to take care of it or not?
Let's discuss the price
but I need to think about it a bit.
I want to use the phone
The phone?
641 for 53 million.
You may be shot with a pistol during the transaction.
Call me later.
Damn it.
It's best not to underestimate the police.
Stealing a letter is also a crime?
Even stealing 1 million yen or a single piece of tissue paper is a crime.
If you get arrested for just one piece of paper, that's a huge loss
No matter what you say
If you get caught, you know
The 1 million yen won't be used, right?
Oh, I see. That makes sense, doesn't it?
What?
Phone call
I see.
Well, it's finally time for work.
hey hey hey,use ashtray.
Where is it?
Here.
There's a hole.
This side here
This side, this side
Push this side, this side,
Okay?
Hello?it's me, yeah
I see
Where is this place?
Yeah, got it
So it's you after all.
Are you going to give me what you took from Hayashi who died the other day?
What are you talking about?
I came here to get it.
It doesn't quite sound like you're asking me to hand that over
By the way, who you guys?
There are a lot of you
I'm here alone, you know
That means you're going on a group trip to the hell.
Since you're a big group, I'd better give this to you.
When I die, there will be fifty thousand women shedding tears
Eventually, it will return to my hands,
see? Has it already come back?
What?
You're so great.
I'm from the Shishido group,Kameda Tatsuyoshi
Ah, this is the third time to see you.
right? That pistol was stolen by the dealer Hayashi
He was trying to use it as a way to sell without permission
Was it you who killed Hayashi?
There's no need to kill him.
It's just a rule
By the way
What?
I like your pistol skills
why not join us?
Are you an idiot?
I'm a lone wolf
Well, if fate allows, we'll meet someday
I have eyes on my back. Goodbye, alright?
I have no idea.
Tell me
I'll take out the gun
Hurry up
Did it hurt a little? Sorry about that
OK
Thank you for your work.
You were quite an honest guy
so how about I give you this medal?
I'm off.
then, you absolutely believe that
Hayashi hasn't done anything, right?
I believe so.
Yocchan got involved for the first
time to help me escape with the funds
I believe so.
Yocchan fell ill in Tokyo
After that, even while coughing up blood in Hamamatsu, Shizuoka,
Nagoya, Kyoto, Osaka, and Shikoku, he stayed by my side
Got it
The remaining doubt is why he was killed.
Did he spend the money from shooting the gun,
or he was erased because he was about to snitch?
You say that Daisuke Kamoi doesn't have it,
so could it be that the
remaining gun is possibly your gun?
If I had it,
I would be dead from that gun
Thank you for having me
Detective
He is my manager
Mr. Tachibana,
He came to visit Miyuki-chan about Mr. Hayashi.
I'm Tachibana.
Do you have any idea who the culprit is?
Oh, roughly
You should practice changing your complexion suddenly
Please come to the club when you have some free time
We will welcome you
Please use my name
Yes, I'm quite busy and broke
Ah, starting the day after tomorrow, there will be a travesty show.
The floor schedule is changing, and it seems the band will be out of the lineup?
I wonder if we'll finish early at night?
I haven't been able to talk with Miyuki-chan slowly lately, ah,
I've prepared another apartment.
You are moving there soon
If you're right next to Yuri,
it's hard for Kameda to come,
you know
Kameda?
Yes,You're making a strange face.
It's just that the boss handed you over to Kameda
I'm not a doll
That's right, you are not a doll
Since you are a living human,
The boss was in the mood to hand you over to the customer.
Daisuke Kamoi
From Miyuki Shima?
There's money inside
Dear kamoi,You haven't forgotten about Kamoi Miyuki?
I'm currently on the second floor of the Aoyama apartment
After Yoshio's passing, I am at a loss about what to do alone
Why are you grinning?
Don't read.
Hey come on.
you want to know?
Yes.
I wonder if Kamoi-sama can understand this feeling?
Do you understand?
I understand, I understand
And right now, what I heard from Kamoi-sama's mouth in the hospital was 'Follow me.'
That's not something I said
Well, I guess that's fine
I believe in that and send it every day
Oh, is that so?
Is she looking for me?
She wants to meet you.
I have to go, right?
Go go.
Alright then
What? I know,
but I understand that I've been taking care from you for a long time
That's right
then just take one for now
Thanks.
Sorry about this blanket
This is a thank you gift. Well then, please live beautifully
You've taken care of me
See you.
No matter how many times I do, it won't change anything for me
Hey, brother! Brother!
What is it?
I can't let go of this right now
I'm heading over there now
Hey, hey, hey!
What is it?
What are you going to do? I'm generally tough.
Among us thieves, this is known as the safest place.
Please be patient for a while.
Hey, look at this.
What is this?
This is a pistol called Devin.
It smells like perfume
How did you get this?
This is from a high-end kimono store
in a department store,
and you’ve hit the jackpot
That's right, at that age,
she was a remarkable beauty at 32,
but you know, from that handbag of hers
I quickly opened the clasp,
I took this off a bit, then closed it again, making sure to wipe off the fingerprints perfectly
The woman was holding this?
That's right.
Wait a minute
is there anything else in here?
This is a business card.
Ah, this must be the owner
Yuko Izumi, President of Setohara Tourism Co., Ltd
I've never heard of
this before.
This is amazing!
This is one of our top 10 so far
Wait a minute
You turn yourself in to the police
What? You are stupid.
You're making a fool of yourself,
I am currently the secretary right now
Hey, listen, this money should be returned to the person involved for now, just leave it to her.
I have my own thoughts on this
Why?
I'm still here.
Hello, Is the president there?
Oh, is that you?
I don't have your purse.
but I caught the guy who stole it and ran away
I want to talk about what's in your purse.
That's very wonderful.
What would happen if I gave the gun to the police?
Where do we meet?
I thought it was a sightseeing company, is it here?
There are a lot of gorgeous women here.
Come in.
You are very beautiful.
Is she really the president?
Yes she is.
I want  her to be a movie actress
You too can be a movie star.
No way, I can't handle being more popular than this
Oh, by the way, I've brought this.
I wonder if there was about 230,000 yen in cash
I'll give you 100,000 yen and this thief 50,000 yen.
You're so great.
I don't need money.
but I do want other things too
So
Take this
Thanks.
I want to say that, but...
I'll hold onto this for you
Come on
I'm saying....
it's annoying
You should go home quickly, it's already getting late
Come with me.
Just so you know...
That woman is holding a pistol, right?
If you fall for a woman like that, you'll end up bad, you know?
I see.
Be careful.
Thank you for your trouble
What's your name?
Kamoi Daisuke.
'Suke' does not means pervert.
Are you the master of that handgun? I'm so glad to meet you
Are you sure?
I hope you can be a great help to me
I would like your cooperation
So why is that?
Do you want to cooperate and have children?
That embarrassment is really something, isn't it?
This is a serious conversation
I'm completely serious as well
I want you to protect this tower, working together with Mr. Sakiyama
With him?
You are a big unreliable person
Well, don't be so angry.
Is this your dead husband?
Do you know why he died?
I thought you were a widow
I just thought that,
but it's not like that
This is my brother Masaki who was killed
Huh? Killed?
He graduated from a good university
Just as we were about to work on this tower together
He ended up competing with Shishido for this dancer,Yuri Fukigami
He was killed
Who did it?
The culprit turned himself in right away and was released
He was a subordinate of the Shishido group
So, it looks like settled it on the surface,
but I can't believe that hey turned himself in
I'm sure it's a substitute,
which means your brother was killed by a pistol.
He was with Yuri Fukigami in the crowded train station in Hokkaido.
He was shot with a pistol there.
Do you want me to find out who killed your brother?
I don't move so easily
No?
Will you protect this store, me, and Yuri?
I really like playing a pistol, but I absolutely can't stand killing
Besides, I think you, or rather
the president,I would like to protect you but
There's another girl I need to protect.
I'm a bit of a cheater, you know
At any given time, I make it my
motto to be loyal to one woman
Who is she?
My wife.
your wife?
We are newlyweds
But you're beautiful, so I'll think about it.
Anyway, I consulted with my wife
Huh? Yassan brought the money, didn't he?
Can you give this to me?
This makes me excited.
so I'll take it.
It seems you have a wife.
It's none of your business.
You are so handsome
Ah, in that regard, you don't have to worry,
so that's nice
You're really persistent, aren't you?
Detective can go anywhere.
You're making a big face again, huh?
Did you fall for the invitation from the Shishido group?
Or Would you like to help women in your club?
It's none of your business.
Lone wolves don't operate on a monthly salary like you do.
Hello?
You look so nice.
What's wrong?
Didn't you come here with a dowry?
Well, let's take it easy.
If you marry me,
it might turn into something more complicated
Oh, What's wrong?
Alright, here we go!
Go home.
What's wrong?
Even though there was a map written in the letter,
Were you kidding me?
If you mess with me like this,
this is what happens
So he was hiding somewhere like a battlefield
The current one is quite influenced by television period dramas
Well then, should I go with my period drama?
No worries,the ninja escaped.
I was persuaded to write that letter
I know who asked you to do that.
Shishido,right?
If that's the case, then everything
in that letter is a lie, right?
You were worried about me and told me to go home.
Don't you think I'm a reliable man?
Just leave it to me, okay?
I've received kindness from Hayashi, and I want to return that kindness
What Japan is lacking now is this human touch, so don't worry about it
I am a stylish man who dislikes the
forced selling and measuring of kindness
I'll keep going until your feelings lean this way
I'll wait.
You know what? Yuri-nee said to me.
What?
I just called Yuri-san a little while ago
I heard about this place, but she said nothing.
Someone from Shishido was nearby, right?
What did she say?
Once a woman is noticed by the yakuza,
it's all over.
Isn't it impossible for someone like me to be loved?
I'm sorry.
If I'm here, I'll be a bother.
so it's better if I leave
I know that if you stay here,
your feelings will lean towards me.
I'm going home. Goodbye
ah, wait!
See, I told you, it's a yakuza
I am a lone wolf yakuza.
What should I do?
I don't know what to do either
I don't care what happens anymore.
I don't care about anything.
I can't live on my own
I'm scared, lonely, sad,
and I want to say happy, but...
As long as this  exists, it will be a nuisance for you, right?
Or are you telling me to cut ties with this?
No, I'm not saying anything like that
I think a real man is someone who can have it but doesn't use it.
so don't just hold onto it without using it?
My deceased mother used to give me New Year's money every year, saying it's fine to have it and use it, but she always said that this brain of mine is the only thing I should really use
I didn't really use this much
Alright, I'll give it a shot, but you know...
The fact that I'm being called from
Shishido means they have faith in my skills
The club owner also believes in my playing ability,
so I'll be working.
If you ask Yuri, she'll introduce me to a job.
You shouldn't get involved with Yuri.
That woman isn't connected to Shishido group.
Well then, how about I send you to be a dancer at Club Tower?
I'm the manager, right? The two of them are just a dancer and a manager,
and if I can endure in the middle of that,
then this really isn't much.
So let's give i try.
The young people are fine
They're taking off the badge?
Of course, then let's go.
If this happens frequently
quite troublesome, isn't it?
The Yakuza suddenly move in
In the end, Customers are annoyed
it's those men of unknown background?
Kameda-kun,
what does that mean?
I have no idea what you're talking about
It's a well-trained monkey's prank, isn't it?
Monkey?
what are you trying to say, president? Well, from where I see it...
The internal people underestimated the female president's management and are pulling strings behind the scenes
What?
I'm not saying anything
Or is it that when I see you getting serious about something, was it because you did?
That's ridiculous.
Well, that story is just a story, but if Shishido group supports it, such a commotion will settle down immediately
I think the biggest challenge in managing this store is the
inability to control the power that needs to be restrained.
How about it? Right?
Yes.
I do get a decent reward for our efforts.
I can't just let the young ones eat for free
It's a shame, but in that case,
Masaki's spirits will not be recognized
That was your brother, wasn't it?
that man has been through something unfortunate, hasn't he?
That's right, one of our Yakuza just got carried away
I’m really sorry about that
That's why
Because of what happened, I'm most worried about this shop and you
It's not like I want to accompany you to this store; I'm just doing it for your sake I just want to lend you my strength.
I appreciate your kindness, but that's all
It seems that my sincerity isn't being understood well over here
That's because you care about your brother and understand that feeling
I know, but
How about taking a moment to reconsider with an open heart?
I know who killed Masaki
The true culprit of the murder is Shishido, and we can take his revenge here
Moreover, tonight's commotion was orchestrated by Shishido
Isn't Kamoi-san here?
If we have Kamoi-san working for us,
we can defeat the enemy right away.
Stop it.
I don't want to give Kamoi-san a gun
He is also patient.
no, I will reveal everything.
Yuri!
now take this gun
and go through the floor to scatter from the back
The car is ready.
I did something terrible
but it was you who pulled the trigger
The Shishido group has given you the buried money
We paid back your debt from gambling.
I didn't kill anyone
Your fingerprints are on it, you know
The boss will give you the money as promised
Now go
Assistant manager.
Pull yourself together. What's wrong with Masaki?
What do you want to say, sister?
Masaki-san, Masaki-san
Yuri!
President
Assistant manager raised their pistols, He came out the back door.
It turns out the leader was inside after all.
Hey you guys! Don't move until the police arrive!
Hey, call police
Once police arrived
Your cute feelings will disappear
You guys should be careful
I don't have anything dangerous on me.
Ohnuki has been killed
What?
Down at the cliff of the driveway with the car
that’s definitely a staged murder
If it's my turn next
You're booking your funeral, but the truth is there are people who will be taken out before you
Someone who knows the murderer of Ohnuki and Yuri
In other words, I want to make sure not to forget Miyuki Shima
Miyuki is an unauthorized person in the Yuri murder case
What if you report it to the police?
How much has Miyuki leaked to the police,
What will happen if Kameda and Shishido come out without any evidence?
The next funeral is reserved for Miyuki, isn't it?
You can protect her but you can't protect me?
If you could just hold this place together, Kamoi-san...
I want you to become a co-owner here
If you seek, you shall be given;
that's the way it goes?
You're the only one who will be dissatisfied in this marriage
I only rely on you.
I have to respond to your request.
I tell you
You won't find a man like this again
Well then, if that's the case,
Tell me everything without holding back?
Where on earth do you live?
I have no idea where you go after leaving this store,
I rent a lot of apartments.
I have to deceive the Shishido Group.
Even so, can't they find you?
That's right.
How about if we let Miyuki live in that apartment?
Kamoi-san, if we do that, you'll protect me here, right?
Well, that's probably a good idea, right?
You don't have a single penny for taxes, do you? Until recently, you were living it up,
but you've thrown it all away on booze, women, and gambling
You know very well, don't you?
I studied physiognomy.
Oh, can you read faces too?
I see, well
Thank you for the meal.
Who told you I would give it to you?
Huh? I have plenty of this.
No matter where you go, I follow you
If you follow me
then I can do business, right?
Just do it
the handcuffs will only dig into your wrists
I say! That Kamoi has it.
He said he got it from the murdered Hayashi
So,he has it, right?
Thanks.
This is because there isn't enough
food left, It can't be helped.
He is perhaps the neighbor around here,
Hello?
Is that Aoki apartment?
Is Kamoi Daisuke there?
Kamoi
Find out the name of his shoes
What are you doing?Refrain from calling without permission
Pay up properly
If I let my guard down, you call me right away.
You are stupid.
You can't take this.
The one who killed Hayashi was Shishido,Kameda
and the one who killed Yuri was Tachibana
This plan will work.
but can I leave this here?
Yeah
They might be able to watch over things for a while,
so can you do that?
I see, she said yes.
You say nice things.
Kamoi-san?
While I'm surrounded by the president's apartment,
With another woman....
you don't have to worry
I used to fall in love three times a day, you know
Recently, I only do it about once every three days,
and they just come to me
I can't even keep up with them
You always make fun of me.
Don't sulk.
I hate people who cry easily.
You say such foolish things,
Wanna be my wife,right?
I'm sorry.
Oh you.
You really are a connoisseur, aren't you?
Yuri Fukigami was shot with a compact pistol.
It's penetrating
You know the power of that shot, right?
I have no idea what you mean by never having held it like that
Or is there none?
Are you saying that I killed Yuri?
I'm pretty sure that the one who killed Yuri, Ohunuki, committed suicide
Tell me you have it or not.
I don't have it.
So was it lie?
Who did you say that to?
No, no, no, it was this morning
It was this morning
that the ghost of Hayashi appeared in my bed
Is it Yoshio's?
Don't trust him.
The ghost says that the guy I entrusted my pistol before I
died knows who the real culprit of this incident is
I can even call souls from the afterlife
What a pathetic guy
I don't even know the name of the criminal
That's your job to find it.
if you're going to believe what a ghost says, then the investigation is going to be a bit of a mess.
Well.
I'm going to make a reservation for the wedding venue now
If you have some free time, please represent as a friend
Come on, let's go!
Hey, if you saw that, just tell me!
Mention one of them, whether it's Shishido,Kameda, or Tachibana,.
the lead about Shishido's gun will come to light
Both Hayashi and Yuri were shot with the same bullet
Getting yakuza to turn themselves in is pointless.
Hey,
Sorry, but you'll need to get in another car.
Another car?
Let's go.
She wants to do business with me
I might have no choice but to accept
To protect Miyuki, I have to crush the Shishido, and in the end, the president will make me her co-owner
Well, if I can protect Miyuki, it's not bad that this shop has become half ours
Wow, that's quite a hefty piece
I used to be very famous for this skill in the police force.
Were you a police officer before?
I want to see your technique
I can fire 15 shots from this pistol at 25 yards.
It possesses shooting capabilities of over 70 points with 10 shots,
is familiar with the techniques of applied shooting, and has acquired mobility skills
Five shots in 15 seconds, huh?
So that's one shot every three seconds?
If we play like that, Miyuki will forgive me, right?
A .22 caliber revolver, that's a rare style
This is my hand made.
Shoot from the left
I'll shoot from the right,
Ready?
Ok
You can start anytime, you know
I was a little faster than you
Today, I'm really lucky.
How was it?
Anyway, Kamoi-kun is amazing.
Really amazing. With Kamoi's presence, the tower is safe
They might be threatening to kill the assistant manager
and even the upper dancers, saying I'm next,
but it won't go that way, right?
No, no, I am a man with no other abilities
I'm only good for pistol and woman.
Isn't that Tachibana, Yuri's manager?
Help me out
Alright, I'll help you, but in exchange,tell me who killed Masaki
Help me!
Kameda killed him.
Help me out.
Thanks.
Stay strong.
hey Kamoi, hurry up, hurry up!
Wait a minute.
Tachibana said that Kameda killed
Masaki-san.
Thank you,Kamoi-san.
You killed Tachibana.
Hold on, I didn't do it.
You did!
Don't joke around.
look at mine
I did it?
That's why I'm telling you thank you.
It's a .22 caliber
This is how the victim was killed.
It must be quite close since it penetrated through
I heard that his hand gun is also 22
Do you know if Kamoi had a .22 caliber?
I believe he did
You mentioned earlier that you used to have the same job as me
The reason for your resignation?
While escorting the suspect, I fell off the train with the suspect.
I see, then please contact us as soon as Kamoi appears.
Ah, Kamoi?
Where are you now?
On platform 3 at Osaka Station?
I really can't trust him.
Take this and go somewhere until everything settle down.
I really killed Tachibana?
Can you think of any other culprit?
Where is Miyuki?
I'll quickly contact her.
Go to No.3 port.
I will prepare a boat.
So hurry up, polices are at Osaka station.
See you.
Miyuki? Kamoi is in a pinch right now
Anyway, if you want to clear Kamoi's suspicions,
Tell the police about the culprit of Fukigami Yuri
and what Yuri-san wanted to say before she died
It would be better to directly report the name of the murderer of Masaki's case.
it's better to directly  go rather than over the phone
How about talking to Doi-san?
Go right away.
With this, the ShiShido group will collapse completely
The club will also thrive
Perhaps Masaki's spirit can rest
It's only Mr. Kamoi who loses out.
He is immortal.
Next, the news
Today, the police headquarters announced that the perpetrator of the murder case from two years ago was a substitute,
and that the real culprit is someone else
There is a daughter who made a delivery
That person is 20-year-old Miyuki Shima, who reported that Tatsuya Kameda,
an executive of the Shishido group, was the real perpetrator of the murder case in front of Osaka Station two years ago
Additionally, Shima has stated new facts that Goro Ohnuki, the deceased deputy manager of the nightclub Tower,
is not the real perpetrator in the murder case of Yuri Fukugami
This concludes the news
What a foolish fool, She's been hooked.
well, From now on,
I'm going to fish
You are stupid.
She's been hooked.
Alright, if it’s come to this, I’ll be bold too!
Oh! Isn’t that you, Kamoi-san?
Hey, Tamako,milkshake! Weren’t you at the club?
Are you kidding me?
I already quit there.
She apparently wants to be a stripper.
Again?
The president over there said she couldn't become a stripper.
According to the director... she could become a slipper
She can't be a stripper,but slipper?
It's ridiculous
I mean, look at this great body I have, right?
Who do you think you are?
And what are you doing now?
I am Yassan's wife.
Have you become a wife of a thief?
Don't say such things that sound bad
I quit that job.
Right now, I'm part of a sales team,The drug dealer.
Thief turned into a drug store.
Every day I'm being made to struggle
So, what are you doing now?
What am I up to?
That's because I am being chased as a murderer!
You are really cool.
Wow, you've really risen to prominence,
haven't you?
Congratulations!
Come on
Wasn't there a girl named Miyuki Shima here?
No one seems to be around at all
So we decided to live here
We've got all the tools ready
After all, She's being protected by the police
Or is the president going to take responsibility?
Alright, I can't just leave it like this. I'll come back again.
Hey, if the police arrest you next time,
What should I bring as a contribution? It feels good
Cut it off!
President, my pistol is that while I may save people, I would never kill anyone
I don't understand what kind of thinking that is
Just calm down,Mr. Kamoi.
I can't.
It's strange that a murder suspect is your partner.
Right now, I just want to say one thing as the president's appointee at Miyuki
I really are a yakuza, playing pistol and having someone killed
Goodbye,that's all I can say
Take me to your apartment
I want to see my girlfriend before I get arrested.
I can't.
Why?
We might get shot at by a car tire before we reach the apartment
Why are you more afraid of Shishido than the police?
Hey, wait, think a little more
If Kameda comes out after a 48-hour detention period due to insufficient evidence
First, the target is her
Isn't that right?
We have to wait one more day
If Kameda's suspicion is strong,
they say there will be another 21 days of detention by the prosecutor
Instead of rushing this moment, let's have a 21-day buffer.
I see.
This is a time for patience.
Boss, who said that?
I don't know
In any case, she clearly stated the location
If we go there, we will definitely find Shima Miyuki.
Where is Kamoi now?
He should be in the storage room of the tower
That's also from her saying.
I really don't want to be in a place like this,
This is not where I belong.
Well, the food is good.
Miyuki Shima was kidnapped.
Are you sure?
Kameda was released?
Yes.
If you take her back
You must accept their challenge.
I just got a call from them.
Did that kid sniff out that I'm already here?
place and time?
Here.
Well, I've double-checked the, so it's all good.
What do you want at this time?
Come with me.
I don't know what you want, though
I'm not in a hurry right now
I'll let you do what you like, so just shut up and follow me
What the hell is that?
I want you to take a look at the handgun
I can't handle this anymore
Ha, it's first time to hear that, let's go
Oh what's this
Would I be arrested for carrying a handgun?
Let me shoot it.
Wait, you can't shoot it.
Why?
only the person in charge can.
That's ridicules.
Come on.
Can you handle this?
What?
The one on the right is the .22 caliber bullet you shot with your handgun, and the one on the left is the caliber of the bullet that killed Tachibana
What do you think?
See, it's different after all
It's about the handgun, you know
Each one has its own personality
Even if the caliber is the same,
the light rays from bullets
fired from the same gun match,
but those fired from different guns do not
Therefore, the bullet that killed Tachibana was not fired from your homemade gun
You get it?
Kamoi?
He seems interested in divination, doesn't he?
You ended up searching for a great place, you know
In a landscape like this, playing gun is a delightful pastime, and the sound that comes out is just wonderful
Kamoi?
Can you please return that young lady to me?
I'll let her the train pass and go home a little earlier
Miyuki-chan, when you get home, cook a steak
Should we go to the police after a bath and eat beef steak?
I'll return the woman
Instead of her, give the pistol over here.
Give me another one.
it's going to be a big deal.
Miyuki!
Hey!
We are not dummies for target practice.
I attached what you wanted to my body using rubber bands.
Just one is left.
It's too far.
Don't move!
Put the pistol down!
Well, I’ve been saying it from the start like that.
Your ride has arrived
This is no use either,
so take it.
I'm glad.
You weren't hurt?
I see.
Kamoi Daisuke.
Arrest you for illegal possession of a handgun.
I don't have anything on me
Look, isn't it strange? Shall we go now?
Goodbye.
Manager, you really have made me into a murderer, haven't you?
You're the only one who can shoot from behind Tachibana at that scene
That's right, I found out your caliber
was 22 when we played the game
Why did you do such a blatant thing?
Hiroko is my girl
You're going to take her from me on the side
I can't stand.
I don't want to let you take Hiroko and the shop
but the president's heart is set on me
a handsome man, just like a guy on the parallel bars
It was Hiroko who said to shoot Tachibana with the 22 caliber gun.
It was also Hiroko who tried to frame you as a murderer
Hiroko was trying to trap you.
Stop it.
Moreover....
Hiroko hid Miyuki, and she was reported to the police.
Hiroko was the one who handed Miyuki over Shishido.
Even so, do you really think that Hiroko loves you?
Stop it.
You were faster than the police, weren't you?
Sorry.
Kamoi.
It seems that he has fallen for you.
so You've deceived my gun.
But I won't hate you.
I really liked your thoughtfulness towards your younger brother.
You won't be able to charm girls until you
can say lines with this kind of significance
Huh? Oh, what a handsome man
You're back again, huh?
He illegally possessed a handgun.
I'm just holding the opportunity to raise your salary
See you.
Your wife is waiting for you.
What to do....
Miyuki or gun.
Gun or women.
They are here.
What the heck?
I really can't become a decent person.
I'm going to stop being a husband for a while.
THE END