Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Bad Reputation
Early Showa period (1926-1989 CE)
I don't know who will win.
I want them to fight to the death.
Let’s go
Get out of my way
What the hell?
Shut up!
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm from Takayasu
Get out of my way
Who is doing this?
You?
What are you doing here?
I know you stole it from us
What the hell are you talking about?
Don't say bullshit
Who the hell do you think you are?
You stoke it,
Fuck you
Bring it on
I'll fight with him
Come on
Don't stop me
Fuck you
Wait!
Catch him!
She's here
People who play in this sacred place are fools.
Don't bet the birds.
It's not good to take someone's bird.
Peasants should only be peasants.
Don't think about anything else.
Shame on you!
Return the bird from now on
I returned the bird
Talk to your brother that I returned the bird
It's too bad, because I could have made some interesting bets.
There are women.
Really? Are there women?
Which Bon festival?
Takayasu
I can't go there.
I can't get along with people in there
If you're worried, disguise yourself as a woman.
Enjoy your dancing
Let's dance together
What the hell you are
Oh you are man
Fuck you
How you know I was there?
It was easy to find you
What?
You look cute
I practiced with my friend
Have a seat
You live in Nakano village
Yes
What are you doing?
Can you meet me sometimes?
I feel like the Bon Dance Festival was a long time
ago.
You didn't drink alcohol.
Really
Why you can't drink?
I have no idea
You are strong with women but weak with alcohol.
Actually I'm married
I kept it a secret.
I was the first to know the joys of womanhood.
I have your baby
In a little while my belly will grow.
Can we escape together?
Are we going to elope?
Someone introduce me inn job
It's boring for a young person like you to do nothing.
This old lady used to be a beautiful geisha.
She was popular with men.
She had a bad life.
You are still young, so think about life often.
We'll have a baby?
I don't think so
I think she miscarried.
She wasn't pregnant from the beginning.
You should go home
It hurts me
Don't hold me too tight
Never mind
Kiyo-san
I need to go home
It's ok
Then
Can you pick me up?
Don't say bullshit
I'm leaving
Where are you going?
I'll go back to my hometown
Please don't dump me
I'll start working diligently tomorrow, so stay here.
I don't care
You
Asakichi!
What are you up to?
What are you up to too?
We are on the way of coming back from Osaka
Were you in Osaka?
We had some fun in the city of Osaka and were ready to go home, but decided to go straight home after all!
Then let's play together, shall we?
Let's go!
Oh she's coming
We were waiting for you
Good evening
Have a seat
Let's have a drink together
Very beautiful women have come
Let's drink!
Where have you guys been?
I met a beautiful woman at a tea shop.
Have a drink
I can't drink
You can drink
Thanks
Are you hitting on her?
It's none of your business
Let's go out
Your name is Oi?
How do you know my name?
Your name is written on this list
My nickname is Kotoito
Were you dancer
I used to work in Hakata
Why you are here?
I also had various circumstances
Because my dad got sick
They are so kids
Did I do something wrong?
Look them in the eye and talk to them.
Who are you?
What the hell?
You'll fight with me?
Fuck you
What kind of yakuza are you?
I won't move from here
What this woman. I'll kick her ass
Stop it
Get out of here
Beat me
Do you know who I am?
Stop it
Fuck you
Beat me
Damn it
I'm glad everyone is settling in.
I was worried
If you didn't stop I would also participate
I hate arrogant people
I know how you feel
You are on the side of the weak.
Right
I wish you could help me too.
I'm sick of life like this
You have a tough time dealing with lowly customers
It's so hard
You are young and beautiful, so I think you can have an elegant customer.
You should make a lot of money and quit this job
Are you sleeping soon?
I think so
It's embarrassing to take off your clothes for the first time
Hey it's morning
What?
It's ok if you come in
What's wrong?
That men are loitering outside.
They're waiting for you guys
You
Don't worry
Have a leisurely breakfast and stand tall.
Hey, can you wait
What?
We came to get revenge last night
We don't have time to deal with you
You say something interesting
This is our territory.
I'm Sadayan of Yoshioka Group
You have shamed us.
We'll beat you guys
Run away!
I lost
It's over
Are you real Yakuza from Yoshioka group?
Hey guys. You are Yoshioka group's.
Don't fight in front of the store in the morning.
You'll pay for what you broke.
I didn’t break
You've broken this
You'll pay for what you broke.
Look this
How much?
It costs a lot
Make it cheap
It's your responsibility.
It's Ok if you pay 10 yen
Don't do this anymore
You guys are so asshole
Do you have any complaints?
Let's go
I want to go out with you guys if you forget this fight.
What?
We can't go out with you
Let's go
Hey you, can you wait?
What?
I'm Yoshioka.
This is my territory
Ok? can you come with me?
To where?
My place
Asayan
I have no choice to go
But
Don't worry
Our yakuza SADA is very powerful
But you beaten him
You are very strong
I'm not very strong.
I'm sure he's stronger if he gets serious
Stop complimenting
Where are you going from now on?
I have nowhere to go
Why don't you stay here?
Am I going to be your henchman?
I don't mean that
I'm not forcing you
I hate yakuza
You are treated as a customer
What kind of business do you do here?
It ’s like a lawyer.
We can earn money a lot
We sometimes quarrel
Have a drink and think about it.
I can't drink
Oh I see
Sada
Punish them
Chuko
Stand up
You ran away
You were scared and tried to escape
Shut up!
Forgive me
Shige
I just went to ask for a helper
Don't make excuses
Forgive me
Stop it
Don't stop him
This is our rule
This is because of my quarrel
I'm tired of hearing their excuses
They ran away for some reason
Please forgive them
Forgive them if you work with us
It can't be helped if you ask
Ok I'll work here
OK,  Sada, forgive them
I hope they take good care of me, but it's not.
It is reassuring to know you are here.
I've only known you a short time, but we're already good friends.
There are hostile Yakuza.
There is a yakuza who is fighting for territory with us
I'm his bouncer, right?
That's what I though
It ’s pretty good to live here.
I felt uncomfortable when I heard that
Don't say that
Bros, you like betting?
I like it
Shall we bet on the dice?
Ready? Let's play
Play!
One more
I bet more
I bet on cho
What should we bet on?
Everyone bet on Cho, no one bet on Han
This will not be a match
You guys are just looking at it
Can you bet on Han?
Am I the only one to put on Han?
How much?
30yen
Ok I'll bet
Ok you bet 30 yen
Ok? ready?
Play!
I'm leaving
Are you leaving?
that's too bad
I only play once
Please play more
Don't win and run away with it.
It ’s not good to play until you run out of money
You should be careful about how you speak
Do you think we are fools?
I bet all the money I have
If it was CHO you guys were taking my money
It does not mean that I win and run away with it.
What the hell this kid
Don't say bullshit
Wait
You are very funny
He just wanted you to have fun
Ok I get it, so we are leaving
Come here again
Bros
Thanks for helping me
What are you talking about?
You are fine
You are so great
It's only right that I help our friends in the Yoshioka
clan.
Yes right
Keep half
Keep it
Thanks
I'll go to Matsushima
What's wrong?
Good people like you will be gone someday.
You are just my guest
What are you talking about?
I'm here
My father chastised me last night.
Why?
Because I mistreated my customers.
That customer was a nasty customer.
He wanted my body.
I want to commit suicide
Can you escape from here?
I can't
They are watching me
You have paid holidays.
In name only.
I'd like to escape if you go with me
I go with you?
Ok
Are you sure?
But we must prepare carefully.
With you, I'm okay with anything.
Please take me to escape from here
Don't worry, Come in
I want to talk with you something
It's an emergency and I'd like you to leave.
What's wrong?
Our boss's friend caused problems.
We need to send some people
Boss asked you to go
Asakichi-san
I'm sorry
Don't do anything dangerous.
Think of me
Don't worry.
We should think about escaping later
Don't move
Thank you
Be careful
OK let's go
Can you wait?
What are you doing here?
I thought it was the last time I would see you.
I'll be OK
Don't come here
Come here
I'm sorry but can you stay here in 2F?
I'll be back soon
Wait!
He is so selfish
I don't know what happened, anyway go upstairs
It is annoying when people like you come here.
I'm sorry
Please go back
I don't want anything to do with that Matsushima gangster.
Run away!
Go backdoor
What are you doing here?
Help me
I won't make you trouble
Please
OK come in
I don't know.
Don't ask me
We'll be here until Asakichi comes back
You didn't need to because the Tennoji bosses interceded.
I didn't have to fight.
Who are they?
They are Matsushima group.
They say you took a woman from Matsushima group.
What's wrong?
Oh Sada
Do you know that Asakichi is with Matsushima's woman?
I don't know
Where is him?
I was with him but where he has gone?
Did you let him go?
No way, I don't know at all
I'll ask him when he return, and We'll send back her to you if no problem
So please wait
Ok I'll count on you, then we are leaving
Let's go
That's true.
Asakichi asked me to hide her
Really?
That's a problem,where is her?
I let her to escape
That's a problem.
We want nothing to do with the Matsushima group
Oh Asakichi
I was hiding in the neighborhood.
The problem is that you are harboring their women.
You're freaking them out.
What?
Don't fight here
I'll go back to home
Thanks
I have done you no favors.
Never mind
This is a parting gift.
Don't worry.
But I'll take this as a today's work fee
Thanks
She is in upstairs?
She's in back door
Really?
Shall we go?
Let's go
Where are you going,Sada?
I'll go to see him off
Watch out them,
It will be in trouble if they find you
I'll talk to them he is my bros
Stupid,He has nothing to do with us anymore
You told him not to play with women.
Of course
I understand Asakichi is no longer with us.
You were pathetic in your flirtation with the Matsushima group.
What?
What do you mean that Mr. Asakichi will give up his woman when he returns?
Of course
You submit to the strong, and I find that
pathetic.
Shut up!
I am ashamed to be in such a weak group.
You think so?
Do you want to quiet?
I want to leave
OK I get it
Thank you for all your help.
Let's go
Hey guys, Say good bye to them
Take care
You idiot!
Beat him!
Bring it on
Stop it!
I will be back door.
Come if you want to fight with me
She's already let her go.
Right?
Do you know where she's gone?
I don't know but don't worry
I don't worry but
Where's your mom?
She went to Koyasan to pay her respects.
She won't come back for a few days
I see
You want to meet her?
It's Ok if she's escaped
But you look down
No way
Anyway sorry for making you trouble
I want to thank you.
Let's have a meal together
That's fine.
We work at a meat restaurant
We want you to come to our restaurant
Right?
Yeah
That's convenience.
Let's go
I want to eat meat too.
May I have your name?
I'm Okinu
I'm Oteru
We are working there
You are so kind
Your mother is kind too
She's very different from Yoshioka
Really
Are you free now?
Leave it to me
He'll be fine?
Don't worry.
He's strong
Let's wait for him
Yes I know her
But I don't know where she is now
I'm not the only her guest
She could have gone out of business voluntarily.
I can't play here if she thinks I helped her escape.
Don't say bullshit
I'm Ok if I fight with you
But I don't know about her
Don't say bullshit
Drop the sword you're hiding.
What?
If you take it, I shoot the pistol
Wait, you have a pistol?
So what?
Because I'm a gangster
Ask your boss if you want to use pistol too
I'll wait for you
What's the deal?
It's ok if you win.
I will kiss your boss if I win
Asakichi
I'll drop my sward, so you drop your pistol too
Is that OK with you?
I'm OK
I know you have another sword
What?
Your subordinates are around here
They will attack me
Then I'll kill you
Oh no
You get ready to fight with me
OK I get ready
Put your sword down.
I'll take care of it
OK let's start
Just bring it on
I'll kill you
What? that's my sword
This is your sword.
I don't have a pistol
You cheated me
I'll kill you
Damn it.
I'll revenge you later
He is wanker
Thanks for waiting
Please
Enjoy your meal
I want to ask you something
What's wrong?
I want you to be my boss.
Please
What are you taking about?
I'm just Yakuza
But I need you
Stop asking that
I'm not putting on an act.
Do you want to fight with me?
Stop it
Sada
What?
We are good brother.
That's ok
Right?
Bros
I was surprised.
We were worried
Let's have a friendly drink.
Bring sake
I will
I will serve you
You are lucky to have a confidant.
He's good man too
He's a compassionate man.
No way
I'm just being good-natured.
Thanks for waiting
Please wait until the food is ready.
Here it is
Please
I can't drink
Really?
I'll drink little
Thanks
Bros
Let's make a toast to her.
We pray for her safe
They are so nice, aren't they?
Don't flatter me.
I like you
That's good for me
I know you like me too
She forces me
I won't serve you if you don't like me
I love you so much
I'm glad
Shall we get drunk tonight and stay somewhere
else?
That's good. Let's go
I've never stayed out before
Don't worry
It's bad
We can go without you
OK?
Go ahead
Thank you very much
What's wrong with Okinu?
I don't care
Oh, she is in the car
Really
You are pathetic to be crossed by your own henchmen.
I am so frustrated I can't sleep.
I don't accept what comes, but what goes, goes.
Your thinking is very naive.
So many housemates come to stay for free.
What?
Yoshioka!
Stop it!
Punching in!
I don't feel like facing you
I cut myself off from those men.
Stop it!
Help me!
I'm the first to take a bath with a man
I see
You think I'm easy?
You look happy
Yes
Your friend is dating Sada
It might be so
What happened with us?
Nothing happened
Why you've come here?
I just wanted to come
I know but
They are now couple, I don't know what happened with us
You have a woman who name is Kotoito
I just play with her
You just play with her.
You're crossing a dangerous bridge.
You are helping her escape
Why I can't help her escape?
Yes but...
If you marry me, you'll have a hard time.
I don't worry
I am traveling all over Japan
I don't know where I'm going to get killed.
So I want to be with you.
My ex-husband was like you
I like to struggle.
What if you have a baby?
I'll take care of him
You are funny
Oh my god, Sister!
Stop it
You don't like me?
I like you
So it's ok
I need you to write a pledge.
Write a pledge?
Please write that I will take care of you for the rest of my life
You make it sound as if I owe you money.
It's piece of cake
I can talk to your mother in the meantime
Is this OK?
Ouch
Oh no
I don't know where to go
I'll trust you, so Don't worry
Let's play
How are you?
You look nice
I have made my dream come true
You gave your virginity to a good man.
I'm shy
Congratulations
Shall I help you?
Well...
Don't be shy
Seriously,Will you go home after eating?
I see
Then come back later
Please
Take care
Thank you
Damn it
Thanks
Oh
Damn it
I have bad luck
Thanks
You won
I won
I see
I'll stop
You are strong
You can cheat
No. I don't like cheating
There is no loss in deceit.
Sada, by the way
They haven't come back for four days
I wonder if they had any problems
I start to worry
Alcohol is running out
Oh they have come back
Really?
What happened?
There is a big problem
What?
The boss of the Yoshioka group was attacked by the Matsushima group
It serves him right.
It's his fault
This was the original problem.
I'll attack them in return
No.
They are looking for you
It's Ok.
I get into them
But, Kotoito has been captured by them
Oh my god
She was captured by the Matsushima clan when she visited the Yoshioka clan out of concern for you.
I got this letter from her
She in Inushima
Inushima?
She is on Inushima in the Seto Inland Sea
I go. Okinu
I know.
You worry about her
But don't push yourself too hard
I worry about you
Please go with me,Sada
You'll be fine?
Don't worry.
This is my job
What's wrong, bros
You'll miss her?
No way
Money
Money?
For what?
If we go to Inushima, We have to prepare money
Why?
If something happens, we can solve it with money
Oh right
What to do if they ask for money?
We can't say we have no money
I see, but How shall we prepare the money?
I'll go to Arima
That's where you eloped.
She has nothing to do this me
Tell her parents why.
I think they will lend me money
She is here now?
She's in upstairs
I see
Oh you come back
No no.. I have a favor of you
The man below said you are upstairs
I see what you mean.
You look fine
Because you left me
It seems you are rich
I can lend you money.
What do you spend the money on?
I'm trying to help a man
A woman, right?
Is that right?
If you speak honestly, I'll lend you some money
You win
To be honest,
I'm trying to help a woman
She was sold
That's what I thought
What's this?
How did you get this?
I'm just taking care of it
I understand your situation.
But I don't have a lot of money
So...
Would you like to do something dangerous?
I'll do anything
What will we do?
There will be a gambling party in Kobe tomorrow.
I will tell you what the customer is doing
Cheating?
It's the easiest way to make a lot of money
I don't like cheating
What if they found me?
Leave it to me.
You just have to trust me
I have a friend of mine.
Can we go together?
Thanks
Wait.
Are you going back now?
You have to kiss me at least
I didn't expect
Ready
Play
It was so nice.
We made it
I'm glad it worked really well
Now we have military funds
Let's get in!
Can we get back on this ship again?
Let's go
Hey guys
You guys came here looking for a job?
Yes we do
Where are you staying?
Would you guys be willing to accommodate us?
The inn called Tokaiya is good
Tokaiya?
How they spell?
Write across the rhyme
Shall we stay there?
Thank you
Here it is
This inn is a good name
How many days do you stay?
4,5 days.
We'll stay more if we like
You'll take care of us?
You don't like me?
No way
I like you.
May I have your name?
Oshige, I'll put your tea here
Oshige-san.
Can I play with you?
Please leave if you want to play with me
She reject him
You can go to the bar if you want to play women
Thanks for your information
Let's have a bath
Please come
Come in
We’ll come here later
There are nice girls
Come to our bar
We’ll come here later
There are nice girls?
Yes. please come in
We’ll come here later
She's here
That's what we thought
What's wrong with you?
This is an island
I know that
How can we escape from here?
Of course, we take a boat
How can we get the boat?
I see.
we need to hire someone who can help us
If we get caught, we can't escape
We wish we could hide 3 days in this island
I was thinking the same
I searched various ways
I keep forgetting that this island is under their watch.
I'm not sure about the yakuza here
They may kill us and sink in this sea
Oh what's wrong?
You look unhappy
I want to ask you something
What? tell me
Who is the boss of this place?
He is a Silk hat person
Silk hat?
What's the hell?
He ran away from his old gambling debts to this island wearing a silk hat.
That's funny
He's opened this inn.
He still comes here wearing a silk  hat
Are you local?
I was born and raised here
Really?
Do you feel a sense of duty to your boss?
No
Be honest
For example ,That you owe him money.
No.. but why you ask me?
Why you' turned so serious?
You do her a favor.
Me too?
What's wrong?
Seriously
We need your help.
Please
I heard about you from Oshige
You are local in this island
I have a favor of you
To be honest
We'll try to rescue a woman
Will you prepare a boat for us?
It's very hard if you let the yakuza woman escape
I know
They already know where you are going to escape
So
The best way is to trick them into going through the easiest channel.
So please
This is money for it
It's not a matter of money.
Oh you are awake
Because I worry about you
How was it?
I asked him and he said he will help us.
That's good for you
He's being treated badly by that man in the silk hat.
Oh I see
Anyway, our plan was successful
It's a little inconvenient for the two of us together.
I'd like to stay at a different inn just for me.
Do you know the inn?
There is a inn called Asaoka near  here
Really?
It's an inn run by the master of the boatyard.
There are many bosses here
He is the boss who manages the boarding
Ok, I'll manage it
Can you work with Sada that we planned?
I'm counting on you
Leave it to me
Hi
Is this photo the same as a real person?
Yes,They are real
They are more beautiful in the real thing than in the photo
Ok, then I'll play
Please come in
Come here, Kotoito
Thanks for waiting
Is it sure that the person you chose is this woman?
Yes,she's more beautiful in the real thing than in the photo
That's true
Please come in the room
I'm fine to talk with her here
You won't stay?
I'll come here again
Don't worry
This money is for you
Thanks
Bring me beers
Yes sir
Please fill this out later
The police are strict
I get it
Kotoito,
You look fine
How you know I'm here?
Your mom wrote us
Thanks for coming
ASAKICHI and I will definitely help you
Thank you for taking care of me
It ’s very difficult to get out of here
You must not be weak.
Mr. Asakichi is planning well.
So cheer up
Yes
Can we go out?
It's hard
I see. it's hard
There is a festival every month
When is it?
Day after tomorrow
Hi
You got nice woman
Don't show off
I'm sorry
Hurry up!
Thanks for coming
We'll talk later.
Hurry up!
Hi
What shall we do?
What's wrong?
I hurt my leg at work.
Oh my god
Don't worry
Where is the boat?
We have prepared
Shall I try to drive?
Yes
Is she fine?
It's better than you drive
Oh you
Where are we going?
Go to another island and then run away
Where is she gone?
She's escaped
Ask the silk hat masters to check the port immediately.
OK
What happened?
Now is the time for the tide to flow in the opposite direction
So where are we now?
Habuya...This is where we were
Let's go up the hill once.
Please, take the boat.
We have no choice but to hide.
I did my best
I know,
thanks
Watch out your step
Hurry up
You run away,
Leave it to me the rest
I'm counting on you
Let's go
I'll go back
I'm just annoying you
What?
We are in trouble because we want to help you
It can't be helped
Tomorrow you can take a regular boat from the harbor.
They kill us or we kill them.
There are 2 ways
Welcome back
I'm back
Hey
What?
Where is the woman?
I was separated from her on the way,right?
Yes
You were with a man
He didn't like this inn and went another inn
May I come in?
There is a person in Asaoka who looks like him
Can you take us to there?
What can I do for you?
Give us the woman
I can't give her to you guys for free.
If you don't give her, you'll be killed
What the hell you are talking about?
I can shoot you
Pistol?
What's the deal?
Who wants to die first?
You?
Can you pass us her?
We can't
You guys are still young, but you do wasteful things
It would be in your best interest if you guys gave her to us.
I see
She is willing to quit her job
I does not mean that I won't permit
Once she's back home, she has to go through the formal retirement process.
She can't
I will go to the police with her tomorrow morning
So you go home
That would ruin my face.
You understand?
If you don't give her to me, I will force you to take her back.
If you move I will shoot you
Boss
If you knew I was the proprietor of this inn, you are being very disrespectful.
S..Sorry, boss
He is our customer in any case
Sorry to inconvenience you.
Let me make an excuse
Give an excuse later
Anyway leave it to me
What do you think?
silk hat-san, don't you complain?
Leave it to you
I also put my pistol away
Thank you very much
Let's go to the room
I was surprised when she came out
I was surprised you had a real pistol
Congratulations
Let's celebrate it everyone
Are you going back to Osaka,Asakichi?
I have a favor of you
I want to send her to Anjoya then
I want to make her a normal woman.
That's a problem
I am the person responsible for her
I decide her destination
I think you are lover
Well...
Don't make excuses
Let's do this
Give you a week's vacation
And you guys do some sightseeing and come back.
Yes
Promise me
Don't break our promise
I'm different from that silk hat man
I have 2,000 henchmen.
Bros,Why do you return her to Inushima?
You should never go there again
Let's escape
Think carefully during the week and decide.
I'm so relieved you guys are okay.
Is she the Kotoito?
Yes she is
Nice to meet you
I'm his wife, Okinu
She is the daughter of the house behind Yoshioka
I see
I'm glad you were safe.
I'm sure your mother will be happy
OK, everything is settle down
Can I go out with her?
OK
OK, so see you then
Cheer up,Kotoito
Thank you
Ok, Let's go
I'll see them off
What's wrong?
I didn't know you have a wife
I don't know why I went through all that trouble to escape.
I'll go back to Inushima
You don't have to go back
But...
How about going yo Tokyo?
That's good for you
I will speak to the Inushima boss with my reasons.
Before that, let's go sightseeing in Nara and Kyoto
You've never been to Kyoto, right?
Do you guys go to Kyoto and Nara?
Enjoy your trip
Did you hear?
Let's go together
I'm OK
Let's go
Thank you,Asakichi
I decided to go to Tokyo
That's good for you
Is everything okay with Inushima?
Don't worry about that
You can go to Tokyo from here
Can you take her to the station?
Sure
I'll go to Inushima
I see
Kotoito
Be happy
Please do your best
You too,Asakichi-san
I'm going
It's rare to find someone as wonderful as he is.
Please take care of him well
I will
You are a good match for him.
You made different promises.
I'm sorry
We must keep our promise
Yes
Yes?
You are going to rebel against me?
No way
I don't mean that
To be honest
I came here to get permission from you
Shut up
You look down me
I don't mean that
Don't make excuses
Do you know what happens if you go against me?
Go out with me
Come
Stay there
I will punish you.
You get it?
Sure
Please punish me
Good. I'll start
You are stupid.
Why you come back?
Say Give up
I won't say it
So what?
You are right or I am right, I am asking my body.
You bastard
Let's play to see if you're right or I'm right.
Don't say bullshit
I will not give up even if I die
I lost
You'll be good man
Your name will be popular
I'll give you this cane, so use it to go home
Now I've paid my debt.
You have nothing to do with Kotoito anymore
My name will be popular? Hahahaha
I have just Bad name
I didn't do it because I wanted that honor.
Bullshit
I won
Okinu and Kotoito
I..I won
I won
THE END