Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Amai Ase / Sweet Sweat (1964)
What's the hell!
Hi.
Yeah, good morning
Oh just lovers.
Don't do anything strange.
Stop it.
If you break this product, you won't just have to pay for it
You're young, so you shouldn't be so violent.
You don't have to deal with him.
I mean, even though Okabe-san has transferred to us, it's still a deal.
I am so frustrated.
It's okay, it's okay,
I don't care how many lovers you have.
Right?
I hate it.
What's wrong with taking the money you make now and saving it up ?
If you're upset, you can earn it back with your skills
Since we are both in business, it is no one's fault whether we win or lose
Don't you think so?
Now that you're 36, you're losing to younger women.
Even Okabe-san
He hates old women.
I have a better body than younger women.
You're just loser.
Hey. what's wrong?
Even though I'm an old woman, I'm very good inside.
I'm frustrated.
There was a big insect.
Emotions aren't necessary in business.
You talk too much good stuff
They say he is good with money and kind
Even among friends, the young people of today are different
Okabe-san is still a section manager, so he doesn't have that much money.
I think he has dirty money.
I've been hesitant to tell you that for a long time.
Now is the time for you to quit
I've been working hard for half a year now
You have to work with her.
You are the only one who is careful about Kanna.
I know a good husband, so I'll give him to you
Really?
Yes, I ran into him on the street the other day
What kind of person is he?
He is very high-ranking.
Really?
That's true,Please stop drinking too much and try again.
It's none of your business
Are there any men like that?
You will be the fourth mistress.
I don't care what number it is.
He was regular customer of us when I was in Shinbashi.
He looked so rich
But you look poor.
You're too good.
No, I called him then.
Your friend has come.
Please don't hesitate to come here.
Can you drink?
I can't.
That's a lot.
Thanks.
I heard from the bartender,Fujii-kun
Fujii-kun said you live in a public housing complex and has a large family
I live in relatives
You don't have any parents or siblings?
No.
My parents died and I was living in different homes from a young age
Now I live with my aunt's family
You're always lonely.
I'll serve you.
Don't worry.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
You live in small house?
Yes 8 members.
That's hard.
I can't imagine.
How hard it must be.
How are they?
Their family are all working hard.
They are nice.
I mean....
The bath is always ready.
What kind of work did your father do?
He was carpenter.
carpenter?
He was more like architecture.
He dies in accident.
Then your mother died?
I see.
That's enough.
that makes the alcohol taste bad
To be honest, I am putting family first
No matter what happens, creating a family is
I think it's a sin for my sons
Even if I have a second or third mistress, I have never told them.
My wife hasn't noticed anything until now
Well, that's the system I used to take care of No. 2 and No. 3 mistress.
Is that bad?
As long as my girl doesn't cheat on me,I will
never give up giving their living expenses or anything else
I'm like that.
You're so great.
it is no good to abandon a woman
I must not make a woman cry
That's my motto
Good.
It's not more but motto.
Do you understand?
Yes, by "motto" I mean...
I can't find the right words to say in Japanese,
but it's a sign
Just translate it to the meaning of the words on the sign
By the way.
Now I don't go to either No. 2 or No. 3 at all
I haven't been there.
But I've given them a house for about twenty years now,
and I think it's my duty to keep quiet if someone doesn't betray me
I'll try to serve you too.
I absolutely hate telling lies too
I don't like either.
Yes, it looks like that to me too. You seem to be the same
Just to be sure
Betray me once and it's all over.
It was the first time I'd ever been told something like that by a man.
I'd been betrayed by a man
women are always made to cry
I have a villa in Fujisawa, and if you want to use it, you can
Have you ever had to rely on someone else?
No.
Do you see a guy?
I did before.
Right? There were quite a few
Come here.
That's scary,.
Sato-chan, Sato-chan
Oh, you just got back?
How was it?
Yes, I thought you were coming back last night.
But suddenly, I decided to go to Miyanoshita.
Hakone?
That's good.
He bought me this and I was supposed to go home
Suddenly I changed mind.
You gain a lot.
Here it is.
Yes, there was a lot of thunder here
But rain doesn't stop.
I'll go take a bath before then
Let me listen more about it later
My tie got wet?
I'm going to wash it all later anyway,
I'll just pay for the washing machine.
You didn't sleep last night?
Hakone was not crowded?
there's an open-air bath in Hakone late at night, no one was there.
When I soak in hot water, my legs look slim and long
I look like a mermaid.
What are you talking about?
I'll get some money from you.
That's enough.
I'll be back soon
I came back and had to return my kimono
He was there?
Apparently.
Thank you very much.
What's the hell?
Did you make a deal?
He was like "I'll let you stay at the villa"
That's good.
First, let's have a toast to thank you
Yes,I am thirsty?
It's hard to pretend I can't drink.
Congratulations.
Thank you for your help.
It tastes good.
I am thirsty
I have received my monthly payment.
Never mind.
You...
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not doing this for the money, it's just for you, don't get me wrong
He is just old man.
I'll thank you
You don't have to.
Let's have some fun tonight, shall we?
Let's have fun.
I'll be your strength.
I'll be kept man from now on?
I'm feeling lonely.
The mood is sad
I don't want you to take my money.
I can always break this story.
If there is a man in power, there will be no women's fights.
Even if you think about a girl's happiness after you turn 40, there's no one to suit you
Aren't the two of you the future font?
I'll make a lot of money now
I'll think about it. It's a good idea,
but are you confident that you can do it alone?
If you can just act as a bridge, then okay
Then let's have fun  tonight.
I guess there's a mood.
Yes, about my body getting stiffer
It's hard being a woman in a place like this,
So where we can have fun?
They are going to come back..
It's okay.
You don't know What kind of feelings does a woman have.
What's the hell?
So, are you waiting in Ogiya?
Are you all too close?
Then We'll take a taxi and go somewhere
Then, see you at the taxi stand on campus at 10:30
Open the door.
See you then.
Oh my god.
Soon all of these house here will be removed
We have to move out.
Everyone will move to the shopping center, right?
I was told the food and beverage district is in the basement.
It will be too small.
Have you seen Oume since then?
Oume?
I guess She returned the kimono and haven't been here since then?
She didn't come to see me.
She quit.
I see, I see, that's it
Some bar has moved out.
But they can do business in the shipping center.
The royalties are expensive.
You worry about the money?
What time?
12:15.
On no.
The rent...
that's how it is
They say it's going to be ours but I don' know how many year it will take to pay back
Are you waiting for someone?
wouldn't she be there? She'd be drinking somewhere
Damn it.
I was waiting for you.
This is the taxi fare. Go get it
Apparently you are not the kind of woman I had in mind
I thought I said that if you lied it would be the end
Who would do that for you?
Anything ok.
I hate women who betray other people's actions the most.
You're pretending to cry.
I won't be fool.
It's no use anymore, stop it
You're not kid.
I am really my aunt's children
Who told you about me?
So you're not lonely,  you have a mother and a family of eight, right?
You're hiding the fact that you have such a large family
It's ok but
If the 17-year-old girl is the aunt's child...
The 65-year-old woman given birth at 48
Right?
She's 70...
She gives a birth at 53?
No. 60.
Is that problem?
You said No?
You told me you were 30.
If you had a 17 year old child, you gave a birth at 13.
You are mean.
Don't say that.
I'm not happy at all
Depending on how you act, I think there may be
sympathy
Go easy on about one of the children.
I don't intend to ask you to do it for life with that , how about one year contract?
What do you think? I'll do my best to serve you
I'm going home alone
So please bring this.
In return, please don't call me anymore.
That car has arrived
I'll take a bath soon.
so thank you for your help
It hurts.
Umeko-san has returned, What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Get up.
Ah, this is my cloth.
Give it back.
You wore it while I was at school
My red pants have disappeared too
I'm upset ? I've ironed it properly
Is it okay
Ah, skirt, skirt, skirt, skirt.
Umeko-san
I tell you.
Did the teacher only tell me.
He said he wouldn't give me the score book because I didn't pay tuition for six months.
Yeah, put yourself in that position
And then I have to take the donation money before summer vacation.
I haven't even paid for this month's flowers yet,  I'm so pissed.
I told him to tell my parents
I know.
I gave the letter to your mother
My mother blew her nose at the letter.
What the hell is going on?
You're awake.
Don't disturb me.
If you just look at my face, you say about money.
I really don't understand.
It happened occasionally If I don't say
this, I won't be able to say it properly
It's a good time.
Did you study?
You act like a mom.
I don't seem to be flunking out.
Is that true?
It's still 1st semester.
I see.
Be quiet.
Get out.
He tells me to pay for food.
I'm mad.
You're our child.
Well, that's why you don't need to worry?
well..
Keep sleeping
I'm really not feeling well.
I won't eat here
Everyone has to work to survive.
I hope I'm fine.
but I can't be bothered with you.
I know there is lunch.
Don't say things like that
If you hate me, hate me
Well, that's how it goes
Take.
How about monthly tuition fee?
Not yet
It was rebuilt while I was away
Going to the pool.
You need bus fare to go skating
Even I, who go to the hospital
have to pay for medical expenses,
it's already too much for me
And when you started going to high school,
Toke-chan's requests started to get more and more...
The cost was more than I expected.
It'll be 5,000 yen for four people: Jiro, his wife, the child, and the baby
I'm running out of money for food too
My medical insurance has expired.
I just found a plumbing job
That's good that Sanpei goes to work regularly at the printing factory
If you get married, you'll probably leave anyway,
and I won't be able to have any more grandchildren living together
Even if We work together
it won't make me 10,000 yen
From laundry and sewing to the kitchen and grocery shopping
It's not easy.
You've been taking care of your grandchildren.
You also have an eye condition.
If I go blind, I'd rather hang myself
Why you guys are repeating like that?
Shut up!
Oh,Who dropped my wallet and took out?
It smells bad.
I borrowed.I'm going to wash it and return.
I put important things from school in there
Isn't it okay to just put something in.
That's ok.
I just borrowed it.
You're causing trouble us.
Don't cry.
It's hard to understand.
Don't give up.
Madam.
Is it bad to have a daughter in her parents' house?
parents' house?
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it
We've been taking care of you guys from Kobe days.
We were drifting to Tokyo, where our grandmother was born
Don't be ungrateful.
I'm really her son.
After my dad fell off the grass and my brother was killed in the war
For the sake of everyone, I've been working as a cashier at a bakery, working in a restaurant and a coffee shop since I was 15 years old,
but I still am like this.
I worked a night job to raise you guys.
That is compulsory education.
I also made money through small business.
When I was young, I would make money but then spend it all right away.
Now we are working
We're in the same boat.
Prices are rising.
You don't want to be treated like a big shot just because you paid a little money.
It's better than nothing.
You can't even take care of her daughter
you don't have to complain about me
I won't.
So I won't let you do anything like a wife
We do the same and get up the same way
You're still 65 at this age.
What do you mean?
you're still young?
Thank you so much, you caught sick person.
Get out.
I'll do it.
It hurts.
What's the hell?
It's all my fault
Stop it....
How embarrassed we all are
Drinking every day, fighting, sleeping on the road
I hope she'll come back soon.
The other day she was walking around with a different guy
If she comes home
She has no work.
So I told her not to have a baby.
Is it really that much of a hassle to have me at home?
Who made me this way?
You all ate a lot of the apples I bought.
I bought a lot of rice.
stop it.
You all depended on me while I was working.
Why do you hate me now?
I'm willing to sell my body
I want my son to go to college.
Yeah, I get it, I get it, sleep.
And I'll have Take-chan take a look at it
I'm going.
Even if I try, I have nowhere to go
It can't be helped.
I can't move out.
The customers will gradually be sucked into the basement of the shopping center
I can't do business in this store any more.
Let's eat for a second
I skip lunch because I got fat.
there's ramen.
Give me one bottle.
Is there anywhere good?
I said I'd be happy to thank you if I could bring in some customers
I can earn money to drink
Your customers will pay even if they drink a lot.
If I get him to drink a lot, I'd like to thank you.
We have no choice but to do business like that.
But you are going to destroy your body
That's fine.
I know some friends who like flowers and mahjong,
so I'll bring them over here.
They drink alcohol even if they lose at gambling.
It would be a great help to us if she could take some customers with her.
I wish I could do that
You can just drink and walk around
it's quicker than finding a husband
This is much better.
Yeah it's easy.
That job is better for my children's education.
You are retiring from your current job.
so I'll try to do it.
I'll ask some
Please bring that guest with you tonight.
Please, that's good
Oh please
There's no excitement in a match.
Yes yes yes
Brother, Do you sell fountain pens locally?
I'm thinking about doing business around here.
I'm home.
There are a lot of people here.
but it's okay, Ta-chan
Take.
No, I thought that was
You have grown so much
You're already adult.
Thanks
Her mother is sloppy
Don't say that
I still sleep with her
I guess she feels lonely.
Until recently, she was drinking my milk.
Don't say that
What are you doing? Because I'm hungry
Is there nothing there?
There's nothing.
I was studying for exams with everyone in the library
You didn't say that.
I told you that if you weren't there when dinner was being prepared,
it would all go to waste
When can we count on you?
I'm going to be leaving early tomorrow.
Prepare bed.
You're doing great.
This is my side business.
Monday is white, Tuesday is yellow, and pink is Sunday, and then Saturday comes
Also, what day is this red one?
I wonder what day it was
Take.
What?
When will there be red pants?
I don't know
It's none of my business
It's easy work.
Even if I work hard, I won't make 500 or 600 yen a month, not 1,000 yen
I have kids so
You need to clean up.
Yes, yes, sorry
I'll help you.
Oh, sorry
please put it on top of the food
Can I put my bed here?
Please, please.
Please move from there.
it's a little small so...
Let's all go to the health center tomorrow.
The construction will be finished soon.
That's great, brother. Let's go. Shall we go? Let's go.
That's enough. Good night
I think you should go to your friend's place
It's too late.
you'll have to turn the lights on every night
Everyone can't sleep
even the auntie over there, she wake up early
Tamako's too
I'll turn it off.
I would be happy to take in Take-chan,
but with his mother there, it's no use
That's what people say
I wish you had no parents.
Yeah.
Please don't bring drunk people into this house.
you don't know the hardships of children
I made some rice balls and they're delicious
Ah, I wonder if I should eat some too. Thank you
Then let's do that.
You don't need to thank.
I owe a lot to you
this summer vacation I'm going to work part-time at my wife's crayon factory
Then see you later
, yeah, I'll be waiting
Make me some miso soup tomorrow morning
No.
You have an exam
You have to eat properly.
Oh well, wait until tomorrow
Please try not to fail
It's a close
try your best
What time tomorrow?
at 7:30
How about you?
We can go out with take-chan together.
Hmm, she's early for a pickle shop
I'll put up the sign tomorrow
I'll go early tomorrow and pack
I should have worked instead of going to high school
Yeah.
so let's do our best
What's wrong?
Hi
Let's play.
What?
You're going to have to pay again.
It's free.
It's free?
Let's go
I don't like it.
I'll treat you to dinner later.
I gonna play.
She is pretty good
She's stylish
Does she buy her own clothes?
She doesn't spend that much money
See, that's right
She has a swimsuit.
She has a sexy swimsuit
I'll buy her a new swimsuit.
Hi.
She is pretty good
Just to play
She has good athletic ability
What's the hell?
Thank you for waiting.
Please eat a lot
Hi Ei-chan.
It's been a long time. I wonder how many years it has been since then?
Let's talk there
Who?
1,150 yen is needed.
Where did he go?
He's thinking of going to Tokyo for work soon
So he's here now.
Shall I introduce you?
He's Tatsuoka-san
I see.
I can't find him.
Were you looking for him?
Then I'll take 1,150 yen later
Do you have 150 yen?
I have 50yen.
100 yen.
Where did he go?
Shall I cancel this beer order?
Don't say bullshit.
You have money, right?
I spent a lot of money on Take-chan
I will pay for 30 yen.
Thank you very much.
Because you said you wanted to come
Where did he go?
Stop it....
Please pay attention to his behavior
Well, I met a rare person called Tatsuoka
He knows all about us.
He also knew about Umeko's past lovers.
You
I have to pay the bill.
I paid.
I see
Thanks.
Be quiet.
Yoshi-chan, you have to be strong,
you have to be strong
What are you talking about?
Ah, give me your hand.
Were you waiting for your mother?
I guess that can't be helped
Seriously, You have not become less tolerant of alcohol.
You're probably drinking even more.
I can't understand you
She is your parent
She should sober up outside.
Ah, give me your hand.
What's wrong?
Are you coming home in the morning too?
No.
I'm scared and have been outside since 1 o'clock
I'm scared because my sister's brother is in the house.
He does some weird things to me.
What happened?
I can't tell you.
Why?
Why can't you remember?
My voice was like a rattling electron
That's a bit suspicious.
Your daughter was attacked.
He attacked you?
Yes.
You say it easily
You are a virgin
I don't understand him.
He's married.
Your brother's wife's brother did something strange to this girl
Oh my god.
You should kick him
She seems to have been waiting outside
Take care of her.
I've been running away.
You lost your virginity
No.
I ran outside
I was surprised.
Mommy is looking for an apartment?
Yes.
Just leave home like this. I've been saying that for a while
You wouldn't find it
We definitely leave the house
Even if you say that, the deposit and the thank you money are expensive
Takako's aunt said she would be happy to take care of Take-chan.
You were flattered.
But she said it wouldn't work if my mother was there.
If he bought this for me, it will be expensive, so that's smart, right?
Hey, I'm going to use this carefully now,
because I don't want to be bothered
It's a bad habit to complain and take the blame for someone else's actions
I would buy a bag like this anytime.
You don't do anything parental.
You get angry when someone sympathizes with me.
I want to do many things for you
I never asked you to give birth.
I sobered up.
Come on, let's take you home
aren't you supposed to be staying the night?
I'll go to the kawabe tomorrow and clean it up
I hope you come to my house and rest in peace
We're both in the same boat.
Take
I don't want to go home
I once had a crush on someone.
He was a store manager in Kyushu.
Wasn't he from Shimizu?
So he was on a big ship.
It went all the way out to the East China Sea,
and he caught shrimp, tuna, and tires,
So?
He died.
I met him in Kobe.
and it was decided to follow him to Kyushu
I did leave this child with my grandma or something
I was twenty-three years old
He was 28 years old and the eldest son of a sailor's family
For me, I was at a crossroads where I had
to decide whether to grab happiness or not
Is that the end?
Yes.
I just mentioned that person's name,Takeko is always angry
I'm home.
Welcome back
Oume is still sleeping?
Yes.
She looks like an owl
She's  awake at night and taking a nap in the day
Have you done?
It's easy, you've already taken it off
Well, May I have some water?
Here's a glass
If Umeko-san leaves the house, she won't be of any use to me.
what's going on.
On the second day, I brought my kid
After ten days, I got up and left again.
For work?
I don't know.
ten days
I was still young, about 18 years old.
You were reckless.
What happened?
No matter how young you are, you can't just go out like that
All I have to earn is milk
Hey, you're sleeping here,
But you gave a birth.
It takes courage
It's just the way things are
But you thought a lot about yourself.
Raising a child is hard.
Where did  she go?  To the factory?
No.
She went to the pawn shop
She put this baby on me again, no matter how many years pass, I'm still taking care of this baby.
They used it for Takeko even though they had been playing with themselves
What's the hell?
Please don't fight again
She doesn't care about her brother
How many days will she be here?
Takeko?
He seems to have attacked takeko
Really?
He teased her.
What's going on? What were you doing in this small house?
I was asleep though
That person is still planning to stay here for 5,6 days more.
I thought she was a kid but she wasn't
Let him go home.
I can't say that because I didn't pay for the food.
You start again
By the way, Eisaku-san was at the center
He met that guy named Tatsuoka who used to come to my house a long time ago
Who?
He often came to the store
I see.
I wonder what he's doing now
It's none of my business.
I'm home.
Ah, welcome home
What's that?
Ah, that's just practice for tomorrow.
Your school's?
I borrowed a tape recorder.
I'm a club committee member, so I'll bring it tomorrow.
I'm hungry
Eat some pickles.
You're stingy
Is there anything else?
It's fine
I'm used to it anyway.
This is awesome.
Do you know the house called Okesa around here?
Do you know?
Ogesa?
We don't know.
Hey Ogesa i, over there
over there
oh, I see
Is this the Ogesa store?
something I can help you with?
I heard she works around here
Who?
her name written as Umeko
Umeko? Ah Oume.
They told me to go to Ogesa
I wouldn't know when she'd come back.
We are in trouble.
should I leave a message when she comes?
Yes, that's right
I don't know because we can't open the bar.
Should I tell her when she gets home?
Yeah.
I'll tell her that.
Is that fine?
This is awesome.
What are you going to do with it?
You did good job
Are you okay?
This is not crime.
This is a hobby if I do this.
I don't get it. .
Please insert this
Are you making money?
No
I'm filming you too.
No way
Don't think about strange things.
Shut up!
This is it, do this, do that
I get it, I get it, it's easy,
What are you going to do with it?
Shut up!
Tell me
Get out.
I'm counting on you.
OK
If you put this over there, it will do a good job.
Let's do this job for a while..
It can't be helped.
Are you sure?
It's going to be a good business
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
It's been ages.
I knew it
I asked about you
I've been searching around here and there for a while now
When did you back to Tokyo?
I go and out
Take a rest somewhere?
that place is just right.
I miss you
I was about to miss you.
You've gained weight too.
I'm glad you came.
Wanna change your clothes?
Yeah, how many years is too long? Thirteen or fourteen years?
I thought it was wrong to rely on you like this
I heard you were working so I assumed you were already married
What are you doing now?
I’ve even raced in keirin before
I put a lot of young things there, did some cleaning, and did some shed work
Now I'm letting him running a pachinko parlor.
hello?
Yes, here are the snacks
You are considerate.
Would you like to take a bath?
I got covered in dust over there.
So as soon as I got ready, let you know.
You made a lot of money today?
What?
What were you thinking?
I was in a good mood right now
Let's remember the time in Kobe
Having a dream?
Have a toast.
Nice to see you again.
It's been a while since I've felt this way
How is everyone?
Yes, how about you?
I have 3 sons
In Tokyo?
They live in Kyushu
Do you go back home sometimes?
No, I live most of it in Kobe
I've changed, haven't I?
But why didn't you get married?
I can't.
Why not?
All I thought about was my kids and I became an old lady.
Why did you think that?
Oh, is that okay?
It's fine here,
but it's bad. It's a bomb
Because I'm in mood?
Drink more.
it's boring.
You are so cute when you're drunk
I'm not drunk yet
Why did you quit the ship work?
Since then, there have been many captures of fishing boats.
So my parents' boat was taken away and I couldn't do business.
I had no choice but to go to Kobe.
That must have been a struggle
Let's stop talking like this.
Excuse me.
the bath is ready.
Let's take a bath together for the first time in a while
Give me a towel
Yes, yes, right now,
Yone-chan, can you get a bath towel?
I'm late, sorry
Look at this.
Hey, I can put under that bed, right? Oh,
there was something like that
But what about the Master ?
It's fine today
Oh.
But you just brought this, didn't you?
You've already brought a guest
You work too fast.
I guess I'll just leave this here and there because it's so cold
I have to hide this.
Oh you finished?
It's just to remove sweat
Do you want me to wash you?
I'm embarrassed.
You're adult
It was good
Hug me.
Get stronger, yeah yeah
Faster..
More.
Ready?
Stretch your back
What's this?
This is some kind of recording.
What is that?
What is that? You bastard!
Where are you going, Take-chan?
I have something to ask Ume-san.
What's wrong?
On foot?
I have no money for trains.
She took something important that I borrowed
If I don't get it back today, I'll lose it
What's the problem?
I'll see you again.
I'll get mad.
I see, so that's the kind of business you're in.
Is that bad?
What?
You are stupid.
You're asshole
Don't get angry and apologize!
I have not taken the tape yet.
What was the song?
I just entered for dance practice,
so who is that guy behind you?
Forgive me....
You ruined my mood.
That's enough.
As a man, any more insults.
don't say .
Just doing this
I thought that doing it with you would be the most realistic experience
I gave in to temptation.
As a man, he went out of his way to visit his ex-girlfriend
I want to show you this kind of shameless behavior
Stop it....
what are you going to do?
I hate myself
If you think about it, it's obvious
Of course
I really hate myself.
Well, it can't be helped
But the fact that you've fallen like that
I'm responsible for it.
Why did you say something so kind to me?
I'm sure you had a lot going on
Actually, You remember Takeko?
I thought we would somehow find a place to live together
I have to pay monthly rent for an apartment anyway
If possible
I could buy a house
Are you looking for a house?
that's not impossible
But people live there and they won't leave
Is it in your house?
I lent them.
He doesn't leave easily.
Well, then,  you manage your business and moving there?
That's a great offer.
You can quit this job.
Takeko will be glad.Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Let's talk about it later
Better put that thing away
Yes
Wanna record again?
No way.
I'll just take it
This is Kaneko.
I thought I had to come and see you, but then...
Well, my wife seems to be doing well
I'm thinking of going to the hospital now
I let my child go first,
but anyway...
There's nothing wrong with her body. It's a brain disease
I don't know when she suddenly feel unwell, no,
There's no need to visit
There's actually something I'd like to discuss with you
Well, I'm worried too, but I have a few more things to say
Can't you come out and relax for a while?
I don't think that's a bad.
If your child is in the hospital, that's a good thing
And there's someone I'd like to introduce to you
Welcome.
They are not lawyers. They're women
Anyway, I'm going to aim for it
I won't say joke.
make sure you have a seat somewhere cool
when I put the hair dryer in,I got sweat.
Is this your friend's?
I asked my friend who worked at beauty salon
You look young.
Thanks
I need you to take this seriously
One more beer
Be careful.
I firmly reject this as a married woman
I'll leave that to you
Here it is
I took up two rooms in Kozu
Now is busy season.
If we have separate rooms now, that's fine
I was thinking we could talk it over slowly
After all, it's a head diseases.
I don't want to spend my money this way for the rest of my life.
Even though things have settled down now..
Yeah.
For a long time now, whenever she gets discharged from the hospital, she get sick again
Isn't it hereditary?
doctor said it was menopause.
I've had so many problems
That seems to have made me angry and I can't do it at all
It would  be better if she die...
that kind of thing will help her live longer
Nobody comes there to buy shoes
I know you thought you had left
and think about your future behind
Can you make it through it?
I'm in difficult situation.
We'll think of ways to prosper
if you could consult with this person and take on the management side,
it would be good for both of them
Well, let's talk slowly until we understand each other
If you still want to quit after that, that's fine
Thank you for your kindness and for causing me so much worry
No, it's because of our convenience
I've asked you to come here to come up with a solution for both sides
Ah, stop here then
Please take this.
That's enough.
If you call Kyutaro, I'll have him deliver money
Sorry to bother you when you're busy
Even if you do go, you can take your time and then decline
if you think about it carefully
Well, I'll be off then
Yeah, but it's pretty sudden, I have a family, sotoo
I think it's impossible to make a decision
I don't feel like making your wife cry just to get into marriage.
what is Tatsuoka's thinking?
We don't have to get together
He'll take care of us?
That's right.
It feels like the path is opening up
I also think he is a savior
That's right.
Please come over here
Oh please, please, please, please,
It's over there.
We'll reserve two rooms for you just for tonight
He said he has an appointment tomorrow
We can stay different hotel tomorrow.
So, excuse me for tonight, I'll talk to you again tomorrow
Good night
that's not a joke.
You're club member.
How much is that?
It costs 15,000 yen,  It's not mine.
It's irresponsibility
What should we do?
It won't be in time
It's your fault.
What are you going to do?
But then It'll be responsible for everyone
You'll pay for it.
That's why I'm apologizing
If you apologized ,the tape recorder back?
so I could record some songs on it
It's your fault.
Is it possible that your family members don't know?
Well, maybe your mom took it to pawnshop.
Well then, why don't you bring it out?
Please bring it out, poor thing.
It's your parents' fault.
What on earth happened to your mother?
Please tell everyone that I'll come back sometime
My grandma said she went to talk to the neighbors,
but it wasn't worth the trouble of having someone call her,
so I guess the man is still there
Please be careful when I get home.
Don't worry.
Should I ask about the recorder when I go there
Everyone else is pretending not to know anymore.
Goodbye.
where are you going alone in the middle of the night?
I was hanging out with a bunch of friends.
It's getting late so I'm walking home.
Where's your house?
My house is nearby
Where?
Yamashita.
So be careful
Calling.
Hello?
Oh, it's Take-chan?
Did the people at home say anything to you?
Are they looking for me?
They haven't called me about anything.
I see.
She's tired after all.
I took the day off today
You didn't have to.
I was worried.
If someone comes, I'll pretend you are not to be home.
You have to eat,
my heart is full.
but you're not eating anything right?
Shall I reheat it for you?
Don't worry.
I have a headache
How can I buy a tape recorder?
What if I find a job?
I wonder if there's a place to live for work.
I think I'll just go back to part-time school
If you work, you'll find that it's hard to take care of yourself
but I don't want to go to school now
Hey, what are we going to do with this?
I don't know
Where is Tatsuoka-san?
Where is my item?
Your wife came to get it.
We paid the money and made the deal.
My wife doesn't do that.
She said you have a mistress.
She was very angry.
She's nice
Where is Tatsuoka-san?
Shut up!
We're just doing what we're told.
Please report your dissatisfaction to the person in charge.
Is that a pachinko?
It could be.
So Tatsuoka-san need someone to do it?
It's none of your business.
All my stores are gone.
So Tatsuoka-san deceived me
Go outside.
Come on.
Ok get out
Do you understand anything about this store?
This is just for sleeping.
What?
Bros.
Good morning.
This restaurant is great.
How many tables will you have?
With that in mind, we will place an order.
Did you order?
This window will have a seascape painted on it.
It's really nice
So, I plan to have wives in their seventies or eighties
We were deceived
Who's she?
Tatsuoka's girl from Tokyo
This was where we were supposed to live
Who is she?
I have no idea.
Who are you?
What's the hell?
Tatsuoka told me to manage here.
He said I'm gonna manage this place.
Please talk to him directly
Let's go
Where is Tatsuoka ?
It's troublesome when things are different
What are you doing?
Hey.
Get out.
But it's a bargain
I think this place is very good
Really.
I called and they said he was there,
I am so angry.
He was the one who got me out of gambling,
He took my store and took it over in a planned way
He used you
That's the kind of person he was.
I was also an idiot
I have a crazy wife
How do I restart at this age?
You were deceived by him too.
It seems so
I thought it was strange, but I didn't think you were bad
I let my guard down
It can't be helped.
I was made fun of because I'm Korean.
More Beers
He's connected the Matsuda gang.
I will not be afraid to take revenge.
I can throw my life away either.
I don't need to live
I'll wait for him here and get my revenge.
See you.
Well, I may not see you again,
but please stay healthy
You too.
Thanks to you.
it was like a fun dream
At the very least, I'll remember it as a fun memory
Umeko.
She's been going crazy like this for about four days.
Sorry
Please eat.
Umeko
A member of the Jindo Club is visiting.
We are moral Club
She wants you to join her group.
That's good?
She'll be right away.
I've been a guest here for a while now
I finally felt relieved
All the kids went to the beach today.
Apparently Takeko's been staying with a friend
so I haven't seen her around lately
it's summer vacation.
I heard she won't be coming home
The Morality Association is a very trustworthy organization.
I invite people who are worried about various things
The membership fee is 100 yen, huh? They give you pamphlets and books at cost
Five hundred yen can brighten up the problems in your life
It may seem a little expensive, but it's actually cheap
People with personality problems can improve their character by practicing this type of religion.
Yes,that's it.
So people who cause a lot of trouble to other people
I'm very grateful.
I thought that bad people were just born that way
I guess they don't even try to fix it.
That's what makes them spirit of self-denial
That means no effort has been made
So the love you have with your children ends up in conflict with your family
That's too bad.
Now I'm here, so we try our best.
If my eyes get crushed , I'll probably pay for the funeral myself
Until then,
So.
I feel sorry for your.
You have to be a good son. You're still young
You have to try somehow, even now
That's right.
I'm not saying anything bad, so try it.
You should think about your own future and participate in this meeting.
That's better than sleeping at home.
I don't mind either way
You have to go.
Thank you very much.
People who suddenly become different people are like that
I hope she gets better.
It's cheap.
Are you working now?
I'm on work.
It can't be helped.
Yeah, she always stayed over at her friends' houses because her parents are bad.
I can't scold her too harshly.
She is already 17 years old
She is very rebellious
Thank you very much.
I'm going out because I have an appointment.
See you
What?
She is very hopeless
Please come back here soon
What's the hell?
Everything is doing well.
Well, when you display it like this, it doesn't look like a used item
Bros.
Hey
what's wrong?
My wife noticed about here.
She asked me who's in charge here.
Let's go
For tonight.
What are you talking about?
Instead, I'll let you know something.
Kaneko is going to kill you
I don't care about people like you
If there was a commotion like a murder,
We are also inconvenienced.
Let you know.
Thank you very much.
Let's talk slowly tonight
I didn't know you were that kind of guy.
What are you talking about?
but life is important
Wait at coffee shop over there
I have to go
Hold on.
I'll have to go back to Kyushu for a while, otherwise I'll have to take care of things
Then I won't come back for a while.
Please go home
I don't want you to come in front of me again.
What's wrong?
Run away!
Stop it....
Bring him out.
I'm unlucky
I lost everything.
I was so close to having my clothes ripped off
That is my house.
I envy people who have a house.
Are you related to Section Chief Okabe?
No way.
He was fired for embezzling company funds.
The police came to investigate
Okabe's crime was discovered
I took a sleeping pill. It didn't work?
You idiot.
I was trying to stop him.
But I almost died
He did a good.
It's hard.
Oh well
, that's fine, that's fine
It's hard to walk.
They sleep like the dead.
Are you okay?
Don't step on their heads
Takeko's back?
It's hot.
I'll open the door.
it's cool as expected
They'll get up in two hours
Then I am be able to sleep comfortably
Water is stopped.
Hey.
Again?
what have you been up to?
Where were you?
Takeko's back.
She's come back then that's fine
She left a note and ran away.
She's here
Where did that paper go?
I will look for it.
This is this
in the drawer...
She left this in the drawer and left the house
But no one notices it because everyone is so sloppy.
I had no idea.
When she came back and asked me if I'd seen it,I told her I didn't know,
This is how it all happened," so it's no wonder she was so disappointed.
It can't be helped.
You've never made a promise to anyone like a parent before
Right?
Did you do anything?
Hey.
Say something.
what?
Well, that's right
She left the house and no one made a fuss
No one was going to report it to the police or have her search for it
We are too sloppy.
If anything happens to her, I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You are her parent
But in the end she came home
but it's your child
I will ask her for more details later.
you brought someone again
You've brought someone along before.
I felt sorry for him so I left him alone
I don't want to be the one who was taken care of either
What do you think this house is?
Get out.
Come in.
No.
Get out.
It hurts
Yeah, what are you doing?
I'm your mom
Go to hell
Stop it....
Cut it out.
Just kill me.
I don't care if you kill me.
You're so bad.
Takeko,where are you going?
I'm never coming back here again
Takeko!
I found a live-in job.
Goodbye.
Takeko!
Bring her back, ok?
Takeko! This
Take this.
Takeko,take this.
See you.
Go by car.
No.
Goodbye.
Don't cry,Takeko.
THE END