Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Anata to watashi no aikotoba: Sayonara, konnichiwa / Goodbye, Hello (1959)
I can't find
Good weather
I'm thinking of going hiking tomorrow
I'll give you sweets
I can't find
Dog?
Is he disappeared?
Your dog is spits?
White one?
I mean a girl, human
What?
I can't find a partner
Would you like to go to the rooftop?
My mom told me to find a partner for me
She worries about me
I want to fall in love with someone
You're serious
The women we know are interested in us.
You are vain
You sure?
Yes
Women get a job to find a marriage partner.
The newspapers say there will be a shortage of women in 20 years.
I don't care about the future
I know you are playboy
I haven't find yet
She wear sleeveless.
She looks healthy
She's into me
They say she is proud.
I like those kind of women
She has good education, I hear
I don't think she is good for you
Have you asked her already?
She looks girly and beautiful
She's polite
No
I like her
I am really into her
Hello?
It's lunch break.
Aota?
Aota? there's a call for you
Thank you
Hello?
Oh Umeko, What's wrong?
How are you?
Are you calling from Tokyo station?
I don't go out much
It's been a year
Yeah, it was summer
Would you like to come to the cemetery
Work? What kind?
I can go out.
Where?
I get it
I'll be there in 20mins
Welcome
I'm here
What do you order?
The restaurant here used to be good, but now it's bad.
Ice Cream
Even in this cold weather
You eat ice cream the American way, even in winter.
But it's not good for your health
I know you're not a bad person.
But don't laugh like that.
You're laughing like you despise people.
Really?
yeah, come
Don't waste time! There's a new specialty restaurant in a department store in Nihonbashi.
Ice cream!
I started working at that branch.
I advance to Tokyo
You'll be busy
So please let me stay a few days
I know
Thanks
Are you busy?
Worries?
You can talk to me about anything.
What is it?
It's a little complicated.
So ask me at the night.
I'm busy
OK
If my business succeeds, I will be very busy.
You're not getting married?
A woman who marries is a woman who cannot work.
If you get married, God will weep.
Did you receive an invitation to marry?
That's good.
I'm getting more and more tired of these men I'm observing.
Men lose their individuality and look like stingy pigs
Right?
It could be
are there any exceptions?
I have no idea
Why?
I don't observe things with the same interest that you do.
That you ignore men at all?
since when do you wear glasses?
Always
You are lying
I changed the flame
You didn't wear glasses the last time we met.
I'll take it off
It's better.
are you nearsighted?
You look beautiful in a daze.
you really nearsighted?
You told me you were busy
I forgot it
You surprised me
I didn't know you backed home
I left the company early
What's wrong?
I told you to go to the dentist.
It's okay. It's cooled off.
Where's dad?
Not here
You haven't had dinner yet, have you?
I had soft foods
Who cocked for you?
Tecchan
Tecchan?
I ate porridge
porridge?
You cocked?
Tecchan
Tecchan?
I think he was cooking your dinner too.
Oh I feel sorry
He can cook good
he had dinner too?
Who?
I think Umeko
is she coming?
I hate talkative girls
Be careful
I just got home
Tokyo is busy.
I feel calm when I come here
because I take care of you
Yeah it's free.
Oh Toothache?
Welcome
Good evening.
You must be in a lot of pain.
It's a big problem
Are you used to it yet? Airplanes?
I definitely don't want a job like a flight attendant
I hope the plane you boarded doesn't crash
Don't worry
I worry about her
You worry too much
She works for your mom
I'm on a plane so feel my feelings
I don't want you to die
You are good sister
I can't take care of your father like you can.
You can't manage yourself either
How is your father?
He goes to work every day.
I know He doesn't have a job, but...
he is a boatman
Yeah
The shipping companies are in a recession.
There are too many boatman
I'm hungry
I bought Sushi at department store
Bring us some tea.
What's your advice?
I'm not sure how serious it is.
More serious
Where's tea bag?
It's in a yellow can in the cupboard
Oh I found it
Money?
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
Who? man?
Woman?
A man.
He's in Osaka
Young Man in Osaka?
I tell you later
About Watanabe?
What the hell?
Go to sleep.
You don't have to fake it.
What's wrong with Hanjiro?
It's none of your business
Wanna eat Sushi?
Can you eat?
Thanks
Your teeth OK?
Watanabe is my sister's boyfriend
He's not
he may be a fiancee
he may be a fiancee?
Dad is back
The door is broken
It is unusual for him to be drunk
I fixed it but The door is broken again
It's not broken
I didn't know you were home.
Give me some water
I have tooth ache
I'm alright
Oh no
I didn't know you had a fiancee
He's not
So I need your advice
Did you had dinner yet?
I don't wanna eat
It is unusual for him to be drunk
Let's take him upstairs and let him sleep
I don't wanna sleep yet
Tsuru is still here?
She's in upstairs
Water
Shall I bring a towel?
Oh welcome
Good evening
How's Osaka?
I'm in Tokyo for work
Tokyo is getting worse
Your Water
Bring me a Sake
Just a little bit of whiskey left
You are already drunker
I resigned company
What happened?
Not that it's any of my business.
There are too many problem
Even executives are getting stingy
they are only trying to defend their position
So employees feel the same way.
So I quit
I'll work as boatman again
Someone asked you the job?
If I want to work, some people have worked with me.
I'm sure you'll find it if you really look for it.
You really quit your job?
Definitely
It can't be helped.
brought whiskey.
It's hard to have to sit at a desk when there's nothing
Being an office worker doesn't suit me
I know it's selfish of me.
I put up with it for nine years.
I thought about it, too.
I felt sorry for them if I quit the company now, having two daughters before they were married.
Forget it
I can't
That's the heart of a parent, isn't it?
Right,Umeko?
And they doesn't have a mother.
I'm afraid I'll be responsible for them if I don't get them married soon.
She's a straight shooter.
I ask her to marry me and she says yes.
Right?
Yes
Good
Good evening
I will go
Who?
It seems Tecchan
Good evening.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm dry cleaner.
The dry cleaner who comes at night is strange.
Come tomorrow
He was dry cleaner.
Oh I wanted to ask him to buy some bread
One bread, and more?
Oh Tecchan, that's all
Thanks
OK see you
He is a night college student.
During the day he works in the cleaning
Give me water
He's still saying
He's lonely
She had a beautiful voice.
She was always singing hymns.
You never get tired of saying the same thing.
I've been saying it since I was a sophomore in college.
It's been 10 yrs?
Eight years this year.
You were a sophomore in high school.
Poor thing, dying at such a young age.
I'm sleepy
I'm sorry for last night
It's OK
when did he go to bed last night?
3: 30
don't you worry about his job?
Household finances?
I don't know. I guess it depends on my father's situation.
If it comes to it, TSURU and I will take care of it.
That's tough.
Let's hear your story.
Why wouldn't she be interested in a man?
You have a fiancee
It's none of your business
He's the son of a friend of my father's, someone I've known since I was a kid.
His father died five years ago.
but his parents had plans for us
they were trying to get you married?
I don't know if it's that clear or not.
I'm stunned.
you'd better ignore
Lately he's been rushing me so much
He's name is Tibetan?
Hanjiro
did he say he wants to marry you soon?
his mother seems to be
He didn't say?
I have no idea
It said, my mother is in a hurry.
He's a man who doesn't make himself clear.
he is an ordinary office worker
Ordinary office workers can propose
I have never been told that by him
You'd better decline
So I'm asking you
decline?
Yeah
Good.
That's so you
It's not big deal
It's not as big a deal as breaking off an engagement.
It's not that I don't like Mr. Hanjirou.
It's just annoying.
They tells me when I'm not thinking about marriage.
So I thought maybe I could write it down on a piece of paper, but it's too hard to do that.
You want me to meet with him in person and describe your current state of mind?
I'm not very good at writing essays.
Okay,
Don't worry, I tell him to decline it
Don't worry
Here's a quote from the Wakayama Agricultural Cooperative.
Thanks
What happened to that story?
What?
transferring to Tokyo.
Oh yeah
I told it to head office
I heard new employees are coming to Osaka.
One in Accounting.
And one more in my place?
I have no idea
My mother wants to go back to Tokyo
she wanted to die in her hometown
is your mother sick?
She's fine
I think you'll get a lot of benefits if you stay at the head office.
How many years have you been in Osaka?
4 yrs
You don't like Osaka women?
I’m not talking about women
You have a guest
Me?
He?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Are you Hanjiro Watanabe?
Yes
Are you Hanjiro Watanabe, who worked at the head office in Tokyo for three years and at the Osaka branch office for four years?
I see,The clerk told me there were three Mr. Watanabe here.
I didn't want to make a mistake.
Nice to meet you. I'm ICHIGE.
Actually,  Kazuko asked me to come here.
Kazuko from Tokyo
I need to talk to you for a minute.
Please wait here
Is meeting room available?
They are available until 3:30
I would have come earlier, but I was busy with work. I'm sorry I'm late.
I am three years your senior at the same school as Kazuko-San.
There was a girl named Koizumi Mori in your class, too, who died of a heart ailment.
When I was sad, Kazuko-san comforted me.
Since then, I have been in a relationship with Ms. Kazuko as if we were Sisters.
I thought women didn't need to study.
I was in my third year of college.
I dropped out.
Everyone stopped me because it's only a year away.
What do you want?
And as I said before...
Kazuko-san and I are like family.
I understand how Kazuko-san feels.
I understand her relationship with you.
What do you want?
I'm sure we'll take the time to talk about these things.
For Kazuko, it's not that she doesn't like you anymore.
It's not that she doesn't like you or that she has found someone else.
I want you to cancel the marriage. I'm just saying that if you honestly and genuinely tell her how you feel...
That's all I'm saying.
Hold on
Have you been tasked by her to dissolve our marriage?
Shortly,Yes
KAzuko said so?
Of course.
I wouldn't say anything that she doesn't say.
I see.
You men seem to think all women want to get married.
Not every woman with a job.
Kazuko-san's work is just getting interesting.
I see.
I hope you understand that.
I understand.
I see. Thank you.
It means I understand what you're saying.
There's something you don't understand?
I'm really close to Kazuko-san.
I'm sure I can answer anything.
It's ok.
I understand.
I'm glad you understand
It's a magnificent room.
It gets a lot of sun.
It's not mine, so there's no need to flatter me.
Something is strange
In short, Miyako's Mom bring Miyako here and get married?
Yes
It means we are brother but not brother
What's that?
You and I are not blood related.
Oh yeah
You are eligible for that candidacy.
What do you mean?
You are my rival
I'm much better than you
What do you mean?
Hold on
Thanks for your work
Good evening
You look good today
Do you think so?
Thanks
Please take care of our customers
You have to serve your customers
I was visiting some company.
I'm tried
You work so hard
You're still here
Thanks
I hear you advance to Department store in Tokyo
Yes I'm working on it
I'm against at her.
It's better to do business only locally.
It's much better to advance in Tokyo
Our customers are waiting
Ok see you then
I don't like him
It can't be helped
Our business is going well
It is good woman goes to university
I dropped out
Did you manage the Kazuko's problem?
He is a serious and solid man, just as KAZUKO said he would be.
So Why you declined?
Women doesn't know anything
You declined many matchmaking
Are you guys in an anti-marriage alliance?
Don't say bullshit
It's about being a wimp.
We just can't trust each other with the other.
It's a heart-to-heart.
I don't like women's world
Give me a towel
You had a hearing problem when you were little, so I assume you misheard.
Ear?
I think what you heard from that woman is ridiculous.
She didn't want to meet me in person
How did you reply her?
I told her I understood
That's bad
It can't be helped
You wrote a letter to her,right?
Write again
I'm not good at writing
I'll write for you
Don't make it complicated
Why?
I wish I could transferred to Tokyo
He's unreliable.
Your boss?
I'll ask human resource chief
I feel good
Yeah
10 mins to Haneda?
I'll be there on time
Yeah
You love me?
What did you say?
Didn't catch me?
I couldn’t
I kicked out my fiancee.
Are you happy?
I get it
Don't make fun of me
Don't talk to me so much.I'm driving
I don't mind I die with you
You'll be on time
Didn't catch me?
What did you say?
No.125
Me
2235yen,A week of unemployment insurance
Thanks
5 people ,right?
Yeah
Welcome
Is this sweet?
That's not good
This is a perfect snack with beer!
I don't buy for myself,but for daughters
It is very tasty with almonds.
How much?
It costs 100 yen a piece!
Give me this
Hi
Are you buying something?
I was going to call you
What can I do for you?
Here it is
I heard you quit.
Who told you?
From Hayakawa.
You'd be smart to quit your job early.
You look better
It could be
You're still young.
I'm too old
Before I die I want to be on a ship again
Wanna drink?
At Cheap eel restaurant?
Not today.
My daughter has class party
They invited me.
Your daughters has not married yet?
Marriage?
I wanna introduce him
is it a dating photo?
He is my daughter's son-in-law's friend
A business card with his educational background is inside.
He's 30 yrs old, so good for your oldest daughter
Give her
I'll call you soon.
I don't mean this.
Good evening
Tecchan?
Here it is
Thanks
It was 65 yen
Thanks.
I was out of home
Your laundry here.
Can you give me today's?
I gave it to you this morning
Come in.
I'll serve you a tea
I'll make the tea
You're used to this house
Shall I cook dinner?
I bought something at store
but this is not very tasty
They are late
Thank you for taking Michiko to the airport this morning.
Was she on time?
Yes
what do you think when you see this picture?
He looks good.
He's good for Michiko
For Kazuko
For Kazuko?
I don't think this person is suitable for Kazuko.
You think so?
Is he her fiancee?
He's not?
Kazuko?
I'm home
I'll do
I'll cook for you
I cut my finger
Where
A lot?
I'm bleeding.
I will prepare the meal
I'm into cooking
You can't cook every day
Don't worry.
You are busy
I will prepare the meal.
I have always cooked
You are stubborn
Oh you are here
I have to go for school
Are you ok?
It's ok,Tecchan
Bring me the photo
That photo?
Look at this
What's this?
Dating photos
I got it for you
No thanks
Why?
I'm not into it
They worry about you
So they gave me
I know he's your friend.
he is a meddlesome
Look at the photo
No
Kazuko
Have a seat
you are stubborn
Why you declined about Hanjiro's propose?
I didn't know until this morning when I saw the letter from his mother.
I was so surprised and appalled.
Why didn't you ask me for a word of advice?
I was thinking a lot too
You don't have to
He's good man
He's good man for sure
I don't want you to worry about me.
I don't mean to worry you.
OK
You're just trying to be sensible.
I won't say anything.
I'm going to OSAKA in a few days
He looks better than Mr. Hanjiro
That's not why we're going.
I'm going on a business trip to the factory in Osaka.
I'm going to Osaka too
I'm going to take the entrance exam.
I hope we are same train
You are still here
You will be late for school
Damn it
See you
I would have cooked for him.
I see
I have no choice but to have you cook for me today.
you are stubborn too
We were on same train
This car is now completely domestically produced
How's this design?
Looks good
I think the engine is good.
When are you going back to Tokyo?
I'm going back now.
The door is better
A guest called Aota is here
KAzuko? Where?
At the entrance
Excuse me
I would have picked up with you
Hello?
Welcome
Come in
It was urgent busyness
Where's your bag?
I left it at the station
Are you going back tomorrow?
Let me stay here
You can stay anytime
You are so busy
I came here 2 days ago, I stayed at company’s dormitory
You are very troublesome.
That's why I hate Tokyo people
People in Tokyo are cold even if you befriend them.
I work late, I'm so busy
You could called me at least
Sorry
I wanna talk with you many things
About Hanjiro?
It's cold today
I was too busy so I couldn't write you
Have you met him?
No
I told him how you felt.
He said he understood right away.
Thank you very much.
So I don't need to meet him
My dad got letter
From hanjiro?
From my mom, she got angry with me
I should probably go apologize to him
But I don't have anything to go to, so I'm feeling kind of weird.
So I won't meet him
From Hanjiro, you got letter?
He didn't send me anything
He's so simple
we are not so close
I'm relieved to hear you say that.
Do you mind if I love?
Who?
Hanjiro
Funny?
I think so
You scared me.
Shall I give you him?
To me? Why?
Are you sure?
So I'll take him
Oh you are here
It's been a while
It's been about three years since I last saw it.
You told her to love someone.
Who?
You smelly
You are making disgusting smell
Oh sorry.
I have my hair cut
He put oil on my hair
You told her to love someone.
Who?
About Kazuko's fiancee
You love him?
That's ridiculous
We think That's not ridiculous
No, it's not.
It's too late to say so
It's okay
Me and KAZUKO are not blood related
What the hell you are saying?
So we can get married
we can get married?
Do you think we are good couple?
Don't be a dick.
I'm serious
I've been thinking about that
I thought you declined match making because of me
You said women don't have to study.
So your head and my arm makes strong
To protect this store it is an ideal idea!
If I married another woman, it would cost me a lot of money.
It will take a time to teach our work
I didn't know you were serious
Yes
I decline you
Why?
I've been called you bros, I can't call you my hubby
That is not a problem
Call me any name
Why are you laughing?
Not good
NO
I'm going to marry him
marry him?
Yeah
I used to say that all men were assholes, but this is the first time I've ever admitted to being in love.
Have you already decided?
He does not know
You shouldn't
He's just a businessman.
It's boring
I don't care
When he gets fired, that's the end of it.
Kazuko also declined him
Why do you love him?
All
You made us trouble.
Why you declined him?
I'm going out for a bit.
Where?
I thought it would be better if I met with him and made it clear
Hanjiro?
Go see him and get back
What's the hell?
I'll go with you
Don't worry
It's more convenient for you to be with me
I'll say for you what you have trouble saying
I'll be ready in a minute.
You've been out and about to see Hanjiro-san, haven't you?
You've met him many times?
Just a few times.
He's always busy so we talk a little
He's really serious man
What's the hell
I don't need to see her, so please don't let her enter the company without permission.
You're no use
I did it for you.
Shall I ask her to go home?
Two of them
Two of them?
Not only her?
I have no idea
I wonder who
Hi Kazuko
It's been a while
I didn't think you'd turn up.
You should come to Osaka
I was going to go to Tokyo and listen to your story.
Hello?
That's not why Kazuko came to Osaka, is it?
Kind of
How is your father?
Yes
How about Tsuru?
Yes she's okay
If you want to talk about it, there's no need to start now.
I've already told you how I feel about Kazuko-san.
I understand.
I see
Excuse me
If you're working, go ahead.
He's so busy
Call the woman who never comes to the conference room to the front of the elevator.
It's hard for me
I'm counting on you
Just say there's a call?
Please
there's a call
there's a call?
Me?
No
there's a call
Here it is
there's a call for me
I wonder who
Me
Please wait in the alley of the building over there
How about Umeko?
Don't worry
I wanna talk with you in person
I was sorry
There's a call for Kazuko
I see
But I wonder why he knows Kazuko is here
That's strange
From Who?
From Tokyo?
I'll check it
It was a call from a company in Osaka.
They said it was urgent and she went home.
It's terrible of her to leave without telling us, no matter how urgent the matter.
That's so her
She has never shown me such behavior before.
Shall we have dinner?
I have work to do.
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, but it's not easy being an office worker.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Sorry I'm late
That's a funny thing to do.
It can't be helped
I feel sorry for Umeko
Forget about her
Let's go
Where are you going?
There's an inn down the street.
I don't wanna go
Don't get me wrong
It's just inn
I often go there for napping
That's a good place to talk
Talk about that?
The story is very important to us
Tell me something
I declined
Are you frustrated?
It's okay to say no.
If they want to let you through, they have no choice.
Why didn't you just tell me in person?
I thought she would refuse without making you feel bad
UMEKO likes you so much.
She wanna marry you
And now you're recommending him instead of turning me down, and you're...
It's stupid.
I thought I was going to marry you a long time ago.
When UMEKO told me, I didn't take it seriously.
I was taking it easy.
It's sad that your mother is angry with you.
Let's be clear.
If you don't like me, just say so.
That's crazy.
What's the real reason?
I tell you, I feel pain
I don't want to be forced into it.
My father wants me to marry him, but he doesn't want me to.
He's the one who's gonna be the worst off when I'm gone.
won't you marry until your father dies?
You don't know about my feeling
When we get married, you'll be the only one who cooks rice and does the laundry.
I hate being a lonely father.
I want him to be bossy all the time.
Don't cry
Sorry
I'm a little foggy.
I can't see your face well without my glasses
Keep being foggy.
You don't have to think about anything.
I didn't know you thought so much of me.
I hope I have a power
I wonder if money is the answer.
money?
Hire a housekeeper. to take care of your father. to take care of your father.
Can passion solve the problem?
You can't
I can't be foolhardy if you insist on that.
That's what you are, isn't it?
I'm sorry I said those horrible things earlier.
what shall we do now?
What do you mean?
Go home?
I'll see off
where are you staying?
I want to go home alone
I wanna cry
Why?
because my glasses were broken
We are Yotaro
What's wrong,Kazuko?
Where are you?
I decided to go home tonight
So See you in Tokyo
What's wrong?
Hello?
Oh she hung up
I'm sure you're busy at the store right now.
Are you sure?
I'm here for a drink.
It feels good to have a drink at another restaurant?
I don't mean that
abalone please
Salted fish is recommended at this restaurant.
I'll have it
wanna drink?
Thank you
I don't understand
For what?
About women
What's wrong?
It's none of your business
I see
I don't understand either
Welcome
Can I sit here?
Go ahead
One Sake
you use good expressions
I feel like that
are you in the same situation as me?
A woman who said she didn't want to get married suddenly said she wanted to get married.
That's not bad
Not with me but with other man
that's a big problem
Right?
what kind of man is that?
He's boring man
he is a useless man who is dumped by a woman
He's bad
why are you disappointed?
I failed the exam
Women?
I failed the entrance exam because I am a night college student.
That's the life
If I can't find a job, I can't get married.
Women are the problem
Are you feeling bad?
Hi Kazuko
Are you still here?
I'm here
You gonna bed?
I wanna eat rice gruel
Ok I'll prepare it
You should go to blind date
You'll be late
I'm going
How can I cook rice gruel?
Put some water than normal
Where's the thermometer?
It's in medicine box
How about the medicine?
I'll check it
I'll manage it.
You should go to work
My stomach's rumbling.
Can you prepare hot-water bottle for me?
I'm home
You are still here
You'll have date today,Right?
Yeah
What are you doing?
You have a blind date at noon.
You'll be late
I won't
Why?
My father isn't feeling well.
He always pretends he's sick.
Last night my father told me to be sure to go.
I'm glad I wasn't home last night.
You won't be married for a while?
You declined Hanjiro.
You are too good
Or do you see anyone now?
Tell me
Shut up
No
There's someone I really love.
If he proposes to your sister, you'll marry him?
No
I wanna marry to Tecchan
With Tecchan?
With Tecchan
I think he's nice
He's suitable with me
He has no job
He found
a few days ago
I didn't know
I should celebrate him
So can I?
I think you can
So can you tell him?
For what?
Tell him I wanna marry him
What's the hell?
You should talk him in person
I can't
You're stupid
It's Sunday.
Tecchan's there. You should go tonight.
You can't just say that.
I'll have to talk to your father about it.
He's nothing to worry about.
I'm home.
You back early
You're still here
I won't go
I see
It's ok
He doesn't look good in the picture.
Don't worry.
I'll call them to decline
I'm hungry
Wanna eat eel?
Who treat?
I got paid
Unemployment insurance, right?
Yeah
You spend money quickly.
You should save your money
Order 3 dishes
You told me you had a stomach ache
I got better after going to toilet
You should call them for the time being
Who?
I can't catch you
Could you please clarify?
I'm busy.
Kazuko-san.
Kazuko Ota?
I'm sorry.
Do you have something important to tell me?
I'll visit you anywhere.
To the office? I'll be right there.
I'm free.
Sorry to call you here.
This is the only place I could find.
I feel more at home but
location does not matter
I am here about marriage talk
marriage?
Do you have a fiancee?
No
I'm glad to hear that
Well..about me?
Yes
I didn't expect that.
I don't know how to say this.
I'm grateful.
It's hard to say something like this when you're close to someone, isn't it?
I agree.
I'm relieved.
I'm sure I'll be able to do my job easily.
What's that?
Tsuru-chan can't say it herself.
Oh about Michiko
She says she can't honestly tell you how she feels.
But
I didn't understand her feelings at all
You knew it
The girl I like is highly educated, so I studied hard myself.
She has only high school diploma
I thought that if I couldn't work, I wouldn't be aware of applying for marriage.
A company with eight employees... that I've decided to join.
What company?
We sell sandal
Sandal?
I heard that there are many orders from overseas.
I think our company will grow from now on
I plan to change jobs in the future
I feel like you're working hard every day
I think Tsuru like that kind of part of you
my monthly salary is low.
When she get married, she will quit your current job, right?
She's just like you, but she's got something on her mind.
you two should talk
Me and Michiko?
Ms.KAzuko Aota. someone is visiting you
Me?
Who?
Come to my house after you tell TSURU that you'll congratulate me on my new job.
See you then
Are you busy?
I'm here for a minute.
Tokyo.
I'll be back
Transfer to Tokyo?
I came to see a little of the state of my house
You rented a house in Suginami Ward to someone.
I'm talking to my mother about it
Your mom's also back in Tokyo?
She's still in Osaka
I'll marry with someone
I see
With Umeko
That's good
you think so?
I knew you would.
she is very pushy
You lost?
I can't help it.
Good for you
I think you and her are very well balanced.
you have a very strong personality
You're mean
But it could be
No, I'm kidding.
I'm sorry I'm late
How are you?
you guys came to Tokyo together?
He went to Tokyo yesterday I went to Tokyo today
How was your house?
my mother seems ready to meet you
but let's go home together
Your work ok?
I will go to the department store again tomorrow
see you tonight
I'll be on the train tonight, so I won't be able to visit you.
Give my regards to your father.
Goodbye
Have a good day.
Tecchan,what's wrong?
I've met this person before...
Umeko?
That guy
Where was I?
Was it a dream?
Do you know him?
I have to go for work
I can't be so sure in front of her.
I'm so bad
She'll be just my friend
He's sleeping
He's tired.
He says he's heartbroken.
Sleeping with a broken heart... that's weird.
You can see better if you adjust the size
this fabric is very good
this is really great
The fabric is the most important thing for a suit
We offer low prices
Will it be in time for the wedding day?
I will definitely make it in time by that day
this is really great
You look so good
He has almost completed all the preparations for the establishment of the company.
But this is a concrete company and I've never done it.
More and more houses are made of reinforced concrete
I hear there are many orders
Mr. Nakamura has a business acumen and owns a lot of stock in this company.
He wanted a companion he could trust.
You just need to follow him
There are a lot of strange people around these days.
Just keep it serious.
Good
not what I expected
You found a new job, and the salary is low at first, but I think it's good.
See you then
who will marry?
Why you didn't tell me
Not ours but just my friend's
Not for Kazuko?
I wanted to make you some tea
It's strange to keep other daughter's deposit instead of your own daughter's.
Oh yours?
Oh sorry
There’s a lot
I contacted many people
you are quiet today
Me?
You don't go out?
I’m all ready for wedding
all my stuff has been moved
HANJIRO came to make a suit today.
You're good
You did everything by yourself.
my brother is too busy to prepare
is he coming to the wedding?
He said he would come to Tokyo for the wedding.
I'm going back to work.
I'm happy for you.
Congratulations.
Is it that good?
Of course, Kazuko...
TSURU-chan will be happy too.
I have something to tell you
What?
would you marry someone?
Who?
Anyone ok
I'm not into it
it's very annoying
Who?
Kazuko
Kazuko?
what did she say to you?
She didn't
If you don't get married, Kazuko can't get married.
No way
you are disturbing her marriage
You are
Really?
she will get married as soon as she is free
as soon as she is free...
But I wonder if Kazuko is even thinking about it.
Why don't you tell her you're getting married?
I have no intention of getting married
I don't care about you
what do Kazuko, look like?
She'll have a bright look on her face and say congratulations.
you say terrible things
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
You're her friend
But what a strange woman you are, too.
You're worried about Kazuko's marriage while you're keeping Kazuko's fiancée.
you say terrible things too
it's like I’m getting married
you are an inexperienced man
you should support her
Why do they have a wedding in Osaka?
I feel sorry for her to have her wedding at such a small wedding hall.
Kimono with her is a rental kimono
she refused it.
I wanted to be like a salary man's wife
Why did you make the clothes at the clothing store that used to make school uniforms?
I made a suit there when I entered the company too
What if it doesn't arrive in time for the wedding?
I'm sorry I'm late.
It didn't mean to be late.
It's just that... it's not all finished yet.
Not yet?
What will you do?
He can just try it
It's not all on the back, but I'm sure you're just a little bummed out.
They won't know once you put it on.
You're right.
It's not good to wear unfinished clothes
I caught a cold and had a very high fever yesterday.
Please take off your jacket and let Hanjiro put it on.
It's just fitting
lend him the clothes
Thank you
I look so funny when I take off my jacket
I'm fine with a normal suit
This is better
It seems that there are no more rental costumes at this ceremony hall.
we are going to go to the wedding venue in 5 minutes.
Your nose gets messy
This is better
Thanks
It's ok
Thanks.
I knew.
I knew you liked him.
You said that it's okay for me and him to fall in love
then will you give him back to me?
No way, I won't
Sorry
You're romantic
Tsuru-chan should have come here too.
She said she wasn't interested in someone else's marriage.
she speaks clearly
she said she was going on a trip
She said she would go to Tecchan's house in the country and do some research.
She got in as soon as he could, took three days off.
Yes that's right
Do I look good?
I'm the best man
What the hell?
Oh I remember who you are
I know you
Oh my god
You told me I was a lousy man who was dumped by a woman.
I worry he still remember me
I'm home
I'm here to greet you
Please come in
Upstairs is better
There are many rooms here
Our house is much smaller
I have remodeled my entryway in many ways.
If I carry my wife's stuff, I'll have no place to sleep.
I'm busy with various things since they suddenly decided to get married.
Don't worry about me
Thanks in advance
So do I
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
They went on their honeymoon.
I just wanted to drop you a line after I saw them off.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
It's like my daughter is getting married.
I thought Kazuko were going to marry him.
I'm sorry about that.
That's not what I meant.
And my late husband had every intention of doing so.
So do I
Umeko shouldn't transfered to Osaka
She ended up to back to Tokyo
Umeko is good woman
I think so
She'll open her store at the department store
Umeko will be the manager for Tokyo branch?
Your store these days has been changed
Excuse me
Please stay here for relax
I know you are more tired than I
Sorry to disturb you
Good night
How was it?
It was a grand wedding ceremony.
That's good
I'm going to miss her after I send her off to get married.
She's very cheerful so
Kazuko,I'm gonna get married.
With who?
I'm gonna get married.
You're lair
You think so?
Why?
What?
Why you say so?
Kazuko,.
There are many things in life.
In their youth, they are very possessive.
They want to own everything.
But as we get older, we're gradually forced to give that up.
No ambition in life, no job, no money, no life partner.
Your mother's dead.
Not that I abandoned her.
But it's the same thing emotionally.
No matter how many things happened along the way, we are born alone and we die alone.
I'm a sailor, and I used to think about that at night on the sea.
I'm alone at the end.
I feel lonely
I won't miss it
That's a given.
But I'd been so careless, I'd forgotten to throw her away.
I thought she was mine.
That'd be okay
Being away from your own children is the
The last and biggest test of your life.
It's difficult.
Kazuko, let's leave each other alone.
No
Don't be afraid of being alone.
You do what you want to do.
Marriage or work?
I don't have
You have
Dad, if you leave me.
I'll go to America.
America.
You have a job?
The company wants me to study in America.
I think it's good
I think it's better to go
You go by ship
Or airplane
We haven't even gotten to that point yet.
I think it's better to go
Can I?
Yes
I felt like I was waiting for your permission
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'll go.
Take care
Tsuru and Tecchan got married, but they don't have a house, so I think they will live in this house.
I will give them the second floor
I think they will cook for me
You are cheeky
Why?
That was your plan all along.
you shouldn't have cried
But, you know... you really should get married.
will you preach to me?
You're still nice
Applications are pouring in.
Don't say bullshit
I think HANJIRO lost out by marrying Umeko.
He looked nice at wedding
I see
You'd better put your glass off
you should not wear glasses
If you can't see it, it can't be helped
I will put it off
Middle-aged women have become beautiful in Japan recently.
It's spring
Yeah, it's MArch
he is going to blackmail me
For what?
hey, Umeko
they don't look like a couple at all
you will be like them
We'll definitely not
hey, Umeko
Stop doing it
THE END