Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Are you OK,brother?
brother?
He'll be OK?
No worries.
His surgery went well.
Yoko...
Hello?
Oh,Chikako
What happened about Mitsuharu?
I'm alone now.
My brother is saying something on his own.
I feel worry
He keeps saying about Yoko
The nurse says he's fine
The nurse says he's regaining his memory in his dreams.
I got relieved
Can you see him again?
I would like to see him
But...
Doctors thought the best way to cure his amnesia was to see someone who was around at the time.
That's why I want you to come visit him
OK?
Good night
Did you get a call?
No...
Shinji hasn't come back yet,right?
Not yet
I really can't believe your husband hasn't come home yet.
This is a 10,000 yen necklace.
Do you like it?
AT THE SIDE OF THE BRIDGE (Episode 2)
Yoko
I was dreaming of you all the way
Mitsuharu
You and I were talking among beautiful flowers
I had such a dream
We used to talk in flowers
Then you looked me in the eye and said...
You are in my eyes
You are in my eyes too
I love you, Yoko
Mitsuharu
Yes, I know that
Did you remember it?
We went skiing in Shinshu together.
Let's get married,Yoko
as soon as we graduate
I'll make you happy
I feel like my memory is slowly coming back but...
Don't worry.
You'll get back soon
I only remember that I love you
Mitsuharu
After I graduated from school and got a job at my sister's company, my father fell ill and I had to return to Kyushu.
You came to see me off at Sukiyabashi
Yes,that's right
I was student at the time
He told me that he would pick me up after finishing school in half a year.
I feel like my memory is slowly coming back
But Your brother opposed our marriage.
I was in Kyushu and didn't know that
I wrote a letter to let you know that and that happened
Are you OK?
Doctor!
I am an architectural engineer
Don't worry
Yoko
I was very confused for half a year
My father got better, so I went back to Tokyo.
I wanted to see you
Mitsuharu
I am not yet able to walk alone
I'm not what Mitsuharu Sugano used to be
Look what my hands are
Look what my legs are
I changed myself
I can't believe it
if you have any reason,tell me honestly
I regret telling you that
Yeah
I injured my right hand and thought I could no longer design.
Sorry.
Did I bother you?
No...
Toki encouraged me all the way
She was my neighbor in the same apartment and always took care of me.
These croquettes smell so good that I bought a lot.
Toki also loved you?
No... I had nothing to do with her
But I couldn't believe it until I heard about her
I found that out when you came to Hokkaido.
Hokkaido.
I was always struggling to forget you then.
I heard you had an arranged marriage.
My brother cheated on me
When Ms. Toki told me about you, I went to see you.
Fujikawa and Aya saw me off
Good luck
Yoko
Mitsuharu
I lost my happiness
because of Nobu
This is his watch, you know?
He left this in my bed this morning
I can't believe it
Yoko
Hold on
I feel sorry about you
Do you blame me?
I was just being honest.
I blamed her too much
I was too selfish at that time
He broke our relationship
he broke our relationship
Please die with me
Calm down
I'll go to die if you don't like
Hold on!
You fell off a cliff and you lost your memory.
I can't remember anything from it
Don't push yourself too hard
You just had surgery
His memory has fully returned.
But some are still missing
I worry about it
Can it be unrecoverable?
He doesn't know me at all?
No way
Sometimes people can't remember even if they try
I think he will remember if something happens
So he needs your help
Can you see him often?
I would try
I knew immediately what this was when I received this from Mr. Fujikawa.
He told me this was my work
I also remember that I was in the middle of designing this
That's good what you remember
But not all
YOKO
You and I parted like that in Hokkaido.
It's been more than a year
I always think of you in this bed
I'm wondering how you're spending the year at that time
Tell me what you think
Why Fujikawa doesn't want to talk about you?
I want to know that
Please tell me everything you know
I met Mitsuharu all the time
I visited him when I came to Tokyo
I went with him to Sukiyabashi and your apartment in Gotanda.
I asked you to remember me, but at that time your memory did not return.
Hold on
You guys visited my apartment?
Yeah, that was my room
I'm Yasuo Tateno.
People call me any way
But I don't know what they call me.
I don't even know what name is Mitsuharu
Who are you?
And why you are here?
I'm wife of Sawano.
I'm here for visiting you
I thought Mitsuharu was died
After returning from Hokkaido, I did as my brother said.
I see
I got married with Sawano..
So we can't see each other anymore
Yoko
Take care of your health
Sis
Welcome back
I'm home
Yoko
I'm back now
You were always with Omori's older brother, weren't you?
Yes
His sister was at his house?
I see.
Come with me
Yoko
Where have you been?
You cheated me
Say sorry to her
I won't forgive her
Yoko
I know where have you been
I knew you visited him at the hospital
Are you sure,Yoko?
she tricked me into going to see him
I didn't mean that
Why did you trick me?
I feel bad for lying to you
I thought I shouldn't be honest
You are the wife of Shinsuke.
You can't see other men
I'm sorry
I'll teach her.
Please forgive her
I won't forgive her,
So I asked you pick her up
Please talk to her and Kenjiro.
I'll discuss about her with Shinsuke too
Hi Sugano.
You know who I am?
What's wrong,Chikako?
You know my name?
Who told you?
No worried.
My memory got return
Really?
I know you are 13 years old
And?
I know you like Steamed bread
Yes,and?
you like playing the harmonica
Yes but not very good
How's him,Chikako?
Her parents died and she was raised by relatives.
I drowned in the river and was saved by the relative.
That's good you remember it
I was worried about his memory
Don't cry
I haven't forgotten to find your grandfather
I'm glad if you are with me even if we can't find my grand father
I'm glad you get better.
Get well soon and leave the hospital
Mr. Imura was worried about his work.
Mr. Imura says he will be able to leave the hospital in a few days.
Will Mitsuharu Sugano be able to work immediately after being discharged from the hospital?
He needs some rest
if he needs a month rest
If so, the design will be delayed.
Our office will work with you on that and try to get it done as soon as possible.
He has a brain disorder, so I'm worried about putting him in charge of this design.
I wanted to build a building with a new feel, so I recommended Mr. Sugano.
I will judge whether he is in charge of this work.
What do you think?
You're right. but it'll be inconvenienced if this work delay
You work so hard
No worries.
I'm happy to work
I would like to see the building you designed
What's wrong?
Sugano will be discharged from the hospital tomorrow.
I see.
He'll stay here?
Yes.
Fujikawa visited me and asked me to clean the room
She's so cheeky
You're in a lot of trouble.
Eh?
Mr. Fujikawa said that even if he leaves the hospital, he won't worry as long as he stays here.
He know nothing about us
I want to go back to my hometown
Why?
I'm really sorry that Yoko caused you trouble.
I'm not upset about it
I'm here because our president was worried about you.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I want sweets
I'll give you later.
Go outside and play
you apologize to her
I'm sorry I lied to you
But it can't be helped
Please understand me
What should I understand?
The doctor told me to come to him to cure his disease.
Don't get me wrong
He already know about it
But I think it would be very sad to take his job away from him.
Job?
What the hell?
Yoko
I think it's very sad that they won't let him design the building.
I hope you understand about my feeling
Miura
The company has not yet made that decision.
What the hell?
I'm sorry but you should scold her
You have nothing to do with the Sugano now
You want me to understand that?
You have nothing to do with the Sugano now.
Why you care about him?
He's saying right
You can't go home unless you forget him
I'm leaving now
You should apologize to him.
Miura
Leave her alone
Boss
I am very sorry today
What the hell?
why did you argue with him?
He came to pick you up
I wanted him to understand my feelings
Don't be too selfish
You are wife of Shinsuke Sawano.
You are so happy woman
you have to be patient
Do you think I’m really happy?
What?
Does it mean that I am happy to have money?
Stop saying
I know what's in your mind
You stupid!
Stop it
You mean you're getting in the way of my career, right?
Thank you for coming
Let's toast for Fujikawa
Take care of your health
I'm glad Sugano is here
How about me?
I'm more glad
I am very much indebted to you too
Don't be too serious
I couldn't do anything for you.
No way
It can't be helped
I can only comfort you
That's enough
How long do you plan to stay in Hokkaido, Mr. Fujikawa?
At least half year
I think it will take a year
It's too long
She'll miss him
No way.
I feel glad
Shut up
Bros
Where's Yoko?
What's wrong with her?
She went to see you
I have no idea
You don't know?
She's left home
Are you sure?
Don't lie to me
Calm down
you said terrible things to him
Is she really not here?
Call Sugano and ask about it
I was misunderstood
Call me when you find her
Hold on
Why she's left home?
It's none of your business
Tell me
We need to know why so we can find her.
Reason?
Because of Sugano
Are you leaving?
I'm sorry I'm late
Yoko's left home
I thought Yoko was happy
I have been concerned about this for some time.
Did you find her?
It seems that Yoko is not in the apartment
Where she's gone?
Please adjust the money
This is an admission ticket.
Where are you going?
To Sasebo,Kyushu
Hold on
Yoko
I think it's hard to forget her
But I think she'll contact you later
Sugano
I want you to be happy.
Please stay honest
See you
Good luck
Don't cry
I wanna go with you
You can go with him for Hokkaido
Get off
I'll be honest
He said about Yoko and Sugano.
Not you
It's OK
Get off now.
You don't have package
I have already sent the package
Madam said to me that
See you,Sis
Good luck
See you
She'll be happy
They are nice.
I'm sure they'll be happy
Let's go home
Shimonoseki is Toki's home town
I found out Yoko was here from Fujikawa's letter
Sorry for the unexpected visit.
My house is small but wanna come in?
Yoko is not here
She left yesterday.
She's gone to Kyushu
Here is my home town.
I graduated from that school
Toki
What did Yoko say?
Well..She told me she regretted a lot
Like what?
So I told her
It was fate that Mitsuharu died once.
So no one will blame you if you get married with other man
You should get your life again
But She is stubborn
She told me It was fate that Mitsuharu died, but It was not fate that I got married to Sawano
It was my responsibility
I felt irritating about her
Yoko left to Kyushu because of me
Why?
I blamed her when she was in trouble
Toki
You know what
If I were her, I would act like her
I was serious to get married with someone when you've gone to Hokkaido
But no one wanna get married with me
That's Kyushu
Yoko is there
You should go to see her whatever Yoko feels
You should go to see her
I boarded this ship 3 years ago too
You and I were lovers at that time
You are married woman now.
I'm here for you
Her Brother Kenjiro picked her up.
They headed to Miyazaki
Miyazaki?
They left this morning.
Her husband Sawano seems to be there
I see.
Yoko made up her mind to see her husband
Do they solve the problem?
I see.
That's good for them
I worried about what she is doing
I wonder she is happy now
I scolded her to support her husband once they were married.
I regret what I said to her
I was in trouble,
I didn't feel like going back to Tokyo
So I visited in Miyazaki
I can't forget about Yoko
I wanna see you in person
Welcome back
So she would go home?
My father and I talked to her
She decided to go home.
She was concerned about public perception.
Welcome back
Your boss is with you
Why you left earlier?
I can't play golf
I need to talk with him
OK
It's inconvenient that Kobayashi stay at this inn
Why?
Yoko feels strange.
You stay here
I'll go to see her
I was sorry
When did you get arrived?
Around noon
Never mind
Are you here for work?
We are building a factory on the coast.
Secretaries should stay in a separate hotel while on business trips.
That's inconvenient
And your boss asked me to stay here
You're so cheeky
Ok I will stay at another hotel
I will find it
No thanks.
Give me some beers
Here's too boring
There is no place where I play at night
Quiet tourist destinations are rare.
You sound like an old man.
I feel so boring
Have you been to sightseeing?
Little
You're lying
Sorry I'm drunk
Are you on trip too?
Kind of
She went on a school trip.
My classmates said this place is great.
So I decided to come here
You didn't go on a school trip.
I had no money
Sorry, I'm getting sleepy
I need to go back
I have one request for you
Don't get angry.
I would like to ask you about the design of the new building.
Please let Sugano-san handle that job.
He did nothing wrong.
Is that bad?
Well..that'll be fine
Yoko!
As long as you are truly happy I am fine. So tell me if you are happy or not
You don't answer..that means you are not happy,right?
I got married for various reasons
I don't have the confidence to throw them away and start over.
we'll be fine if we work together
Now you and I are in different positions
Why you got married?
Why you were missing in Hokkaido?
Why did you lie to me at SUKIYABASHI two years ago?
I came to Shimonoseki, Sasebo, and Miyazaki in search of you.
It's been a long journey, but I had hope
I also went to Hokkaido to find you
I traveled alone by train and ship.
I was lonely
I loved you then more than I love you now.
Oh Madam
Wait
let's go back to Tokyo with me
You don't love me now?
I love you
Yoko..then..
It's too late
Good morning
It's been a age.
You arrived here yesterday
I'll leave first.
We'll have meeting today
But you don't need me
Please contact Yoshida Construction Company when you return.
do you have a meeting with the design engineer?
I will say hello to the manager
Thanks
Have you decided who will be the architect of the new building?
Yes we've decided
Do you still worry about it?
He cheated me
I was suddenly kicked out of my house
I was just surprised that my wife came suddenly.
Did you get along with her again?
It's ok if you wanna leave here
You were able to reconcile with your husband.
I'm sorry
Don't get upset
I'll keep it a secret what happened this morning
Yoko
Dad
Did you meet with Sugano?
I regret saying something terrible to you
I came here to worry about you.
I'd like to bring you back home if that's okay with you.
Dad
I regret not letting you marry Mr. Sugano
Forget about that
I won't cry anymore,Mitsuharu
Happiness doesn't come from crying
A year later
Your wife wants a divorce because of marital differences and her relationship with your mother-in-law.
So you think it was Mitsuharu Sugano
yeah
I think you're jealous of him
That's not true
I loved her
But you guys have already been separated for more than half a year.
No way
I loved her
But
I loved her.
she is poor but I got married with her
I want you guys to make up
If you can't do that, then I hope you get an amicable divorce.
we have been talking about it for half a year
I wanna ask you one thing
Do you intend to withdraw your divorce request and think again
No at all
Come in,Sawano
Have a seat
We have been trying for a long time to find an amicable solution.
But We couldn't make it
As far as the court is concerned, there is no further progress in this conversation, so I would like to terminate it now.
madam
Divorce is not allowed unless your husband allows it
Your husband doesn't want to live with you and wants to rent a house somewhere and have you live there.
tashiro
See you again
Welcome
Thank you for coming
I've been looking for your house
CHIKAKO rushes home from school on Saturday and goes to Hamamatsu right away by train!
The Brother asked me to come because he is lonely.
You are good.
How's Mitsuharu?
He's fine
You should go to Hamamatsu too.
You should meet him and talk about various things
It's the time
I can't go
You've failed in divorce mediation, and now you're going to a divorce trial, right?
I can't help you.
I don't think you can solve it by yourself
I don't know what to do too
It is my responsibility to marry with Sawano
I said good bye to Mitsuharu in Kyushu
I will be patient as my divorce is finalized.
It can't be helped
Keep this story a secret from him
I find it painful for her to lie to him
I'm sorry
Are you Sawano's wife from Toyo Light Metal?
Yes
I see
Do you know about him?
He is a client of ours and I have met him a few times.
Thanks
he is a very good lawyer
Don't make me laugh
Am I bothering you?
It's OK.
I can't be loud
Do we settle in district court?
Yes
I will support you
Can we pay in installments?
Ok that'll be fine
I hope my own body recovers.
your appendix will heal soon
You'll get well soon
Please take care of me.
I'm old fart
You're still young
you are good at flattery
Bros
You've been raised
What's wrong?
I just greet you
I tell you before I forget
What?
Toki told me if you ask me about Yoko
Then?
She told me to tell you she is fine.
That's good if she is happy
Do you worry about her?
Yes
You're already adult
Toki is fine?
She's busy.
The patient she is in charge of now is a lawyer.
she said it was convenient
Why?
Well...she's studying law
Really?
I can't believe what you say
We will now begin deliberations on the divorce of Yoko Sawano and Shinsuke Sawano.
where is the plaintiff's attorney?
Well
What's wrong?
Sorry
Sorry I'm late
You should be prepared to substantiate.
Wait a min
I will slightly change the purpose and cause of the divorce request.
In short,we will claim 1 million yen from him as compensation.
Yoko..you are so mean
Sensei
Leave it to me.
This is the way to win the case
Yoko
I think it's a very terrible way to claim alimony from him.
You should speak up on the witness stand it
I will
Thanks.
Because you the judge will know what kind of mother-in-law you are.
you should have divorced her earlier
You were also concerned about other people's eyes and opposed the divorce.
Don't get argue
What do you think?
No worries.
Leave it to me
Yoko
I consulted with the president.
You have been asked to leave this company.
Eh? Why?
It's a problem with Sawano's house, isn't it?
That's so mean
This company does business with our company.
It is not convenient for us to have you working for us.
Are you sure?
I'm not allowed to work here?
Your brother said you wanted to be with Sawano-san again.
That's not true
I wanted to divorce him, so I went to court.
I see.
Hold on
Niimuera.
That's what I thought
The person I hired is Yoko.
Not Sawano's wife
So forget this issue
Are you sure?
May I report this to the manager?
we also have a deal
you are a very big company.
I can't believe you would do something like that, so I'll call your president and see.
Hold on.
You don't have to
The president of your company is a woman, so you seem to understand how women feel.
It might be so
That's good she is nice person
We're back
Where did you arrived?
Sis, he is....
I'm here because I want to talk to you
I see.
I invited her for dinner
Come in,Yoko
It's been a age,Yoko
Sorry for the unexpected visit.
he is going abroad
Eh?
To Ka...what name is it
At the request of Professor Imura, I decided to go to Cambodia.
I'll go for him
Where will you depart?
There is a visa issue, but I will be there by the end of next month.
Why don't you tell us anything?
Yoko
What's wrong with her?
Yoko will...
Toki
Let me say.
She's working now
She is in court to separate from her and her husband.
Are you sure,Yoko?
I worked hard to forget you this past year
That's also the reason why I go to Cambodia
But the truth is, I thought of you every day.
I thought of you every day too
I didn't know you were suffering so much.
I wanted to divorce Sawano on my own.
I am trying to solve it myself
I wanted to get back myself, Yoko Niimura, and saw you again
I thought it was the only way I could get you to forgive me
Yoko, don't think too much
Mitsuharu
I haven't changed my mind
Me too
I love you
I am happy to meet you after a long time
Be happy
I'll support you from now on
The complaint states that your husband SHINSUKE was unreasonable out of jealousy.
do you know why he got jealous?
No
Do you know Mitsuharu Sugano?
I know
Last July, you visited him a lot while he was in the hospital.
That's true
But he had a special disease called amnesia.
I was told by the doctor to come in for his treatment from time to time.
I thought I could tell my husband about it and he would understand.
If his illness is cured, you won't need to see him,right?
No
Have you had anything with him since last July?
Right
Have you never met him since then?
You met him three days before September 15th.
Machida 3-chome, Shinagawa-ku.
Shumpu apartment,Toki machida
You met him and spent two hours in that room.
You went to Shinagawa station with him and shook hands on the platform and parted.
Objection!
I ask her the truth
This is a leading question
This is no!
Be quiet
Keep going
That'll be inconvenient
I'm sorry
I didn't know there was a detective.
It is inconvenient for me to be unfaithful
It was not unfaithfulness
Sorry
you had better not see him for a while
I see
what will happen to me?
you have to prove his infidelity
We have to find the address of ASAMI, the secretary.
Leave it to me
If possible, I want to be by your side
I don't care if I lose everything
It didn't hold up well in court.
But I was very happy to meet you
do you remember when you were a student,Yoko?
we were full of hope
If you win the case we'll be back
We did not obligate ourselves to this matchmaking.
this was a natural match
She was glad too
My case is not going in my favor.
I feel so miserable when I see them
I'm thinking of you all day long
I'm about to go to Cambodia
I consider this work to be rewarding..but
I don't know what to do if your case won't work well
I'm writing happy news today,Mitsuharu
Asami?
We've found her.
Your lawyer met her yesterday
Is that true?
I contacted her home but no response.
I found her friend and got her contact
She was working at bar.
Kanzaki lawyer found her
I think our case will work well
I got express letter.
Asami will prove you?
Kanzaki lawyer got promised with her
Asami does not feel good about Sawano
That is good news
I will be in Tokyo to see you on the next court date.
I think my lawyer will allow it.
I'm looking forward to it
What? telephone bill will be high?
Ok see you then
Hold on
Hi,I'm Chikako
He hanged up the phone
Witnesses must tell the truth.
If you tell a lie, you are committing perjury.
You speak to the presiding judge.
Do you know Shinsuke Sawano?
Yes
What relationship you have with him?
I was her secretary when I worked at Toyo metal co.
When was it?
It was between Feb to Oct last year
I see
Besides your work, you had a special relationship with him
What?
I mean you were his mistress
No way
No?
You didn't have such a relationship?
No
You accompanied him on a business trip to Miyazaki last September.
You stayed with him in a hotel for three days.
Yes
Besides you, Was there another co workers?
I was only the worker
You did nothing to do with him?
No
You eat and drink in the same room with him.
I can call the maid as a witness.
I felt lonely to eat alone, so I asked him to eat together
There was nothing happen more than that
I met you at bar 1 week ago, 10/3.
You told me different
I have no idea
You should be honest
Witnesses must tell the truth.
presiding judge!
He insults the witness.
Please reject
You watch your language.
I get it
What? She rejected?
I can't believe it
Kanzaki got in trouble
We got in trouble
I will go there to see her
That's bad
It's not convenient for you to be here.
I'll call you when the court is over
She looks tired.
I will ask her a few questions
You changed your hotel 4th of your trip schedule
Yes
Why?
Niimua asked me to change my hotel
Did you know Yoko Sawano visited him that day?
I found out it later
You didn't meet her that day?
No
She backed in Tokyo,not saw her
I met her
When?
Next day the morning
Damn it.
She was bought up
Oh morning.
Around what time?
Around 5 am
It was too early.
Why?
I just walked around
Then you met her?
She was alone?
No
With her husband?
She was another man
Not husband
What were they doing?
They were sitting together and talk
Like what?
They seemed to be fun?
Yeah
Oh no....
She seemed to be crying
The man seemed to encourage her
It means, they were like lovers
presiding judge.
This is an inductive question, so please withdraw it.
This is not
presiding judge.
Please withdraw your questioning.
OK I will
I ask you last question.
Do you know him?
I know
Who?
He is the architect MITSUHARU SUGANO
Ok I finish
Thank you
Why you were lying?
You are making my year of hard work go to waste.
And moreover, I will be in big trouble for the rest of my life
My bad
Don't get angry
I would say Sawano paid you
I won't blame about it
I want you to speak the truth.
I am not righteous in your affair.
I didn't do it.
Don't get me wrong
I want to divorce with him
I wanna leave from him
I know you love that man
Do whatever you want
You don't know what I feel
Yeah. you are happy woman
It was fun Journey
It was first time to get on plane
It happened just 1 year ago
I don't care if you guys sue me
You know what.
People want money when they are in trouble
Do you want to postpone your departure date?
Yes
YOKO almost lost the case at trial.
I can't leave here
I know what's in your mind but We've already arranged with our clients.
I'm sorry to say this but Please turn me down.
Turn you down.
Don’t say bullshit
I’m not in the mood to go
this is an international job
I recommended you for this job instead of me
Thank you, but
I don't want you to mix women's issues with work either.
What? 1 hour ago?
We’re sorry
How was it?
She said she left with a man an hour ago.
I think that man is Mitsuharu
It's really bad for them to be together
they are making the same mistake
We are worried about them.
Where have they gone?
I feel worry
do you think they will commit suicide?
Don't say bad joke
I think TOki worries about us
I will not go to Cambodia
You have to go
I don't care if your lawyer gets mad at me
What should I do?
You just stay with me
If I lose the case, I will always be Sawano's wife.
Stop thinking about it,tonight
Yes
Hello
No one here?
He's still sleeping
it's definitely this house.
It was snowing at that time and it was different from now
I remember this house
Yes. it's outside this window
I proposed to you outside this window
We were supposed to be happy
Let's have fun today
Forget everything until the sun goes down and then think about the future
Yeah
It's same with 3 years ago
At the time they were singing in their cabin.
we made a promise to get married outside the window
Can you make a promise again?
Please
And as IMURA said, please go to Cambodia.
Why?
I will continue the trial
I'll fight up to the supreme court
Yoko
I got courage from you
I will put up with not seeing you for half a year.
please go to Cambodia.
Thanks
And Promise me again that you will marry me.
You guys won't sleep
Day breaks soon.
We'll board the first train
It's cold in the morning so please be careful
2 more hours
Mitsuharu
Replace this in place of the ring.
We’re glad to be here
Thanks
Good morning
I'm going to miss Judgment Day.
Chikako
I wanted to say good bye
I had no time
Chikako
Get along well with Toki
I hand down judgment No. 57
Bros!
Good luck
I hand down judgment about Sawano Yoko and Shinsuke's case
I dismiss plaintiff's claim
Litigation costs shall be borne by the plaintiff
Our court heard your opinions and made this decision.
Good luck
I'm sorry for my incompetence
what are you going to do next?
I will appeal the decision.
I'm leaving here
Thank you
THE END