Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Previously in Episode 1 & 2 of  Series
I pronounce judgment on the divorce claim of SAWANO YOKO and SAWANO SHINSUKE.
I would dismiss plaintiff's claims.
YOKO lost the trial.
YOKO's six months of efforts were in vain.
Their love began when they were students.
Suddenly an unfortunate incident occurred.
Mitsuharu was gone
I married with Shinsuke Sawano
A glamorous but empty wedding
But
Mitsuharu is alive
He lost his memory
His memory is getting recovery
And
They got to meet again
Yoko!
His heart was broken.
He was asked by Nimura to go to Cambodia for work
He accepted it
He's focusing on his work now
YOKO was in divorce court with SHINSUKE.
But she didn't work well
Yoko was lost
In desperation they met again.
Mitsuharu needed to leave for Cambodian in a few days
They walked around the part where they used to visit often
And
Please go to Cambodia as Nimura told you
Why?
I will continue with the trial.
I will fight it all the way to the Supreme Court.
YOKO
I got courage from you
I will put up with not seeing you for six months.
They were feeling braver.
They exchanged their watch
For their love
They walked in the park in the morning and go home
Mitsuharu will go to Cambodia in a few days
End of Episode 1&2 Summary
AT THE SIDE OF THE BRIDGE (Episode 3)
This is my first time to leave from Japan
I'm parting from Yoko bit by bit
How are you doing now that the trial is over?
We are away now, but we believe in each other
I believe in our future so I don't worry about being in Japan
I passed Hong Kong, and Indonesia
I adjust the time
I'll arrive in Phnom Penh
It's still rainy season in Cambodia
It's raining
This is Phnom Penh city
I'll stay here for 3 months
The hotel where I say is in the middle of City
This is my first time I spend the night in Cambodia
I still feel like being in Tokyo
I'm getting lonely to be alone
It's getting night here.
I guess Tokyo is mid-night
The Southern Cross is very visible here.
Japan embassy
Here close at 1 pm.
Shall we go out?
This is Angkor Wat.
This is so great
I've wanted to see Angkor Wat.
Oh you are architect
It's easy to go there.
There are plane for there 4 times a week. and it takes 7 hours if you get a bus
I definitely go
What's wrong,Bros?
I'm on the work
Ask me when I finish my work
I might be fired
Eh?
They'll fire me
Tell me why?
Because of you
I'm your brother
That's so mean that they fire you
Sawano is department chief but
They will fire me for some reason or another.
To be honest. all is your fault.
It's because of your divorce decree.
Please Yoko
Please think about our feelings as my family will be confused.
You don't have to be stubborn.
I'm not stubborn.
you don't listen to my wishes
Bros
Do you still love Sugano?
You are an idiot
I've got 3 days off
I decided to go to angkor wat
It takes about 7 hours by long-distance bus
This is very simple long trip
I was thinking about Angkor Wat
Angkor Wat is one of the seven wonders of the world
I learned about it when I was in elementary school and saw the picture when I was in junior high school.
I aspired to be an architect when I saw these ruins.
I'm here now
this is beautiful,right?
Are you Japanese?
Yes I am
It's good to see from here
I always watch the sunset from here
Angkor Wat sunset is the most beautiful in the world
My first day here was so dreamy
I wanted to share this excitement with Yoko.
I really wanted it
My brother called me again
I was worried about my brother's company, so I went to see him.
He is Mr. Kadokura who is a journalist
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kadokura
Let’s get down to the work, OK?
When did Director SAWANO buy a new car?
I think he bought it late last year
Why you ask me about it?
The story matches
Director SAWANO received a huge bribe from Kawabata-gumi for this construction
he is trying to fire me to escape his responsibility
Really?
After Mr. Kadakura investigated it, I understood clearly.
He was about to be in trouble
what are you going to do?
With his help, we publish in industry magazines
This'll be only way I survive
are you okay with that?
I have no choice but to do it
If Director SAWANO is demoted, he will be promoted.
will you help me?
But
Please help me to solidify the evidence
I understand your position
We journalists cannot tolerate such injustice.
Let's have a drink together.
I'm happy to have a drink with a beautiful woman
The ruins have been sleeping in this forest for a thousand years.
As an architect, I was very interested in these ruins.
I wanted to make something related to Angkor Wat in my next work.
thank you for guiding me today
I forgot to introduce about me.
I'm Mitsuharu SUgano
I'm Erina Shiozawa
Shiozawa?
It's like Japanese name
My father is Japanese
Three days stay was too short
Some people wants to stay here forever
I returned to Phnom Penh by evening bus
She will also fly to Phnom Penh tomorrow.
See you again
See you
See you in Phnom Penh
Are you the president of Toyo Light Metal?
Yes
I'm Kadokura who called you
have you published this yet?
Not yet.
We will officially print it tomorrow
You did a lot of research and wrote the article
Thanks
What can I do for you?
Would you mind if I published this article?
I'm not happy
I heard that SAWANO's father is a major shareholder of Toyo Light Metal
I think he will be surprised if he reads this article
What do you want?
This is all I need to trash this article.
OK
But I have one condition for you.
What?
Who told this?
No one
I think it's someone in the company
Director Sawano will be removed from the department head's seat and asked to go on a business trip to Europe for a while.
Mr. Yamada, the sales manager, will take over his job.
Yamada
I'll tell you your disposition later
what is my disposal?
Do you want to know?
You shared company secrets with an outsider.
Actually, you guys were going to be fired from the company.
You know?
Kenchikukai Tenbousha Magazine
Oh Nimura
I stopped publishing that article.
There was still a lack of proof.
I didn't know you are such a person
That's the gangster way
gangster?
Yeah, people say that behind me
First of all, it's your responsibility
You should give up
Toki is also leaving
I want to go back soon, but my mother is sick.
She's old so it may takes long
It can't be helped
I miss you
I wanna ask you a favor
About CHikako
I'll look after her
I am also responsible
I feel sorry for her because she spends her time in many houses.
I hope her grandfather can be found
Watch out!
We're sorry
Are you OK?
Oh
Your kid?
Yeah
Where's your mom?
She died of illness three years ago
I see
did you hear about your brother?
I tried any way, but It does not work well
at least he wasn't fired
I heard that you took very good care of my brother.
See you
Who is he?
A strange man
Do you get letters from Mitsuharu?
Yes sometime
What did he say?
I won't tell
Sorry to ask you about it
I will travel on a business trip next month
i want you to accompany me
Yes
Mr. Hori always accompanies me.
He's not feeling well.
I'm going abroad, so I want to go with a beautiful woman.
abroad?
i forgot to say that first
To Southeast Asia
Bangkok
Do you know there?
Thailand
There's a big Nissan dealer there called k2 motors.
Please ask the Foreign Affairs Division for details.
Please reply as soon as possible because there is a relationship between passport and visa.
Chikako!
I have a news
Welcome home
Excuse me the other day
i have something to report to you
What's that?
About your brother.
he is not fired
He will be transferred to Kyushu
Thanks for telling me
i think you misunderstand me something
i stopped him from getting fired
he misunderstands me and says it's my fault
Sorry to bother you
I like women's room
I'm jealous of you
I'm curious as to who designed those blueprints.
My friend designed it
he is very creative
Are you curious?
I'm curious
Her lover
Chikako
You got a  lover
No way
I'm starving
I'm leaving
He seems to be great
i wanted to be an architect
See you again
sorry i didn't do anything to you
I think he is a rude person who suddenly enters the room
i want to know your news
I might be able to meet Mitsuharu-san
do you go to Cambodia?
I’ll go to Thailand
Thailand
Next to the Cambodia
That's so nice!
I'm envy you
You're fever is gone.
Yes
I feel relieved
You have been a great help to me.
i feel sorry for you to be here
I just wanna to be here
But...
your father is worried about you
do you feel bad for him?
I will fly home tomorrow
I see
See you
I wanted to have a meal with the whole family before he went abroad.
you like formalities
You have a bad mouth afterwards
I thought this would be a good time to discuss
Don't you think so?
It's waste time
I think Yoko needs it
i know how you feel but...
I see
You're not home all the time, so you don't know how they feel.
Bangkok?
Yes
Did you make up your mind?
Our family is in a lot of trouble right now.
But this is my work
You're kidding me.
I know you wanna meet with Sugano in Cambodia by the way
You...
You mean I can't go?
Don't worry about me
Your husband will be relegated to Kyushu and you will go abroad, so that's a good thing.
I see
I'm sorry
What the hell!
What's wrong?
Nothing
are you crying because you are happy?
It might be so
are you okay alone?
Don't worry.
I can do anything
i will come back as soon as possible
please take your time sightseeing
Thank you
today is my departure day
I will fly in the southern sky in the same plane you boarded
This plane passes Phnom Penh and goes directly to Bangkok
I will pass over Phnom Penh where you are
But from Bangkok to Phnom Penh it takes only 1 hour by plane.
There are flights every day
i want to see you somehow
It's my dream to make it happen on this trip
Excuse me but Are you Ms.Makimura?
Yes
I'm sorry for being late.
I'm from K2 motors
I heard that the president will pick me up
He had an urgent business, so I came instead.
I see.
She is the secretary SAWANO
Pleased to meet you
I heard you're staying at our house tonight.
Your house?
I forgot to introduce myself.
My name is Erina Shiozawa
are you the president's daughter?
He's my father
sorry he's late
He always back home late?
I have no chance to eat with him,but tonight...
Oh he's back
You're so late
I'm sorry
You're bad
Thank you for coming
It's been a age
Have a seat
did you know her?
How did you know her?
It's been 20 years since I met her
It's been 25 years
enjoy your meal everyone
my father was a little strange.
he is usually very arrogant
i think their relationship is strange
It might be so
Because she is very beautiful
is she married?
She's still single
I have thought about going back to Japan with my daughter and remarrying.
But I end up staying here
I can't go back now
I never imagined that I would meet you again, who became a manager.
This deal is in your favor.
i want to make amends to you
Shiozawa
I decline it
I didn't come here with that intention.
I get it
Angkor Wat, next to Tasom is Krumpur
You can get there soon by plane from Bangkok
Do you often go there?
Yes
These are photos that I got there last time
This is so good
Who takes this photo?
Well
Your friend?
You don't wanna show me?
I can't
Go to there if you wanna see Anchor
But I'm here for work
Your work finish tomorrow, I'm happy to guide you then
Thanks, but
Your bed gets ready
Thanks
Let's go there together
Yes
I'm sure they'll permit you to go
Good night
The president show me around Bangkok
But I only think about going to Anchor
This way
We can stay for 24 hours in Cambodia  even if you don't have the VISA
I really wanna go there
I think of nothing but going to Cambodia
I wonder Elina talked him about that
I heard Sawano wanna go to Anchor
Ah..yes
Did you talk about that?
Yes with Elina
She only wants to go there because of you.
I'm afraid, I'm on the work
It's ok, 1,2 days
It's ok. You asked me about Phnom phen.
Do you have a friend there?
Yes Kind of
Who?
Just friend
He or She?
What does he/she do there?
That's weird question.
Her face shows that the friend is young man
Oh really?
Do you wanna see him?
Don't get me wrong, but I actually
Don't bully her
What does he do there?
He's there for Architectural Design
Ok Please go
We have time for boarding
Thank you
You help me a lot
I just happened to think of going there
But We can only stay there for 24 hours
It can't be helped
Where is he staying?
He stays at Hotel Phnom phen
Hotel Phnom phen?
Do you know?
Yes I know.
What does he do there?
He's there for Architectural Design
Is this fine?
Yes
You made mistake
Check Ms.Sawano
Mrs. is Ok
Why?
I have some reasons
Can you tell me what his name is?
He's Sugano
I see
Where's Mr.Sugano
He's gone for Anchor
He's gone for Anchor?
He told us to stay there for a few days
If We fly tomorrow morning to Encore, it's 10:00.
Our flight for Bangkok is 14:00
We have 4 hours
You can see Mitsuharu if we have 4 hours
What's wrong?
You just said Mitsuharu
I told you he was Sugano
but not Mitsuharu
Our hotel is there
Why you didn't tell me about him?
It's natural that you and he got meet
But you should tell me about him earlier
I feel sorry that you hide me about him
He told me you were just friend
So?
I've been just wondering
But it's wrong
He's your lover,right?
Oh, Elina's lover is Sawano's...
His name is Sugano
There are few Japanese Architects there
Why you didn't stop them to go there?
It can't be helped
I thought that made them solve something
One of them break hearts later
You're so mean
Elina really wanna get married with him
I can't stop
It can't be helped if she got broken hearts
I didn't want to give her a hard time.
If she gets marry him, I'll be willing to give him my all assets
You mean Sugano is more happy if he marry her
You are ironic
I'll leave it to your imagination
You are so mean.
I felt sorry that I made your heart hurt
But I have nothing to do with my wife's assets
Forget about that
I'm guessing Anchor wat is the problem
What do you mean?
My wife and I went there together.
It made us change our life
Anchor wat has something power.
Then We got married
You are very literary.
I was going too far
Once you go there, you'll know
So there's a woman's curse on Encore.
He's not here.
Let's go to Paya
You should be in hurry
I wanted to come here alone
I really feel bad
You love him, right?
You keep silent.
I don't have to worry about you?
Don't worry
But I love him too
This is what I really feel
How can you say that?
Sorry but you are not single,right?
Hello?
He's there
Come on
What's wrong?
Yoko
I shouldn't have come here
What?
What do you worry about?
I'm not blaming you
It's not your fault
You have nothing to regret.
I've had this kind of experiences before
But not now,Yoko
Yoko
It's time to go
Hold on
You don't have to leave today
But Visa is available for 24 hours
Yoko will be unable to go back in Japan
It will work out
I have to go
You may get upset if I tell this
I don't think you and Sugano get along well
Sorry but I'm too honest
I never think about that
You don't know anything about us
I don't know well about you but
My predictions are usually right.
Don't tell this to anyone
Shiozawa and I were lover before
We were student and he went to teach a french man as a tutor
His daughter was very pretty..then something happened
I got shocked and tried to commit suicide
I ended up to think like this.
He was rich man. If he got married with his daughter, he was going to be happy
I could get married with him if I force to get him back
But I think he would have regretted marrying me.
I never had that confidence.
So now I understand what we decided
Men are untreatable
I don't trust men
What do you think?
I never think in the way of your thinking
That is Waterloo
Are you sure to go back yesterday?
Yes We have finished my work
But I want you to stay here little longer
I'm sorry
2 months later
Yoko
Aya!
Where did you get back?
Yesterday
with Fujikawa
He's still in Hokkaido
Oh why?
why did you come home alone?
i decided to get married
I came back to prepare for that
You were already married in Hokkaido, weren't you?
that's a secret
Only you guys know, so please keep it a secret
You're so cheeky
You’ll be busy
I have to find an apartment, find a wedding venue, and decide on a wedding date.
i have to buy furniture
do you have that much money?
If I have money, I will spend it
Look at this,Yoko
The building that Mr. Sugano is building over there is very popular.
Fujikawa-san is very impressed
What's wrong?
Did you see him there?
I'm ok
do you get letters from him?
Yes sometimes
I haven't seen him in a long time, so I won't have anything to write about.
Sorry to have kept you waiting
Thank you
talk to me for a minute.
Don't run away
I told you.
I have nothing to do with you
Please stop waiting for me on the street
Why?
I wanted to see you
Please stop it.
I worry people’s eye too
Don't get me wrong
you think I’m a bad person.
But I'm not
I am very serious when I meet you
I know
I know it's lonely at Christmas alone
Please go home
Your kid is waiting for you
Excuse me
Will you go back to Hokkaido for New Year's?
I wanna stay here
I'm going to be glad if you'll stay here
I don't wanna be alone
next year you won't be alone
Why?
You and Mitsuharusan will spend the next year together.
Maybe next year I'll be alone with you
So we should be good friend
Why?
That's weird
He's supposed to live here
I plan to leave here.
I'm thinking of entering a high school with a dormitory next year.
You're strange these days
Thank you for caring me
Let's congratulate Fujikawa-san.
Cheers
Congratulations
today is a sad day for me
You should be honest
Congratulations
Enjoy your meal tonight
What can I do for you?
Mitsuharu Sugano is your student
He works at our office
This design document was written by Mr. Sugano.
This is what we are building in Cambodia
You know the latest Building, don't you?
Oh, that's an American architect.
I haven't seen the latest issue yet
I think this design is the same as the American building.
What do you think?
Yeah
i don't think this is a coincidence
What do you wanna say?
I think he stole the design idea
Are you still busy?
Where are you going?
Hold on
What's wrong about Sugano?
Congratulations
I just got a call for you
From Mitsuharu Sugano
he called from haneda airport.
He'll call you again
What's wrong?
Well
Talk to me after you meet IMURA-sensei
I know nothing about it
No comment?
Tell me something
Stop talking to me
Sugano
Where are you staying?
I learned about you on the plane.
I never imagined being caught by a newspaper reporter.
Thanks for helping me
you're going to have a hard time
Where are you staying?
I haven't decided yet
Come to my hotel
I feel sorry
You should stay at my hotel to get away from the newspaper reporters.
do you doubt me too?
I trust you
I just want to make sure you're not plagiarizing.
It's strange that this design got votes at the same time
That's an original idea that I came up with for the encore.
I didn't steal
Calm down
I get upset
he feels same as you
People think our company stole IDEA
He got shocked more than you got
Sorry
Welcome home
What's wrong
Could you check if there is a man outside the window?
Yes there is
I know that man
Shall I call a police?
He was just chasing me
But...
I understand he is in Japan.
Did you meet him?
Why?
He seems to be busy
you can meet him tomorrow
Yeah
Be sure to meet him
I want to go with you, but I won't
Is this oK?
Thanks
This message is for you
I told him you would be right back but he left this message and left
Thanks
All day yesterday a newspaper reporter chased me and didn't have time to contact you.
If I meet you at the company, I can only talk a little.
i think we have to talk for a long time
I don't care if you get mad at me
I will be waiting for you at my hotel from around 4 o'clock.
Please come
Elina
It's been a age
when did you come to japan?
This morning.
I thought you went out because you weren't in the room
I decided to go to Germany for a while
to Germany?
I will study at a German university
i have an appointment with my father
I see
See you
Madam
Why you are here?
Hold on
do you really think he plagiarized?
I'm here to talk about it
It's none of your business
Excuse me
Please listen
i know some truth
I'm not lying you
If a woman named SAWANO comes, please give this to her.
I get it
Are you saying you have proof that he plagiarized?
I don't mean that
What do you know?
you look so scary.
i won't attack you
Tell me now
What are your thoughts on his plagiarism case??
he's not the type to do that
That what I thought
You're right
he is innocent
why do you say such things?
i have the proof
I'll let you see it now if you want to see it
Wanna see?
but there is a trade-off
What it is?
Will you be my wife?
Don't get surprised so much
I can control his architect's life
I won't reveal this secret easily
I want you
Stop it
Please
Please be my wife for one night
Please go home.
I'll call someone
Go ahead
i like you so I’m not afraid to be embarrassed
I'm really serious
i want to dedicate my life to you
Please stop it
Sis
What the hell?
Excuse me
he came again.
the air in the room is dirty
Oh
Brother is there
I think you have him confused with someone else.
Did you meet him today?
He must be bros
He doesn't have to come
How do you know?
Bros!
Tell me the reason
I don't want to bother you any more
that's a very old idea
If you leave the company now, you have admitted plagiarism.
You may be right
why don't you fight?
i don't feel like that
What?
i want to start all over again
don't be sentimental
It can't be helped that you don't understand my feelings
I met Shiozawa-san and Erina-san last night.
Did you know they were in Tokyo?
Yes I knew
Did you know he's staying at the same hotel?
I see
do you still love him?
Or
That's good for you
I have worried about you from time to time.
Sorry
That's good for you
He is a problem in this plagiarism case.
He didn't
He is not one of those people.
Really?
I am determined to give up on him
I still have mixed feelings actually.
I came back from Cambodia and suffered a lot from that.
I don't give up on him because he plagiarized.
What do you mean?
i don't despise men like you
Actually your lover...
That's not true
he's just unlucky in life
That's what I thought
I accept his humanity
what are you going to do now?
I want to live in a rural area away from Tokyo.
I think I can do things like shop design
i can't even stay in a hotel
It's time to say good bye
Hold on
i want to support you
What?
how would you like to work abroad?
But
I have an acquaintance at the University of Hamburg in Germany, so why don't you study there for a while?
you won't be lonely
I won't but
What do you think about it?
It's easy
Excuse me
Are you Sawano?
Yes I am
I'm Mistuyo Murata
I was Kadokura's wife
don't be so surprised
But
What?
i heard his wife died
you believed it to be true?
I have a favor to ask from you
about his son
my son too
About your son?
Last night he came to me drunk
he blamed himself
that's what he often says
I got argue with him
But he didn't go home
I think he's gone to home country
to home country?
i don't worry about him but i have a kid
i want you to take care of him
Me?
Why me?
i have a husband now
it's not convenient for me
But he is your son
he hates me.
he runs away when i go see him
but I’m in trouble
i have nothing to do with him
I don't think so
i don't blame you
he seems to really like you
No way
He may be joking, but he said he would go home and commit suicide.
Suicide?
that's his catchphrase
Please aspect my favor
I can't handle him.
This is something small
Hold on
Thank you
Did you decided to go to Germany?
Not yet, so I'm here to talk about it
The University of Hamburg is one of the world's leading universities in architecture
i dreamed of studying there
I'm worried about Shiozawa-san supporting me.
It's been so hard for me to be in the country side for a few years.
It's great to be able to go to the University of Hamburg.
That's good that rich people support you
You are so mean
Shut up
Fujikawa
do you really think so?
What the hell you are talking about,Sugano?
Are you thinking of Yoko?
You won't tell me about Yoko
you are so cowardly
I tried to tell you, but I couldn't tell you
Yoko and I have no more chances
Don't say bullshit
Don't be loud
i don't know what happened to you guys in Cambodia.
you guys believed in each other so much
You guys are lying about something.
Be strong!
Fujikawa
Are you going to leave Yoko and go abroad with a sponsor from a rich person?
Say something!
Calm down
Shut up!
There is something he doesn't know, so you should explain it to him.
Ok I tell him.
Come on,Chikako
Chikako
Have a seat
she didn't go see you because she was feeling well
Why you are here?
Yoko is not in Tokyo now
She is not?
She was in Hokuriku by train a while ago.
To Hokuriiku?
To the Noto Peninsula
why does she go there?
i will talk about it
please read this before
I had to go to Noto Peninsula with Mr. Kadokura's child.
Ask chikako the reason
I don't want to see him, but I have to go for my child's sake.
This trip could be the end of our love affair.
Mr. Fujikawa and others has encouraged me a lot.
My love did not win Mitsuharu-san over.
i am going to give up
i feel so miserable now
Only our vehicle went to Wajima.
Wajima is a town at the tip of the Noto Peninsula in the Sea of Japan.
there it's cloudy like my heart
Excuse me
What can I do for you?
Is this the house of Rokutaro Kadokura's older brother?
Yes this is
Oh Toshibo
Where's Kadokura?
he is working now.
Hey Rokutaro
Rokutaro
Please come in
Stupid
I don't know her but she brought him
you are a terrible father
welcome
i wanted to make you suffer
I tried to make you suffer by pretending to commit suicide
I never imagined you would come here
I only came here because I feel sorry for him.
You saw right through my methods.
I'm sorry
I'm so bad man
As an apology, I will share with you the truth about SUGANO's plagiarism case.
I used to want to be an architect
Two years ago there was a design competition for the National Concert Hall.
I submitted a work that took me a year to make.
I devoted my life to the work
i was confident
The result was I came in second.
But far from 1 place
Sugano took the first place
I was surprised to see his work
I fully admitted my defeat
since then i threw it all away
i became poor and my wife left me
I went to your house and saw the blueprints on the wall.
That was great work
I just found out that is Sugano's work
and you were your lover
I got jealous of you
I was jealous of his job and his lover
I totally hated him.
The plagiarism trap was simple.
I coped his design.
And I asked my American friend to publish it
That's all
So you are
I'm the criminal
Please tell him
This will prove he is innocent.
Ok, I'll tell him
Thanks for telling me
I don't get it why he's going to Germany
I hear A supporter paid him
He leaves you here and go
I don't know why you are ok
Madam?
He's gone for Yagura hot spring
I see
What's wrong?
I'm guessing Sawano visited here yesterday
She stayed at Fujiya inn and go back by first train
She's from Tokyo,right?
She told me she took a bus
Bus? not a train?
She wanted to see sea side.
She took a bus that depart 8 am
What for?
She told me the sea was very clam more than I thought
I taught her Sosogi beach.
The waters there are rough, but she said she wanted to see it.
Yoko!
Where you've come here?
Let's go back
You got wetting
I need to tell you something
Kadokura committed plagiarism.
Kadokura committed plagiarism.?
He told me that
So You'll be innocent
I see
When I return to Tokyo, I will tell you about it and congratulate you.
That's not important to me now
I was worried about plagiarism and was thinking of going to Germany.
I was so mad
I was thinking that without making an effort to meet you
Fujikawa scold me about that
You won't go to Germany?
Yeah
Why You won't go to Germany?
I will not go abroad without you.
You should go
you will regret it in the future
What are you saying?
you don't need to turn it down for me
Don't get me wrong
Why you don't understand what I feel?
Yoko!
I ask you again,
Are you Ok not to meet Sugano any more?
You can't wait for him?
I believed you would visit me at that night
I worried and I waited until 8.pm
But you didn't come
I thought you declined me
I couldn't wait to see you
There was a light in your room
I was afraid to come in
I visited your hotel at the night
After seeing you at the encore, I was very distressed.
I resented you and blamed myself.
I wanted to give it all up.
I made up my mind to see you again when I read the letter
I came to the hotel at the appointed time
But You were with Elina
You've come
I felt miserable and went back
I made up my mind not to see you any more
It was very surprising to me that Erina-san was there at that time.
I feel same way
But Why?
I lost my confidence.
We won't get along well
I don't think so
The coincidence that you met ELINA is very shocking to me.
I had that feeling too when I was you and Elsa at the encore.
Don't get me wrong!
Be strong
And believe in me
I was thinking all the time on the train.
i hurt you so much
But forgive me
I really need you
Did you tell her?
Our father is in critical condition.
I called her company and they told me she's gone for Noto
She's not here.
I have no way to get her back
Our  father is in critical condition.
Officially She is My wife.
Please call her now
THE END