Translation/Subtitle: Translator requests anonymity
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
AT THE SIDE OF THE BRIDGE (Episode 1)
I'm reflected in your eyes.
And I'm reflected in your eyes.
Yoko-san.
I love you.
Mitsuharu-san.
Wow.
Yoko-san, let's get married.
Soon after we graduate.
I'll definitely make you happy.
SUKIYA BRIDGE
I'm worried.
If I leave today and go home,
when will I see you again?
It's only six more months.
Six months?
What do you mean six months?
As soon as I graduate and
get a job, I'm coming for you.
All right.
Before I go to your
house and ask for your hand,
you have to take care of your father and
heal him so that you can come to Tokyo with me.
Thank you, Mitsuharu-san.
Next time we meet here, we'll be engaged.
Right.
So take care of yourself.
Okay.
KUJUKU ISLANDS, NAGASAKI
No matter how many times you say it,
I have no control over Yoko's situation.
Everything has to be decided
by my eldest son in Tokyo.
I cannot give you any answer.
I understand.
I'm going back to Tokyo and
talk to her brother about it.
But…
What do you think…
about my marriage to Yoko-san?
You came all the way from Tokyo to see me.
I'm really sorry about that.
Can't you at least stay one night?
I'm not a student anymore, so
I can't do whatever I want.
But we haven't seen each other in six months.
I'll meet up with your brother
as soon as I get back to Tokyo.
You'd better do that.
I'm sure my brother will understand.
I've met him a few times myself.
So it's going to be all right.
So just make your father well again.
So that you can come to
Tokyo whenever you want, okay?
TOYO LIGHT METAL CO.
Please come in.
What is it? What do they want from me?
I don't know.
Niimura is here.
YOKO NIIMURA
- Niimura-kun, is it?
- Yes, sir.
You know him, don't you?
He's the father of Director Sawano.
Yes, I know.
I don't see the resemblance.
Unfortunately, I don't
remember that beauty either.
Why did your sister quit the company?
Oh.
She temporarily quit due to family reasons.
What is it?
Actually, you see, this is a marriage proposal.
My son is very much enamored with your sister.
He has a weak spot for her.
Where is Niimura-kun?
He was just called into
the president's office.
Oh, that's fine then.
Yes.
A visitor?
Niimura is not here.
He's in the president's office now.
I didn't expect that.
Why is your brother against our marriage?
Your brother looked at me as
if I were a thief or something…
He left before I could say anything else.
I left the office like I was being kicked out.
Yoko-san.
Yoko-san, I know you're
at the far end of Kyushu.
If I could reach you,
I wish I could hold you now.
Yoko-san, I want you to make up
your mind and come to Tokyo.
I'm waiting for you.
As promised, I'm waiting for you at the
small park at the foot of the Sukiya Bridge.
No matter what anyone says, we'll get married.
And we'll be happy.
Call an ambulance!
Hang in there. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
His legs are bruised.
The right arm looks like a
severe compound fracture.
Good work.
We might need to amputate his right arm.
Bring me the equipment.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, you've got to help me.
Sure.
[INDISTINCT]
I have to…
I have to!
I… I'm an architect.
[INDISTINCT] The design…design…
Doctor!
It's okay, it's okay.
Hang in there.
Here.
It'll be over soon.
Yoko-san.
Mitsuharu-san.
Why won't you write to me?
What happened to you?
My brother has brought me
another marriage proposal.
Did you meet with my brother?
It has been more than three
months since we parted on this island.
I can't stand it any longer.
My father is feeling a little better.
I'm going to Tokyo.
I have only one purpose.
I only want to meet with you, Mitsuharu-san.
At that small park by Sukiya Bridge.
Mitsuharu-san!
It's been a while.
As you can see,
I'm still too nervous to walk alone.
We can't really talk out here.
Two cups of coffee, please.
Certainly.
I…thought about writing you a letter.
But I thought that if I had written
to you, I'd have only hurt you.
How very self-serving of you.
Do you know how many letters
I've written in the last six months?
I wish you'd have figured it out yourself.
Figure what out?
You promised so much on the island--
Yoko-san.
I'm not the old Mitsuharu Sugano anymore.
Look at this hand.
Look at my legs.
I'm a changed man.
No.
That's not true.
There must be some other reason.
Just say it. Don't try to play games with me.
There's no other reason.
You can imagine whatever you want.
♪ In a strange city ♪
♪ When the sun is setting ♪
♪ The evening moon on the stream's bank ♪
♪ Watches your shadow and mine ♪
♪ Standing still and in silence ♪
♪ I tried to see you, but our happiness ♪
♪ Our happiness was lost in the clouds ♪
That was dangerous!
Yoko-san!
Back up! Back up!
I knew it was you.
It's me.
Fujikawa.
Okay.
Madam, I'm going to take a seat.
Oh, no.
Don't peek too much into our dressing rooms.
Go ahead.
This is kind of like my nest.
Fujikawa-san, would you like
some freshly made rice balls?
Well, I heard that Sugano graduated and
went to work for Imura-sensei's design office.
I haven't had a chance to meet him yet.
I shouldn't have been
away in Kyushu for a year.
I mean, you believed in Sugano, right?
Yes, I did.
But…
Well? It'll calm you down. Have a drink.
Here.
What's that? You're an idiot.
She's not a hussy like
you lot, she can't drink.
Madam!
Why are you so foul-mouthed?
What? Oh, sorry.
Yoko-san.
Well, I'm going to see Sugano.
You should go home to your brother.
If you don't want another
marriage proposal, just say no.
I want to help you, even
if I can help only a little.
So, when are we going to
meet Director Sawano's parents?
Yeah, after I got a call from you,
I called the Director right
away to let him know that
Yoko was here, so he'll
decide in a couple of days.
I hope Yoko-san is all right.
What?
Because she was with that boy Sugano…
I heard he recently got a new woman.
I've been doing some digging.
It seems she was his nurse
when he was hospitalized.
Well…
Then thank goodness you said no to him.
I knew he'd be that kind of a guy anyway.
Welcome home.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
you were back, Brother.
You look tired, Yoko.
Was the train crowded?
No.
Thanks for taking care
of our father for so long.
Take it easy tonight, we'll talk tomorrow.
Brother!
What is it?
Well…
Did Sugano-san come to see you sometime?
Sugano?
Oh, a friend of yours from school, right?
Didn't he use to come to our house sometime?
Yes, did he come to see you?
No, I don't recall that.
I see.
This is Sugano-kun's
sketch. Can you believe it?
This is Sugano's?
There's no trace of his old talent.
I ordered him to redraft it.
He's lost the use of his right
hand because of an accident.
No, this is not about his hands.
He has no inspiration now.
Actually, you came to visit him
today, but he's absent without leave.
Don't you think it's strange
for a very promising young man?
He must be out of his mind to show this to you.
This is a mental problem.
He's troubled about something right now.
I'm trying to give him a job in Hokkaido.
Hokkaido?
He needs a new life.
What do you think?
Did Sugano say he's going?
He's badly struggling right now.
Sorry.
Did I disturb you?
No.
It's okay.
Your hands will get better.
Don't get upset. Okay?
By the way…
I was on my way home from the hospital, and it
smelled so good, I bought so many croquettes.
They're still warm.
Hey.
Do you want to eat together?
It's okay, right?
Sugano-san, you have a visitor.
Hey, Sugano.
Oh, Fujikawa-san.
It's been a while.
How's your arm?
Yeah, it's much better.
I went to Imura-sensei's today
and he told me you took the day off.
Please come in.
Shall I make you some tea?
Please.
He's mad at you
for taking a day off without notice.
Is that so?
I heard you're going to Hokkaido.
Are you two going together?
I'm sorry.
I was surprised to hear about Hokkaido.
I'm going to Hokkaido in the near future.
I see.
Then before you go,
you should have another x-ray.
Sugano.
I met Yoko-san yesterday.
What?
That poor girl.
She feels betrayed by you.
Hey, Sugano.
Did you really do something to betray her?
Or maybe you got a weird
complex from being injured.
I hope you're not thinking of
stepping aside for Yoko-san's sake--
No!
Please don't talk about that.
Okay.
You and I have always gotten
along oddly enough since school.
You're my older brother in terms of talent,
but I consider myself a
senior in terms of worldliness.
Hey.
Why can't you talk to me about all this?
I'm sorry.
My current suffering is…
I believe that I have no
choice but to solve it myself.
Oh, hello.
Um, this is a rather impolite question, but…
Yes?
What kind of relationship do
you have with Sugano-kun?
What kind of question is that?
Huh?
I'm a visiting nurse, a friend, a…
And a lover?
If I were his lover, if he didn't tell
me that he was going to Hokkaido…
That's strange.
This is not a lucky night for me.
As you see.
Toki-san.
I was going to say something
a little earlier about Hokkaido…
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's better this way.
I get so worried when you're around
that I just keep coming to visit you.
But if you go to Hokkaido, I can give up.
Before you come back…
…I'm going to get married.
I'm going to get married in an
arranged marriage or something.
Mitsuharu-san.
When you are in Hokkaido,
what if you were with her?
With the woman you parted ways with yesterday.
Because it's silly to look at sketches
of your memories all the time.
Yoko.
Tonight I went to a bar in Ginza,
courtesy of Director Sawano.
Well, he totally treated me.
But when you're a Director,
you're popular even in a bar.
Yoko, this is for you.
The Director insisted that
I give it to you. It's a cake.
Want some?
No, I…
Oh, well, I'll just take it then,
and I'll give it to my subordinates.
We'll just thank him tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yeah, we're going to have dinner tomorrow.
I don't want to.
Idiot.
The Director is inviting us
as a favor, how can I refuse?
We're going to dinner.
You should join us.
I see.
I'm surprised.
I didn't know she was this beautiful.
You're right, Sawano-san has a discerning eye.
No, ma'am, it was Yoko-san's work
ethic that caught my attention first.
So she's not like you in that respect.
Niimura-san, where's your wife today?
It's just that we have three children…
It would have been nice if you
had brought her on a day like this.
I'm sorry.
Yoko-san.
I heard your father is
not feeling well. Is he sick?
Yes, he has a mild cerebral hemorrhage.
Well, well, that's a long illness.
Everything's ready.
They say they're ready.
- Shall we go?
- Let's go.
Hey, what does that mean?
I'm surprised, too.
But it can't be helped.
It's bothersome, isn't it, Yoko-san?
…No.
Shall we end this formal meeting
early and go to Ginza later?
Niimura-kun, please take care of the rest.
Madam.
Sugano will leave for Hokkaido by
plane and will not be back for a while.
He wants to see his
friend Yoko-san before that.
What are you going to do when you see her?
They would have to talk
to each other to know that.
Sugano-san, I believe my
husband has turned you down.
I don't want you to wait for Yoko.
You have no right to say that.
It's Yoko's matchmaking day today.
Matchmaking?
That's ridiculous.
That's a lie.
What do you mean it's a lie!
If you don't believe me, ask the Prince Hotel.
Her date is a young director.
The president of the company is
taking on the role of matchmaker.
But Yoko-san is--
Yoko, you know, volunteered to go.
- No, I'm not talking about--
- Sugano-san.
I heard that you have a woman with you.
How could you come here?
Did Yoko-san tell you that?
Yes, she did.
So she chose this matchmaking
on her own after thinking about it.
Do you still want to interrupt her?
You're a brazen one, aren't you?
You say a lot of things that are hard to say.
Fujikawa-san.
That's enough.
Please just tell Yoko-san
that I came to say goodbye.
Please.
I see.
Thank you very much for your time.
Stop a car, you're going to miss your flight.
What's that? You're the one who stalled me.
Hey, stop! Stop for a second!
Sugano-san, find a nice woman in Hokkaido.
(ANNOUNCEMENT): I would like to
inform you about your departure flight.
(ANNOUNCEMENT):  Japan Airlines…
Oh.
Time to go.
- You got the card?
- Yes.
Take care.
Forget about her.
I might go there sometime.
See you in Hokkaido.
Okay?
You were right…
I should have been more honest…
I should have said I love her if I love her.
But… it's too late.
Idiot.
Congratulations on the successful agreement
of your marriage with the Niimura family.
I have brought the betrothal gift to
you today, as it is a very lucky day.
Yoko.
Yoko!
How unusual.
I wasn't expecting you to visit.
What's wrong?
I've come to ask you for a favor.
What is it?
Please take a seat.
I would like you to break
off your engagement with me.
What?
I never said I was okay with this proposal.
That's…
But I haven't heard that.
Please don't blame my brother.
It's my fault for not being
clear with my brother.
No, this is not a matter
of blaming your brother.
I'm sorry.
You've got to be kidding me.
Think about the president of the
company who agreed to be our matchmaker.
I don't know how even the good-hearted
president would feel about me or your brother.
Maybe your brother would
have a harder time than I do.
Please, help my brother…
Don't ask too much of me.
Yoko-san.
Do you hate me that much?
It's not like that…
So are you saying that you like someone else?
Is it Mitsuharu Sugano?
Sorry, but I've been
doing a lot of investigating.
But I don't mind.
Everybody has done that once or twice.
Especially a beautiful woman like you…
I, excuse me--
Wait a minute. Please think calmly.
I decided from the moment you joined the
company that you were going to be my wife.
That's enough!
We disagree on a lot of things,
but I'm not changing my mind.
Yoko-san.
I can make you happy.
I'm going home.
Go ahead.
But, Yoko-san, I'm not giving up.
He was already gone last Sunday, so it's
been ten days since he went to Hokkaido.
Hokkaido?
I think Toki-san can tell you where he is.
Who is this Toki-san?
She's a visiting nurse who lives here.
She's been taking care of
Sugano-san for a long time,
so we just assumed that the two of
them were going to Hokkaido together.
She's working at the hospital now.
He's at the Yubari Coal Mine in Hokkaido.
It's a construction site.
But why didn't he tell you?
He didn't have to tell me.
Why not?
But you're Mitsuharu-san's lover, aren't you?
What?
Such a waste of time to complicate
things when you love each other so much.
Complicate things?
I haven't…
Then why?
I…
I think you're the one who did that.
Me?
Oh, you must have misunderstood something.
Am I misunderstanding something?
Yes.
I just wanted to know
why you didn't follow him.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I don't blame you for misunderstanding
me after the way we met.
I didn't know anything. I just went along.
I've been thinking about you a lot since then.
But…
I felt like my happiness would
disappear if I began to talk about it.
I was happy just to listen to him.
I moved into a room in
front of his apartment…
I was content just to see his face every day.
I guess people who don't
know me would think I'm an idiot.
I loved Mitsuharu-san, and
Mitsuharu-san loved you.
I didn't know.
But why wasn't the misunderstanding resolved?
Even Fujikawa-san knows about me.
I'm certain that Mitsuharu-san
went to see you, too.
On the night of his departure for Hokkaido.
What?
Yoko.
I heard you went directly to the Director
today to refuse the marriage proposal.
Why couldn't you ask me,
your brother, for advice?
What would happen to my
position after that kind of outrage?
You need to think about that a little bit.
Brother, I've not wanted
this from the beginning…
Yoko.
Where do you think you're going?
Where are you going with your bag?
I'm going to Hokkaido.
I'm going to Mitsuharu-san's house.
Don't be absurd!
Brother! Just this once,
let me have my own way.
No! I won't allow you to go to Hokkaido.
Yoko-san.
Don't think like a schoolgirl like that.
Please.
If you're willing to treat me like an adult,
why did you hide the fact
that Mitsuharu-san came here?
That's…
It's because I thought about your future.
That's so selfish!
Yoko.
Think about it.
Do you know how everyone is envious that
you and Director Sawano are getting married?
We're doing everything we can
to make sure your future is secure.
Nothing you say will change my mind!
Yoko-san, wait!
Wait, please! Please think of us too!
Your brother is on the verge
of becoming an executive.
So that's why you're asking me to marry him?
You want me to sacrifice myself.
You idiot!
Yoko-san.
It's not a sacrifice…
We thought about you, too, you know.
Suit yourself.
Okay, it's not much, but
you don't know what need.
But…
It's okay.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Now you can be happy. Okay?
Okay, be careful.
Do you have makeup?
That's not good.
Here!
There you go!
Have a good trip!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Take care!
YUBARI, HOKKAIDO
♪ The windows are wet with evening dew ♪
♪ The capital is already far away ♪
♪ A traveler heading back to the north ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ Tears ♪
♪ Never cease to flow ♪
I want to die.
Shall I die with you?
You're early.
It's going to rain today.
Nobu-san.
How did I…
What?
How did I get here?
You don't remember?
You were so drunk. It's no
wonder you don't remember.
Come on.
Wash your face.
You and I almost died together last night.
We promised each other we would die together.
Did I say that?
It's easy to die.
But it's even easier to live.
See? You're alive.
What's wrong with you, you look so worried.
It's okay.
Come early this evening.
Sugano-san, a beautiful young
lady came from Tokyo to visit you.
What?
I can't believe you went home in the
morning even though you had someone like that.
Well…
So where is she?
I gave her the directions to the office.
I'm pretty sure that's her.
I believe she said her name was Yoko.
I see.
Yoko-san.
She said she wanted to go for a short
walk, so I showed her the way to the dam.
Thank you.
Yoko-san!
Mitsuharu-san.
I came here…
leaving everything behind.
I've never thought of
marrying anyone other than you.
Yoko-san.
I'm telling you the truth.
I really am. I hope you understand.
It was my fault.
It's all my fault, I was weak.
I was…
This hand is to be blamed.
This hand got in our way.
Yes.
But it's okay now.
It's getting a lot better.
I don't care if your hands don't get better.
I can be there for you from now on.
I can do anything for you.
Right?
I can stay in this town, right?
Yes.
But…
You can't say you don't want me to.
I came here determined to do that.
This is the room.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Is this room Sugano-san's?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Yoko Niimura from Tokyo--
From Tokyo?
Yes.
And you?
I…
I'm Sugano-san's…
I'm here to return Sugano-san's belonging.
What time is it?
What?
Oh, you don't have your watch.
The girl at the bar just came to deliver it.
And?
She probably went to the
inn because you weren't here.
What?
Something like this happened in Tokyo too.
Mitsuharu-san is so kind-hearted that
I'm sure he couldn't be very clear with me.
So…
But…
He's going to marry me.
We just parted today,
promising to live here together.
Please don't torment me anymore.
Torment you?
I… I left my brother's house
as if I was running away.
I can't go home anymore.
I'm not sure if that counts as torment.
I suffered like I was dying.
You're like a little girl.
Would you be surprised if I told you that
I'm not just a passing acquaintance with him?
No! He would never do that!
No?
Please, no more…
I…
I would do anything, if it's
the money that you want.
But I don't have any money here right now.
I'll give it to you later--
Don't be so self-serving!
There are some things you should
say, and things you shouldn't say.
It's his watch.
I know you recognize it.
He left this watch under
my pillow this morning.
No!
No way!
Nobu-san.
What did you do?
I was just telling her where that watch was.
Yoko-san!
Wait!
You're a terrible person!
Are you blaming me?
Can you blame me? I was just telling the truth!
Yoko-san!
It's her fault!
I was really going to walk away.
- But she made me mad!
- Yoko-san!
Yoko-san!
You are not going to forgive me, are you?
Do you hate me so much?
This morning, I was glad to be alive.
I thought everything was going to be okay.
And then I met that girl, and
everything went dark in front of my eyes.
And now you're looking at me
like that, I don't know what to do.
You…
You've ruined things for me and Yoko.
It's not my fault.
It was bad luck!
You promised me last night.
That we would die together.
Meeting Yoko won't do any good now.
Die with me.
Die with me!
Hey! You're being ridiculous.
You don't want to do it?
If you don't want to, I'll do it alone!
Wait, wait!
Nobu-san!
Hey, who's the person she tried
to commit double suicide with?
He's an architect named Sugano.
His body hasn't been found yet, though.
Either way, we have to wait until morning.
That's right.
He can get swept downstream.
By the way, that woman Nobu,
wasn't she in this hospital last
year after a failed double suicide?
Tell me about that.
I'm going to write an article about it.
Go ahead.
What about Sugano-san?
I see.
You couldn't find him.
I feel sorry for you, too.
Sugano-san and I…
There was nothing between us.
That man was yours.
He's gone.
He's no longer in this world.
My soul is also gone from this
world along with Mitsuharu-san's.
From now on, what hope is there for me to live?
Father, why don't you
understand? I told you last night.
I know you told me that, but at
least I want to be at the wedding…
You're causing me trouble.
Today, the president of the
company and executives will be here.
Are you ready?
Yes.
You're beautiful.
It's almost time, so let's go to the venue.
Okay, then.
I can't leave without seeing a little of Yoko's
happy day after coming all the way here.
Don't say that. It's hard for me, too.
Father, don't leave the room.
Do you understand? Okay, then.
Um…
As the matchmaker, I will first
introduce the bride and groom.
The groom, Shinsuke Sawano, is
currently the sales director of our company.
I'm sure you all know that he's rapidly
improving the sales performance of our company.
MIYAZAKI NICHINAN COAST
We flew to Miyazaki for our honeymoon.
And then to Kagoshima.
KAGOSHIMA
And then to Saikai, near my hometown.
SAIKAI BRIDGE
It was my first luxurious trip in my life.
NAGASAKI
But for some reason, it was an empty journey.
I tried in that emptiness to forget
all the past and to love my husband.
ONE YEAR LATER
I was a little surprised when I
came across this when I was judging.
It's just so extraordinary.
Is this so extraordinary?
There are a lot of engineers,
but real architects are hard to find.
This Tateno fellow must be the real thing.
Are you going to appoint
this man to be in charge?
Yes, I would highly recommend him.
You're building a new building and
you're trying to develop your company,
so we should let a man
of this caliber do the work.
Can you vouch for him?
I highly recommend him.
Very well.
- Yamana-kun.
- Yes.
- Call Niimura, the Deputy General Manager.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
To be honest with you, we've had a number of
meetings, and we couldn't come to a conclusion.
It's a very unusual architecture.
You're certainly right.
So I thought I'd go back to you, the expert,
and find out what you think, and then decide.
Come in.
It's about the design request.
I need you to negotiate with this man
to have him come to Tokyo right away.
I understand.
DESIGNER: YASUO TATENO, HOKKAIDO, JAPAN
When are you going to Tokyo, brother?
Not yet.
Why?
They asked you to come right away, didn't they?
But…
Why?
I really need you to go to Tokyo.
I thought I'd come with you.
I asked my uncle about it, and he said he was
worried about you going to Tokyo by yourself,
so he asked me to go with you.
So let's go to Tokyo together.
Okay.
But.
I don't know anything about
anything but design, though.
It doesn't matter!
They asked you to design it for them.
So why don't you just go ahead and do it?
Yeah, I know, but I'm a little worried
about going to a big city like Tokyo.
You have no backbone for a guy.
Don't worry, you have me.
And you always said you had
to thank my uncle for saving you.
Yeah.
So, you have to go to Tokyo and work, right?
Oh, you!
And besides, I have a grandfather in Tokyo.
I don't even know where he lives.
Excuse me, when are you coming home tonight?
I don't know.
After all, there are a lot of
invitations from vendors these days,
If you're sleepy, just go to bed and wait.
No, it's okay.
Have a good day.
Do companies really have
parties every day like that?
I think there are a lot of
invitations from construction
companies because they're
building a new building.
You're a little too meek, ma'am.
Don't say such nonsense.
Oh.
What's this?
I found it the other day
when I cleaned out your room.
I thought you could still wear
it, so I took it to the cleaners.
It's an old sweater.
This is from my school days.
Miki-chan.
I'll give you that if you like.
What? You would like to give it to me?
Yes.
But it's old-fashioned, so you can send it
to your sister back in the country instead.
Hello? It's me.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Director.
The engineer from Hokkaido, Tateno, is here.
Well, just in time.
Would you like to see him right away?
I'm going to go to a meeting with
Yasuda-san to discuss the engineer.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to
go ahead and meet with him.
Yes, sir.
Brother.
How would you introduce me to everyone?
Right.
Can I just say you're my sister?
Good.
- So then, it's not weird for me to call you big brother.
- Right.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yasuo Tateno.
You…
You're…
I'm new to Tokyo,
and I can't walk around by
myself, so I brought my sister.
This is my sister, Chikako.
Are you really called Tateno?
Yes, I'm Tateno.
Um, are you feeling hot?
No.
But…
There are so many cars in Tokyo.
I can't walk the streets of Tokyo
without you with me, Chika-bo.
Don't worry, I won't leave you.
Do you know this area?
No.
But maybe I've been in
Tokyo more than I thought.
Here.
Thanks.
[INDISTINCT]
Welcome.
Hey.
Since when do the guys from
Toyo Light Metal come to this place?
Well, it's just recently.
But they've been every night for a while now.
They said they were invited by the company.
Um, do you know that showy bastard
who's talking to Madam right now?
That one?
It must be Sawano-san, the sales director.
He has something with Midori-chan.
That's Yoko-san's husband.
- What? Really?
- Yeah.
No, Fujikawa-kun, you're the one who
will feel the most pain this time around.
What's that?
Yeah, I've commissioned
the design to someone else.
I'm very sorry about that.
You mean that Tateno guy
who won the competition.
Actually, we're looking forward
to seeing what it's going to be like.
But, Director.
I'm a little worried.
Are you sure about entrusting
this much work to such a young man?
You always say the same thing, don't you?
Anyway, does he know about this place?
He's late.
He doesn't know Tokyo, so I gave
some directions to the girl that's with him.
That's a bit unreliable.
Why don't you at least make a phone call?
Do you know the hotel he's staying?
Some kind of hotel in Nippori.
Then I'll make a call.
Thank you for your patience.
Everybody's quiet today.
Midori-chan.
I feel bad for the Director's wife.
I heard something.
I heard that you had a great
love marriage, didn't you, Director?
- Who told you that?
- Oh, my goodness! It's well-known.
I heard a rumor that the wife fell
in love with the Director,
chased him around, and forced him to
marry her even though he didn't want to.
Well.
Am I wrong?
Huh? Wait.
Maybe it was the other way around.
I'm sorry.
Welcome.
Ah, welcome.
Please, come in.
Is something wrong?
What?
It's nothing.
You were very late.
Everyone's been waiting for you.
Go ahead.
Well, gentlemen, I'd like
to introduce him to you.
This is Yasuo Tateno-kun.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tateno.
And this is Yasuda, general
manager of Uchiyama Construction.
Sakurai-san.
Fujikawa-san, the designer.
I'm Fujikawa.
Please sit down.
No need to be shy. They're all very friendly.
- Excuse me.
- Please.
Excuse me.
I'm Chikako.
Pleased to meet you.
Excuse me. I completely forgot.
Come on, sit down.
Ah, there you go.
Oh, my! Sugano-san!
Sugano-san!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Sugano-san.
And you are? My name is Tateno.
What?
Tateno?
Sugano?
I even mistook you for someone named Sugano.
Well, it's rare to find someone
who looks so much alike.
Right?
What? Yeah.
Hey, just keep bringing the beers.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, where is your hometown, Mr. Tateno?
It's Hokkaido, Japan.
Which part of Hokkaido is it?
Hokkaido's…
Actually, I kind of forgot.
Brother.
Your head hurts, doesn't it?
Don't try to remember.
Are you ill or something?
No, it's not like that.
Excuse me.
Call the cab!
- Aya-chan! Call a cab!
- Come on!
Are you okay?
When I say this in front of
my brother, he gets mad at me.
I want you to understand.
My brother has amnesia.
Amnesia?
He was drowned in a river, and he was rescued,
but he doesn't remember anything before that.
So don't remind him too much of his past.
He's in so much pain.
- They're here for you.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Are you okay?
- Hold on. Are you okay?
- Let's go.
Are you okay?
Be careful. Are you okay, Sugano-san?
Goodbye!
Sugano… Sugano, huh?
I said I'd give it to you, but
I didn't tell you to wear it.
I told you to give it to your sister.
But I was just trying it on for a bit.
I don't want you to wear it,
even for a little bit.
I don't want you to wear it in front of me.
Don't you get it?
Yes.
Yoko-san, a moment.
Don't scold your maid for trivial matters.
You're not used to a maid, so you wouldn't
understand, but we're short on them right now.
I understand.
What happened to Shinsuke?
He said he was having a banquet at work.
Ah, I see.
Yoko-san, do you believe that he has a banquet?
When we were young,
they used to say it was the wife's
fault if her husband came home late.
And even tonight…
He's early…
Yoko, look.
How's that? It won the first prize.
Yoko, do you get it?
I don't know, but I think it's wonderful.
What's so great about it?
It's such a bizarre building.
I guess you know a lot more about architecture.
All right.
I'll take you to see the guy named
Tateno who drew this next time.
What?
Why would you do that?
That's right.
I'm inviting him home this Sunday.
I'll show you the genius' face once.
He's from Hokkaido.
So, your real name is Sugano.
No, it's not.
I've never heard that name before.
But the name Tateno was chosen by a doctor.
The doctor when he saved you from the river.
Sugano…
I don't know it at all.
My head…
Sorry, I shouldn't have
made you try to remember.
Your head hurts sometimes
more than it used to these days.
Oh, Yoko.
Hey…
What is it?
There's something I need to tell you.
What on earth are you talking about?
Actually…
Calm down and listen to me.
You're overreacting, Brother.
It's about the man who's invited today…
Tateno-san, the architect?
I'm off to the main house to say hello.
Yeah.
The thing is…
What's wrong?
He's Sugano-kun.
What?
Mitsuharu Sugano.
Yoko!
Steady!
Well, that's very kind of you.
I'm not sure if it will suit your palate.
I know Yoko is always so clumsy.
No, she works quite well.
She can't compete with a young
lady who grew up in our society.
It's because everyone is so mild-mannered.
I'm worried about what would happen
if you guys suddenly met each other.
I thought I should let you
know as soon as possible.
Mitsuharu-san.
He's alive?
Sawano-san is a terrible person.
I can't believe he knew that and went
to the trouble of inviting him to his house.
What is Mitsuharu-san thinking…
Sugano-san has lost his memory.
Memory?
He forgot about you too, of course.
Or maybe he'll remember
the old days when he sees you.
Oh.
Thank you for inviting me today.
Please come on in.
I think it's about time.
Ah, yes.
Please.
Yoko!
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Yoko-san?
Are you sick?
No, I'm not.
It must be Tateno-kun.
Yoko-san.
Welcome him at the door.
Good afternoon.
Um, I'm here on behalf of my brother.
Oh, it's you.
What happened to Tateno-kun?
Uh…
I'm terribly sorry, but he had a
sudden headache since this morning.
He couldn't come here.
So he told me to say hello
to the Director and everyone.
Does his head hurt that bad?
It's terrible.
I feel so sorry for him,
I can't even look at him.
Really?
Um, I'm worried about him, so I'm leaving.
Goodbye!
Oh dear, I even changed my clothes.
Yoko-san, please help me.
Yes.
He's certainly a troublemaker.
Especially since you took
the trouble to invite him.
You told Yoko.
What?
About Tateno-kun, I mean.
Mitsuharu Sugano.
I'm sorry.
I was going to test her feelings.
If she still can't forget him,
I'd be worried as her husband.
I'm very sorry.
Niimura-kun!
Why didn't you tell me?
That Tateno is Sugano!
Um…
If you're like that, there are
going to be problems.
I'm sorry.
Can you remember?
I'm a friend of yours from school.
Her name is Toki-san.
Toki-san.
She's the one who was there for you
and used to take care of your injuries.
I don't know.
I've never seen any of you…
It's okay.
I'll get some fresh air in.
Anyway, let's have a doctor
take a look at you once.
Oh, welcome back.
Who are you?
Ah, she's a friend of Tateno-san.
Okay.
Finally, someone to take care of you.
Chika-bo.
Don't say that.
They went out of their way to pay me a visit.
I know, I know.
(BABBLES): I can take care of him too.
I can't say for sure until I examine him,
but he probably has a hematoma in his brain.
Hematoma?
Yes.
He has a chronic subdural hematoma due
to injuries sustained when he fell off a cliff.
So he could have a bag of blood, and the
pressure of the bag could be causing amnesia.
If that's the case, it can be cured by surgery.
That surgery is hard, isn't it?
Of course, it's hard, because
you're opening up the brain.
You're going to open the brain?
Yes.
But it's even more dangerous
to leave it as it is now.
I think you need to get
checked out as soon as possible.
Where is she?
She said she wanted to visit a friend.
Her friend?
What friend?
I don't know.
You should at least ask where she's going.
I'm going out.
Where are you going?
I can go anywhere I want.
This is the room.
Who are you?
Yes?
Mitsuharu-san.
Mitsuharu?
Who is that?
My name is Yasuo Tateno.
Some people call me by different
names, but…I don't remember any of them.
I don't even know anyone named Mitsuharu.
Who are you and what do you want?
I am…
I'm Sawano's wife.
I came to visit you.
Yoko-san.
Who are you?
Take it to your brother.
Yeah.
Toki-san… Maybe I shouldn't have come…
Thank you for coming.
So he couldn't recognize you either.
How ill is he?
It's very bad.
If we leave it alone as it is
now, his nerves will be damaged…
Yoko-san.
What if you took him?
To somewhere memorable.
Maybe then he'll remember a few things.
I hate noisy places like this.
What's this room?
Toki-san has been using
this room for a long time.
She just vacated her room yesterday.
Go ahead.
Tateno-san.
What is this room…?
This is the room Mitsuharu-san used to live in.
It's a sketch.
Yes, it's a sketch.
You're…
Do you remember?
Who are you?
I'm Yoko.
Yoko-san.
Please remember.
I'm Yoko.
You've uttered this name many times.
I also called you Mitsuharu-san.
Mitsuharu-san, it's me, Yoko.
I was your fiancee.
Fiancee?
Yes, I was your fiancee.
I was your lover.
I see.
Did you understand?
Please remember me!
I'm… I'm Yoko.
Or maybe it was really so.
Maybe I had a girlfriend too.
Maybe it was you.
It's true.
It's true!
Please stop it already!
I can't even remember my girlfriend.
No matter how many
times you say that…I can't…
I want to believe you, but I can't.
Please don't cry so much.
I think I know how you feel.
But!
Because I can't remember you,
I'm in more pain.
No one can understand this suffering.
Can't you understand?
I didn't want to lie to you.
I'm asking you why you went there.
I went to visit him because of his illness.
Fine.
I'll be quiet just for today.
But I will never allow you to see Sugano again.
But he's sick.
What's wrong with visiting a sick person?
That's enough!
You're my wife.
If my own wife goes to see her old lover, you
want me, the husband, to pretend I don't know?
I'm not that forgiving!
Ma'am, there's a call for you
from someone named Fujikawa-san.
He's been in a bad way since you left.
He's just been admitted to the hospital.
He's sleeping from an injection right now.
I hate to break it to you,
but he shouldn't have strained so much
trying to regain his memory during the day.
Hello?
They're going to operate
on him in a couple of days.
The doctor says there's nothing to worry about.
I'm going to the hospital right now.
No, even if you come
now, Sugano is just sleeping.
You're in a difficult position with Sawano-san.
I'll get back to you when
the surgery date is set.
Please don't worry too much and wait.
Is it about Sugano?
Okay, you can go visit him if you want.
I've said all I have to say.
JUNE 17: SURGERY APPOINTMENT
MITSUHARU SUGANO, AGE 26, SUBARACHNOID HEMATOMA
Brother.
They said the surgery is easy.
It doesn't hurt at all.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm so relieved, Brother.
Everything is going to be back to normal.
It's wonderful.
Everything, huh?
That's right!
Sorry everyone, but can you
give me a moment alone with Toki-san?
Okay, let's go.
Me too?
I'm sorry.
Chika-bo.
I'm here for Yasuo Tateno-san
who's here for surgery.
Doctor!
I was worried about the surgery.
Thank you.
Sugano is happy that so many
people are concerned about him.
Toki-san.
I can't stand such anxious feelings anymore.
But…
I don't know what it means
to get my memory back…
It's okay.
You don't have to think about that now.
Right?
That Yoko-san…
She said she was my fiancee.
And you were my friend.
Mitsuharu-san.
Mitsuharu Sugano.
I wonder what I used to think about Yoko-san…
I'm worried that my regaining my
memory will make her unhappy…
And Toki-san.
I don't know what I thought about you.
That's…
Even if I could go back to Mitsuharu
Sugano… I doubt anyone would be happy.
It's almost time for the surgery.
Yoko.
I knew it!
You're here too?
How's it going?
Everything is good.
Good work.
Okay.
You! Why did you sneak out to come here?
Why did you do such a crazy thing!
If you don't act more
carefully, you're in big trouble.
You are Shinsuke Sawano's wife.
Yoko!
I'm getting a lot of grief from
Sawano-san about Sugano right now.
You should understand my position a little.
No, for your sake, you'd
better go home quickly.
Mitsuharu-san is in the middle of surgery!
I know.
I hear there is nothing to worry about.
The results of the surgery--
Brother!
Why, Brother!
I know my position.
But Brother, is it wrong for me to
worry about Mitsuharu-san's illness?
Niimura-san.
Why don't you let Yoko-san stay?
But this is not your problem.
Maybe you're right.
But even you have no right to
meddle in Yoko-san's love affairs.
I, as the older brother--
Niimura-san.
We're all here because we're
all concerned about Sugano-kun.
I wouldn't want anyone else to be here.
I agree.
Even Yoko-san is not a child.
I think she came here after
giving it a lot of thought.
Right?
If you worry more, she'll misunderstand
you, even if you're her brother.
Don't worry about it.
You must be busy with at the company.
Yoko-san.
I'm worried about you in a
different way than your brother.
I'm sure you've given this a lot
of thought before you came here.
I can't think about anything right now.
All I can think about is
Mitsuharu-san's recovery.
I see.
All I want is for Mitsuharu-san
to remember the old days.
That's all I think about.
If only he could remember the old days…
I…
Give me the electrocautery.
The drill.
Speed up the blood transfusions.
Yes.
How's his blood pressure?
It's a little lower.
The cannula.
Wipe my sweat.
Ah, how was it?
How did the surgery go?
They're not done yet, but he's okay now.
They are just about to give him his
last skin protection and transfusion.
Hey.
Why are you leaving?
It would be better if I wasn't here.
Why?
I don't know what to say.
Your brother will be as good as ever, right?
Mm-hmm.
So…
I think your brother would be
confused with me being around.
Why?
I don't understand.
I'm not sure how to say it.
I mean, I think your brother
would find me annoying.
Really?
Got it?
Yeah, a little bit.
You don't need to get it.
Okay then.
See you soon.
Hey!
You're a good person.
Thank you.
Chika-bo!
Next time, I'll look for
your grandpa with you.
Yeah.
Goodbye.
Goodbye!
The hematoma has been completely removed.
There is no need to worry anymore.
And how about his memory?
Yeah, if it's caused by a hematoma,
I think his memory will return.
So it might not come back in some cases?
It's hard to say, but if it's due to other
causes, for example, psychological shock.
Anyway, we won't know
until he regains consciousness.
I'm worried about something.
What is it?
You know what?
When my brother remembers the old days…
Yeah.
He's going to forget what happened
during the time he didn't remember, right?
Well, I guess so.
So what about me?
Hmmm…
I wonder how that will turn out.
Well, don't worry about it.
I'll find your grandpa.
You all say the same thing.
You have no idea how I feel.
If my brother forgets, I'm on my own.
Yoko-san…
Yoko.
THE END