Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
AT THE SIDE OF THE BRIDGE (Episode 4 Final)
Please enter from entrance
Oh It's been a long time, young madam
Your father in law worried about you until the day he died.
I see
Yoko
Sorry for being late
Sorry for interrupting so suddenly.
What the hell you are saying?
You are the wife of the family here.
Our dad has passed way.
Why you didn't telegram us
I was sorry.
I was on the trip
With whom and where did you go?
I'll talk you about it later
You're my wife,Ok?
Be a nice wife for me tonight
We are ashamed of you.
Our boss and others are here
Oh wife
Nice to see you
Please burn incense.
Your dad worried about you and Shinsuke all the way
You lost nice person
We have our father's will?
I don't know about it
I got it from him before he die
All family members are here tonight.
And Our boss will be the testimony. so I will read out
Ok go ahead
Why didn't he tell us about it?
People will be happy to go to heaven without thinking about it.
But I worry something if I die
I was under failure in my business in Kyushu.
I have no money
No money?
What the hell?
He asked me about the business issue
He kept secret to you about that.
And he tried to get it better
I didn't know he had no money
That's true.
This house is related about that
This house is mortgaged.
No way!
His Kyushu mountain project failed due to flooding.
He died early because his business failed.
I feel sorry about you and your wife
Don't cry, mom
Our dad was so stupid.
Why he invested in mountain project?
He should have asked me about it
And there is another will for you
You are selfish and naive.
That's him
Good luck changing your mind for my mother.
You should divorce with Yoko, and step in new life
He has nothing to do with us
Tashiro,The will should not be binding.
Yes, that's true
I'm for what he thought, Sawano
You fix the problems in your home and move on with your new life.
We have no problem.
Nothing will be problem if Yoko get back home
I think you are in a very difficult situation.
Mind your own business
don't be angry with him
You should apologize to him.
he is the president of your company
Hold on,Shinsuke
Oh my god
It was fate that Yoko was unhappy
Yoko and Mitsuharu's romance began when they were students.
But they parted very unhappy in Hokkaido.
Mitsuharu was missing
she couldn't live without him
Later she married Shinsuke Sawano.
It was a very gorgeous wedding, but she felt very sad.
But Mitsuharu is alive
He lived with Chikako in a farmhouse in Ishikari.
Then they ended up meeting
she was already married.
For her it was very sad.
Shinsuke and his mother-in-law doubted their relationship.
Yoko couldn't trust him and decided to divorce him.
He was asked by Nimura to go to Cambodia for work
The day before his departure they went to Memories Park
Mitsuharu returned to Japan after a year
He went to see her on the Noto Peninsula
she was happy to meet him.
But her father died, so she had to return to the Sawano family again.
End of Episode 1&2&3 Summary
Sis
Welcome back
you weren't alone and lonely?
Come on!
What's wrong?
Mitsuharu is here.
Really?
I'm back.
Yoko has come back
Welcome
Chikako told me that you were coming to house today.
I was planning to go home soon, but I was busy with various things
Chikako was worried that you wouldn't come back.
I worried about you
I'm going out
Where?
I don't wanna disturb you
i will buy your food.
See you
Were you OK?
You had a hard time
It doesn't work very well.
For what?
I tried to settle the divorce issue with Mr. Sawano once.
But It does not work
please tell me more about it
Hey you
You're Chikako,right?
Yes  I am.
What can I do for you?
I know Yoko has back home
I have no idea
Don't pretend you don't know
I know she is at home
Excuse me
Hold on
Get hands off of me
will you kidnap me?
Sis
i wanted to talk to you but why is he here?
Don't get me wrong
Come with me!
Let's keep calm and talk together
I understand very well that you are angry.
I was rumored to have died in an accident just before I got married to Yoko.
This was really a disaster for me
I tried to forget Yoko for two years.
I had a very hard time.
I don't think your marriage with Yoko is happy.
no one is bad.
everything was weird from the beginning
It's already been over a year since you guys separated.
Yoko is no longer your wife, I think
Your blaming her will do no good.
I know I have no right to tell you this
will you divorce her?
Is that all what you wanna say?
i want to explain to you
you are her cheating partner.
You used to be in jail for adultery
I won't divorce her.
Mind your own business
If you say such things, I will fight you all to the end.
notice.
At the request of SAWANO SHINSUKE, 1-chome, Ichiban-cho, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo
You had an affair with my wife and destroyed my marriage.
I have suffered mental persecution from you, and I am claiming 5 million yen in compensation from you.
If you don't pay the ransom, I will take legal action.
He is so selfish
He sent this to you and he's so angry
If Yoko is free, I am willing to pay him alimony.
But 5 million yen is too high
Does she know about this?
He also sent Yoko this same copy.
She told me to meet him once
Excuse me
It's been a whole
Yoko
I never thought my child would betray me
Relatives are very cold to me. When the money runs out, everyone goes away
Shinsuke has left me too
I'm alone and lonely
I know how you feel
Thank you for coming
i know what you are good at now
Will you live here with me from today onwards?
I don't mean that
you came here because you were worried about me?
I'm here to talk to Shinsuke
To shinsuke?
What for?
He is claiming compensation from Mr. Sugano for me.
He is claiming compensation?
he didn't tell me about it
How much?
It's not your business
tell me everything
How much?
If you were a lawyer, you would have checked to see if there was any effort on his part to pay me the $5 million.
I have no problem going to trial.
If you want to go to trial, I don't need to be here.
Why you've come here?
i think money solves everything
What do you mean?
I think you can reduce the price by 5 million yen.
Do you think the alimony should be reduced?
Kind of
If I pay the money, can Yoko get a divorce?
You can put that in the condition too
Hold on
We need to talk more
money is no good for anyone
I don't mean that
don't make excuses.
i will give you this room
are you guys quarreling?
What can I do for you?
I'm here for that alimony.
he wants to negotiate
How much?
If you go to court, you can only get about 500,000 yen at most.
he knows that too
So How much?
How about 1 million?
1 million?
I think that's fair
you can ask him for alimony many times
It's too cheap
Here's the 1 million yen
I thought it would be better to pay early
are you going to Hokkaido soon?
I borrowed this money in the form of an advance payment for work.
Don't be sad
If I deliver this money tomorrow, you will be free.
But I worry
Does it work well?
If you are worried, you can ask someone to be present.
You're lawyer...
kanzaki?
I think he can help you
It would be great if he helps me
Yoko
Please come to Hokkaido when the divorce issue is resolved.
We can start new life
I drunk too much last night
Did you celebrate Tokyo giants won?
you say nice things to me
Everyone knows you are big fan of Giants
Are you sure?
This is the invoice
Please submit the money
Let me check
Hold on
Where is Sawano's divorce papers?
I'll give it to you later
I won't give you this money until you give it to us.
Do you still want to go to court?
It's not what you promised us
If you go to court, you can settle it for less than 1 million yen
3,400000yen at most
i have heard a lot of rumors about you
The trial won't go well like last time.
That was nice
To be honest,he needs money too
I'll see you in a few days
i was thinking too easily
Kanzaki-san is by my side, so I think things will go well this time.
Thank you in advance
Don't worry
See you guys in Hokkaido
Don't worry.
See you
Have a safe trip
Long time no see
How are you?
Thanks
Does it look good on me?
From now on, I should pay for summer clothes in cash.
Thank you for doing business with us for a long time but...
Why you have come here?
Because I don't have cash
he said he would come to my house but
I heard that you will pay this money.
It costs 180000 yen
How do you know I have that money?
I heard from Tashiro that you have money.
1 million yen
Shinsuke will take the money later
I can't pay this, sorry
You decline?
Ok
I have no money so please call the police
Will they bring the alimony tomorrow?
they declined it
I want them to suffer mentally
For about 1 million yen, they...
But her mother-in-law received it
Eh? really?
She received 200,000 yen as a deposit from Yoko.
What's wrong about money, Mom
You are very bad for taking money from Yoko.
How did you know about Palimony?
A god tell me
Oh welcome
You are really great for making up your mind!
I thought that would be better
when will they bring the money?
they bring around noon
Then I'll wait here
Please sign this form before they arrive.
this is divorce papers
These are the terms of our deal with them.
No way
Clam down.
I did not want to go to trial.
I thought a settlement would make more money
you were going to trick me from the beginning
If you don't like it, change lawyers.
But No one want to handle this work
my father took care of you
What the hell you are talking about?
I was just getting paid as a lawyer
I do this kind of work for you.
i can't do this job anymore
Stop it
If I reveal your cheating, you will be charged for alimony.
do you speak it in court?
I'm going to do something with you
To Mitsuharu,
Shinsuke is missing, I'm looking for him
I have no means of doing anything
I haven't seen you in two months.
I should be there
I think he ran away because he hurt Lawyer Tashiro.
he is cautious.
I feel sorry about him
But the matter of divorce with him was postponed
I feel sorry about it
To Yoko.
I have happy news for you
We are likely to find Chikako's grandfather soon.
We visited a farmhouse in Ishikari where we used to live
We found something about him
He currently lives in a fishing village near Hakodate.
We'll go there to see him
how was the train trip?
I came by sleeper so I slept.
How long does it take from here to the fishing village?
About 2 hours
I'm confused
Why?
what should i do if i meet him?
you really don't know what he looks like?
i remember him hugging me
Grandfather lives in such a beautiful place
Is Sugano from Tokyo?
He must be my grand dad
are you my grandfather?
You're the Chikako?
Do you remember what I look?
I'm not your grand father.
He is over there
Oh you are not
You're the Sugano.
I'm Gosuke who lives with Yoshida
After receiving a telegram from you, he suddenly said that he did not want to see his grandson.
He doesn't wanna meet?
I have been arguing with him about that since yesterday.
But never mind
Are you there?
Where has he gone?
why doesn't he want to see me?
he is ashamed that he has no money.
he has a difficult personality
I'll check it out
Don't think too much
I think he will be relieved when he sees you
You're my granddad?
I remembered how you looked
Do you remember what I look?
she is your grandson
She is the grandson you were always talking about.
Really?
Chikako
Granddad!
I live in poverty and I'm ashamed
It's very rural here
i always worried about you
let's go to Tokyo with me
I won't leave him and go to Tokyo.
I worry about him
I’ve been taking care of you
I’ve been taking care of you!
don't you want to live with me?
Don't get me wrong
Please discuss that with her later.
He has a very difficult personality and worries about small things.
Don't you think so?
I feel sorry for her, she's all alone.
It can't be helped.
Her grandfather doesn't want to be in Tokyo yet.
I think they will live together after she graduates.
Fujikawa takes care of her, so no worries
let's talk about us
Are you still worried about SAWANO-san?
I don't mean that
Cheer up
We will start a new life in Sapporo from tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Nothing
Let's go
What's wrong?
Are you tired
i go to the building site and be back soon
Let's have party tonight
Was that person driving our car?
Yes
he may have a different name
He must be Noguchi
He is a new employee from Tokyo.
Let me check
Is he?
He is
Yes
he won't come back to the office until night
But he always comes home for lunch
You can see him at his home if you are in hurry
Mr. Noguchi always says that his wife's home cooking is delicious.
His wife?
he's been married for a month
He comes home at noon every day to eat her cooking.
Madam
Has your husband returned yet?
Not yet
You have a guest
See you
You think he got another new woman
Don't get me wrong
But I'm serious
I understood his situation and get together with him.
He promised to divorce his wife and marry me.
You don't seem to believe me
No way.
I have suffered a lot over the last two years about my divorce.
it's hard to believe your story
As you know, he caused an incident in Tokyo.
That's why he couldn't contact you
But the lawyer didn't sue, so there was no case.
He doesn't worry about going to jail
It would have been better if you had let us know that earlier.
i can't believe he changed
I’m afraid he is cheating on you
Please don't speak ill of him.
He's back.
You'll know if I am cheated or not
Yoko
I'm sorry
i suddenly have a headache
Are you Ok,Yoko?
Yoko!
What does doctor say?
he says she's fine
her headache is better.
She will feel better if she sleeps
If the same symptoms appear, she needs a thorough examination at a large hospital.
i was relieved to hear that
This
What's this?
This is Yoko and I's divorce papers
Please give this to Yoko
I left Tokyo and now live in Sapporo.
I found out how I am stupid
I only love the woman called Tokiko
I'll be here for a while
I see
I hear you work in Sapporo
If possible, I don't want to see you very much
Please look after Yoko
I was surprised
We finally get married
Don't cry
i feel dreamy
I can't see anything,Mitsuharu
Because you are crying
No
I can't see your face
Flowers..and Neon..
I can't see anything,
Yoko!
Don't worry
Toki..when did you come?
Since 1 week ago
I decided to work in Tokyo again
she has a brain tumor
I was surprised to hear that from Mr. Fujikawa.
But since it was discovered so quickly, I don't think she has anything to worry about.
Toki,he has had brain surgery
I forgot it
She'll be  fine
Don't worry
you always worry us
Who are Yoko Sawano's relatives?
Please come with me
Please come in
her surgery went well
I think her headaches and numbness in her limbs will go away.
I see
but it is temporary
her tumor was getting worse
I couldn't get rid of them all
does that mean it's too late?
You might be right
she will be fine once
but i don't think she will live long
Yoko
If the tumor adheres to the surface of the brain, it is easy to remove.
In that case, the tumor is completely cured.
But her tumor is inside her brain, so surgery is not possible.
what will happen to her?
her tumor is getting bigger
Like a cancer
I feel sorry about her
But now she has no choice but to think this
She will live a normal life once her surgical scars heal.
Please spend time with her happily until she dies.
About how long?
maybe 1 year
A year and a half later, I think she will have symptoms again.
I can't say for sure what will happen
I think she will live in about a year and a half to two years.
2 years
let us get married
I don't care if you don't live long
Even if you die tomorrow, I still want to marry you
So get better soon
I'm like in a dream
I gave up on getting married at that time
Really?
When I was told that I would have surgery at the hospital as soon as I returned from Hokkaido by plane.
That bring me back my memory
Mitsuharu
Please be honest
will i die from a failed surgery?
Cut out your tumor and you'll be fine
Can I trust you?
i want you to be honest
Don't worry about that
Honeymoon trip to Ise-Shima for 3 nights and 4 days
you looked really happy
I cried in my heart to see your smile
i think it's too early to give up
Advances in medicine may lead to new treatments
Our love will cure your disease
Did you get a reply from the doctor again?
I heard that Meiji Medical University has a radiotherapy specialist.
However, it has not reached the clinical stage yet.
How's Yoko these day
she is fine and has an appetite
I lost my appetite recently
take care of your health
Fujikawa
I feel uneasy even at work
I worry about Yoko
You found me
Please play the piano
I can't play now
you should practice the piano
I hear you are good
My late mother liked classical guitar
Brain tumors are common growths like any other child
a brain tumor grows inside the skull
A malignant brain tumor slowly grows larger, causing the head to swell.
Patient has body numbness headache dizziness nausea
These are discovered by X-ray examination, etc.
tumor must be removed immediately
The tumor is inside the skull so there is no room for it to spread
But as the tumor grows, it destroys the skull.
Welcome back
are you waiting for someone?
I'm on the way of shopping
Welcome back
you guys are good friends and I envy you
her brain tumor is the most malignant of all brain tumors
The Tumors grow very fast
It destroys brain tissue and is nearly impossible to remove.
Most patients with this tumor die
i wanted to take a nap on Sunday
I was asked to make things and take out the trash
I tried to call a carpenter to make
she told me she didn't have the money to pay the carpenter
Men don't understand why pregnancy is so hard
Even when he comes home, he doesn't help me at all.
I really hate it
You're in trouble
my husband is very selfish
i want him to be like your husband
You think too much
Your husband a person who notices small things very much
No way
I am going to leave home and annoy him.
Can I stay at your house for about three days?
But did she leave without staying?
When I prepared dinner, she started to worry about her husband.
She was worried about what was in the refrigerator.
she suddenly decided to go home
That's funny
He also told me that marrying her was a mistake.
But the next day he bought a souvenir for his wife.
At work, my colleagues say they fight once every two days.
What's wrong, Yoko?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry
I feel lonely
Are you?
we have never had a fight
i think we have different personalities
they honestly say anything but we are...
Yoko
I'm sorry
You take care of me too much
I'm too happy
At the hospital where I work, there is a doctor named Tachibana who came back from America last year.
He's doing research to cure brain tumors by something gas
I think it's mustard gas
I talked with Yoko about that
The doctor wanted to visit the hospital with the data
I also called the doctor who was in charge of your operation.
In your wife's case, I don't think the treatment I'm researching will be very effective.
I'm sorry
You should give it try
This treatment is not possible because of the risks involved.
but there is no other way
I think you should take the risk and try treatment.
But it's too risky
We can't do that under the current circumstances.
I see
But in your wife's case she is very presently symptom free.
She currently has no headaches or numbness in her limbs.
she may have hope
Please consult with Dr. Aoki and don't give up until the end.
That's all what I cab say now
Lately, there have been times when I feel like telling Yoko everything honestly.
Why?
I lie to her all day long
I'm frustrated about it
would you tell her she has no life?
I think I should tell her the truth
we live a life of lies
It's sad that Yoko died without knowing the truth.
I know how you feel
I I were her, I trust you
And go to die without knowing the truth.
About the piano that I gave Yoko as a present
I regret that recently
Why?
According to the doctor, it's been a year and a half since the operation, so it's just now.
she starts to go numb in her limbs
If her hands start to go numb
I think she will suffer a lot if she can't play the piano.
her hands can still move
Really?
She can play the piano?
Well, okay then, I was worried.
she won't let me hear her play
I see.
i made you worry
Welcome back
You got wet
You've improved
I practiced the piano a lot
You're great
You make me wetting
I feel cold
she looks at me and smiles
i can't believe she has malignancy
there are no signs that she is progressing
She's fine
Little by little I'm starting to hope
Hope?
Doctors are also misdiagnosed.
The doctor I met the other day said it's too early to give up
There are many cases of terminal cancer miraculously cured.
I hope it make happens to Yoko
Great if so
If she's healthy in the fall, I'll stop believing the doctor's diagnosis.
The fall
Madam
What a lovely!
i made sweets
I want to eat so I'll make you some tea right now
thank you for your hospitality
It is very surprising that she is healthy
But it's too early to be optimistic
You said she'll start having headaches and dizzy symptoms by summer
I didn't mean to tell you the exact time
In her case, I think the tumor is slow to develop.
The anti-cancer drugs used in her treatment may have been very effective.
But there have been cases of brain tumors miraculously recovering.
I can show you
You may be right.
But I'm a doctor, so I don't believe in miracles.
but i want to believe it
I'm sorry I'm excited
Why don't you take a medical examination by Dr. Tezuka of the University of Tokyo?
Do you know of him?
I know his name
He is famous for his brain surgery. i will introduce you next time
I know how you worry
I can't say that my diagnosis is correct.
my mom who died loved this
What disease did she die of?
Cancer
It was hard time
she didn't know about her illness
i cared too much for her.
I remember it every time I make sweets
I think she may have known about her illness
Excuse me for talking about this during dinner.
Please eat
I'm home
Yoko?
i got surprised
You are childish
were you surprised?
Yes I was
i bought this for you
Ticket for musical academy
I'm so glad
Good seat
It's been a long time since I went to a concert
In return, Yoko?
Let's go to the hospital together before going to the concert
Why?
Let's do a thorough examination once a year as the doctor said
I see
It's just in the case
OK I get it
But I worry
you're fine so don't worry
Take care
I was relieved that you were fine
From the beginning you told me not to worry
Yes but
You are right but
to be honest i was worried
For what?
About Detailed examination
I was worried that you had some bad disease
Is that so?
I can't say that in front of you
I was really happy when Dr. Tezuka didn't worry about us.
today is such a wonderful day!
Let's take a break from work, eat, and go to a concert.
how is her sick?
She went to Dr. Tezuka's for a thorough examination.
So?
it was the same as my diagnosis
So her brain tumor is getting worse
After consulting with Dr.Tetsuka, I decided not to tell the truth.
I also worried about my husband Sugano
i lied to them
I see.
how was he?
He was so glad
Does he find it difficult for him to make a facial expression in front of his wife.but He was so glad
How long can Yoko live?
Until next spring when the cherry blossoms are beautiful
cherry blossoms season...
Let's have a wedding anniversary party together next spring
we should thank our friends
It must be cherry blossom season
Later
Spring's come
Dr.
It's been a age
Are you coming too?
I've been invited
The cherry blossoms have bloomed
Please come in
Welcome!
Please make yourself at home
Welcome
where is she?
What is she doing?
Hey,Yoko
Yoko?
What's wrong?
she is dressing up
She needs my help?
I'm going
you look very difficult
Sorry to have kept you wait
You are very beautiful
Welcome
I'm sorry for being so rude
Thanks to you she became very well
That's good for you
You became very well too
i want to hear you play the piano
I can't
Please play the piano
Please
Oh my god
I wonder if I can play well.
My fingers are not feeling well these days.
she is so beautiful,right?
Look at her fingers
i can't believe she is seriously ill
I think there's something in her body that's stopping the disease from progressing.
I can't say anything
If so, it's a miracle
it's a miracle
that's the power of their love
Even doctors don't know
Sugano
Phone call from your wife
Thanks
Hi,it's me
Mitsuharu..I am..
You sounds bad
i have a headache
and my one hand is numb
Are you OK?
What's wrong?
Mitsuharu.
Yoko!
I wanna see Dr.Oki
he is in surgery
Dr.Oki see her health
Which room?
No.8
That room is currently occupied by another patient.
No. we transferred him
prepare for blood transfusion
breathing is weak
Give me Mitakan
how is her blood pressure
It doesn't go up
Add to Karinigen
When her father wanted to build her grave here, I objected.
I wanted to build her grave in Tokyo.
But I'm glad they made it here
this is a very good place for her
Actually, that was Yoko's intention.
Really?
she wanted to build her grave here
when did she say that?
this might not be telling you
she visited me before you got married
The two of us came here to visit a grave
She said she wanted to enter this tomb when she died.
i told her i will die before you
we laughed together
That night I woke up in the middle of the night
Yoko was not at home
i couldn't understand anything
I think she knew she wouldn't live long
she was very kind to me
she looks different
It's hard to feel the reality of someone's death
i think she is still alive
I still can't believe
I understand
How did she know she couldn't live long
She knew it?
Yes. she knew..I don't know since when
Welcome back
I'm home
It's hot,right?
You are sweating
Bath is ready?
Yes, it's ready
It seems that Mr. Fujikawa had another fight with his wife.
Again?
But he said their kids will support her so I can't win
i bought a goldfish
So cute
The goldfish I bought last year died.
Good evening.
You went home, but you didn't answer, so I was stumped.
This dress was delivered by cleaning
I paid for your newspaper out of the money you gave me.
Thanks
Not at all
You have a hard time
I have been wondering about something for a while now.
I was here last year chatting with your wife.
I told her about my mother dying of cancer
I was surprised that your wife died
I regret ever telling her about it.
Your wife didn't mind, but I feel very bad for her.
i shouldn't have said that
I'm really sorry
Don't worry.
she died without knowing anything
I feel a little better
i wanted to tell you about this
Excuse me
Madam
when was it last year?
In autumn
I came here to bring sweets in September
I see
i got surprised
You are childish
were you surprised?
She read this
she read this before i came home
I put this book on the bottom.
I never put this book at the top
She put this book on the top
Yoko
You knew that
You knew that when you went to the spring party and the concert.
Why you didn't tell me?
i wanted to tell you the truth
I thought I'd tell you everything until the day you died
i really wanted to tell you everything
I had a hard time.
You had a hard time too
Why you didn't tell me?
we wanted to suffer together
it makes us happy
You thought I would be satisfied if you died knowing nothing?
I think it's too selfish
What should I do?
I can't take it back
Yoko
What's wrong?
You has gone from my home
Please stay strong
You were just dreaming
I don't care if it's a dream
She came to see me once again.
THE END