Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Asa no Hamon / A Ripple in a Morning (1952)
Bank of America, N.T. & S.A. , Tokyo, Japan
Yes, the letter of credit
distinctly mentions porcelain dinner sets.
Even so, porcelain dinner sets could be toys.
If it had been specified as general merchandise
there would have been no difficulty.
That's where I want you to give
the meaning leeway in the interpretation.
If the bank accepts the meaning, it can be done.
As far as the merchandise is concerned,
we have every confidence
that we can do much better than any other firm.
Sanko Trading Co.,LTD
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Was it really no good?
He said ok
Oh, thank you for your hard work.
It took a while for him to approve it
But I made it
Finally, it's a great success!
It's great to have this deal
Satomi?
In the end, it's all about the trust in the reference books
Wow, it's all about Tokimoto-kun's skills
No matter how many times I went,
He didn't approve.
There
Well then, preparations this.
I'm going to Towa Bank
Car.
The car is parked.
Kitatomi
I need to get the trade bill discounted
You'll be in New York next week.
so please take care of things while I'm away
Is Takimoto-kun going too? To America?
No way.
Kimura-kun, can you take care of this sample?
Yes.
Are you going home already?
I wish I could be let go during the day sometimes,
I'd like you to send a telegram.
To the Jefferson Company in San Francisco
OK
Do you think Kaji can make a deal with?
Of course,
I'd like to get it done before breakfast
Kaji works hard?
Ako-chan,you are better than him
Oh....
I'm a ghost!
Whoa, whoa! W-Whoa! Whoa!
Hey, say something.
It's very rude to say nothing.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
What's the hell?
What do you mean?
Ah! This is strange!
Kenji! Come out!
Is it okay now?
Kenji!
Yes!
Oh, big sister,
Welcome back.
As expected, you didn't bark
What prank?
It's not a prank
We're serious, you know
See, Peke hasn't been barking at all
So we are having Ino-san scare
huh, Ino?
Ino?
My best friend, Ino
I was also playing a part for Peke,
you know, Peke
I apologize for the inconvenience
Well then, I'm heading home, Ken-chan
Oh, that's mine, just leave it as is
Oh, right. I'll go get my stuff
I'll take it.
Peke.
Don't get angry
Wang!
That's not good
Come on.
oh mom
Welcome back
Welcome back, Aunt
Oh, what a nice dog!
What's its name?
Nana-chan
Nana-chan?
Both of them are yours?
Yeah,
Peke is my dog
Right?
Yours?
Let's take a walk
Who's he?
He's Ken-chan's best friend
Well, it seems like he really loves children.
Hey, Ken-chan?
What?
Is that person your sister?
No, she's not.
She is my relative.
What about your dad?
He died in battle
In the Philippines
Where is your mom
She's in Hakone
She's working as an office clerk at a hotel
Office clerk?
That's why I'm living as a freeloader
You know, Peke?
Peke!
Peke
Hey, catch the ball!
Once again
Just now, Shiro-san stopped by
Wow, that's unusual. What's wrong?
It's about your marriage proposal,
but no, I'm not thinking about marriage at all
It sounds like a nice offer,
so maybe you should meet him
But I'm sorry, I don't want to compromise my life by
getting married just because of an arranged marriage
I have to decline.
You still can't forget about Fujiwara-san,
who has disappeared, right?
No, that's not it
Sure, at first I might have tried to forget by immersing myself in work,
but now work is my whole life, you know
After all, women should be feminine
I intend to be feminine, you know?
Is that so?
I’m really thinking more seriously about my life
Oh? That sounds like something my father back.
Well then, I’ll leave it to you
Yes, I stopped by the art club
for the first time in a while
because there was an exhibition by Akae
Well, is that so?
The Iwayama bookstore visited here
So, this person
He visited about book royalties.
I see.
I bought that
What a wonderful flower
Oh? Ken-chan!
Ken-chan!
What happened?
Oh, Peke did it again!
Ken-chan!
Yes!
What?
You have to keep Peke
on a leash properly!
He is always crying
He makes such a pitiful sound
I really don't want to hear complaints from the neighbors anymore
One dog is enough
I don't think we need a stray dog.
Ken-chan, come on
Ken-chan?
Mom
Ken-chan takes care of him well
But...
Well, I'll be asking
Ken-chan, shall I go with you?
Have a dinner.
Peke!
Oh, isn't this Ino-san's?
Ako Takimoto
Hello?
I'm sorry for the other day
Not at all.
Thank you for returning the book
I received the book from Ken-chan
Where do you work?
I'm working at the trading company
Trade?
It's Fuji Trading Company
I hear you are Reference Trading Company
I hear your English is very good
Did Ken-chan say that?
I'm not good at it, you know
I'm really no good
Come on
I really don't have that talent
I do read it,
but I can't speak it
I'm not the type of person to work for a trading company.
Why is the sky so beautiful?
I saw the same sky in Myanmar
In Myanmar?
This design's not so good. Mm-hmm.
This is our best number. How do you like it?
- I think that's just what you wanted?
- Yes
But the price is too high.
Mr. James, don't forget it's exceptional quality.
You made it
You're very busy while the president is away.
Why?
It seems that Satori-san has quite
a bit of resentment towards you
In other words, your skills is too good
He is jealous of you
You're a secretary and you do a great job.
No matter what is said to me,
It's fine
I'm doing for our company.
No, that's not
This is a reference shoji
You have a visitor
Who?
Mr.Inoda
Oh, were you surprised?
No, not really
but is something the matter?
Well, by chance,I got two tickets for the Menuhin concert
Menuhin concert?
This is the ticket for tonight,
but can you make it?
Oh, I'm just a bit busy right now,
but I'll take care of it right away
Well then, I'll be waiting outside
So, is your name Ako?
No, it's not Ako, it's Atsuko
You are not Ino, but Inoda, aren't you?
Oh, You won't go home?
My buyer and I have an appointment at 6 o'clock.
Mr.Thomas
Oh, then I'll go ahead,
Ako-chan
Who is that person?
He's Ken-chan's best friend who is at our place. Goodbye
Goodbye
Thank you for waiting
They say it will start exactly at 6 o'clock,
so let's pick up the car
If we hurry and send the food to the community hall...
Takimoto-kun! Phone!
Is it a call? Ohashi?
The president is calling you
To Hakone
just say I've already returned
I refuse to engage in any business related to play.
I'll just go and decline, sorry Just a moment,
I'll be right there.
all the paperwork
related to that document?
yes, I understand
I'm really sorry
I made you waste
a hard-to-get ticket
It's ok
Well,  invites someone else
I'll give you the ticket as a souvenir.
I'll take this ticket, thank you
It seems like you enjoy working
Yes, I love it, but I'm busy
What about you, Inoda?
Well,I do like working too
But I'm not good at trading.
I want to quit, you know
Are you going to quit?
However, they don't let me quit easily
The mountains of Hakone are the pride of the nation
I'll stop by Ken-chan's mom's place on the way back
That's good.
Ito-kun
Inoda-san
Good morning!
Are you leaving already?
Actually,I shouldn't go out
The paid holiday period ends today
Oh, that's not good
Take care of your health
Thank you
I'm going to the personnel department.
Inoda,You don't need to feel sorry for him
Because of his chest illness
It's not like serious desire.
What's wrong?
Are you going to let me resign again?
Today it's not about me, but about someone else
I can't believe you're taking on even the matter of someone's resignation
You're quite an overbearing man, aren't you?
I don't want people who get sick to quit work.
He goes to work even though he is sick
You should talk to your manager about that,
but I would like to request a special arrangement
Well, speaking of which, I heard you made another mistake.
Sigh, I'm really not good at English
Yes, but that is an important job for us as well
Somehow, please wrap up the conversation well.
You are called Hanpeta(A man who often makes mistakes), aren't you?
Yes
Oh, I see. However, I don't think so
You are not Hanpeita
Anyway, I can't fire you while you're still a Hanpeita
Haha, I'm happy about our love
No, this is not just your problem
I hope that at least streptomycin becomes
more affordable,
Streptomycin...
I never thought I would end up like this when I was in the south
What happened with the work?
I don't think there's any prospect
It's a business worth 150 million yen
Japanese traders are losing their motivation, but it's not easy
Thank you very much
Hello, could you please connect me to the pharmaceutical department?
Oh, is this the pharmaceuticals department?
What was the name of the company that makes Streptomycin again?
Hey? Could you please look up the address for me?
That is Malcolm Company
Ah, so it's really Malcolm, huh?
Is something wrong?
Actually,
When I was working at a bath detention center in Burma,
there was an American young man named Mal
He was suffering from malaria,
so I secretly gave him quinine
That Mr. Maru is called Henry Malcolm
But isn't it a misunderstanding
about Malcolm?
Well, I guess that's true.
There's a visitor.
I think she'll come soon
Welcome
Aunt.
Welcome.
It's been ages.
Thank you for calling me this morning
Not at all.
Are you staying over here?
Yes, Ken-chan is very energetic
I'm sorry for the trouble
Is he studying?
Don't worry,
I'm sorry for the trouble
It must be tough for you too, aunt
I'm getting used to this job
Since last month, I have been in charge of foreign customers.
I hope you'll be with Ken-chan soon
But in Kenji's letter
Apparently he made a friend named Ino
Ino?
Ino really takes good care of Ken-chan
Really?
He's the same age as Kei?
He a real adult
He is a bit of an oddball.
Is he hanging out with adults like that?
but Ken-chan has his good points too, you know?
Is he a friend of Atsuko?
He has nothing to do with our house.
I see.
Atsuko should really consider getting married soon
Oyato is back
I see.
Hold on.
Hi! Isn't that Atsuko-san?
Hello, Mr. Bradford!
Welcome back
Thank you
- How do you do?
- Fine, thank you!
- Have you been playing golf?
- Yes
- How was the game?
- Great!
I'm having a little trouble, Atsuko-san.
It's about business.
Doesn't your firm handle toilet articles, Atsuko-san?
No, Mr. Bradford.
It's for an order of about thirty thousand dollars.
- Thirty thousand dollars?
- Yes!
And if you care to handle it, I'll give it to you.
I went ahead and said okay
That's way too easy.
Those kinds of craftsmen are often from long-established businesses,
and they're truly troublesome
I don't like things that come with so many complaints
Besides, I don't like it when you steal orders;
such despicable acts affect the company's reputation
However, I don't think it's stealing since the other party didn't show up on the contract date
Mr.Bradford is having trouble with that
Is that not good?
I can't agree with that, you know
Moreover, our president is currently absent....
Takimoto-kun
Let's do the job
That job is about 30,000 dollars,
which is roughly 10 million yen
well...It's not about money
It's a business you've taken on without any selfish desires
Kicking that is just harassment towards Ako-chan,
That's not acceptable.
I did it selfishly
You did it selfishly?
Don't say that
Until now, haven't you been the one bringing in all the work by yourself?
I was also reckless
Decorations are difficult, aren't they?
Besides, it's the first time for us,
so isn't it interesting?
It's not like our company can't do it
Let's do the job
I don't mind fighting with Hisatori
Kaji-san, do I seem cheeky?
Am I an unpleasant woman
from a man's perspective?
What's wrong?
Please tell me honestly
I don't think so, but?
But?
Women who are good at their jobs are more likely to be disliked by men
In the end, It's just male jealousy.
I don't like being thought of badly by others.
Ako-chan has that kind of side to her as well?
You should be well thought of by everyone
In other words, the woman is being needy
Kaji, will you go with me?
to Mr.Bradford's office
It's all about business, right?
We'll take care of this job
Will you?
I'll say this for the sake of doing it
It's better to keep business and personal feelings separate
Personal feelings?
Welcome back.
Are you alone?
Thank you very much.
Is something wrong?
Where's Peke?
I keep him at home
because my aunt will get mad.
Huh?Peke Peke Peke?
What's wrong?
Oh here
That's not good,
He pissed.
Peke, that's not good
Where did you bring it?
Nana?
Nana!
that not good
Nana? Nana? A ghost?
Oh Ken-chan
Peke,that's not good.
The location for our school field trip has been decided.
Where?
Hakone
Hakone?
I hope that but actually Nikko.
I see
I found Ino's house. It's huge.
I was surprised
I see
Nana?
Don't let him into the house
Ken-chan, could you guide me
to Ino's place?
Now?
Are we really going?
This is a very big apartment
Inoda Niheita.
Sis
Here's like haunted house.
Hit this
Sis
I'm going to try hitting this
Welcome.
Um, is Mr. Ino.....Inoda there?
Who are you?
We are Takimoto.
Please wait a moment,Sakimoto
Um, this is Takimoto.
Akimoto?
Takimoto.
If my name is hard to understand,
it's 'Kagawa'
Tagawa?
not 'Ta', but 'Ka', 'Ka'. 'Kagawa'...
Ah, there are so many names
that end like that,
and you are here to see Masako?
She went out earlier
I'll just take care of this for a moment,
Please stop messing around.
How about we go check it out?
Well...
It would have been nice to bring Peke along
Big sister.
Please.
Well, it's the first time such a beautiful young lady has come to see him.
Hello Ino,
Kenichi
Oh, it's you!
Hello?
I apologize for sitting down
It's because my maid said you're friend of Masako
Come in
That old lady is an interesting one,
isn't she?
Yeah, that old woman is here from long time ago
Excuse me.
This is awesome.
but that's quite a dirty teacup, isn't it,
Ken-chan?
It's too dirty.
It's a nice teacup, you know
Korean pottery,
huh? Really?
Please, come on in
Well then...
actually, Thanks for the ticket for the other day.
You are called Niheita?
That's right, my late father was 1 heta, and I am 2 heta
In my company, they call me half heita.
It's called Hanpeita
Hanpeita?
It's meaning half a portion
Mr. Inoda specializes in economics, right? Yes,
I'm studying Keynes
I want to quit
trading and study more,
but I just can't seem to stop
Why is that?
I made a terrible mistake
Did you completely outsmart me?
Me?
I messed up our appointment at 10
o'clock on Tuesday
It must have been 10 o'clock on Thursday
I'm terrible at the phone call in English
About Mr.Bradford?
Ino?
What's wrong?
Peke took one of this.
That's not good
Is the culprit you, Peke?
I'm sorry.
Peke-kun is really lonely too, you know
Kenji,right?
I left something.
This is my younger sister, Masako
She's attending art school
Her part-time job is as a sign painter in Asakusa,
You're annoying
This is the talented company president's secretary, Ako Takimoto
Calling me talented is a bit of an exaggeration
I'm taking my shoes.
Excuse me as well
Excuse me
Brother
Isn't it wonderful?
For Hanpeita,
this is quite an achievement
You were planning to go to the concert with her.
She came today to thank you for that
Hmm, there's a relation
She was just coming to say thanks
Then I guess that's how it is
I think so.
Spring has come for Hanpeita-san
Senior
Hello
welcome, Numazawa
I came to contact you from the rowing club
Please, anything but donations.
It's not a donation.
Dr. Uehara from Hokkaido is coming to Tokyo for the first time in a while,
so the doctor is coming
So, Mr. Hayakawa is really enthusiastic about
the welcome race, or rather, the welcome event,
where we have a competition between alumni and
students, and then we can drink and eat afterwards
This is good idea, isn't it?
It's been decided for this Sunday at 3 o'clock
Alright.
I'm fed up with the company
Alright, it's been a while,
let's give it a shot
However, please don't complain about the difficult situation
Don't be silly, will I really lose?
I wonder if you are okay?
Inoda-san
About the Bradford case, right?
I found out that the order was placed with Nankai Trading in Kobe
I see.
It seems that a person called Kaji is in charge of it
Kaji?
That Kaji and Takimoto is getting marriage
Getting marriage ?
It's about the time
In other words,it's soon
Oh I see
Well, Inoda-san, leave it to me
But you see, that's completely my responsibility,
so just watch and see
Getting marriage ?
Kon Kon chi ki
Ako
What?
I just got call from Nankai trading company, but It seemed something was wrong.
What do you mean?
Right now, they're hesitating about whether it's too late to catch up
What's the reason?
They say that productivity isn't improvingdue to management legends,
That's strange.
They're making excuses.
I asked them to follow through. I forced them to sign the contract.
I wonder Fuji company has something with it
Fuji company obstacle us
I can only think of it that way
Who on earth is the one who messed up that order?
I also found out about that by chance 2,3 days ago
It's a person named Ino-san or Inoda-san
Ah, that guy
Someday, she came here
Yeah, He's suspected
It's strange that He's getting closer to Ako
To the person who took his job
But I don't think Inoda-san is that kind of person
Are you close to him?
I'm not
It's not like that
He's not like that person.
so I understand that he takes care of Kenchan well.
Hello
This is Kagawa.
Isn't my mother here?
Is she a customer?
She's the office staff here
The office staff here?
She's Kagawa Kayo
I'm Kagawa Kenichi
Mom! Mom!
Hello
Kenichi
You should have called me if you'd come
Wasn't it a school trip to Nikkō?
I wanted to surprise Mom too,
Kayo.
A person is waiting for something
Please wait a moment
Oh Mr. Kimura?
because he wanted to stay with his mother
I brought him here
I appreciate your help
Ken-chan
You are not a clerk, huh?
Even my sis says
you are a clerk,
so I'm sorry for lying
I won't stay
It's ok if you stay here
Ken.
I'm going
Mom, mom
Ino-san didn't know at all,
Ino didn't lie to Ken-chan,
Ako sis seemed like a liar, but she thinks about Ken-chan Since she lied,
Get it?
Ken.
Stay strong
I wonder why my dad died
Ino-san went to war but came back
Forget about it
Ken-chan? Should I take you to the boat races?
Ah, that sounds good
Are you going to do it, Ino-san?
Yeah,
I'm excited.
Ah, will you really take me to Asakusa?
That's nice.
Are you really going to take me?
Alright,
I'll go later
I came to see your losing
I won't lose that easily
See what happens.
Well, I am off then
Hey Ken-chan, huh?
Oh, is big sister at home?
Yeah,
I heard she's really busy
Hey, it's cold there, so make sure to get some exercise
Hey, where are you going?
To the company
I'm busy.
Ken-chan
Let's hurry and go.
I'm off
Hey, are you still not ready?
I'll be borrowing Ken-chan for the whole day today
Thank you for always taking care of Atsuko
Not at all.
Well, there's a boat race at Sumida river
from 3 o'clock today
I'm going to take
Ken-chan along to the boat race
Boat race?
Are you going out?
Ah, in a poor company
like ours, we can't even take Sundays off
I'll be heading out now
Thank you for waiting, I can't find my hat.
Is this ok?
let's go
I'm off
Please
Peke
I'm going
Shall we go see the movie in Asakusa?
I want to eat a katsudon
Katsudon, huh?
I'm off.
What's wrong?
I forgot something!
He really seem like a nice person
Is that so?
Hi
Oh Furuta
You are really late.
My bad.
It's been a while
Hey, Furuta, you're a strange guy
Is he your friend?
that's right
We saw movie in Asakusa and had katsudon
So I'm late
Well then, I'll show our race to him
Hey I'm not kid
Alright, alright,You are great
hey, Furuta
As a punishment for being late, I'll take you without a warm-up
OK
Big brother,good luck
Hurry up.
We'll have race now
Oh Atsuko sis
People from big companies are quite something, aren't they?
I envy you for being able to play on your days off
Kaji
I understand
Inoda, let's compete fairly in the marketplace
I want you to stop the malicious interference
Even without that, we are already at a disadvantage
I can't stand dirty dealings
Dirty?
A big company like yours shouldn't have to worry about such a small deal.
Inoda-san, listen
You have unfairly taken away the contract that we obtained fairly.
That's not fair.
Kaji
Why don't you calm down and talk?
Business should be about fair play
Inoda, Nankai Shoten has finally given us their last warning today
This is clearly said to be a connection to Fuji company
Don't you think so?
Mr. Inoda
Say something
He can't say anything
But Inoda-kun,
Takimoto-kun, and I are all in this together
We're putting our lives on the line for this business
Just remember that well
I see.
What a big nonsense, you say?
What do you mean?
It's a big nonsense indeed
You're rude.
What do you mean?
It's not a scam
You truly are a something like non sense
I have no regrets about the past
Inoda! Let's go!
He's weird
One day, I'll peel off the mask,
I feel....
Let's go home, it's so ridiculous
Ready?
Come on.
Here we go.
Ready?
Keep it up
Let's have a toast
Ryo-chan,
Let's have a party
We can do Kinchan here
What's Kinchan?
That's Kintaro
That's right.
We can pay by credit here
That's funny to say
Yeah.
Please enjoy as much as you like
Madam, you did very well.
Ah, he will be a full serving
I started this business
You guys have to come here
Sure
We will spend money here
Will you take over this business?
Have a seat
I'm here to help you!
Konkonchiki
I'll do it,
Is that the Kon kon moon?
However, The boat race was fun
From the beginning, It was difficult to judge
I really couldn't bear to watch it
In front of that woman,
it's like a real swordsmanship dojo
Definitely like this.
There was a theory that said he became a woman hater
It seems that's not the case
It is a good trend, right, Heita?
Inoda-san, everyone
is making fun of you, huh?
Well, it's fine to be Hanpeita.
Let's sing, senpai.
Did you tell Nankai Training Company to stop selling their products?
I can't do that with the reference shoji
I knew it. Can I cancel that?
It's just adding shame on top of shame
Even if I approve it, Mr. Hata will not approve it.
We can't
Please consider us.
Is this a reply from Malcolm?
Oh, it was Malcolm Jr.
I heard he returned home safely, wow
As expected, he's the son of Malcolm Pharmaceuticals?
So you asked about the medicine?
They can't be mass-produced in America, after all
There's an allocation, so they can't be free,
That's just how it is.
That's impossible.
Inoda-kun
Ah, well, I appreciate your hard work, but
I want you to head to Nagoya today
What for?
I would like you to make a contract for the
registration for the Williams Town Association
Hi.
Are you off to Kobe?
For Nankai company?
Is Kaji-kun not with you?
No, I'm alone
Oh, is Inoue-san also off to Kobe?
that's not right
No, I am off to Nagoya.
I'm going to buy ceramics
It's really dangerous,
you know
It's true.
But it's tough, isn't it?
It's my responsibility.
I was the one who brought this story up first
If this continues, it will become a breach of contract
Well then,
I'd like to introduce you to the dining car.
It is now tea time
Please feel free to make use of it
Excuse me
I apologize
May I come in?
I'm from reference company.
Is your boss around?
He isn't here.
He is at the factory.
He was here until now,
but he has left
Excuse me
Hi
Oh Matsushima
Welcome.
I'm in trouble
I'm here to ask you
We are in trouble too.
Is that a duty to Fuji Company?
And then there's the issue of power saving and blackouts.
Um... with this, it would mean we are in breach of contract with Mr. Bradford
Unlike large companies like Fuji Trading, if we did something like that, our credibility would drop to zero
It might be a fatal blow to the reference company
Matsushima-san, um,
I see
please ensure stability until that day
Thank you in advance
Please
Matsushima-san, please
If it comes to this, I'm going to tell you the truth
I'm being threatened to stop doing business with your company.
We also get some flexibility from the Fuji Trading Group
In this case, it's a matter that concerns international credibility rather than the pride of our companies,
so it's troubling to hear that
Forgive me....
Please tell the union leader about it.
But
I am in a bit of a hurry.
Yes, yes,
hello, reference shoji?
This is Takimoto here.
Is Kaji there?
Do you know when he will be back?
please let him know when he returns
Please tell him that it is no longer possible to do business with Nankai Company.
Inoda
Phone call from Kobe.
I see.
Ah, hello? Hello?
Is this Nankai?
it's Matsushima, isn't it?
This is Inoda from Fuji Trading
Um... about the reference shoji we discussed...
That, um,
Ako?
Oh Kaji
I heard about the phone call yesterday
I flew here by plane
I was giving up today, but I'm counting on you, Kaji
I just can't help it, it's definitely about Fuji Trading
Yeah, it's Fuji Trading. Anyway, we sent telegram to Nankai company.
Hmm, should we go check it out right away?
It's a matter of international deliberation
I want you to think about that again
What happens if the shipping company and the loading contract are settled,
the loading day is approaching,
but the crucial goods cannot be obtained?
Please consider our position
Eh, Matsuyama-san, of course, We've brought this for you
I'm asking you to somehow run
around and gather the items for us.
Please.
You know there's going to be problems if you break your contract with us.
You must have been prepared for something like that
Are you trying to uphold Fuji's reputation until then?
Isn't the reputation of all Japanese traders more important than that of Fuji?
Please consider that
Please.
Matsushima-san
I received a telegram from you last night.
I was just thinking about reconsidering things
I'm really grateful,
please do it
Well...
Starting tomorrow, we'll be storing all the goods in the warehouse for a week
And it's wonderful, isn't it
We're glad.
Thank you very much.
Make sure to check them
Everything is ok
Check this
beautiful decorations
are made by the hands of poor women
I felt sorry watching that
Well, it's like we're feeding those women
Oh, Kai, Kai, wait a minute,
Keep going.
This
Ah, thank you
Ako-chan
Shall we go play in Osaka after work?
Please enjoy the soft-shelled turtle cuisine in Kyoto
soft-shelled turtle cuisine?
I really want to try soft-shelled turtle in Kyoto; I want to experience Katsuragikyu
What a drag, that's
not interesting at all
it's not a temple
It's pretty much the same thing
That's no different from a landlord's content
Is that so?
It looks beautiful in the photo
It has a Japanese beauty
That Japanese beauty is the problem
Why?
Things like beauty and rust are just sad excuses for
losing in this poor country with so few resources
"No excuse; if anyone has any information regarding
these lost items please step forward;
accompanied by the culprit (dog) and prepared to be scolded."
It's not easy to sell, is it?
I wonder when my sister will come back?
She's busy with work, you know
I want to be with my mom,
but she is working hard to endure
that too,for you
It's okay that I'm poor
If I'm with my mom, I'll do anything,
Kenji.
Let's try to meet mom soon, okay?
I want.
We are KonKonchiki
Come on.
Ino-san
(Inosan-tablet)
I don't remember much about my dad,
Ino-san is like my dad today,
but having a best friend is better than a dad
Hello?
This is mine,
oh, I'm sorry.
Ken-chan
Say sorry
I'm sorry
I'm glad it went well;
I'm really happy.
Thank you very much
Well, we both have our struggles,
Oops,This is a song about heartbreak.
I'll stop.
I'm not good at anything other than business.
What?
Hey, Ako-chan
Once this job is done, I think I'll leave the company and become independent
That's nice
Let's do it together
I have high expectations for you, Ako-chan
Dad's ban has been lifted
He says he's going to start a company again
He has a lot to do with the South Seas countries.
so let's travel the world together
My dad was just a partner in South Seas countries.
but I'm doing business with the world
If it's Kaji-san, I think you'll succeed
So is it OK?
What?
Is it OK to get married?
Wait
Why is that?
that's rude
Do you dislike me?
It's not that I dislike you,but you scared me
You're so calm.
It's not that I'm calm,
but it's such an important matter
I want to think about it slowly
You know, You have a very feudal character.
That might be true. Once you enter a family,
I might unexpectedly become a boring housewife
You're too modest
But sometimes I feel that living a life solely
focused on my business isn't really a true life
I wonder if there are more truths
in the world that I don't know about
How about you moving to Tokyo?
Oh, if you're considering it, should I
talk to my company about it?
Thank you.
But There is a problem with the house
If you like, you can live in my house.
But I think you'll be getting married soon.
No, I really can't do that
I'm really sorry.
After all, He is a bad dog
From now on, Please keep the dog on a strict chain.
Sorry
Sorry.
We can't take care of Peke anymore
I will give Nana to Ken-chan
Isn't Nana much cuter?
Pedigree is important for dogs
Peke, say sorry.
Please, could you take Peke and leave it?
Oh, Nana
Good, good, good.
I understand, it must be tough for Ken-chan
Well then, let's ask someone him throw it away for us
Alright, alright, I see, I see,
I'm going now
You'll be taken care of by someone, got it?
Peke.
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, but I can't take you home
I'm going to have Ino-san take care of you, I'm not throwing you away, I'm leaving you with him.
Oh Kin-chan?
I'm not Kin but Ken.
Ah, Gin?
Niheita's not home.
He won't be able to return?
Isn't he coming home tonight?
He is on a business trip.
He probably won't be coming home tonight.
Let's go
Well, It is unusual to see you.
When did you back?
I just arrived now
Ah, Ken-chan didn't come back yesterday
Really?
Oh, that's terrible. What happened?
Did he not visit here yesterday?
I went to see Ken-chan's mother while I was on a business trip here yesterday
Did you call Hakone?
No, my mother didn't want to worry
Kagawa-san and didn't call
He didn't come while I was there.
I wonder where she went?
Please wait a moment
He's with Peke so he must be in Tokyo.
in Asakusa or Ueno, though
I'll ask my company for permission and go look for him.
I'll also take a day off to search for it
So, shall we go together?
Oh, I'm fine going alone,
I wouldn't mind going alone either
Yes, I think it's more convenient with two people
Oh, then just a moment.
Bros.
I'll be careful around Asakusa
Please
More importantly, it's a bad trend that you're coming home late every night
I changed my part-time job
Please don't worry
I worry
Did you work at a nightclub?
Well then, I'm off
The only person taken into custody at the police station here last night was a runaway girl.
Aren’t tired?
The other day, The street children were having fun playing
Ken-chan must have also wandered off from home,
It was wrong to try to make him abandon his pet
However, the name 'Peke' is utterly ridiculous
Because it really is Peke
Even if a pushy salesperson comes
He's happy
He's a good-natured one
He doesn't naturally doubt people
As you said, he's lazy
He's good character
Well, it's strange to say that a dog is nice,
I like those kind-hearted dogs
It becomes a problem when you're the one taking care of him
As long as you have him, you have to love both the maid and the pekes equally
We do
Well, it's because he wags his tails at everyone, it's a sign of loneliness
Even Ken-chan is like that.
It's because he's lonely.
I'm sorry, dear
Shall we go?
I'll search by myself
Atsuko!
Hmm... I wonder what happened to Kenji.
Is it a souvenir for Kenji?
I bought this at Hamamachi station
Shall we grab a bite to eat?
Let's go to the loach restaurant that I went to with Ken-chan.
Let's visit that place once
Yo, Yo-chan
Welcome
Good evening!
Please come in
Welcome
I wonder if Ken-chan didn't come?
No,I also looked around him here
Thank you very much
I'll pay on credit today.
Don't worry, senpai
I want to order soil and beer
How about this today?
I'll have it
A soil and beer
Do you smoke?
No.
Well, sometimes it's nice to be in places like this, right?
It's nothing
welcome.
Ken-chan is in a grave?
We are going to search him again from now on
Masako. Is this job the reason you come home late?
This is also a lesson for life
Come on.
Masako didn't said anything to you?
Are you guys also playing the kon-kon-chiki?
That's right,
it's the kon-kon-chiki moon.
Please work with the spirit of boat racing in mind.
Don't worry.
I'm getting a little help from Masako-san, which is a big help
Oh no..
It's delicious.
I was surprised
Am I not allowed to drink?
I can't stand to see a drunken woman.
I won't get drunk
I can't agree with a woman who drinks too much
I also really dislike men who drink too much
It's fine to drink
but what I dislike is a lazy person who only
drinks and seems to have no other thoughts
Maybe it's me
What do you think about Atsuko,Afureko(voice acting),Afureko's child?
That means you're just a slave to the company.
You're mean.
Well, It's fine with the big companies
Just like Inoda-san, being laid-back and carefree
Do you think so?
Mr. Inoda is not seriously facing life
He is commonly known as Hanpeita
What is life?
Business is not life, and life is not
just about living.
I understand
But you see, life is not just about living
Besides, it's not about living a life.
I'm envious of you.
You get to talk about life with such a beautiful wife.
I really understand that now
Sorry.
I'm having fun
I'm enjoying my life
How about you?
Anyway, let's call Ken-chan's mother right away
She seem like a nice person with a tough exterior, gentle and beautiful
If it's inconvenient for you, I might have to file a missing person report
but no, I won't worry my aunt like that, I'll find them
I have a responsibility, you know
Are you taking care of him out of responsibility or out of love?
If you have that much love,
you should marry Ken-chan's mother and make Ken-chan happy
What did you say?
If it weren't for Ako,
I might have slapped you
Oh, Inoda-san, did you just insult me?
You're also insulting Ken-chan's mother
Atsuko
The real Ako-chan shouldn't be like this
Inoda-san seems different from that Inoda-san today
I'm off.
Ako!
Beer please.
Good morning
Inoda-san,Congratulations.
Congratulations.
What's wrong?
Don't you know about this?
I received a contract from Malcom Company.
That's good
Congratulations.
I think Japan would be very happy if we could secure a contract for that drug.
I'm honored to receive your praise
Hmm, I have three requests regarding this
Three?
First of all,since we're finally able to get it
I would like to have a rehabilitation facility that accommodates employees like Ito-kun
Sure, that sounds good
And?
I would like you to hire one more person
She's called Kagawa Kayo who is War widow.
Well, what about the other one?
I'd like to take another day off
Please
That's just ridiculous.
But this is Matsushima's story
Actually, the one who was bothering you was Inoda's colleague
Did Inoda really ask you to bring that out no matter what?
I'm getting motivated about it
I must go to Fuji Trading and say thank them.
Shima.
I'm off.
But the business has completely succeeded, hasn't it?
It's based on people's thoughts, you know
That's not the issue
It was us who made Reference Trading Company a reality
Yes, exactly, thank you
Ako-chan, there's nothing to be down
If you have complaints, we'll take all the complaints next time
It's 1 million yen
that can fulfill 10%
But don't we need to reflect on this?
Reflection?
Reflecting won't change a thing, will it?
Yes, yes, it's me
Well, the Shinagawa
Technical Consultation Office?
Yes, thank you for yesterday
Hello, about this matter...
This morning... I heard they took in a child about Ken-chan's age
They say they took him in at the Sarajou Academy in Kokubunji
Ah? No, no, the name is different, though
They say he's walking a dog
He must be Kenji
I will be there right away
Just ignore someone else's kid like that
The police will look for him
It won't go that way.
More importantly, let's do it together
The next job is interesting because I deal with a lot of cult leaders
You can really savor the essence of business
I'm currently busy looking for Ken-chan,
Once you find him, It's best not to get involved with vagrant children like that.
Do you have pocket money?
If so,bring it for the taxi fare
I have some
Mr. Kai, There's a call from Mogi campamy.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
The situation here is stagnant, but
However, it is showing strong signs
The market is strong.
I definitely think it's Kenji
Please take a look
But it would be unfortunate if it's wrong
Please view from a distance.
I understood.
Atsuko!
Ken-chan
Peke
I knew he was here
I'm glad
Kenji
Ken-chan
Ino!
Atsuko sis.
Atsuko
Ino!
I have something I need to apologize to Inoda-san for
I just found out this morning
About Mr. Bradford
Well, you must have had quite a hard time
I’m sorry
No....
Aren't we going to take a break?
ken-chan!
Shall we have a rest?
I thought I had been living earnestly until now.
I thought my serious way of living was my life as it is
But I feel like I'm finally starting to understand that there are many things in life that I don't know
No, I have learned a lot from Atsuko-san
Same here.
You said to me once
I thought I wasn't living seriously.
I'm sorry for being cheeky
Same here.
Atsuko-san, why aren't
you getting married?
Huh? Inoda-san,you too.
Me?
Actually,there was someone I thought about marrying before
She married someone else while I was away at war.
Since then, I have had a distrust of women.
I have had such experiences.
Engaged?
He died in battle.
Atsuko-san is also a victim of the war as a doctor
I hate to say this,
but actually,
you know...
Recently, I finally met a woman who I think is the one for me
When I took Kenji to Asakusa,
While walking, I decided to clearly express my feelings to that person
So? What did you do then?
Well, just when I thought I would show my confess
I ended up meeting Kaji
and it didn't go well
Oh...
I'm indirectly confessing my feelings to you.
Not at all.
I'm off.
Ako.
Atsuko sis!
It's a great view!
Be careful.
It's Hakone there, right?
Yes, that's right
Your mom might be on the Odakyu line right about now
That's good, alright, I'm fine now
Are you fine now?
THE END