Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Ashi Ni Sawatta Onna / The Woman Who Touched the Legs (1960)
I glanced out the window and was struck by a mysterious feeling
The unfamiliar scenery flies away
I should be on the express train to Tokyo
The Tokaido is, so to speak, a well-traveled line.
There's no place like this along the line
I became worried and stood up to ask the conductor
The train boy was found before the conductor,
but he didn't wake up no matter how much I called out to him
When I got closer,
I smelled a sickening drunken scent
I proceeded to the next carriage to look for the car
I prefer to be smaller
It fits in my palm like this.
You demand so much.
Here it is.
More discount.
They deal pistols.Even when I approached themon the train, they pretended not to notice me.
There should be a sense of public safety on express trains
The train is running in a strange place
There are people buying and selling handguns.
I spoke to him, but the police officer glared at me and said, "Shut up,
are you trying to criticize my win?"
He pulled out his gun and aimed it at me
My throat was dry and my knees were shaking
The dining car was like a bar. There were bills on the counter like tissues.
I have no use for these guys
I thought I'd go to the engine room.
when I finally got there, there was a gangster in the engine room
You know?
Next time you come to a junction, turn left again.
Forgive me....
I turned left just now.
Due to this, the train timetable is a mess.
Shut up!
Or I'll shoot you.
So if I die, who will run this train?
Just one left turn is enough if you give me just 100,000 yen.
I'll give you another 300,000.
If we are on a train and I can't trust the
driver, who can we trust?
I feel bad.
Where is here?
Isn't it Japan? Isn't it the country where I was born?
Such crimes have become commonplace in Japan
The terminal symptoms of criminal Japanese capitalism. It is only natural that the world will become like this
in a world where consumption, greed and money rule everything
Money, money, money, what can we do without it?
Kill or be killed?
I have made up my mind
I want what I want
I pulled out a bunch of Colts from under my shirt
I yelled
I yelled some more.
Hey.
isn't this your wallet?
It's hot.
It tastes good.
Where did you buy that lunch box?
This is not a lunch box
But a train lunch box is usually one you buy through the window at a train stop.
You can't do that on the express train.
on the express train, the woman in the dining room walks around in a bun
If you miss out on that, you won't be able to eat anything until Tokyo.
Because it should be a public railway agency
Railroad companies contract with cafeteria companies.
There stuff we should buy.
Did you eat that lunch?
That's what I think.
Did she pass by here?
Yes I bought it from her.
You were so busy reading your book.
I didn't notice.
What is that?
A crime Japan.
Auther: Gomi Kosuke
He writes like this.
Gomu Kosuke, not Gomi
What do you mean?
Gomi means dust.
I meant Gomi Kosuke who was linguist.
I never heard of him.
I am a fan of Gomu Kosuke
I respect him.
I've never heard of him.
Hes great.
The book is interesting?
Yes.
Let me see.
I'm reading a really interesting part right now,
so can you go to the dining car?
There are some foods?
Yes. go there.
This novel is shit
I understand your careful consideration very well
If you think about it more casually, you will be able to write more easily
Our editor-in-chief also emphasized this
I have also been told that you will receive a special manuscript fee
I don't want money.
What I want is free time.
I understand that
But you are great, the magazines want you.
Novels like "Criminal Japan" are hidden bestsellers
What I'm writing is a novel called Crime Japan
This is well sold but The pundits do not approve of my novel.
I mean...
I knew.. you are Weekly Jabon,right?
Speaking of Weekly Jabon, it's one of the best among the many weekly publications out here
I'm a third-rate novelist,
so you're too superior
Don't say that?
What?
I only tell the truth.
You are all very elegant people
You must think my novel is a gross exaggeration.
but that's just how Japan is now.
Japan is in an unbelievable state right now
For example, I saw the word "buffet" written at the entrance to the restaurant
When I first saw it, I thought it was a toilet
In Japan, Japanese people can read it, but Japanese people don't understand the meaning of the characters
that's incomprehensible.
but that's reality.
Crime and gruesomeness
We are just like barbarians.
What's the hell?
Are you Mr.Gomu?
I respect you.
The public knows that I only write the truth,
and I will continue to write the truth.
I just want some free time
There's no point in receiving royalties
There's no point because I don't have time to spend money
Money is like a flower
Don't you have anything else I can eat?
Beer.
I don't need beer I want something with chicken
Apparently there's only roast chicken
That's a good thing
Please eat a lot.
Roast chiken.
How about a story about a beautiful pickpocket girl?
beautiful pickpocket girl?
That's an old fashion.
No one wanna read about that.
There's no beautiful pickpocket girl.
If she's beautiful, she does not do pickpocket.
She can live a cool, flashy life.
If there is a pickpocket girl,
First of all,she must be the clumsy old ladies who have realised they can make money by their face.
Excuse me for asking, but you're the one with the prejudices
I mean prejudice is the cause of war
You're the one with the prejudices
Don't get involved with him.
There's a beautiful pickpocket girl.
That's an old story
There's.
I want to meet her.
I'll let you.
Where is she?
Osaka
Osaka? I was in Osaka until this morning but I didn't see her.
Maybe she's boarding on this train.
That woman is a vehicle specialist
Is she on this train?
That's scary.
I'm just saying maybe
pickpocket, thieves, robbers, murderers, they're everywhere, with us
This guy is too serious, you're single too, right?
He's too.
Single men have no sense of surveillance over women
Even if you say arrogant things,
Deep down, you look into her eyes and admire her.
I think a woman who wears false eyelashes, high shadow, and has curves is beautiful
It's normal for young women to have curves
But she is the most unfaithful woman I have ever met in my life
I can't trust you.
Please believe in me
Believe in you?I don't know you
Yes, it's dirty.
Sorry, it's fine
Is this yours?
May I smoke?
Go ahead.
I’m sorry.
No, it's fine, I'll get used to it quickly. It smells really good
You're kind.
Traveling with someine is fun.
It's so fun to be with someone as beautiful and kind as you
Where are you going?
I'll give my my business card.
I would love to show you around if you come to Tokyo
Thank you very much.
How about joining me as a diner?
I'm full.
I see.
Excuse me.
Ouch.
My stocking is broken.
Wait.
Sis.
Be careful
it broke again
Sorry.
I told you to be careful when kicking
nylon socks because they tear easily
It's just a play to set things off
Why don't you just stumble?
Don't kick
How much do you think these socks cost?
Sorry, sorry, sorry
I'll pay you back by working someday.
so will you work?
Don't do that.
I'm gonna throw you away
Please don't.
You shouldn't wander around too much.
The Kita-san is here.
Really?
He must have been chaseing you.
But how did he know?
If he catch a big one,his monthly salary will increase
You are the one?
Of course
Really?
Kita-san is in 2nd class?
I think so.
Anyway, it's fine, I'll just beat him
What do you mean?
Sis
you're so noisy
This is my business.
This trip is not just a trip
You told me to tread carefully
If we miss something so impressive, what will we do to the humiliation of the pickpocket?
Let's see.
Big sister, try turning off that switch.
I'm not good with scientific things.
No matter what anyone says, it's a stupid job
You'll understand our work if you try it yourself
Even if we arrest people, crimes just keep coming one after another
Laws are necessary. Justice must be done
However, we have reached a point where the police alone cannot do anything about it
It's boring.
It just makes us tired.
Are you going to Tokyo for work?
here's no point in complaining,
so I drive there every day like a horse and carriage
My boss told me to take my accumulated vacation days,
so I have no choice but to take vacations.
My colleagues are in trouble
We are short on manpower.
Our boss says
the rules are the rules
It's strange, because even if I get a vacation, I don't have any money
All we can get a free train pass.
I was thinking about going to Tokyo and checking out the International Beauty Contest
I want to quit Police
The publishers are doing well?
That's not ture.
He is on vacation
Why don't you ask him about something? He's  an expert,
so I'm sure he has some interesting material.
I'm not a writer who can't write without a model
You're being quite arrogant
Who's this guy?
Oh really
I'm very sorry
Your novel is very popular among us.
Especially First novel.
Stop it....
I didn't notice you because you changed your hair.
Your hair grows pretty fast
If you're a police officer, you can read,right?
Calm down and take a good look.
I'm not trash(Gomi)
I'm Gomi.
Many people get my name wrong.
I'm sure you guys call me gomi.
Oh, you've already done it.
It's very crowded
Even if I extend it for an hour or two, I won't die,
You're funny.
Is it me? Is that so?
Hey you.
Me?
I’m sorry.
I'll pick it up.
I don't know who is he but
Let him to pick it up.
I'm very sorry Madam,
you shouldn't say rude things.
Do you think this person is a wife?
Do you think she is my wife?
I’m sorry.
He's so rude.
He's bad novelist.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Someone is here.
Oh.
this train is moden, right?
Please wait a moment, I'll have to blame it on a telegram before departure
I'm not talking about telegrams.
I'm talking about lights.
Isn't that supposed to be the case.
That's automatic
You have to work.
I'll check it out later.
You can't say it like that
Why don't you just say sorry?
I'mletting you know
I'm sorry
It suddenly becomes dark and surprising
It is too late to act after a robbery.
Was there a theft?
that was a big problem
I mean if it's happened.
It's a great opportunity for pickpockets
Were there any pickpockets?
I don't know if you asked me
My walltet is missing
What was that?
Were there any pickpockets?
My wallet was stolen
That's what I said.
That kind of young, decent guy is a suspicious idea
Modern pickpockets are well-dressed.
Anyway, please come in.
Is there something wrong?
My wallet was stolen.
Don't tell him.
What was stolen.
She swapped it with my wallet
Don't tell him.
It's a bit tricky.
But.
Excuse me, customer, but please come in for a moment
I'm in trouble because there is no public police today
But I'm on vacation.
Let me go!
You're the thief,right?
You're the pickpocket and yet you are on vacation.
Who?
Don't do that.
Although there is no clear evidence
Even if you say that
Calm down.
what are you doing?
The pickpocket is a woman
A woman?
Do you have any idea?
Who are you?
Thank you
I'm sorry, but please listen to this person
I'm on vacation
This is not my jurisdiction.
Sorry
Did she sit next to you?
Yes.
Did she hug you?
You did a good job
What kind of woman was she?
She was beautiful
Did she have a different Japanese personality?
She was 25-6 years old, 1 meter 60 cm tall, and has big eyes
Nice leg.
Damn it.
She was on this train.
It can't be helped.
She is a pickpocket within my jurisdiction.
I'll take care of this case
Thank you.
She is popular in Osaka
You thought she was a beautiful woman?
I'm a feminist
I'm not asking about you.
She was a beautiful woman.
Thank you very much.
My wallet is in here.
the business card holder was stolen.
There was something important in there?
No, it's just a business card.
That's not true, right?
She won't get it wrong.
Oh, customer, 1st class is here.
Oh, excuse me
What's wrong?
I'm so sorry
What can I do for you?
Something must have gone wrong
Please don't make fun of me.
I'm sorry
You're great.
What?
You stole it
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just taking care of this.
She's my sis.
I know.
I'm sorry .
Hello
Hello.
what a coincidence to meet you here
What a coincidence.
You worked in first class.
There's no point in talking about anything.
Don't pretend you don't know.
You're probably the only one who did it.
What do you mean?
Young and tall
beautiful woman with big eyes and beautiful legs
Not really,
Come.
That's wrong way
I'm not going  first class
I've been in second class the whole time,
let me see your ticket
Oh, I put that in my suitcase and left it on the seat
That's suspicious
Police.
Did you see me pickpocket?
No.
So you're going to do a physical examination?
You are talking nonsense here.
Let me go!
But.
Ouch.
I got hurt.
Why you chase me?
Don't say bullshit.
I'm going to Tokyo
You just happened to be the one who got me
I have a destination in mind too
Where are you going on this journey?
I'm going back to my hometown.
Your home is Atsugi in Kanagawa Prefecture,right?
Yes.
For what?
It's none of your business.
You went to Osaka when you were three years old.
Your father died early. your mother also died when you are thirteen
But you're not the only one without parents
Are you not going to do any serious work?
You don't have to do anything bad
Don't get too cocky just because you checked your family register
Did you see our hardships written in our family register?
so we have our hardships
Is everyone suspected of being a spy?
The spy ?
My father committed suicide
My mother died from overwork.
That's what he kept saying until the moment he died
They asked me to avenge them.
I'm gonna knock them down like bang
Who?
Those relatives in Atsugi.
I'll hit them.
You shouldn't do that
I never thought you'd become a murderer
They asked me to avenge them.
Don't do that.
I can't stand it anymore, but if you insist on doing it,
I'll hit them for you.
That's right, I'll do it.
I'm not saying kill them.
I use dynamite
But dynamite is dangerous,
I'll ldo Memorial service
Memorial service?
I want to show them I have a good life.
They called us traitors and drove us out of Atsugi.
By Memorial service?
By lugjurilous Memorial service
Who pay the expence?
I earned.
When?
All the time.
You were in prison less than three months ago.
After leaving
Wait.
That's bad.
I earned.
If you have a complaint, get some evidence first
Goodbye, see you again in Osaka
Kita has been following us.
I was worried about whether you and he were together.
I met him.
Really?
Let's leave
Don't worry.
Please don't stay near me.
We are mate.
You're just helping me..
I don't want you to be a criminal.
Because there's hope for you
But
But?
You are not the kind of person who would pickpocket someone.
You look shocked all year round and so clumsy.
The only thing you took just now was a business card.
Because it's a business card holder
You will go to a memorial service
Please don't let the money for the memorial service stolen.
I just mistook the right and left pockets.
I'm still skillful.
the next car is 2nd class.
so please make sure you find your seat carefully this time
A train boy will be in that car too,
so please ask him to guide you
May I help you, grandma?
That's a lot of work
Thanks.
You're so kind.
What's wrong?
I can't enter the first class carriage because of my dirty clothes.
It looks similar to this, but it's a little different on this tiny piece of paper
This is for 1st class.
He misread it.
It's impossible.
I definitely have a second class ticket.
When they checked it, they mixed it up with the
other tickets and gave it back to me, right?
You proudly returned to 1st classcar with this ticket in hand
Thank you very much.
A soft chair is better for the elderly.
You are very kind.
You are so lucky to have such a wonderful wife
Is she my wife?
You are lovely couple
Bring her luggage to her seat
Don't say bullshit.
Thank you very much.
I never thought that there would be someone as kind as you
guys, even among the young people.
I'm glad.
Come on, take her away quickly.
Please take care of my luggugue.
telegram information.
To Mr. Tanaka : A telegram has arrived for Mr. Tanaka
Please inform the crew
Thank you very much.
Hi
Oh you.
She was not here.
Yes.
I see.
Damn it.
Where were you from?
What are you doing?
All I'm saying is
Now that I'm almost at the end of my trip between Osaka and Tokyo,
what are you even saying now?
Get out.
where have you been all this time?
It's none of your business.
Why don't you go back to your seat? It's my seat
Do you have the ticket?
Of course,
let me see it
Car No. 11, No. 17, I'm the same.
Oh yeah same.
It says eleventh
It's none of your business.
does it look like eleven?
this number is eleven.
11 is here
It's always vacant.
Thank you, my seat is over there. The one at the front desk is...
There is a problem with their writing.
but I'm a person who follows the rules
Here you go.
It's your suitcase.
So She is your sister
No, that's not true.
I don't know him.
Are you still going to complain?
Sorry
Then I'll borrow this book. I'll return you back.
What are you muttering about?
That person took my book.
What a strange person
He's also constantly bothering you.
Ah, I know that. he wanted to talk to me forever
Why?
Because I'm pretty,
but
it's just a coincidence
The ticket you stole from that old lady was for the seat next to me
Did you see me pickpocketing?
No at all.
It was a small thing.
It was wonderful
He's back again
Don't be so familiar.
I have a ticket,
2nd class.
I don't approve of women who are clumsy with their hands
In that sense, I like you.
You will be good at sewing in no time.
Will you marry me?
I'm telling you, why don't
you change your business?
I can introduce you to a job
It's a waste to spend the money
It's a waste to spend money on memorial services
Why don't you use the money to fund your store someday?
I'll do memorial services.
Think carefully about it.
Reviewing things doesn't resonate with modern people at all
That makes sense to me
And the method is old-fashioned.
Doing this will make your chest feel refreshed.
Legal matters are boring
I will give them a great treat
There's no need to treat your enemy to a feast
The world is all about profit and loss, so to speak
You should be kind to the old lady,right?
No, it's just because I feel sorry for her.
I see.
That's why I think it's boring being police.
I'm trying to bring you back into normal society.
But you don't accept it.
We can't catch a pickpocket unless you catch him red-handed
There is a pickpocket right in front of me, but she is making fun of me.
I’m sorry.
I have nothing else to do since it's my vacation anyway, so I'll walk by your side forever
There's a chance,
Don't do that.
I'd be in trouble if you come.
It's okay, I'm wearing casual clothes, so I'm your lover
Please get out.
I dropped.
I can't see it. Where did it go?
How much is it?
Is it a 100 yen coin?
I'll find it.
Never mind.
It's waste.
She'run away.
What's wrong?
She.
Train is leaving soon.
I know
You'll miss it
it can't be helped.
Be careful.
Where's my wallet?
Damn it.
She picjocketed.
I am happy to see Haruko-chan again after such a long time
You've grown so much,, and Hashiru has grown a lot too.
You were still so cute when I picked you up.
How is The economy in Osaka?
It has been really bad lately.
How are chikako and others.
They live in different places.
so it's not a business that has been around for a long time.
I'm going to quit too
It's so noisy.
Outside?
Isn't it bad?
Is that real?
Of course,
that's a waste.
Thanks to that being so careful
I'm can sleep well listening to this sound
It's a terminal symptom of capitalist society.
So now it's time for going to Atsugi?
If the world like this
So I thought it would be better to do it quickly when I said what I wanted to do
My sister watches a lot of TV
so she knows a lot about world affairs
Even though they had been so cared for by my father,
They told the Military Police.
that's just how the world is
They repay kindness with evil
How much did you bring?
30000.
It was hard to make all that
If my sister have a little extra money, she just buy handbags
clothes and treat us ramen.
So, you're acting weird.
Don't call her sis
It's cute
Him?
What are you talking about?
This boy has an ideal.
I want to become a ramen noodle coock.
He coock nce.
The owner of the ramen shop offered to give me the rights to the shop.
Where is that money? Let me see around
Go to kichen.
I can buy it for 30,000 yen
Are you guys still upstairs in Kamaboko shop?
I'm the only one.
How's Saya?
She moved to the second floor of the local greengrocer.
She hates me because I've become manly, but I'm lonely
Saya.
That old woman did it.
She pickpocketed.
It was stolen. Your money was taken?
That old woman pickpockted her Cost of legal services
I told you off.
She acted weird.
Don't cry.
She is the one who wants to cry
There are some nasty people out there who take other people's money
People have bad heart.
Recently, a newspaper article said that a man who was robbed of his company's money committed suicide
That's how I feel,
but isn't it okay to not die?
Be careful.
I won't stop you from committing suicide
Why don't you hang out for a night? Won't you come and play with me?
Who said I was going to die? If you say something weird, I'll call the cops
Hello? Hello?
What's wrong?
Why won't you let me die? Please, let me die
Don't say stupid things
Ah,I met you on train.
Insurance saleswomen are underpaid
But I don't feel like doing anything weird
there's a person like you with a strict sense of ethics..
That's unusual
I came back without having anything to eat and saving up my money
I've also felt stuck lately
Nothing comes from crime and eroticism
It's time to change my way. Your story is truly inspiring
Could you please give me more details?
That was all.
Don't say all those cold things like that
You have to help me
I believe that I am the man with the mission to
bring new morality and soil to this troubled Japan
I just made up my mind, so this is who I am
You know that
My name is often mistaken
Person who name Gomi is also writer?
Excuse me for a moment
Please wait a moment
Don't take it easy, you are tired,
this is a home where you don't have to worry at all
It's an inn where I use instructions for work
But thank you for all your help
I have no choice but to give it to you the money.
I don't mind the money.
I can't ask you.
how much did she steal?
100,000 yen
100,000 yen?
Isn't that a lot?
Why didn't you report it to the police?
She wouldn't be so stupid as to just go and give the money back to the police
I'm sure you won't get your money back if you report it to the police,
but I think it's embarrassing to be scammed, so I'd rather not go to the police
I would rather die
That's the great thing about you
The spirit of blaming yourself first before blaming anyone else
I want to hear about all of that
I can pay you 70000yen
Could you give me 70,000 yen?
Thank you
You're so honest, aren't you? Do you want to take a bath? Let's get together
Can we go in together?
Yes, please.
Have you finish yet?
I felt very good.
but please take it easy
Takahashi..shiranami..
These are too old.
I thought school teachers weren't that great.
I don't have to stay here long.
why you're wearing clothes?
Have you finished?
I am taking a bath just for a while.
It's quick, but if I am alone.
It is a cheap thing if I think about saving one life
Sorry, now I can show my gratitude to my parents
I just received an advance for a magazine article.
Are you novelist?
What do you mean?
You've been misunderstanding me all this time
I'm sure you'll be tired tonight, so maybe I'll listen to you talk while you sleep
What are you doing?
Thank you teacher
I will never forget this
I don't feel like forcing yourself to sleep
You should have at least told me your story
That's too bad.
Isn't this a terrible world?
The modern world is full of crime.
I went back to my sister's room in the apartment and slept properly,
You came back so pretty late, I know that.
I didn't know.
you fall asleep as soon as I eat udon,
you snore, you break your teeth,
I didn't do anything.
Who would give you 70,000 yen without doing anything?
I was just taking a bath.
See?
I took alone
it seems you didn't keep what I said after all.
You don't remember when I left Osaka three years ago?
There are many type of pickpocket.
You shouldn't use your body to make money
If you make a mistake
Your dead parents feel sad about you.
The pickpocket is the one who leaves before the street is the best
The secret to pickpocketing is to avoid even touching the thier body
I don't have the skill to do that. I guess I just have to settle for shoplifting
But I haven't soiled my body
Your were about getting
naked in front of a guy.
Sorry to interrupt your conversation.
It's so hot I'm going to get a sunstroke
Can I rest in the shade over there?
No
We have to find our home.
Your hometown is here,no?
Yes.
If so, it's here
Big sister, stay strong
We got on and off many trains from early in the morning
and finally made it here
There's no way a place like this is my hometown
There's nothing there but planes flying around
The village of Kiyose in Atsugi
There is a beautiful little river flowing there.
There are small settlements there.
My mother always said that.
When I think back on that time, I feel very nostalgic.
There was no airfield?
I knew there was a naval airfield
called Shimizu Airfield nearby.
You don't know anything, big sister?
Yeah, I was kicked out when I was a baby.
In twenty-four or twenty-five years
things probably change a bit.
Well....
We moved here four years ago
We don't know about the old days.
When we came here, the ecconomy were ridiculously good
Even so, I paid a high royalty fee to buy it,
and now I have no idea what's going on
Because there's nowhere to go now
We are in trouble.
If you want,We can rent you a room.
Please don't say weird things.
I mean..
I'm sorry for bothering you
Are you her mother?
Me? her mother, no way.
I'll rent the space in front of the store.
What?
Please stay here.
Oh, hello detective.
■That's what I thought.
I knew that if I came to Atsugi, you would definitely come.
Sure. If you want to be by my side
that badly, come with me. Let's go
Just give me your wallet
You know there's not much in my wallet
You did it just to annoy me, right? I got into a lot of trouble
Last night I asked a friend who works at the Metropolitan Police Department to limit the number of police officers
I borrowed 500 yen today and came here
I'm in trouble
I've confessed so much
Give it back with the drums that made my heart melt. That's great
That old lady, um...
I want to keep this between us, but I was rubbed the same way
So if it's true
Do you remember the old lady carrying a big furoshiki on the train?
My head hurts
But that's not what you came all the way here to do. Too bad
How much did they take?
I'll lend it to you
Well then, goodbye. Hey, I
don't want to bother you. It's today
While I am fighting over my parents' grudges
Everyone is getting in the way, so who is everyone?
Are you going to hold a memorial service? It's not worth reporting
I can't find my hometown
Look at my hometown, it's just an airport and planes
Have you asked anyone? It's weird that you don't know
In this case, the quickest way to find out is to ask at the police station
I used to work at a police box,
and I was required to know everything about the residents
within the designated area
There is no such thing as certainty
I'll go with you. No way. Come on
Poor sister
In the end, she was dragged away by the factory workers
and it was all her fault
She suffers because she is too soft on men
That's what happens when your opponent is a big guy
Ha ha ha it's gradually decreasing
In the past, there used to be a lot of birth houses called Shiozawa
Do you know where it went after it was transferred?
I didn't record the destination
It was originally a naval airfield
and has been expanded many times to become the vast airfield it is today
Well, it seems that more than one or two villages have disappeared
The residents have become numb
Well, if there's even one Shioza left, they're relatives
You may know where I'm moving to,
but I'd like to ask you a question
How do I get to Kyomura? There were a lot of people there today
Oh dear, don't be so scared of famous people
I don't know what famous people think about me
Did you do something, girl? Play with me, teacher
Who are you? We were somewhere
That's right, I'm sorry, I'm a detective from Osaka
No, I know this detective. Ah,
this woman wanted to introduce me to a beautiful soup restaurant in Osaka
I'm sorry, I'm an old acquaintance of yours from Osaka
It just so happened that I was here
He came with me. He's very kind
There was one enemy in Shiozawa
My predecessors had beautiful handwriting and I couldn't read it
Excuse me. I'll draw you a map now
It's a very confusing place. What happened? Please point out the difference between a man and a woman
I don't know how you know me here
I know it's strange to say this in front of her,
but people like this are also considered beautiful
What do you mean by beautiful woman?
Is she as beautiful as this woman? Of course
She's such a beautiful woman. Wait, what a cowardly man
You're not going to do anything until Wednesday
because you're jealous of me and her
Apparently she couldn't stand the manager and ran away
Please tell me, I really did arrive, I just said I did arrive
She's a beautiful woman who's already been sat on
A beautiful pickpocket. A stupid detective
That person is a victim of scams. Will fishing be scammed? A relative without compassion
A crystal of hard work and sweat. Of course, it's about money
He was so upset that he tried to commit suicide,
but I saved him
Apparently the story is well-known, so I also had my doubts
But even now, she's still there
So it's true
that it's true
Is your house Mr. Shiozawa? Yes, your house is the only one
There's a house called Shiozawa around here that's good
My name is Saya Shiozawa
Oh, so it's yours? My father is Shiozawa Monnosuke
Do you know him? He used to live around here. We were relatives
Yes, that's right
It used to be quite painful
My relatives are also pros in Kiyose Village
Don't you know about Kiyose Village? If my grandfather was alive,
he might have known a little about it
What was the name of the old man who started last year? He said he was Sugizo
Sugizo is a liberal arts guy, so that's what I thought
This is my relative
It's terrible
They're building a golf course and they're telling us to move out
I'll try my best to get a good price, so I'll say it
Heaven is an adopted child
I work on the outskirts of town
He's a smart guy. He's got it all together
But I said I'd go to Tokyo if I got in
Where are you from? Osaka, Osaka
Yeah, people who leave early have an advantage
Osaka is a nice place, isn't it? Where did you go? I've looked for you a long time
The house and village where I was born was somewhere on that airfield
No one I've asked knows anything about that village
It's history, it's the power of history
Even if you didn't take revenge,
History has destroyed the village that drove your family out.
This is a complete revenge.
It makes me feel good.
Could it be worse? I don't have a home town
Oh, stop that airplane noise
I want to go to a quiet place
I don't know what to do anymore. Let's go back to Osaka
I want to go to prison, it's so quiet there
I miss that place so much now
Have you ever been to prison?
Are you a pickpocket?
Yes.
Shut up
I'll give you back the 70,000 yen because I don't need it anymore
70,000 yen?
Did someone lend you this much money?
Take it.
Thanks.
Well then, put me in jail
I can't.
Every human being thinks of their spiritual home
You just found out your hometown has died
And I was shocked to find that your
spiritual home was a prison.
You poor woman.
I just hope I never go to jail again
Bye.
You were trying to get me,right?
Wait.
I need a beauty pickpocket.
Oh I'm against it to go to police.
Stop here.
If you're going to the police station, please stop the driver
If you go to the Metropolitan Police Department, you'll definitely find Kita-san there
It's so cool that you added "Tekanai-san" to it. You like it, don't you?
Kita-san, what are you planning to do after you go to prison? I'm still thinking about it,
but I'm not getting anywhere
I won't be young forever either
There's no point in getting naked when you're fifty or sixty
That's why I always say,
if you hone your skills and you're good at it,
First of all, how old is my sister
who doesn't have to pay tax? Leave me alone
Even though I look like this, I'm called the Tree Maiden's Spring
It's not as degrading as the color makes it seem
Is that what the first day will be like?
It would be fine if you bought the rights to the ramen on the run
Big sister, I'm disappointed
For the past 20 years,
you've been thinking about revision all the time, awake or asleep
That's a lie. I told you the other day that I don't like permanent hair
Didn't it remain for ten days? This is the Metropolitan Police Department
Mr. Kita, are you the teacher again? I want you to release Shiosae
Did he get caught? You caught him, right? I didn't see him again
Don't be mean, I really need to be beautiful
The deadline for the magazine is approaching,
but without a girlfriend,
Gomu Kosuke is going to be a model for the sake of his reputation, right?
Help me, that's right
You said that you don't need a model to write a novel
It depends on the time and the situation
So you're not chasing that woman because you like her?
You're in love with her
When it comes to who you like
There is no other way to save such a woman than to become her husband
That would be a problem
I'm a police officer who said that if I married her, I'd have to quit being a police officer
There is no back clause, so that is what actually happens
How can you support her?
Aren't you already worried about supporting her?
Why is this bad? If you don't give me water,
then everything is bad
Modeling a poor woman like you
Like drinking cheap alcohol in healthy amounts
Isn't it a good thing? You're saying terrible things
I'll get it together
I don't really know who introduced me to her,
even though I'd like to talk to her about that house
This side is the one in front of me
Even though I'm in Kanto, I'm tired
Kanto is Tokaido Fujino White Snow Looking to the west, Chichibu Mountains,
Kono Plateau, East, Nishitama Water, Musashino Spring
The following three people grew up listening to the sound of the gold bells
pounding out of the nearby Choanji temple in the morning and evening
Please be quiet
It is small and stands in front
The ceremony of life begins with a small body
The other person I will be posting is Nao Shiozawa, also known as Onee-chan
No matter where you are in Izu, you will be able to come
and join the 500th event for your brother and friends
I hope you will take this opportunity to make
a connection with us
That's impressive. Who did you come to see?
I knew you were arrested. I didn't know
I'm a stranger too. I'm a little crazy
When I told you to match me, you asked me who I was, so I introduced myself
Catch me please, can't you hear my voice?
If you catch me, that's love
Yeah, you should definitely do something about it. We're not lovers
You call me about all those things, yeah, I get it
Catch me, I'm three, then I must be a little crazy
It's not weird. Historically, Osaka's three is three
I hate it. I'm a detective in charge of the Osaka precincts
That means there are 3,000 in Tokyo too
The reason why there is a police officer in Osaka who can't stop fishing in Osaka is because of a traffic accident
Take me home, I'm on vacation
I don't want to touch any criminal cases. What are you saying?
Don't you know the police are short on manpower? Take him home
Is there such a rotten way of looking at things? Who are you? I'm Hoshi Kei-san,
please go home. I'm the detective team
However, since it is autumn, I will have to pay for the travel expenses
I'm in charge from that place
I was very grateful to hear various
useful information
I have one question. Is it possible to catch someone
even if they are not caught red-handed or engaged in trolling?
What do you think? You said it yourself,
so there's no doubt about it
Confessions are unreliable, so
how much would be appropriate for drugs?
You guys left but I can't hold on today
It would be a problem if you just let me do it
Oh, was this Professor Rubber? Excuse me
I'm worried about your happiness
It's the first time I've heard such a thing from an intellectual like you
The world is full of crime, sex and eroticism
Is it especially profitable for the teacher? I want this island
Yes, that theory is based on the fact that this person was taken care of in Edo
She is a pickpocket.
She has 29 convictions.
I can't get too excited, it's a problem
I still haven't decided to quit being a police officer
Will it go in? How long will it take?
I guess it'll be about a year
What should I do? What do you think I should do?
I haven't yet decided to quit police.
Why are you quiting?
Hey.
My socks were torn.
Ouch.
Don't disturb me.
I'm sorry.
Haruko also said hello to you
Ah, that person I often meet
Once you see it, you can't forget it. Oh, how sly
Don't wake up the model
I shouldn't have paid that money back.
I wonder if I should ask for it.
Don't you think I should get it from someone like this? It's my right,
but what if I don't have it?
Don't take money from him
Why?
Whatever.
THE END