Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Banka / Elegy (1976)
Papa, Hiromi's ball is gone
Try looking for it one more time.
If you can't find it, Papa will help you
Yes.
It hurts.
It appears she was injured.
Does it hurt?
I really want you to do something about it
It's your beloved dog, right?
He has never bitten anyone
I've never been bitten either
I love dogs.
Is that so?
Do you like dogs?
Then I'll give you that dog's sibling
As a token of apology
Hiromi's house is just over there
Are you coming?
Then I'll go to pick him up sometime
Well then, let's go
Where is Hiromi's house?
Over there!
I am Katsuragi.
See you.
Alright, let's pack a bit more into the wall behind number 2 and swing!
It's a seagull, but not just any seagull
Mosupage's guitar sauce is really good
At least if we had a little more budget...
If you look up, there's no end to it
We create the best stage
even with the minimum budget
Isn't it up to our talents?
Mikio
Are the taxidermy props ready?
Ah, I'm supposed to go
pick it up on Wednesday
It's a museum, right? I want to go too
Don't say silly things
You have a poster starting today,right?
There's no ticket seller
Hey.
Can you give me a little time later?
I'll go sell the tickets.
Okay.
What are you thinking?
Why are you silent?
Can't you say it?
Um, is Mr Katsuragi here?
He is not here
aunt's here,
but please wait a moment
Akiko aunt.
What happened?
Someone is visiting you.
You haven't even had breakfast
Did you used to paint signs?
I went to buy some band-aids to put in Tome-san's mouth
If you think I am old and look down on others, what would his wife say if she were alive?
Tome-san.
Dad says he wants to talk
He seems to be doing well financially.
Huh? Oh, Reiko?
what?
Sit down.
I was thinking of talking yesterday, but
Actually, Dad's company has been struggling with cash flow,
so we decided to sell the mountain
With that money, we're going to renovate the factory
I was thinking of setting up a new office
Why don't you do it your way, Dad?
But if we do that,
there won't be anything left for you all
Well, if you marry into a good family, I would feel at ease
Why don't you think about yourself instead of me?
You're still young, so why not get a wife?
Don't be silly
Oh right
I'll make you some clothes
What do you think?
Is there anything that pleases you?
They are all lovely, but I don't think they suit me
You  can't always wear things like this
You're at the right age, so you should make something too
Then let's make it with georgette
I want to stand on the street corner like a prostitute in a purple georgette dress
Reiko, stop messing around
Then I don't need that
Don't worry, I'll definitely order a georgette
that will make you look like a wonderful prostitute
Reiko, it's the building
across from the new office this time
I'm looking forward to your next performance.
As expected from our chairman, you really know
I've heard about it from Rei-chan
What?
About an arranged marriage?
Did you have another arranged marriage?
Yeah
I was said by my Dad yesterday
Who is the partner this time?
A middle-aged man with children
Really? Then I can't fall behind either,
but you know... his wife committed suicide...
If you don't get married soon, there won't be anyone left to marry you.
You have someone you like, right?
Yeah
16 people?
What?
This is the number of members in our theater troupe.
Oh.
Were you still awake?
you really need to go to bed now.
Come here
Good night.
Sleep well
You should go to bed too.
Excuse me.
Who?
Hello?
I remember you.
What can I do for you?
Please come in
Please
Welcome back.
Is your wound okay now?
I actually like getting hurt
because scars leave memories, don't they?
we made a promise to give you a dog, didn't we?
I came here because I have a favor to ask
Please
Call me Hyodo Reiko
I was hoping you could buy our ticket for the play
A play? Are you an actress?
No, I'm working behind the scenes
Oh, well, I guess I could buy tickets
That's enough, I'll stop the hard sell
In that case, how about I promote the restaurant downstairs instead of the ticket?
It's delicious
I really love pineapple juice
I've seen you before.
Oh, where?
Do you ride that car every day?
That car?
Well,not every day, but when I go to the site
Thank you for waiting
When we were young,
I want to travel around the world
in a car like that
It has been my dream to see the Silk Road,
the Inca, and the Mayan temples
Please.
So, was it also a dream for you
to build your own house?
Is Hiromi-chan okay?
You remember well,
She's doing fine
How about Hiromi-chan's mom?
Excuse me.
Can I come visit your office?
I won't disturb your work,
so that's fine
Come anytime
It feels like I'm not myself
Of course, it's your first dress
Well, it's about whether you want to show it to others or not
Which one?
I want to show off
Really? I'm glad
How about this
for the sleeves?
I've been through quite a lot
Isn't it better not to?
I see.
Have you known him for a long time?
I've always been in his care, you know
Did you get money from him?
Not yet. Payment can be made later.
No, you have to get it quickly
His company is doing poorly in terms of sales.
You're really good.
Well, that would be a problem
If you come near my house,
I couldn't help but wait because you wouldn't contact me, would you?
I'm sorry, but I don't want it to be known until I talk to my husband, so he doesn't know
Doesn't he know?
With that kind of outfit,
you truly look like a happy housewife
I'm not happy at all.
I can tell that your husband becomes cold when he's nearby
He have to go on
another business trip?
Don't say it like that.
There are times when I want to
see you too.
Kazuya! Wait!
Mikiyo!
The store will be closing.
Hey.
You're always late!
then, I'll borrow this
They say there are no seagulls, so I'll use a black-tailed gull instead
(Great White Swan)
Wow,Great White Swan
a swan swimming unnoticed in the pure white snow,
what would that be like,
Mikio?
Would you be interested in writing a script with the theme of a dead swan?
I think dead swans are more beautiful than living swans.
Is that so?
It makes me feel at
ease, doesn't it
Let's go.
Hurry up
Come here
Hi, please come in
I have to excuse myself for a bit because of work
Director. Well then, I'll be off
Hold on.
Hello?
What do you think? Isn't it amazing?
This is awesome.
I'm so jealous of the queen who gets to live in such a wonderful building
I'm not really a fan of modern architecture
I see.
but modern architecture made of iron and
cement must also be beautiful in reality
At the same time, it's important for us architects to build homes where people can live happily
You designed your own house, didn't you, Katsuragi-san?
So it's a house where you can live joyfully?
You, Katsuragi-san, Hiromi-chan, and your wife are living happily together, right?
And there's one more person, niece
That's not what I'm asking! I'm asking whether it's fun or not.
Isn't it fun?
I wonder who thought of turning cotton into snow at home
This morning, when it arrived from the mountain,
It was snowing, right?
Master, this is the third time
I decorated Daphne's Christmas tree,
welcome
Two coffee please.
How long do I have to avoid people's eyes like this
That's why I said it many times
I want you to continue living in Tokyo, anyway
If I go back to Tokyo, will that be the end?
I mean
but if a man is doing this during the most important time of his life,
you will end up failing
What do you mean?
Until I met you,
I thought studying was important
and I intended to continue my research
But I realized that life is not just about it
The fact that you are someone else's wife is not a problem for me
It all depends on how you feel
I never imagined it would turn out like this when I was
asked for directions in front of the station back then
I definetely....
Thank you very much for waiting
Thank you very much
Thank you for your work.
But you know, it can be frustrating to prepare for it
It takes six months to prepare, but the event in the park is only over in two days
I want to travel.
Hey.
why didn't you go with everyone?
You too
Because it's boring, you know?
I feel same way.
Look at this.
Mr. Katsuragi
Oh you.
Excuse me.
Just for a minute, please
It's been a long time since I last saw you.
She was secretly peeking into my office
Is that so?
You thought it was rare to see a female thief, huh?
Do you want something to drink?
No.
you going to get scolded at home
for drinking this late?
My friend is waiting
Well then
do you have a pen?
Then
Actually, thank you for the advice
But more than that, I think
it would be better for you to return to your comfortable home
Your wife probably isn't feeling lonely, though
I'm a thief who has taken a look at your life
Excuse me
Have you decided to go home?
When did you peek into my life?
What are you planning by coming to my office?
It's because I want to see
pictures of the building
I thought so too
Just leave it at that
Bad curiosity can lead to injury
Why do I have bad taste?
I kindly taught you, didn't I?
Please don't tease me.
I'll teach you one more thing
You are a man whose wife has been seduced.
You get it?
Are you angry? Let me say it again
Go home.
Are you scared to go home alone?
Those who are out were surprised,
If weure going to do something,
Gauguin will have the master do it
Rei-chan is late.
We are preparing the cake.
She might be at home.
I thought you shouldn't be here.
Then go home
I... I actually came to apologize,
even though you hate me, right?
I was thinking of taking you out tonight
Me?
If you don't come here,
I'll search all over the city
Seriously?
Are you coming?
Are we in a relationship?
What should I tell Dad when I get home?
I can't just brush it off since Dad is a total loser
What on earth were you thinking
bringing me here?
It's probably Akiko's fault, isn't it?
Did you just bring me out?
If this is a game,
then it's a nihilist's game
Do you understand why I followed you?
Reiko
You don't think about me at all
You say you don't think about me
Don't say things like that
Just think of me tonight.
Please.
It's not a big deal,
Aren't you surprised?
Most things
Don't feel sorry for me.
I don't.
Do you know about baku?
It eats dreams, right?
What are your dreams like?
When I was little,
I wanted to be a pianist
Before my hands got worse, you know?
But now I want to be your mistress
mistress?
You have a lot of boyfriends, right?
You were at the bar together the other day
Mikio is my childhood friend,
and everyone in the theater company is like a boyfriend to me
Dad is arranging a marriage meeting,
You're busy
So come to the office again
I'm always there in the evenings.
Oh I was quite worried
I was wondering what to do until I received a message
If you're staying overnight, you'll need permission.
You will be getting married soon with someone.
What kind of person ?
Do I have to say it?
If you don't want to say it, that's fine
You're at that age too
Just make sure to draw the line.
This was something someone asked me to do.
What?
This looks like the real.
Who gave me something like this?
You also know the person
From Iris's Madam?
Dad is always popular and keeps going around and around
These days, Rei-chan hasn't shown her face
What are you thinking about?
It's about you
You're kidding.
Even when I'm holding you,
you're always thinking about something else
What will happen to us?
Do you think it's okay to break up with me?
But I will never break up.
You're lookingun happier
than when we first met
Why is that?
Is it because you think
I can't make you happy?
Hello, please wait a moment
It's a phone call
It's the person who called yesterday when you were out
I believe he's Mr. Katsuragi
You're not sick, right?
Why aren't you coming?
I was worried
What are you doing now?
Right now?
I am on the phone
Are you going to Sapporo?
Two months?
It's good.
There's only one week left until departure
Yeah, but I want to talk to you about it first
Go to the office, huh?
Then where should I go?
I can't say anywhere; I have nothing to talk about
Daddy,you are not coming home forever?
While I'm at work, you need to behave, okay?
Is it really alright for you to have so few?
I'll buy what I need there.
It's like going back home to Sapporo
There shouldn't be anything inconvenient.
I'm home
Welcome back
Are you okay with the study?
Don't worry,
I can study better without you around
Come on
You
I will also be going to Sapporo soon
I haven't been in touch with your father and mother either
No, you don't have to worry
Hiromi is here
so you don't have to come
I went to see the swans at Furenko during the New Year
Was it beautiful?
It was wonderful
I was really moved
I did a lot of sketches too
I have a favor to ask,
could you be a model for me?
Sure
But I want to do it nude
What time is it now?
It's just before 3 o'clock.
What's up?
You've been worrying about the time
for a while now
Master
You've got some alcohol, right?
There's whiskey,
but are you really going to drink it?
You look pale
It's because I'm sleep-deprived
I'll feel better if I drink.
Welcome!
Sorry to keep you waiting
This is an announcement from Towa Domestic Airlines
When boarding, please check your boarding pass and seat light...
it has started to rain
I wonder if I should drink more alcohol.
Welcome
Sorry to keep you waiting
Mikio?
I want to see a swan
Furenko?
Is it impossible with my legs?
that's impossible
I want to see the swan die
Try shooting with the old Lancaster
Hey.
Didn't you say you needed a model?
Isn't that person better than me?
I wonder if a woman looks that beautiful when she's betraying her husband
Hey, let's get going soon.
Isn't it still okay?
From tonight, I guess you don't have to worry so much
I can't do that, considering Tomoko-chan is here
Thank you very much
I'll go and give her
You left this.
Thank you for bringing back the item
My name is Reiko
I’m your fan
Because you are beautiful.
My friend said
He wants you to be a model for his painting
Is that okay?
Will you come to that shop again?
We're really looking forward to it
Well then, I came by eventually
Promise me.
You're heading home now?
You're still late as usual
But today is actually early for me.
I have something to talk about
Are you going to make me some clothes again?
No
I met the person you like
I got a call from Katsuragi yesterday. he said they want to see me
What did you talk about?
He said he wouldn't be able to see you before he went to Sapporo.
I got this from him.
Did you have a fight with him?
You were with him on Christmas Eve, weren't you?
Did Katsuragi-san talk about it?
Even without saying anything,
Dad somehow understood
I thought it might be rude,
but since you didn't come,
I'll leave it with your father
Two months isn't a long time
Please have good dreams and stay healthy
What kind of person is he?
What do you think?
He doesn't seem like an unserious person;
I've heard he has a good reputation in the company
Did you look into it?
we're in the same building,
so it's natural to hear about it
It seems that he's such a skilled engineer that it's a waste to leave him in a rural area like this
I've heard that even the
headquarters in Tokyo wants him
Dad!
No matter how great an engineer he is
That person has a wife and children, you know?
It's not like Dad would be unaware of that!
So, it's strange, and I'm worried about you
Dad.
You only need to worry about Aunt Iris, okay?
Did that lady really agree to be a model?
That's why she drew the map for us
Yeah, isn't this the place? Look,
it says Katsuragi
Hello,
welcome!
I came right away
I'll take you up on your offer
Welcome
my name is Mikio Kusada
Excuse me for intruding
Come in
Hello
Please, make yourself at home
It must have been cold, right?
I'll make some tea now
Oh
This is a nice room
So, what does Katsuragi do?
It's certain that it's not proleterian art
That's strange
That wife
I can't understand why she would come like that
She's a brave madam
Maybe
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Please
How about starting, Mikio?
Is it okay now?
Huh? Already?
I shouldn't be moving, right?
No, it's fine
Please feel free to do what you like
Excuse me.
but could you let your hair down?
Hair? Yes
Hiromi-chan
Please bring the book of mom's and the mirror over there
Yes.
Here you go
Thank you
Oh dear, wait a moment, your mouth
Is that your husband's room next door?
Yes.
Can I go see it?
Rei.
I don't mind
Please take a look.
Is a swan a big bird?
Yes, they come from Siberia
They are particularly large, but yes,
they are about the size of a human body
Your husband is quite the scholar, isn't he?
There were a lot of books that looked difficult.
Is he working as an architect
Is Furenko far away?
It's not good that Mikyo left me behind
It's scary to go to places like that,
but you can only see them during the winter
I'm thinking of going again
If the lake and the birds were white,
it would be beautiful, wouldn't it?
Would you like to go with your partner, who you were with at Danne?
It would be beautiful if I could float you as swans on the lake
I get so entranced that I want to catch you
but I'll run away
If you run away, I'll kill you
Are you going to Lake Furen again?
If it's convenient for Tomura,
Reiko
Don't be too mean to that lady
I'm not being mean at all
I'm getting along just fine
I see, I had a feeling about that.
Since when have you been on her side?
Think whatever you want.
Are you planning to home?
It's not a good idea to go during the daytime.
Who are you?
Well...
Are you a student?
On a leave of absence
Where is the school?
Are you investigating my identity?
My school is, you know
a devil's school
Did you learn the kind of words that told me?
I learned the opposite of that.
Welcome.
How far are you going to follow me?
What do you mean?
Two coffees
Hurry back
Let me hear the story,
welcome
What are your intentions when you meet with Akiko?
It's because I like her
Then why did you say that to me?
I don't want to capture you, Akiko
What is your purpose?
Until you tell the truth
I'm not going back,
and I'm not letting you go
So, if I say it, will you believe me?
I actually like hearing about you from your wife.
so stop saying ridiculous things
It's not a joke.
It's true, I really think I'm starting to like you
I am suffering.
Give me some water.
What happened? Reiko-san?
I drank a lot
I'm sorry
Akiko
Are you alright?
I'm sorry, I have to go home
It's too lare.
I'll take you home tomorrow morning since it's so late now
Take a rest
Did your partner come today?
No, he didn't
I ended up seducing him
Your lover.
I didn't want to lose you.
Are you alright?
I'm really sorry
I apologize
I'm sorry for taking her stay over
I appreciate your actions.
May I ask who are you?
My name is Katsuragi.
Katsuragi?
Are you alright?
I'm off
Thank you very much.
Take care.
Why did such a refined woman become your friend?
She's quite the curious one
A cute girl who came to visit you
while you're sleeping?
I wonder who.
Well, you've certainly developed quite an appetite
But if you don't get enough sleep,
You'll end up being sick back again, you know
It's okay, it's just the sickness of love
If her appetite gets any bigger, I won't be able to handle it
You are stingy.
we're both in the way,
thank you for your patronage♪
Reiko,Are you alright?
Thank you for your help during that time
Oh, are you going somewhere?
I came to ask you for a favor
Can you lend me some money?
You're going to drink?
I am going on a trip.
Do you understand how I feel?
if I don't let these feelings out on a journey, I might go crazy.
I wonder if you'll be okay
I'm okay now, I'll control my appetite.
Thank you, Hiromi-chan
I will buy you a souvenir.
What do you want?
A doll
A doll?
Oh, that's great,
I will buy you a souvenir too.
Don't worry about that.
Just take your time and enjoy yourself
Welcome.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You look pale.
Because of the night train
Did you get your parents' permission?
You came without his permission, didn't you?
That's why I can't let my guard down.
If I tell them that, I won't be able to come.
You always push yourself too hard.
Welcome.
We'd like a coffee and a pineapple juice, please.
Were you well-behaved while I was away?
Are you just dating me for fun?
The reason you still haven't talked to your husband?
we can't be happy together
Are you really going to pretend nothing
happened and live with your husband?
you know Reiko,, right?
She is trying to seduce you.
Don't say bullshit.
You deserve a girl like that
Don't change the subject.
Mom
I'm going home. That's for the best, right?
Were you thinking about me?
Yeah,
As much as I think about you?
More
Is there any change in your body?
Would it be a problem if there was?
Yeah
What about you?
I want to stay as I am now
I want to live with Akiko and Hiromi
just as we are,
I want to stay as your mistress
Promise me to leave me as I am
Do you have someone else you like?
Why?
Because ever since you came here,
you've been saying
you want me to be my mistress
I wouldn't say something like that
Do you want to be held captive by me?
I want
You are a strange child
Then let's meet at two-thirty.
I want to take you somewhere.
Well then.
The architect Wagner said that architecture
is purpose, which is structure, which is death
If I had the time and money,
I would want to build my favorite buildings
in my favorite places.
Haha, talking to you makes me want to talk about dreams all the time
I prefer the way Katsuragi-san talks like that
Do you enjoy the cigarettes you smoke?
Katuragi-san
You are stupid.
I feel sorry for you
Why?
I have children
I never said I was going to get married.
I made it in time
I had a great time.
I'll be back by this time next week
Take care until then, okay?
Papa
Souvenirs
When Katsuragi-san get back,
make sure to apologize to Katsurai-san
Stop talking about that
I got a letter from that person
He apologized for you
running off to Sapporo
I understands that
you went off on your own
Oh, and when he come back,
He wants to see me
So, are you meeting?
I'm too embarrassed to want to meet
Last time, his wife came to apologize,
so what are you really thinking?
Dad, make sure to pay back the money to Tanioka
Isn't it okay for you to do at least that much?
I'm acknowledging your relationship with that lady too
I intend to clarify things with that person eventually
I see.
Congratulations, Dad!
Thank you!
Hello?
Is that Reiko-chan?
When did you come back?
A week ago
I was sick and in bed
It's because you're pushing yourself too hard.
Come in.
Did you wet the bed?
This is a souvenir for Hiromi-chan
Thank you very much
I'm glad to hear that
Here, this is for Akiko-san.
Can I have one too?
How is it? Do you like it?
Is it okay if I take it?
Akiko-san has been so helpful to me
Thank you, I will continue to be a bother, but please bear with me
What is Papa's souvenir?
what could Papa's souvenir be?
My husband will be coming home this evening
Oh really?
I wonder what Akikosan's husband is like
He's kind, quiet, and serious?
Well, I wonder about that
You don't like him?
Mom,This has come off.
Akiko, which one do you like?
then take this and go play over there
Which do you like better, your husband or your boyfriend?
I'm sorry for saying something strange.
but if you're with someone like me,
your husband will scold you
That's not true
Shall we have dinner together tonight?
I'm sorry
I don't care.
I prefer that.
I think I should go home after all
Don't say like that again
I should have dressed up too
You're young and beautiful just as you are
I don't want to be disliked by your husband.
Oh, it's Dad!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Dad
Hiromi, have you been behaving?
Welcome home
Where are my souvenirs?
Here are they
Dad!
Hurry up
Reiko-chan, Dad is here
This is Reiko-san
whom I talked about earlier
He is my husband.
Well then, I'll go make some tea
You understand, right?
Of course I'm your mistress.
You let words get in your eyes
Stay down.
kiss me!
Hurry up,
Stay down.
Reiko-chan
This is a souvenir my father gave me.
Don't you think this is cute?
See, did you like it?
I'm going home
Oh?
He hated me.
I will never come back again.
That's not true.
I'll drive you home.
No.
I searched for you all over town.
I'm worried if I don't take you home
Aren't you angry?
It's not like getting angry will change anything
You must have been in pain too
I should have discussed this with you before I went to Sapporo.
Why would you say something like that?
You shouldn't be traveling after being sick
Did Akiko say that?
No,Hiromi said that
She says anything, you know
So that's how you found out about that person's affair?
Just stop it
You have quite the pride
You seem to think that jealousy is related to your pride.
I'm just being foolish
we're both the same
Shall I tell you why I fell in love with you?
It's because you're foolish.
I wanted to touch your wounds
Having scars is quite an appeal
Is that why you say that,
because of your arm?
That's just my hobby.
I will not see you again.
Goodbye
I can't stay in a place like this any longer.
No...
What's wrong,sis?
It feels kind of strange when someone who’s usually not home is actually there.
I'm happy that you're worried about me
I heard Dad is getting married
What do you think?
Hey, don't worry about unnecessary things
You should be worried about your own exam studies
I know
You have a visitor.
Mr. Katsuragi's wife.
Please come in.
Hello
Welcome., what happened?
I've been worried because you haven't come to my house since that time.
Please have a seat.
It smells really nice.
Are you worried about my husband?
Hiromi, stay down.
Katsuragi must have been tired that night too, surely
Please come and play again like before.
No.
She's just being selfish.
Well, even though your husband has called many times
She pretended not to be home.
Have a tea
Thank you so much.
Do you remember?
This was given to you by your husband.
Akiko!
I'll tell you, I even went to see him to Sapporo
and I went to Lake Romanes.
■It's a familiar place for you.
Katsuragi is a good person.
I...
Of course.
You betrayed him.
Reiko
Are you happy?
That's not good
You need to take care of yourself.
What's wrong?
You look pale; I can't sleep
Hey, Miki, stop talking like that! You shouldn't be so high and mighty.
I can't.
If you don't sell it to me, I'll just steal it.
You should not take this medication regularly.
I just want to sleep.
I'm going back to Tokyo.
I will never see you again
That's all.
I will always.....
Please make Reiko happy forever.
Hello, Mikio?
Yeah, that's fine
Are you at Daphna?
Okay, I'll be there right away
How is it? You
Finally you finished it
Huh? I'm going to go
Once this exhibition of the work is over,
It seems that Akiko...
It's near Cape Nozuke.
Let me go too.
I apologize for intruding,
but are you Katsuragi-san?
Yes.
Reiko!
Please be careful
Are you a member of her family?
Yes,
Thank you for coming.
Good bye.
THE END