Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Boryoku / Violence (1952)
Where are we heading out?
Come over
Was she dead?
So, which woman?
She was at the Kotobuki tea house,right?
it's at Yamada's place, right?
I'm sorry, but could you go call them for us?
Alright
I'm going to head over there.
Thank you.
It appears Hatsuko committed suicide by jumping in front of a train.
Really? She was dead?
She is idiot
Can you go there?
I'm going
What a fool.
Who is Hatsuko?
She's the girl who came
to play with us for a bit
Oh I see.
Prepare a bath for me.
What's going on?
She is.
You should hold a funeral for her.
What?
What are you talking about?
Well then! If we're going to have a funeral in this recession,
We can't afford it!
Why on earth would she wanted to die?
It seems that a woman
committed suicide around that area
This railway is the Kansai Line, running straight from Osaka to Nagoya
If you go this way, Kamagasaki, famous for the Tobita
brothel district, is over there in that slum area
The other side of the road is the new world, let's go check it out
Hinode street is over there.
Is this helpful?
Yes a lot.
Many novels themed around Osaka have been published.
That doesn't capture the real Osaka.
I need you to write good novel.
So, can I write?
In the past,
Without any distinction between night and day, This
road used to be where night women sold their services,
but now everyone is just holed up inside
They use elderly solicitors to run their business.
What a lot of people..
What on earth are these people doing?
They  not doing anything; they are just walking, trying to do something
In this town, you can live for a day
with just 50 yen
Humans generally live like this
Well, you can eat nutritious food for just 9 or 20 yen
This is not because merchants are not making a profit, but simply because if the price is too high, it won't sell
Where in Japan is there a town like this?
Is that why so many people are gathering here?
The people who come to this town are all those who have strayed from normal civic life
Everyone here is a person with a shadow
A habitual thief, a man who came straight from prison for shoplifting,burglary
What are they going to discuss?
They are whispering and talking all day long
There is some profit that we can't even imagine
Their socializing is gambling; people who are tired of working are risking their lives in a desperate game of give and take
Everything, including Go and shogi, is gambling
The lazy time of humans who have lost their will to live is being actively marked
There is a police station at the entrance of this alley
However, I don't know how many criminals are here and what they are up to
People spilling out from Hinode
Yokocho flow into this area
The cinema, female sword fighting, and strip shows are all part of the theater district
And then the backside of that town is Tennoji Park
There is a beautiful lawn and an art museum
This place is a paradise for vagrants.
At night, it also becomes a hotel for prostitutes
The minimum living conditions give rise to minimum prices
You can also get a fresh haircut for just 10 or 20 yen
All of these people are those who do not pay taxes
They are fragments of a broken Japanese family, individuals who hold neither rights nor obligations as citizens
So, while this is indeed part of the map of Japan,
It's a city that has been built by people who do not have a direct connection to the country, yet are indirectly linked to Japan
Oh? There goes the only daughter walking over there, right?
I don't know what she's doing,
but she's quite well-known around here
Let's call her over for a moment
Taka-chan?
What's wrong with the photo?
She's not going to take a picture of your face
Come on, teacher, let's go over there
You're probably going to put this in the Castry newspaper again, huh?
Hey, you damn it!
Get out from here
You bastard!
Just bring it
Oh my god.
Take him away there
It can't be helped.
Please give me your hands.
oh, are you feeling unwell?
It's okay
It's often happening like this, let's go
Why? Was that all?
I guess I should just go to Shikoku,
but I can't help but to go
Oh yeah
This is News paper from Tokyo.
I wonder what happened
What are you going to do?
What's wrong?
The future is headed towards the shores of despair
Is life like a withered tree....
Hey man.
Open your mouth
I feel like I'm traveling to a place where emotions can be exchanged
What is he doing?
He is a poet.
Wow, what a strange guy.
The future is headed towards the shores of despair
Is life like a withered tree....
Here, connected to the Valley of Seki-Ryo,
the future greets the shores of despair
Is life like a withered tree....
Racing across the wilderness
This is a triple feature of film, women's swordplay, and striptease, featuring the number one in the strip work
Feel people's indignation
I can't wait anymore!
Hi.
There are three shows: movies, women's theater, and striptease.
Lily Akebono, making her debut performance here
No customer turnover
Please take a look quickly, everyone!
Hey man
Hey
What are you doing?
I need to money back
I get it.
Isn't this different?
You are a bit sleepy
You're just making a profit,
but come on, get them.
Come over here
What's wrong?
Well...
Can't we do something about that Take-chan?
You are stupid.
I won't let her be forced into prostitution.
It's all about the money
How much you pay?
Well, have a seat.
Considering the market conditions
I'll continue my business.
Talk to me later
There are three shows: movies, women's theater, and striptease.
Lily Akebono, making her debut performance here
Please, everyone, take a look as soon as possible
Yo-chan
What's going on?
I'm gaining money
What was that? Is it just this?
If you're unhappy, quit this job.
Sorry
Please take care of here tonight
You can't take a off
I can't do this anymore.
It's so hot
Ah, it is 106 yen, right?
Here is it
Take it
Madam, How's your business?
I have no idea
Hey wake up
It is yen, right?
Here is 80 yen
Thanks.
I will pay you
Alright, 160 yen
Thank you for your work.
Osetsu
Can you lend me a few?
People are watching,you know
Please don't say things like that
It doesn't matter how much
I haven't eaten anything from the site
It can't be helped.
How long are you going to keep this madness going?
I wish you'd hurry up and go somewhere
Hey, how much?
It's 10 yen
This is only 10 yen
This fee is 20 yen
Please discount
I can't.
You are stingy
Please, everyone, make sure to watch
it soon
Um, where is this house?
Over there
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Is this Kotobuki-ya?
Yes, Sister!
We have a customer.
What can I do for you?
I'm Nakata Hatsuko's mother
Nakata Hatsuko?
I have no idea.
I heard she was being looked after here.
I was invited to come here
Nakata Hatsuko?
Oh that Hacchan?
Just wait a minute
That dead Hacchan's mother came to the entrance,
What did she say?
I have no idea.
Get her out
You say to her
It can't be helped.
Are you Nakata Hatsuko's mother?
Yes.
We are in a lot of trouble because she died.
She hasn't paid the 500 yen rent for the room yet.
I'm sorry she caused you trouble.
I don't know what she was doing
She didn't contact me at all.
I was very worried about her
I heard the news that she had died from police
She committed suicide on the railway
I can't believe she did that
She should have come back home
I feel sorry for her.
She worked hard since she was a child.
She did well in school and was well-liked in her neighborhood.
What are you going to do?
I heard that she was taken care of here
Well, I thought I should at least say thank you
Ah, I see
Well, thank you
I'm sorry to have disturbed you.
Who's her?
Hatsuko's mother
Hey, take a rest
Grandma!
I didn't know you were here
I searched for you
I had a little meal.
This is also from Hacchan,
Thank you very much
Let me check this out
It will make a good souvenir
I'll show it to the people in our house.
I don't know how Hacchan felt, but it must have been tough
She didn't contact me at all.
so please listen
On the night of last year's festival, She was attacked from the neighborhood's foolish son
If only he would keep quiet,
but instead, he's bragging all over the place
It's so embarrassing that she can't even stay in the village anymore
She came out from the village
but I wonder how she felt and dead
how far you will go home?
To Fukuyama
I think you should go home soon.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to have disturbed you.
Grandma, do you understand that you're getting on the train?
Yes.
These women are all women of the night
Street women are no longer the star of the era, but
On the contrary, the number of people keeps increasing
Isn't there more than passerby?
They look just like an ordinary girls
It's so much that I
can't even tell them apart
Yeah.
After all, during the day, they goes to work
There are quite a few people who do this at night, you know?
Now it's becoming a profession
There are quite a few who are working in cabarets and cafes
If they work in a store, they have an excuse to the police.
But they will be charged a percentage for that
That's true
They have to pay a referral fee
and it may seem easygoing, but this isn't easy either
That's right
there are quite a few
people here
It's really tough
People come here on business from all sorts of places
They've come a long way from the new world we saw during the day
Even such a young girl?
No,that's just a furniture store's promoter
She doesn't have a handbag,
So I can tell the difference.
What should we do?
Anyway, let's stay somewhere, I'm exhausted
Good evening
We going somewhere?
Are you alone?
Yes.
Here
why?
Are we going back again?
But wow, this is amazing
Please go ahead
Welcome.
Good evening, the second floor is open
Where is the room?
Matsuno room
Alright, Let's go
Please come in
Are you going home already?
How much?
Thank you very much.
Yeah, it's so hot
What are you doing in a place like that?
Come in.
Please make yourself at home
Are we going to sleep together
in this room?
Is that okay?
You're really close, right?
I'll bring a watermelon
Seriously?
Excuse me.
She's terrible
You get it?
They stay here
Did you get money from them?
Not yet, huh?
Is it okay if you bring two beers for them?
Okay?
Welcome back!
I'm home.
Good evening.
Welcome
Shin-chan, Just stop it
Do you think this would suit you?
This look good
Wow, you did a great job
I see
You're quite skilled, aren't you
Takako? It seems like she has
something to say to you
You should notice that this guy.
I know.
Is that so? I hope you understand
Come on
why don't you eat something?
Reach!
Good evening.
thanks for your hard work
It's Matsuyama on the second floor
I see
We offer you a cheap service today
3,500 yen
Yes, 3500 yen
Thank you very much.
We'll bring you the beer
Ah, over here, over here
Please make yourself at home..
Good evening
what are you all doing?
Excuse me.
Where did that woman from earlier go?
That woman from earlier?
Taka-chan?
She is the daughter of this house.
Damn it.
Osetsu
I'm going soon
Hurry up
Bring me a drink
When I get tired, my shoulders get stiff.
Rub my shoulders
What's wrong?
Something went wrong
There seems to be a problem
What's wrong?
It seems there's a problem
It can't be helped.
Are they saying women are different?
No, Taka-chan is just too beautiful
You guys deceived us
What's the hell?
Do you know this place?
You complain and we hit you.
Hey! What do you think?
Come back after you think it over!
Why are you messing around?
What's wrong?
You guys should just come out quietly.
Put on your shoes and get moving!
You should be careful in this area
okay?
What about the money?
Are you not giving refunds?
What did you say?
I paid three thousand yen!
You bring your face
Here how it works
Welcome.
Two coffees please
Iced one
You guys
can we hang out for a bit?
What?
You're treating me to coffee, right?
Come on, let's play!
Come on.
Bros
Shut up.
We've had a rough time, haven't we?
Just hanging around wasn't good
Are we going on tonight's ship?
We can't.
I am very frustrated
I want revenge on them
They are just prostitution.
Don't be so angry
Well, if that's the case, then you'll go alone
Please take your time
and have a little rest
Take-chan
Let's have a rest
Why? I don't want to sleep at all.
Come here for a moment
This place is better.
Well, I can at least take care of Shi-chan, you, and Mom
You also run this inn with your mother's money.
She is your benefactor
you really should forget the past
You can talk bad about people who don't get along with your parents,
Do you have a tendency to speak ill of others?
Me?
Don't get me wrong.
I would like to be able to live with you and your ex-husband's Sukezo.
So what do you want?
Do you want me to be your mistress?
I really don't want to do that
Well then, I want to be friends with you.
You are stupid.
Why are all men so dirty?
I'm off
Hold on.
Please listen to me
Have a seat
Do you force me?
Don't say like that.
You're trying to deceive me with Yamada.
I don't need this
Don't be mad
That's not what I intended.
How much will you give me?
I'll give you as much as you want
but the treatment is expensive
Tell me
1 million yen.
Seriously?
Hey come on
No.
Stop it!
You shouldn't act so foolishly
Hey, Taka-chan
You are not going to go home
until you listen to what I say
Excuse me.
What?
Hey, someone who wants to meet you
I get it.
Thank you very much.
Who?
Are you alright?
Just wait a moment
My sister came to pick me up,
so I’ll be leaving
I know
You were supposed to have a proper meeting, right?
Well, either way, Goodbye
Damn it.
She has gone
I get it, let's call someone else
Hurry up
Let's have a rest
Are you alright?
Don't worry.
Let’s go.
it's ice candy,
enjoy it!
Thank you very much.
Eat without getting your clothes dirty.
it's delicious,
but how much does it cost?
This is delicious!
Is there still　some left?
Do you eat that too?
I'm eating that too
I wanted my mother to eat this.
What did you need, sister? Huh?
It's nothing really.
Is it nice weather?
Yes,there are beautiful clouds out
It's a relief to be here, isn't it
Shi-chan?
What's wrong?
Why?
It's nothing really.
What is our ex-father doing now?
Oh, Shi-chan, shall we go see movie?
Are you alright?
Don't worry.
They are sliding on the water
What kind of person goes sliding?
they are being pulled by a motorboat
Why don't they sink?
I don't really know
Anyway, they are sliding
They fell
Shut up.
next time it's a mountain,
That's a snowy mountain
it's beautiful!
Please don't be noisy.
Hey
What?
Can't you come over for a bit?
There must be someone all in white, right?
No one is there
I see.
Please take care of this
Don't worry.
Where?
Over there
What's wrong?
Stop doing this anymore
You know?
What's wrong?
He ate and drank without paying
Why did you offer him food?
Why do you say such nonsense?
He said he was hungry
That's normal.
Did you plan to eat and drink without paying from the beginning?
I'm so hungry that I can't do anything about it
If you don't have money, you can't eat.
I know.
Put me in jail
What are you talking about! This
gacha! Stupid!
Please stop.
Don't hit him
Hold on.
Excuse me.
I'll pay his fee
Is he someone you know?
I don't really know
about this, but...
I'll pay his fee,please forgive him
If you do that, I'm okay.
You should be careful in the future
I'm counting on you
Let's go
What's wrong,Dad?
I’m sorry.
Let's go
Where did you go?
Get the bath ready quickly
I'm sorry
Aren't you with Takako?
Why are you alone?
What are you doing?
Hello
Thank you for your work.
I received a call from you earlier
What's wrong?
How is your business?
The world is currently in a recession
Well, actually, I just got a call
If you see someone like this staying at your hotel, please contact us immediately.
What did this person do?
It's a car robbery
I have a hard time remembering young people's faces
Yeah
It can't be helped.
Um, I might have seen this somewhere before
Dad
You go somewhere far away,please.
I don't want to trouble you all,
I want to go somewhere far away, but I can't eat there, so I ended up coming back to this town.
Things were better back in the day
If my arm works,
I can run my clothing store like before.
That's my mother's fault.
Don't say like that.
It can't be helped.
She was conscripted and hasn't returned for eight years.
Don't worry
I'll go somewhere eventually
If it's about you all being happy,
I'll do anything
I can't be happy, you know
Why not?
I feel sorry for Dad too, but...
We don't know what will happen from now on
No matter how much we struggle, it seems like nothing can be done
That's my mother's fault.
we're just getting more and more unhappy.
No matter how much we struggle, we have no strength left
Dad went off
After that, our house burned down, and we just kept sinking deeper and deeper,
even though we hadn't done anything wrong
Why is it like this?
What's wrong?
What?
What do you want?
Just stay with me
for a little while
I'll go anywhere you want
What kind of place is this?
Hey,you really gave me a good time last night
Be careful.
You were dazed.
You are stupid.
You little brat!
Give it back to me
Hey!
This is the payment from the other day
Hey! Thief!
That was good.
I feel so relieved now
Let's have fun
What do you mean?
Things aren't going so well
So what will happen now?
This is getting quite interesting, isn't it?
Have a seat
well, if you're calm like that, it's fine. Soon enough, You will be beaten down
She's scary.
I wanted to see your crying face
Come on, take it
What are you guys doing coming to this town?
You guys are very brave.
People become normal, I guess
This is what happens
You are stupid.
Get out
How much?
It's 8 yen
I see
That's how it is.
When a person
becomes mature, it turns out like this
Come on, drink more, there's plenty to go around
You guys are still young
I feel comfortable with you
I've never seen a woman like you
before.
Don't tease me
I respect you
Drink more
Hey come on
I need to eat first
You are guts less
Stop it....
Shut up!
This place has become lively.
Shall we go?
Hey dude
Bill please
Watch out
You bastard!
Just wait a minute
I'm going again
Is there really someone who would sleep with a person like that?
Let's drink some alcohol and be happy.
Bye!
shall we go?
This area is where I grew up.
My daughter is Soliciting clients for prostitution, my father was a vagrant.
Like that
Oh yeah.
Keep drinking
Stop it
What, you are just brat!
You are stupid.
What?
Hey, I need to drink
Yes, let's drink
You've had quite a bit to drink
Where are you all from?
Tokyo
Where are you headed?
We were thinking of going to Shikoku
What for?
A friend of mine runs a ranch
I'm thinking of going there and becoming a cattle rancher
I see.
I see, the countryside is nice, right?
Yeah, the countryside is great
The sun is bright and the sky is really blue
Besides, I hear that the ranch is in a place where you can see the ocean
Yeah, it sounds like a nice place
I've never seen it before
My classmate run
He said I can come anytime
Right?
Hey, can you take me along too?
Really, you?
Yeah, please
Are you serious?
Yes
If you're really interested,
I might consider it
But....
I want to go with my mom and sister, the three of us.
I want to break out of this town
Just the three of you guys, huh?
But who knows...
I can't tell if
you'll have work or not
I think it's better than here, right?
It doesn't matter, does it? Take us with you
Well, I guess ...
Please.
You're quite a bold woman, huh?
So, where does the ship leave from? Huh?
that's, um...
A ferry departs from Kobe, huh?
Stay at my place tonight
I'm going to consult with my mom, so we'll decide quickly, and we can catch the ferry tomorrow, right?
Let's go
with this, open the back of the second floor
and go in, you know which room it is, right?
Welcome back
I'm home.
Business is bad, huh?
I see, eat dinner.
It's ready.
What a feast this is!
That's not it
For Yamada
Oh...
Where's he?
He's playing Mahjong again
There are bed bugs.
I feel itchy
maybe it's better to just tell the truth, right?
Whatever
But I feel sorry for her
Even though they are doing this business properly,
They won't go to Shikoku
She's insane
You think so?
You may be right
But she was serious
well, we can stay here tonight without money.
Isn't that good enough for us?
While we were talking about the Fake Story about ranch earlier,
I really started to hope that it was true
I wish I had a small friend's ranch
Come on.
Hey cheer up
Well, anyway, let's just go to my place, okay?
My place is a poor place with no fields.
But they're probably discussing it down there right now
That's right, Mom
No matter where we go
It's definitely better than now
I haven't said anything until today,
but that Yamada is using us
He's terrible.
So let's go for it
We can work at the ranch
I think there are other jobs available.
Even if I'm poor, I want to live with a bright mindset
Now, Mom, make up your mind
But...
Well, what do you  think about that Yamada guy?
You  think he's a great husband?
He's a terrible man, isn't he?
If it's for money, he would even sell his daughter
Ex dad is wandering around here like that,
and if we stay here like this, we...
I don't know what will happen
from now on
Shi-chan, what do you think?
I'll do anything like my sister says
Once you enter this town,Everything will be over
We get used to the lowly life of the people here,
and no one can escape
We've been like that too.
if I hadn't met those people over there...
I probably wouldn't have been able to make such a decision
Maybe the god of help has come
So let's go!
By the way, what will ex-Dad do
when we go?
It's fine if he comes with us
Anyway, please make up your mind
I guess I need to make up my mind
How's your business?
Thanks.
Good evening.
Shi-chan
You're doing great job
Hey.
Shall we go to the second floor?
Yeah
We are going out on the second floor
Go ahead
This time it should be okay, right?
Leave it to me.
Don't worry.
I can't count on it
I tell you
Yesterday's expenses were wasted.
My 2000yen?
Don't care.
I'll throw in three beers for you.
It can't be helped.
I need to call her.
Hold on.
Mom, We made up our mind
We don't need any luggage.
Just go as you are
Bring us beer
3 of beers
Takako.
You should come and check.
What are you doing?
Shizuko.
The customer says they'd like to have a beer with you.
Hurry up.
Now put on your glasses
and stand up, stand up
I'll help you
Don't worry.
Take this
You guys have something to do, right?
Work hard
Let's go
Don't worry.
She'll be fine
Watch your step
There is one person to bring along.
This inn has a hot spring mark( means red light).
I wonder what they're going to do
It would be nice
if they at least brought some tea
She said we can stay here for free.
We won't interfere or anything
I'm sure it's a secret from her dad
I sobered up
Drink beer
Seeing Shi-chan like this,
She's quite beautiful too
You should thank him.
He'll take care of you
Thank you very much.
Please give him a drink
Here
It's ok
Take your time
You really need to provide proper service, you know
Hey
Should I just say the truth?
You're surprisingly honest, bro
I'm sorry I have not to treat you guys.
How about we grab a beer?
Yeah, that story seems to be going well
I'll bring the beer right away
Just wait a moment, okay?
Hey, come over here, this way!
Come on, come on, over here!
Well....
How old is Shi-chan now?
I'm 18
Hmm
So, you're 4 years younger than your sister, huh?
Yes.
Your sister is beautiful, but Shi-chan is also a pretty girl
Is that so?
Come on, don't stay so far away
Come a little closer
I’m sorry.
Don't worry.
Come on, don't stay so far away
Excuse me.
Sis
I'll serve you
Okay, I'll have this cup too.
It can't be helped.
It can't be helped?
Don't stare at me
I can't go home
What's wrong with you?
Is there something wrong?
Bros
You are stupid.
What are you doing?
When did you guys sneak in?
Are you Tsutomu Sakamimi and Ryuji Kijima, right?
The photos are properly posted here
Hmm, even if I try to deceive,
It won't work
This how they work
We were arrested
You are stupid.
It hurts me
They are car robbers
You are stupid.
You should have been more careful
Where did they hide their shoes?
I’m sorry.
Hold on.
I met a lot of different people
but you were a good person
Well, I hope you do well from now on
I'm sorry, sis
The whole story about the ranch is a lie.
You shouldn't say that
You guys are really shameless
It's starting to rain
Don't bring in people like them
You know?
Hey! Orusu! Bring some beers.
Yes
The sun is bright
and the sky is blue,
countryside
A large ranch with a view of the sea
Hey! Orusu!
It's time for the husband to come home!
I came back from Karafuto
Can you hear me, Osetsu?
Me, Sukezo
What is he doing?
Get out!
You are the thief who stole my wife.
Stop it....
Don't hit him
Please...Please...
Give me back my wife
What?
Please leave
Give me back my child
I'll give you anything in return.
Get out now!
Let me go
Watch out.
Leave it!
Shi-chan!
Mom.
Shizuko.
Leave her alone
Shi-chan!
I haven't done anything.
You are stupid.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Stay strong.
It hurts
my leg hurts.
Please be patient
I call a doctor.
Your leg may have been broken
It hurts.
It's okay if you don't call a doctor.
Hang in there!
I'm going to play mahjong
It hurts.
Shizuko
Did you get hurt?
Are you still here?
Get out
She's my daughter
What are you talking about?
You are stupid.
What's wrong with meeting my daughter?
Get out
What? You're so persistent!
Kill me, Kill me!
What's the hell?
What should I do?
Stop it....
Don't touch my father!
What?
You are so cheeky! Move!
You are stupid.
Damn it.
You're an idiot!
Takako
No one can stop me
Help me!
She is a murderer
autumn sunset
People come back to life
My life is not now
The layout of the poor house in Aienkuboru is even a bit shabby
The blue flowers have bloomed
It seems that a murder incident occurred around here yesterday
How scary.
She killed her adoptive father,right?
I really have no idea what people do
Please write a novel about the truth of this town.
I will.
THE END