Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Chatterley Fujin wa Nihon Nimo Ita / Lady Chatterley of Japan (1953)
Today I also pass through the gates of marriage
There are probably several young people here
And that gate should lead to the land of happiness,
but due to a slight twist of fate,
There are some who live in falsehood as a couple and die in falsehood as well
Welcome, Miss.
We, too, were like that as a couple
And I am a mother who will soon marry off my daughter.
(Unfinished Girl Statue)
Sakiko!
What are you doing?
Get your hands off of me!
Please get that done quickly
Don't worry.
That painting is ours.
Please take care of the rest.
Let's go.
Have a seat.
You cut your own face, didn't you?
Please give me an excuse
Say something.
I don't want the other people see the painting.
Why?
You know why too, right, Mom?
I felt so sorry for myself in that picture.
I tore up such a filthy picture
why? Why do you say such things?
You really want to make me say it, don't you?
That's cruel
Sakiko.
Shall I say it then?
What did you talk about with Uncle Kazama today,
I heard about it
I completely heard about it
This arrived while you were away.
Please call Sakiko.
Yes.
Please sit there.
I think we need to talk before you get married.
Do you know about this?
These are photos from our wedding
Becoming a soldier's wife
was a dream for girls back then
Your father had a successful career.
He became the battalion commander of the Kanazawa
division a few years after getting married.
This surprise attack was a great success today.
Also,with Mr. Shimada?
He couldn't beat me today.
The liquor is all gone.
Hold on.
When you get even a little distance away, I can't stand.
You're like a baby.
Hey, bring another sake!
Stay up straight
Turn left, and move forward.
Stop
What is it?
I thought I'd drink while looking at the flowers.
That's funny.
I'm feeling good.
Should I sing a song?
Please.
This is a lullaby from Kumamoto.
This is awesome.
You should try singing one too.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Because.
What?
You want to have a baby with me,right?
Oh no, I wonder if this has been noticed
You’re mean.
Well, don't hold back.
just take a sip and try it.
May I?
Bring it here.
Military wives need to learn to drink.
Is that delicious?
Are you alright?
I am very happy.
Really?
Once the training begins, you won't be coming back?
I will be back in about two or three days.
Emperor Taisho visited the Goto family
Wait.
Thank you very much
I'll give this to you.
What's this?
This is said to be a charm given by pregnancy.
I'm sorry for making such an unreasonable request to you.
From that day, a large-scale training began
While waiting for my father's surgery to finish
I have never felt that time was so long in my life
Uncle Kazuma, who was present at this major
surgery, was a military doctor at the time.
Sister, the surgery has progressed
How was it?
There's no danger to life
That's not good to go.
Why?
Calm down, sister, please calm down
The pounding rain continued to fall as if it were stirring my heart
I'm sorry for getting flustered.
I didn't mean to get you so excited
I was sorry for that.
But isn't it true that you can't feel at ease until you see it with your own eyes?
That's understandable.
but in my brother's case, he recovers in a way that doesn't interfere with his military duties
It's better not to meet him now.
Why is that? Please tell me,
I promise I won't make a fuss anymore.
Then please sit there.
I have a secret that only you and my older brother know
Please listen calmly
I also say this as a doctor
Gunpowder got into his body.
and he has lost his qualifications as a husband physically
Stop it! Don't say like that.
Don't say like that.
Why are you telling me such a story?
I don't want to hear it either
But once I start talking,
you have to listen quietly
And that's when our tragedy began
It's so hot today.
You are so sweaty
You need to take off your shirt quickly,
or you'll catch a cold
1.2.3.4.
I'll go to bed.
Here's fine.
Please stay by my side for life.
No matter what happens, I won't leave you.
The clothes aren't dry yet.
I will dry it immediately.
You scared me.
Give me some water,Tomoko.
What are you doing?
Don't you think you don't need this anymore?
You can't sleep?
It's very cool tonight.
Shall I give you a massage?
That's enough already
I get it.
Utsunomiya
Military personnel change jobs frequently
He came to Tokyo again.
Come on.
Oh no.
Madam
He's going fishing again?
Yes, he'd loved it since a long time ago.
Oh, isn't he always with you?
I caught a bit of a cold today.
Hey,what's this?
Hahaha, just one more step and the operation will be complete
Damn it, you're too strong.
This is alcohol, isn't it?
This is for you guys
Thank you very much.
This makes me 100 times more energetic
Come on then
What is that? Oh no!
I knew it would get better after all
Oh no.
Madam,The boss sometimes goes fishing.
On most days, after work, he goes straight home to his wife, yes,
He doesn't eat or drink much outside.
He is a very loving husband
I really have to treat you well.
He always catches small fish.
In the military community,
it's considered shameful to cherish one's wife,
but I think that's outrageous.
Please stop flattering her.
This is not flattery
As a modern soldier, I thought I would take him as a model if I were to get a wife
For that, it's a requirement to have a beautiful wife like her.
You have no prospects.
Shout up.
Come on.
Welcome back.
I didn't notice
It was cold outside?
Who came?
They were Lieutenant Nogami and Lieutenant Shirosawa
Lieutenant Fukami and then Lieutenant Koyama
Everyone is doing great, and it's
been a while since I joined them all.
You went to tie your hair up, didn't you?
I thought it would be rude not to change much
I've never seen you so cheerful for such a long time.
You've never even put on makeup
when it's just the two of us
because...
what's going on?
I've heard you're quite popular
You're a loving wife.
What were you feeling when you asked that?
Hurry up and clean that up
Is the preparation for the drinks ready?
I'm sorry
I'll do that.
Don't get carried away
But didn't you say to everyone that I was feeling lonely and I should come and play?
Everyone was saying that
I truly appreciate your feelings
So...
I'm not asking you to act like a geisha.
But
You are stupid.
Who?
it's me.
I'll get out soon.
No, it's fine.
oh, you untied your hair, huh?
oh, I'm so hungry
You should drink some alcohol first
but it's not good to drink alone.
How about you?
Would you like one?
Thank you
Sorry.
Ah, it's fine, it's fine
I couldn't reach,
so what? If you come over here...
Tomoko, I was wrong earlier.
I apologize.
Don't say like that.
I understand that very well
Here it is.
Have another shot.
Let's make up.
Forgive me....
It makes me sad to hear you say that so much
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Come on, have a drink.
even though you couldn’t drink,you can drink now
Well, that's because I've been accompanying you every night
That's right, you have been working hard to master the art of drinking for my sake,
You've been trying to comfort me in some way
Not at all
You are truly an impeccable wife
I have no right to be husband.
Why do you say such a thing?
I see, this was a promise not to talk.
Sorry.
I've also become stronger with alcohol
That's the power of that grand exercise
You.
Oh right, my bad, my bad
It's good to be drunk tonight, right?
Let's do that, shall we drink and sing a song?
Please.
I will also have some and be set free
Let's do that.
You forgot the promise again, didn't you?
That's right, this song was like that too
Why do you keep saying things like that tonight?
I hope you will still wear makeup even when it's just the two of us
You are gradually losing your feminine emotions
Even with a husband like me, I still want you to be a woman and a beautiful woman.
Tomoko, I ask you, I entrust this to you.
He will soon become a lieutenant general
And he was appointed as the Undersecretary of the Army
and will be living in the official residence
Madam
I am Kyohei Sakai
I just received a call from my husband
I was asked to paint a portrait in celebration of her promotion
Thank you for your hard work, and I appreciate your work.
I will do my best to paint
Grandma, please guide him to the room we just decided on
Please come with me.
By the way, Mr. Sakai will be living at home from now on
Well, this isn't a very good painting, is it?
Is that so? But Takashima really like it, especially
Well, it was painted with a lot of effort
It seems that Takashima really values Mr. Sakai as a person
When it comes to his affection, he truly takes good care of him, doesn't he?
Takashima is someone who doesn't really understand art well
My older brother is trying to distract himself from his loneliness in some way
By the way, how is it going?
What do you mean?
Well, I really think it's great to meet you
I wonder why
Having stood in dangerous places as a woman for a long time
and it doesn't show at all
You don't forget about that.
At your age, it's not something you can easily forget
But you are being pushed to a place you must not forget
You're holding back your youth.
Well, you see, I can say this bluntly
because I am a doctor.
Sister, you have never consulted me
Kazuma.
Please go home if you wanna talk about that.
I can't tolerate such an insult to Takashima
I said something trivial
I apologize
I'm off to draw
Take care.
Is that Sakai-kun?
Eventually,Sakai-san's paintings started to
be selected for exhibitions multiple times
It seems that guy's reputation in society has improved quite a bit.
Hey, why don't you try to make him to draw a portrait of you?
I don't have to
We can hang my painting alongside yours.
Make him best work.
What's wrong?
I can't.
Why not?
Your wife is just too beautiful
The painting is going to be redone again
But for me, being a model almost every day is becoming increasingly difficult
Turn this way!
Please, Sakai-san
That's all for today.
How about the portrait?
Not yet
It seems that Sakai has been studying quite a bit
I think I'm going to take a little break
Why?
I'm feeling very tired
I see.
By the way, I'm going to travel to Hokkaido for about
three months starting tomorrow
Is it going to be that long?
I hope your beautiful portrait will be finished in the meantime,
That adds one more thing to look forward to
Well then, I'll go wipe off some sweat
When do I start drawing?
I don't know.
shortly after he departed,
the terrible day of fate arrived
It's a hot and uncomfortable night
Who?
It's me
Sakai? What happened to you now?
I can't sleep
I'm worried about the painting
about the painting?
it's your painting
Why?
I can't draw it well.
Is my face that difficult to draw?
There's no wind
What happened?
The spider's web.
oh dear, no, no, no,I don't wanna hear it.
Sakiko
Just now, I despise you.
but please listen to the end
Sit here and listen carefully,
no matter how much I'm despised or hated, it's fine
Eventually, your father returned from Hokkaido
the car has arrived
Come in.
You must be aware of the recent Manchuria
Yes.
I also don't know when the time will come for us to part ways
Thank you for putting up with someone like me until now
You are also a pitiful woman
In this day and age, even if a military man's wife were to remarry after my death, society would not allow to re-marriage.
Please forgive me
You.
I just want to say this while I still can
Bring the comfort bags later.
Why are you trying to avoid me?
We live together.
I feel it's cruelty.
Don't get me wrong.
Then please leave here and marry me
I can't do that
Why can't you do it?
What will happen to Takashima if you do that?
So what will happen to me?
Does that mean you no longer loves me?
Stop it
it's the hardest thing for me to hear
Wife, I have thought about dying many times
But I couldn't even do that
You will be born.
I had to live strongly for you.
What did you say to do it again?
I'm pregnant.
Please feel free to divorce me
Whose child is it?
Sakai's.
Sakai's?
Get your hands off of me!
You.
please cut me off
Tomoko
Yes.
It shouldn't have been like this.
I was excited without thinking about my age.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
You're still young
and your youth is being sealed away
I never thought you would go through life without any mistakes
The two of us are a married couple
I'll take the child.
It's for us, after all
Why do you show me such pity?
Why don't you blame me more?
I have lost my qualifications as a husband
Yet you have served me well
I am truly grateful
I have forgiven you
If I think about you not being here,
I can endure anything
Please give me your wife
What?
Please
Please give her to me
No way!
But we have children...
the child is mine
To call it your own child, Your Excellency, is cowardly
What?
Your Excellency is only thinking about your own reputation
So...
What?
Whose help has allowed you to draw until today?
That's a separate issue from love
Shut up!
Yes, it is a separate issue
What?
Get out!
Tomoko.
Did you talk to Sakai?
For what?
Did you talk to Sakai that I couldn’t have sex?
Never.
Thank you
I let Sakai to have another house.
That's better.
Your father became fond of the Sanbo headquarters,
and we moved to our current home
And that is when you were born
Thanks to you, the Takashima family is filled with a brightness as if dawn has broken
And it was around the time when news of the Greater East Asia War began to be reported in the town every day
Oh dear, are you sleepy, Sakiko?
Sakiko is feeling a bit worn out
Father, I see,
I'm sorry about that
Next time, I'll sing for you again
Good night.
Hi Madam.
it's unusual for you
Since you're not here, I wrote you a letter.
I was planning to go home
but I understand
You're drunk again, aren't you?
Again?
I drink alcohol every day
That's not healthy for you
You know everything.
Takashima also says the same thing.
He said?
Mr. Sakai, this...
What's this?
I would like to receive that painting you made
I don't want
I don't want to lose to his kindness.
Being treated kindly is painful for me
Takashima thinks he is sending you money every month
What?
Takashima thinks that Sakiko is making amends for what she took from you
But you don't accept it
I feel pain
I'm the one who is suffering more
I'm waiting forever for my wife to come here.
You are a terrible person
It's a terrible mistake to try to avoid me while
knowing my feelings so well; just once is enough
Once is enough.
So, you are okay with trying to isolate me forever, huh?
Madam.
Takashima has already been given up on by the doctor so please don't bother
We have to evacuate
Soon after, your father passed
away while worrying about you
Eventually, the war came to an end
Mr. Sakai became a top-notch painter and gradually transformed
into someone who seemed to have attained a certain enlightenment,
and before long, he started coming to visit our home
It was because he wanted to see you more than myself
Ah, welcome
I thought your painting had changed quite a bit as I was looking at it
It's becoming quite a reflection
Where's Sakiko?
She's going to school.
Is she not home?
Madam.
I have something to say.
What's going on?
I've been feeling lately that my work
is less important than Sakiko
Please forgive me for saying something that will make you suffer again
I never thought the pain of not being able to call myself a parent would be this great
It would have been better
if I hadn't seen Sakiko since that time
Mr. Sakai
So what do you want me to do?
It's even more painful
because I don't understand that
Even if I claim to be her parent now, Sakiko probably won't believe me
It's better for that child to not know
Yes, I think so too
Mr. Sakai, you've been quite weak lately
I can't even draw.
I drink alcohol every day.
Here.
Please go.
What,Mom?
please come in.
Uncle
Uncle.
Are you here?
Oh Sakiko.
Just now, mother said I became the model for you.
Mother said that?
I'm really grateful and happy
I will tidy up my room.
I've been wanting to draw you
for a while
That's right.
But this is my first time being Model.
so just sit comfortably and that's all that matters
Come on in
The white scarf is really nice
You look good.
Come on, sit in this chair.
and try reading it.
Don't move your legs.
Wow, that's nice
Good.
This is going to be my great work.
But I've been using it for a long time, you know
Okay, okay, I understand
Do it now, before your feelings change.
Sakiko, let's turn a little more to the right
Align your eyes
I'm home.
Welcome back
I'm starving.
Bring her some donuts.
Did you visit Sakai?
You told me so.
Thank you for your work.
Was he drinking alcohol?
His room smells like alcohol
Oh.
Who exactly is that man?
He used to be a painter at our house a long time ago
Father is being very kind and taking care of you, isn't he?
I wonder why he isn't getting married?
I have no idea.
He's really unusual
So, Sakiko, have you started on your painting yet?
But I ended up not liking it
Why?
Because he's looking at me with such creepy eyes
Well, anyone would feel a bit creeped out when drawing
I really dislike him,
Sakiko shouldn't say things like that
Oh, why is that?
Why is it wrong to say I dislike someone?
Well...
I don't want to be a model
Sakai-san seem very happy?
I really dislike him.
Are you tired?
but it's better to finish quickly
What are you doing?
Hurry up and draw it!
I can't draw that fast!
Why?
I'm putting my life into this job
I don't like this,
Sakiko!
Don't you believe in my work?
Huh? Sakiko!
What are you going to do?
I'm going home
Why you act like that?
What?
Did you ask my mother?
Were you our painter at our house long ago?
Excuse me.
Don't go.
I'm sorry.
Now is the most important time.
Please.
You did something good for him.
But you know, I thought that thinking about it
later might actually make Sakai-san suffer more
However, regardless of Sakai-kun, he can see Sakiko right in front of him every day.
Truly, suffering continues to come one after another
When Mr. Sakai expressed his love as a father,
I was really in trouble.
Is that so?
Does Sakiko dislike Mr. Sakai?
Yes, lately it has been getting worse and worse
Well, that's something common for girls around that age
Is that so?
I'm home.
She's back.
Then let's see if I can manage to talk things through smoothly
Please
Welcome
I've been told that you've been modeling for Sakai-kun lately
Is it already done for today?
Am I not going anymore?
Why?
He is very disgusting
artists are always a bit eccentric, you know
But I don't like it
There are other models, right?
Mr. Sakai is saying he wants to draw you
I want to ask my mother
why she told me to go to someone like that
Sakiko.
I don't know what happened, but if you quit halfway,
it will be a problem for Sakai-kun too
Could you please go?
No.
Around the time of Mr. Sakai's first anniversary
Mr. Kazuma has brought your marriage proposal
I can assure both the person and the family sufficiently, you know
Could you leave one thing to me?
I believe it's quite a significant matter, is it not?
Well, if you say that,
it makes it worthwhile for me to take care of her
Sakiko is not here?
That child seems to be avoiding me lately
That's bad.
She makes various excuses to leave the house
She might be thinking about Sakai.
Isn't that a bit of an overreaction?
It's time to send her off to her husband
Mom.
welcome back
I'm home.
Muraki is here.
Please show him to the reception room.
who is Muraki?
He's an art dealer
He's been saying for a while now that he wants to hold an exhibition of Mr. Sakai's posthumous works
Well, as for me, I would like to keep only the paintings of my husband
and Sakiko, and sell everything else
I see, that makes sense. It's better to let go of painful memories quickly
Excuse me.
please call Sakiko for me
uncle?
Over here
It seems like you haven't been getting along with mother lately
That's not true.
Well, if that's the case,
You need to get along
since it's just you and me.
I wonder if mother is hiding something from me?
What do you mean hiding?
I don't really know,
but it feels like there might be something
I don't think so.
It's rare to find such a wonderful mother
Well, I think so too.
By the way,
How about it?
Do you have any intention of getting married?
Oh dear,
Even if you're shy, I'll encourage you.
After all, I don't want to either
Even your mother is worried about you
in her own way
Well, I'll leave some photos behind too
Take your time to think and reply later.
It troubles me.
Don't say like that.
I was surprised that things are progressing so smoothly.
She really is a strong-willed child, you know
I didn't expect her to agree so readily
I wonder if this is what a true good match really is
Yes, thank you
My eyesight has really gotten worse, hasn't it?
It will be lonely when I'm gone, won't it?
I can only imagine how lonely the young lady must feel
I often think how nice it would be
if only her husband were here
Dad is such a fool, not even watching me get married
Yeah.
Is this enough?
Please ask your mom about it
She would be happier if she never knew about it.
I used to think that way,
but I can no longer keep this hidden any longer
But she's supposed to get married
Now that it's come to this...
I think it's time to finally open up
I wonder if that's true.
Sakai died without letting her know this.
If I let her know about it, I think it will be a good memorial for Sakai on the first anniversary of her death.
Despite being her real parent,
His daughter didn't think he was her father. I feel so sorry for him.
My father is a liar.
That's cowardly.
Well, I'll head over to Exhibition of Mr. Sakai's posthumous works
then, is that okay?
Sakiko.
What are you doing?
Get your hands off of me!
Calm down.
You said you cut it because you felt sorry for yourself in that painting
That's right, it's embarrassing to have anyone see such a dirty painting.
You're cowardly and a liar
Father and Mr. Sakai are all liars too
Sakiko, it was wrong for Mother
to hide things until now, but...
I intend for you to know everything
when you get married
I think it's terrible to ask for
understanding of the parents' secrets now
I'm not just asking for your understanding
I opened up thinking that I was okay to be looked down upon or blamed, no matter what
It's because I truly wanted you to have a genuinely happy and correct marriage
Marriage is just foolish
Sakiko
Everyone is a liar. Living together for decades
is terrifying.
I hate marriage.
Sakiko, you liked your father, didn't you?
I loved him very much
Your mother resented that father, you know
Just once
On that summer night, it was just once.
That's a lie, a lie
Sakiko.
from that lie, I was born
I am not my father's child
No, you are definitely your father's child
He truly love you.
With great affection, he really cherishes you
That made it even harder for my mother
I am also in a lot of pain
I understand very well
But you know, Sakiko,
There are many things in the world that you
can't possibly understand with your current youth
I think as you get older,
you'll come to understand what it truly means to be a weak human being
You are still young and beautiful, and everything is ahead of you
Stop dwelling on your mother's past mistakes
and thinking negatively about yourself
Please hold onto brighter hopes and become stronger
That is the most important thing for you right now
Hey, be happy for my sake too.
Your happiness is what your late father and Mr. Sakai would be the happiest about
Did you understand?
Adjust your posture.
my father often said this to encourage me when I was feeling down
Mom.
What?
I'm sorry for bullying you, mother.
Adjust your posture.
Sakiko.
Dawn is breaking.
Do you want to sleep?
Please wear this for me.
You look so beautiful.
Come over here and give me a good look.
Wow,it's so warm.
This is the first time I've seen such a beautiful sunrise.
The End