Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
There's no development in our relationship any more.
We're both looking out for each other's future.
Wanna break up with me?
Yeah
You're unhappy because you can't have sex with me.
It could be
I'm proud of myself
So you don't mind if we split up?
Yeah
I'll find someone more desirable.
Okay.
Bye.
Are you alone?
My friend has not come yet.
Can I join in you?
Okay.
Thank you very much
You're a student?
Yeah
It's 11:00 in the afternoon, and your parents worries about you.
I don't live with them
I see you're training to be a bride in Tokyo.
You must be popular
I'm not such a woman
I get it
You're simple.
All beautiful women seem to have a lot of pride.
You must be thirsty after five games.
Go ahead
I can't drink
Try a bite of it.
I'm sure you'll like it.
Don't force her
It's like juice.
Even people who can't drink will eat this one.
I'll take it then.
How is it?
It's delicious.
What do you think about Vietnam?
Should the U.S. back off?
I don't like war, but it's none of my business.
Which of these three, the U.S., the Soviet Union, or the Chinese Communist Party, should Japan choose?
I don't know.
What do you do,Yasui?
Take a guess
I don't know.
Oh, come on, don't be a stickler about identity.
It's more fun for strangers to hang out with each other in a casual, fun way.
Yeah
I’m sorry
She looks so nice
It's no surprise.
I've had my eye on that girl for a month.
Drink up.
Thank you very much
You're as generous as ever.
As you can see, I've had nothing to do since the death of my partner.
I can barely eat.
The effects of adding drugs to cocktails have been seen.
I'll go home
I'll send you
What are you going to do with me?
Dai Akuto / The Great Villains (1968)
Who?
I finally found you
It was hard to find here
I'm in trouble
Please go home
Let me stay here,
We're not strangers.
Please go home
That's cold.
If you want me to leave, I'll leave.
But first, I want to show you something.
I'm good at taking pictures, right?
Keep it as a souvenir, miss
There's more.
I've taken about three or four dozen of them.
There's no use tearing them up,
I have the negatives. I can copy hundreds of them.
Give me the negatives.
If you don't give it to me, I'll call the police.
What do you mean, the police?
I'm a yakuza.
I asked the manager of this apartment a few questions in the guise of a marriage survey.
Your father is the principal of a famous high school in Nagano Prefecture.
He'd probably be upset if a picture like this showed up on the news.
He, of course, then resigned as principal and retired.
Your family's going to have a hard time
You have no filial piety.
You go to the biggest tailoring school in Tokyo.
What do you think would happen if I walked around handing out
They'd have amazing
No one wanna marry you in th future
Is that what you want?
Give me all the negatives and photos, please.
I'm weak when it comes to tears.
I'll do you a favor, then.
Really?
In exchange, I need you to do one thing for me.
What is it?
You are handsome
You are cool
Pacific Recoding at 2:00 p.m.
4:00 p.m. Taihei TV rehearsal
This will be cut off at 30 minutes
five o'clock at the film studio for airing
Back to Far Eastern TV at 8:00
the climax of the song is in production
9:30.
Special show at Club Candle.
That's enough.
They're going to kill me.
You gotta make as much money as you can.
To make you money?
This is Akatsuki production.
Thank you very much
His August schedule?
He's booked solid through the fall.
Hold on, when?
It's been a while.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
I'm kind of busy today.
It won't take long.
Thank you for waiting. well...
He's too busy, sorry
What you want?
I've got nice girl
Want one night?
I'm too busy
You're too popular
No matter how much popular you make.
If you get girl into bed with you, it's a scandal.
I know you want sex
Not really
Take a look
She's a dressmaker's schoolgirl, a proper young lady with a proper temperament.
You don't have to worry in the future
It's a good shopping for you
How much is it?
30,000 a night.
I don't need a girl.but I pay the pocket money for you
You give it to me?
No
I just want us to talk about this once and for all.
Think back to the old days.
You're an unknown, but we brought you up and made you a star.
I haven't forgotten.
I've handled your show many times.
I've taken care of the girls, but I don't remember giving you any trouble.
I feel guilty
But the police have banned gangsters from the entertainment business.
You'll still make your money.
but my gang's broken up and we're all on the street.
I feel sorry for you
So I figured out what to do with myself.
No matter what I try, it doesn't work.
I got into this business because I had no choice.
Please help me
I'm in trouble
This map, apartment number 603.
You push the button, this girl comes out, you give her the money.
This is just business
Let's not treat me like beggars.
We've got a deal.
Tonight at 10:00 p.m., you're gonna come into my apartment, and I'm gonna give you the keys to my room.
I'm staying at a hotel.
What can I get you?
Coffee
What's the matter with you?
If I go out with this guy just once tonight, you gonna give me the pictures and the negatives?
Yeah
When do I get it?
As soon as this is over.
You sure?
You insist.
You're dealing with a popular star
He's popular among women
You may be lucky
I'm not one of those women.
Well, you just have to be patient, 'cause it's gonna be a little bit of a bad dream.
You're a real lady.
I'm sure 30,000 yen won't be too much for you.
Come on, let's go to bed, we don't have time for this.
Come on, let's get you into bed.
Turn off the light, please.
I'm paying you.
Let me do what I want.
I don't want
What are you talking about?
I like the light better.
I like you
You can't do that
Yasui, what's that?
This?
Stop it....
I filmed good
What are you going to do with it?
I'll think about it when I see how it's used and how well it's done.
You tricked me.
Don't get violent.
If you get hurt, it's bad for business.
How much can I pay for the film?
We can deal it later
Your job is over, okay?
I'll give you the exact negatives of the nude photos as promised.
Burn them, bury them, do whatever you want with them.
What happens to the film I just shot?
I don't remember saying I'd give it to you.
And now you're blackmailing me again.
Yeah
After all, this one has a real bed scene with a guy.
It's a brand-new black-and-white film.
Compared to the intensity of that.
What's the point of these nude pictures?
That was the plan all along, wasn't it?
It's not easy to let go of a woman once you've had your eye on her.
As long as I have this film, you're screwed.
I bet your father and mother would have cried if they saw this.
They will be like  I didn't raise her to be such a shameless bitch.
Where are you going?
I'm going
You're staying here tonight.
No
You don't mind if I send this film around to your home and your school?
If you don't like it, stay here and be quiet
Stay down, you are mine now
I made a promise on the phone earlier.
One moment, please, sir.
You have a visitor.
Get them here
Are you Teruo Shima?
No
You are
You can go home now... and get ready for school.
But I have class at 6:00 p.m., right?
Go somewhere till then
Anyway, we're up against Yakuza,
We're a popular businessman with a lot of weaknesses.
I'm sure they'll come up with a big payday sooner or later.
I can't just do what they want.
I don't know what to do.
It's your fault.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Please don't do that and help me somehow.
I know you are specialist about this kind of case
Am I specialist  lawyer for Yakuza?
I don't mean that
I'm a bad lawyer with a bill of goods, according to the judges and prosecutors.
Do you have any good idea?
The quickest way to get out of this is to charge them with extortion.
Don't do that.
What if people know about this
You'd be locked out of TV.
Your popularity will plummet.
You're the only one I can count on.
I'll leave everything to you.
I'm counting on you.
I hate yakuzas.
I'd be happy to take you in, but it's going to cost you a lot of money.
Of course, I'm prepared to pay for it.
What is my fee?
How much you need?
million
No way,I'm not going to ask for you if I'm going to pay that much money.
So I decline
I'm not really into this
I get it. There's no choice
We'll pay million
In exchange, please settle the matter so there'll be no trouble
What are you doing?
Give me the film
Please
Where is it?
Damn it
You won't give me?
Of course
That was a money-making scheme.
I'm not giving it to you.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go.
You don't mind if I spread the porno film around?
I don't mind
I'm ready for it.
I don't care what they do to me.
I don't care if I can't have a proper marriage, or what people say about me.
But
I don't want to live with yo
I don't want to see your face .
I don't care if you kill you.
Well, then, I'll kill you, as you wish.
Don't fuck with me.
Don't talk big if you don't want to get hurt.
You can't leave the room like this.
Stay down
Are you Yasui?
who?
I represent Teruo shima.
You're a lawyer?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Here's good place
How did you get it?
Did you extort her to collect on a bad debt?
What can I do for you?
Yasui?
The girl who slept with Teruo was a businesswoman you hired?
Just because a popular singer hooks up with a professional woman doesn't make him a scandal nowadays.
Don't say bullshit
He slept with my wife
He is the star. The world won't forgive him for messing around with other people's wives.
Your wife?
She's here now
She's sleeping there
He's depression about Teruo
You sure?
Come
He's lawyers, so whatever he ask you, don't answer.
This is my wife.
See if she's a businesswoman.
I see.
Wife, I'm Tokuda
I'll be visiting from time to time to represent Mr. Shima.
Thanks
By the way, let's take a look at the film
What are you going to do with a film?
I can't give you a price without seeing the film.
I'm the one who sets the prices.
You ask to Shima
No way
I'm lawyer,I'm not at your mercy.
Let me show you.
Wife,This is your commercial photo?
If you have any problems...
Come here anytime.
We'll be happy to help you.
Interesting, isn't it?
How much do you want for it?
This is rubbish
this film is worthless
I can't pay a penny.
Are you sure?
Now that I'm on board.
I'm not paying you a dime.
That's bull.
How can you work as an agent if you destroy the story?
Yasui
If you think you can blackmail people with pornographic photos, you're wrong.
The world is not that easy nowadays.
You think so?
I don't care how big a mouth you have.
This film exists.
You can make or break TERUO SHIMA.
It's up to you to decide how to handle it.
But in my hands...
I can free him from your hands without paying a penny
After all, I'm the man who can do the impossible.
Don't be lair
Don't be sorry.
You'd be safer if you didn't make such a fuss.
You make a move, you'll be strangling yourself.
I'll do it.
Mr. Yasui
What can I do for you?
I have something urgent to tell him
He's busy, I will listen
Give me a call.
I'd visited you
I'm a yakuza. I'm in a TV studio. Is that a problem?
This is his important TV studio.
So please
If you don't want me to come, don't send some strange lawyer.
We can't deal with
That's outrageous.
We wanted to reach an amicable settlement, so we asked Mr. Tokuda.
Then let's get rid of him.
He's being rude?
He's an asshole.
It's going to get more and more troublesome.
Tokuda Law Office.
Yes he is here
there's a call
You
Please buy me some cigarettes
About what you asked me the other day.
Actually, things have changed a bit.
We'd like you to withdraw from the case.
I'm in trouble
I'm a firm believer that once I take on a case, I stick with it until the end.
I don't take orders from clients.
Maybe Yasui threatened you
I'm not a coward who stays at the Yakuza and backs down.
Anyway, can we please forget about the other day?
I'm begging you.
If you insist.
I'll tell the reporter about the incident in the paper.
They'd be happy to publish
No way
Then shut up and watch.
Wife
You're very well dressed,
I ran out to see if you could help me.
Lend me some money for taxi
I'll go to pay
Did anyone see you enter this room?
No, sir.
Hide here.
You don't want to be seen.
Cigarettes.
You can go home today.
I see.
I see what you mean.
I get it
Lawyer makes the impossible possible.
You said you can't blackmail people with funny pictures
Please help me
I was lying
If I show weakness to the Yakuza, they will take advantage of me.
I was just trying to scare him
I'm not so sure.
Can't beat Yasui?
No, you can't.
Please
No thanks
Then take me to the police.
If I tell the detectives everything,they'll arrest him.
But for a charge of kidnapping and assaulting a woman, he'll be out in a couple of years.
Generally speaking. Yakuza are vindictive and bored.
Wherever you're hiding, they'll find you and pay you back.
You'll suffer worse than you do now.
What should I do?
You'll be in trouble
You become a prostitute and end up dying of disease.
Or commit suicide or be admitted to a mental hospital.
You'll never survive.
What should I do?
you may be saved
What way?
If Yasui is dead
he die from an illness or from a traffic accident
If I wait for such a coincidence, I'll become a grandmother.
You should be more serious
Do you think you'll live long by Yasui's side?
So I can't be saved
Anyway, you and Yasui are the only ones who can survive.
Be brave.
Be brave?
he's crazy
You'd better throw him in the nuthouse or You should kill him
You're asking me to kill him?
Life is a battle.
Killing each other.
Every human being has the right to resist.
But if I kill him...
I'll be murder
Killing someone doesn't make you a murderer.
In my five years of experience as a lawyer
Yakuza bosses and politicians never go to jail.
That's rare.
We should have a visitor by now.
I know Yoshiko is here
Yeah
She's in the back room.
So this is it.
You took her out?
She jumped in from the other side.
You're bad husband,
I can't believe your wife ran away
What did you teach her?
Nothing
I'm just telling her what happened
I was just trying to be sympathetic and comforting her
You slept with her?
No way
I'm not playboy
Lawyer.
Get off this case before you get hurt.
I'll think about it.
Are you drinking?
Yoshiko, if you don't want me to kill you, go back
Wear this
Don't pick on her.
She's my girl.Shut up
You made me shame
Why did you meet him?
Did you sleep with him?
How was it?
He didn't do anything. not like you
I'll ask your body
Bear in mind, don't sleep with anyone without asking me
Stop it....
I'm not?
no
I'm on period today
i don't believe it
Stop it....
Yoshiko,You're my girl
You can't leave from me
You'll be making money for me until the day you die.
I choose clients.
permission...
I'll kill you
You understand?
Hello?
This is Yoshiko
What's wrong?
I killed him.
I'll be right there.
You made it
But how did you manage to kill him with those skinny arms?
Because he was sleeping off his whiskey.
I was preoccupied.
What am I supposed to do?
You killed a man.
You're going to turn yourself in to the police.
You said
Killing someone doesn't make you a murderer.
Murder's not that big a deal in a case like this.
You'll get five years and probation.
If you don't want to do that either, why don't you cross one dangerous bridge and try to win?
It's more fun for me.
What do you mean by that?
I'll get you acquitted.
Anyway, as soon as I get back, you get on the phone and call Police.
You're leaving me alone?
If they find out we're related, you're not gonna make it.
When you go to the police, they'll make sure you get a lawyer.
That's the first time you mention my name.
I'll be there
Then?
All you have to do is follow my lead.
This is?
Well
the murder weapon was a necktie.
You used two?
First one I used was broken
Oh, this.
Now you're free at last, aren't you?
Let's drink a toast while looking at Yasui's corpse.
Come here and give me a drink
Don't say bullshit
I'm serious
We don't have time
Hurry up
You drink too
I can't
If you don't want to be a murderer, drink.
Let's drink a lot
You got scar
Why did you chock me?
Next get naked
For what?
To get acquitted.
We've got a lot of work to do before we call the police.
If you want to save your life, you're gonna have to drink it.
I can trust you, can't I?
Hurry up
I do
I make him naked too
Your mom has visited you
She came to Tokyo from Nagano last night.
Yoshiko, you've done a terrible thing.
Why did you go with a yakuza guy?
I had no choice.
Because you had an opening.
You've always been a little strange
Lawyer, please help her
I will
When can I get released from here?
The prosecutor accuses me every day and it's very painful.
Soon.
Please hang in there!
I need five copies of this case and five copies of this case.
You must be prosecutor Okano.
I understand you'll be handling the second half of Yoshiko Ota's case.
I'm defense counsel, Mr. Tokuda.
Pleased to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
Are you going to try something again?
Of course not.
I can't help you with this one.
The defendant confessed to the murder.
Confession is the king of evidence.
For my part, I have no choice but to rely on the sympathies of the procutor.
What can I do for you?
The defendant's bail, if you could please let her out.
Not until after the first trial.
What time did the victim YASUI come back to the apartment on the day of the dimension?
I believe it was around 8:30 p.m.
What was the defendant doing?
I was on period that day
My head was heavy and I felt very bad.
I was in a daze when Yasui said...
What he said?
You're wasting time. Get a client.
I told him I couldn't do it today.
He hit and kicked me
I thought he was going to kill me.
Then?
And then, just then, that man came in.
Who was he, and what did he look like?
I don't remember.
Yes, he had been hit pretty hard with a band and he was out cold.
And he was wearing a white mask and sunglasses.
Yasui called him "bro".
What was he doing here?
I didn't get a good look at him.
I think he hit Yasui out of the blue.
Why he hit him?
He was kind of angry.
He looked like he was going to kill Yasui.
Yasui just kept apologizing
Finally he got into a good mood,They started drinking whiskey together.
When he was drinking
Did the man take off his facial mask?
No, he didn't.
No. He pulled it up a little and poured it into his mouth.
That's funny.
He said he was wanted by the police and he didn't want anyone to see his face.
Yasui said softly
What did you do after that?
He asked me He asked me to pour him a drink.
When I had no choice, he asked me to drink too.
When I refused, Yasui said
Yasui said, "Are you disobeying my brother's order? and forced me drink
I was in so much pain.
They made me drink so many drinks
I didn't know what was going on.
Then, he told me that drinking alone was boring.
He told me to try something different.
What was that?
He told me and Yasui to get naked and demonstrate by hugging each other in front of me.
And what did the defendant do?
I didn't think it was possible.
Yasui told me that my bro had always been a man who would make me do anything he said, even kill me, and that there was no use in resisting him.
So you did it?
Yes
He forced me
I was embarrassed.
Carry on
The man was getting more and more amused, and he even told me what to do with Yasui.
He made me do things I couldn't say out loud.
When Yasui was on the bottom and I was on top, the man said again
It's no fun to just hug each other!
He told us both to close our necks around each other.
He made Yasui pick up his tie.
Why did he make you do that?
He said that choking each other would make both the man and the woman feel much better
You made it?
He said it would make BRO happy.
I strangled him with his tie.
Yasui also tightened his grip on my throat.
When I looked at his face, it wasn't human at all, it looked like a hideous creature.
I couldn't hold back any longer and squeezed is his neck as hard as I could.
I was so tight that I couldn't breathe.
I got passed out
And then what happened?
When I came to my senses...
I found the masked man was gone and Yasui was lying there naked.
I wondered if he fell asleep, but his body was as cold as ice.
That's when you realized that Yasui was dead?
yes
Suddenly I got scared and called the police right away.
you said you  lost patience when you  put on his necktie.
In other words,you  intended to kill Yasui?
Significant.
It's an interrogation.I ask you to withdraw it.
Why don't you change the question?
How did you feel?
Was it because you were sexually aroused?
Or did you intend to kill him?
I couldn't take it anymore.
I'd wanted to kill him
Who wouldn't want to be humiliated like that?
I'm a woman.
I'm a human being.
This is the tie you wore around Yasui's neck, isn't it?
Yes, I believe so.
We're done
Do you have a cross-examination?
No
Yoshiko
I'll go back to Nagano
I've been sitting in on the trial the whole time.
I'm so embarrassed and ashamed.
I can't stand living in Tokyo
Even if I go back to my country, I'll never get out.You'll resign and we'll all go into the mountains and live in secret
This is all your fault.
I'm sorry.
I won't see you anymore
See you
I'm finally alone.
We don't need a society or a family to survive.
I did that
I'm a woman.
I wouldn't dare.
Don't worry, I'm here.
By the way, that was a very good courtroom act.
But if I don't, I'm a murderer.
Don't worry.
Once we get him to trial, he's all ours.
Why?
Cops are hard to fool, but judges and prosecutors are easy.
They all look like pretending great but
They don't know the world, they don't know women, and they have a weakness for beautiful women like you.
I don't believe it.
Besides, the defendant confessed in this case.
They must feel comfortable cutting corners.
This will be the key we will win
You're really going to save my life, aren't you?
Trials are fun.
The prosecution's case is closed today.
Now it's time to get to work.
Mr.Yasui, is the room still the same as it was at the time of the incident?
Yeah
He bought here
Actually, we'd like to reexamine the crime scene.
I was wondering if you'd be willing to come down and take a look at the crime scene?
reexamine?
No worries, it will finish soon
Moldy. You haven't changed at all since then.
That's good for me
Something's wrong with this tie.
It's cut.
Do you know this defendant?
Yes, I do.
What is your relationship to her?
I met her a few times in Tokyo because we are from Nagano Prefecture, but we are not close enough to have a relationship.
I see.
By the way, does the defendant drink?
One sip of beer and her face turned red and she was in agony.
You've seen this tie before?
Yes
Where did you see this?
In Mr. Yasui's room.
The lawyer found it in the wardrobe and showed it to me.
That's enough
Prosecutor, cross-examine the witness.
I don't have
The defendant was severely intoxicated when he tied Yasui's neck with his tie?
Yes
You can't drink at all.
How did you feel when he forced you to drink whiskey?
I was dying
Were you in a position to clearly remember the pattern and color of the tie you were wearing Yasui?
No
And I was so embarrassed that my head was spinning and my eyes were blurry.
Then you must have been mistaken, or misremembered.
That's Leading questions.
Counsel, would you like to change the question?
Yes
Here are two ties.
One was submitted by the prosecutor as the murder weapon.
The other two were newly discovered by me.
Which did you use to strangle Yasui?
Well...
Take a look at these
I remember... this
Why do you think so?
When I strangled Yasui When he strangled Yasui, there was a cracking sound and the tie broke.
The color and pattern were like this.
So you didn't use this one submitted by the prosecutor?
No
Why did you admit to having done this until now?
When the police showed me this, I thought I'd killed someone.
I was so preoccupied with what to do that I just nodded my head, not understanding what was going on.
You said yes even though you didn't know
How about you were interrogated by the prosecutor?
I didn't expect to be shown another tie at all.
So I was careless
Did you make a lame confession?
As a prosecutor, after fully assessing the defendant's mental state
That's why we interrogated him.
Presiding Judge., the prosecutor is conducting a cross-examination.
I haven't finished my statement.
Prosecutor, please be careful.
Presiding Judge. please be careful.
As defense counsel, I would like to submit this newly discovered necktie into evidence.
What does the defense hope to prove with this tie?
The defendant's innocence.
If the tie submitted by the prosecutor is the murder weapon
If she didn't use it, he's not a murderer.
There must be someone else who wrapped this tie around Yasui's neck and strangled him to death.
It was probably the man Yasui called his brother.
That man is the real murderer.
What is the opinion of the prosecutor?
Several trials have confirmed the murder weapon and the defendant's guilt.
Defense counsel's sudden assertion of the defendant's innocence is an affront to the court and a contempt of court.
Therefore, the Prosecution objects to this request for evidence.
Presiding Judge, the courtroom is a sacred place where the truth is sought by all means.
Prosecutor ignores defense counsel's statements and refuses to allow the defendant to prove her innocence.
The prosecutor holds the court in contempt.
All right.
I'll allow the defense to present its evidence and the Prime Minister's Office to make its request.
Tokuda is great, he said Yasui's bro is murder
I thought it was a simple confession case.
I guess we let our guard down.
I wonder who is the bro
We have too many case, have no time
Do you think the bro is exist?
I wonder tokuda's lie
Anyway let's investigate
This is a picture of Yasui's brother.
Remember which man came in that night?
I don't know.
He was wearing a mask and sunglasses.
Can you tell me what his face looked like?
I really don't remember.
Why?
As I've told you many times, I've been beaten, I've been drugged, I've been embarrassed.
be honest
No wonder you don't remember.
There was no bro from the beginning
There was no one at the crime scene but you and Yasui.
there is
trust me
Don't underestimate the prosecutor.
Tokuda taught you, You lied,right?
Why would I lie?
I've always told the truth.
Cut it out
You conspired with the defense to defraud the prosecutor and make a fool of the judge.
You committed murder and perjured yourself again.
You're in contempt of court.
No, sir.
If you want to keep a clean slate, that's fine.
But if you think you can deceive me forever, you're wrong.
A lie is a lie, and it always gets exposed.
The prosecutor is insist
I've been getting called in every day for questioning.
They must be desperate.
If you're acquitted, they lose.
I worry our lie will be found out
We live in an age of lies.
Everything from TV commercials to politicians' statements are lies.
Compared to that, our lies are cute.
But we're dealing with prosecutors and judges.
That's why the layman's in trouble.
The bottom line is, trials are a game of lawyers and prosecutors.
All we have to do is win.
The expert examined this tie.?
what did you find?
There were extremely large amounts of human skin fragments on it.
Can you determine that the skin fragment belongs to the victim Yasui?
A small amount of blood soaked in this tie was analyzed.
We have confirmed that it is Yasui's.
How do you think the skin piece got on the tie?
I think it is due to the tightness of Yasui's body and throat.
I'm done.
That's all
The defense claims it was the bro who was at the scene of the crime.
This is just a guess.
And the newly submitted necktie... Probably used by the defendant, YOSHIKO.
He kept it secretly hidden and suddenly brought it to the court to confuse the medical examination.
Also, the defendant's confession that a man named BRO was present at the crime scene is highly doubtful and not credible.
I, the prosecutor, find the defendant guilty and sentence him to five years in prison.
The defendant's confession is the only evidence that proves his guilt.
If it is a lie that Bro.
If Bro was there, then the whole confession is a lie, and there is no way to prove the murder.
Also, the prosecutor said that it was my imagination that Bro killed the victim.
Looking at the crime scene photos, there is a cup and a cigarette butt for the defendant and another for the victim, so we can conclude that there was indeed someone there.
It was Yasui's Bro.
And that he had the intent to kill Yasui.
It is clear from the defendant's testimony.
The necktie the defendant used was a cheap, thin one.
It would break easily if he tried to tie it around his neck.
If she kept squeezing it, it would break.
She can't drink.She was on the verge of fainting when she got up
Suppose she finds a sturdy necktie in the wardrobe
It would be completely impossible for her to strangle Yasui again
The tie broke and she fainted.
Perhaps Bro took a sturdy tie and strangled Yasui to death.
Yasui is a yakuza.
He must have misbehaved in some way and was sanctioned by Bro.
For Yakuza, killing a gang or two is nothing. Killing a thug or two is nothing to a drug addict.
After the crime, Bro puts his broken tie back in the wardrobe.
and walked away quickly.
It's the most natural thing to do.
Based on the above, I am convinced that it was Bro, not Yoshiko, who killed Yasui.
Therefore, as defense counsel, I plead the defendant's innocence.
I believe she should be released for lack of evidence.
How was it?
It didn’t work
The police have mobilized detectives to investigate Yasui's Bro, but some of them are missing.
After all, since the gang was disbanded, everyone is in different places.
Besides, the Yakuza are always covering for each other.
It's not good.
In order to convict Yoshiko, we need to take testimonies from all the Bro's and prove that none of them were Yasui. to prove that no one met Yasui.
If that's impossible...
Tokuda must have seen through it all.
If Yasui wasn't a yakuza, our lie would never get through.
He's so obsequious to Bro, and then he gets killed.
Yasui's an idiot.
I wonder what's going to happen to me
Killing people and lying about it.
I'm not the innocent girl I used to be.
Innocence is like being a virgin.
Get rid of it and live happily ever after.
Yoshiko, the accused, step forward!
I hereby submit a motion for judgment.
Reason.
You were found not guilty by a lack of evidence.
You're free to go.
I wonder if I've really been exonerated.
If the prosecutor doesn't appeal, the verdict's final.
There's a principle in the law that no two cases are ever the same.
The same case never goes to trial twice.
If you're caught lying in the future, you won't be punished.
I see
Will you come to my office tonight?
We'll have a private toast.
1,500,000
Is this my reward?
You forgot the amount we agreed upon.
I haven't forgotten, but things have changed since Yasui died.
Please accept it.
This film Yasui was just showing off, it's pretty good.
Don't look at it
If I hadn't taken the locker key earlier.
This film would be in police hands by now, and the press would be all over it.
So what?
I'll get the press together for a preview instead of the police.
Lawyer, you're not blackmailing us?
I just want you to keep your word.
Please pay the correct amount
Five million exactly.
The price of a bed scene between you and Teru-chan.
I can buy up a bar for you
bar?
The prosecutor withdrew the appeal.
So you've been exonerated.
You'll never be able to live like a human being again.
I'm just trying to give you something to hold on to.
Thanks
I said I can't give you this much money.
I'll lend it to you... by signing this contract.
This money is mine.
I don't need to borrow my own money.
Your own money?
You recommended that I kill Yasui.
You got this money because I did what you told me to do.
I deserve it.
What if I say no?
I'll tell the police what happened.
I'll never be a defendant again, but you're in a lot of trouble.
You falsified the crime scene and defrauded the court.
You'll be disbarred, and you'll go to jail.
Right?
You'll never be a defendant again
you're blackmailing me. you are great
I killed a man because of Lawyer.
You know how horrible it is to kill someone?
I'm not afraid anymore, I can do anything.
I've been a tool for Yasui, for you, for men, and I've had it rough, but now I'm going to bully men.
Yeah, because that's what you do for a living.
I'm going to open a bar and it's going to be a thriving business.
After all, I'm a woman who committed a crime.
I'm sure there will be a lot of guys who will love to come in.
I extort a lot of money from them
Goodbye, lawyer
The money and the girls are gone.
All that's left is a single photograph.
Jinpei Tokuda, if my opponent is a man, I won't lose but she's a woman
It's okay if I lose
THE END