Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Are you alright,Nogami?
Are you alright?
Every time a bullet train passes by, her pulse races.
190 per min
B29..B29
What's the hell about B29?
It's an old American bomber.
In the last war, they rained bombs down and bombed the hell out of this neighborhood.
So her
She remembered that 30 years ago again on the bullet train.
Go back to the hospital, the pharmacy's probably busy.
You're treating her like a parent.
My family didn't want to take the bullet train, so they ran away.
I won't let her die alone.
If you're here, I'm here.
Stay strong
Does the JNR president think we, the plaintiffs in the Shinkansen pollution lawsuit, are stupid?
We've been to court 10 times and you haven't shown any sincerity!
A Shinkansen is 60 tons per car, 960 tons in gravity.
This thing breaks through every 5 minutes at 200km/h.
Do you know how much noise and vibration that makes?
I understand your suffering, sir.
We will build a soundproof wall to slow down the speed in the city.
We will also put up a joint antenna for television.
We are doing our best, sir.
That soundproof wall won't work
The cup on my desk is shaking.
How can a human being live here?
We have paid 100,000 yen per person as a primary guarantee to those within 50 meters of the line.
We continue..
That's not enough
Give us 1 million
Babies along the line cry all day long for the bullet train.
Some of them died because they couldn't have a milk
Seven adults died, too.
What are you going to do?
Say something
If You're going to use your power to crush the trial.
I'll take a stick of dynamite and jump onto the bullet train.
Nogami
She died
She died finally
She just got well after being in the hospital.
Why didn't you answer?
You're strange these days
You've gone completely quiet.
You're always off at the hospital, always off somewhere.
What the hell are you doing?
I need you to steal 15 CCs of nitroglycerin from the hospital pharmacy.
That is a deleterious drug. It's heavily controlled.
So I'm asking you
pharmacist can handle it.
What for?
Don't worry
Trust me
If you don't like it, I'll steal it.
OK
I'm painful
Blood pressure
What's the name of the disease?
Heart failure due to hardening of the arteries.
The patient's address is listed as ATSUTA 2, Nagoya City
What do you mean?
Noise and vibration from the Shinkansen are particularly bad here.
Isn't this heart disease also caused by Shinkansen pollution?
You always blame pollution.
Next
You need to go right down that hallway.
Excuse me
I'm off to Europe
Europe?
Only for 3 months.
Since when ?
Tomorrow
Tomorrow?
What are you doing there?
I got a tourist visa.
You're a resident now.It's time to study.
I can't believe you're going on a sightseeing trip.
What's the point of being a goof doctor ?
I'm just going to get my dad to pay for me to open my own practice.
Throw me out and leave me alone.
Don't you love me?
I'll write you letters.
Lots of them.
Domyaku Retto / Dynamic Islands (1975)
Excuse me.
Toilet clogged.
I can't flash
Can't?
What's the hell about SHinkansen.
The ticket is high
What's the hell about national railway?
Work properly
The toilet is broken?
Something's clogged up in there.
What is that? It's fluorescent paint.
It's a tea canister with felt wrapped around it.
If it's clogged with this stuff, there's no way it's going to flush.
Damn it?
What?
Could be a bomb.
The code for the dimensional equipment is broken.
I'm KITAGAWA from the forensic lab.
I'm Special Investigation Team Leader, AKASHI.
Thank you for your hard work.
The tea canisters and fluorescent paint are ordinary stuff sold all over Japan.
What's inside?
Mud for explosives.
I split it in two and examined it.
I found a plastic baggie filled with 15 cc.
We also found a letter of warning in a plastic bag.
warning letter?
Here's the warning letter.
Mixing nitroglycerin in with the MUD makes it dynamite.
If you plug in the code from the dimensional device, you could easily blow up the SHINKANSEN.
This is a warning to the JNR authorities.
Here's the conditions to solve pollution caused by Shinkansen
1.Reduce the noise during running to less than 60 minutes sound.
2.Reduce vibration to 0.6 millimeters per second.
3.Reduce the speed in urban areas to 70 km/h or less.
Establish a 50-meter-wide buffer zone on both sides of the tracks.
I will destroy the Shinkansen after 10 days, shut it down for at least two days, and paralyze it for at least a week.
destroy the Shinkansen?
This warning letter is not a prank.
To prove it, we will derail the Shinkansen tomorrow.
I saw the warning letter.
JNR receives nearly 10 duress letters a month.
And we get bomb threats every day.
But it's all harassment and pranks.
I think that letter was one of them.
It's serious.
He's a very smart guy to plant a bomb in a bathroom.
Why?
A bomb in an aisle or on a shelf would be easy to spot, but in a toilet, it's invisible.
To get it out, we'd need the time and the tools to disassemble the electricity.
And if he did it, he definitely succeeded
That man derailed a bullet train today.
And he's threatening to destroy it in nine days.
The only man who can arrest him is you. You're the only one out of 200,000 police officers in the country who can arrest him.
I'm not an agent.
You are a brilliant man who easily passed the bar exam national civil service exam and got into the police department.
That's why I sent you to study criminology in the United States and Europe for three years when I was Director.
I'm grateful for what you did, Mr. Director.
We created the Institute of Criminal Science in the National Police Agency and you became director... for what?
To use computers to solve crimes nationwide.
This case is perfect for you.
But it's only been nine days.
Can you find the killer among 100 million Japanese?
You can do it, but you're the only one who can.
Impossible. It's too hard
I'm asking you.
What's wrong?
Be quiet
This SHINKANSEN was supposed to stop at the Toyohashi station platform But it derailed.
Was it the brakes?
Why did it derail?
We don't know the cause.
SHINKANSEN derailed
Don't worry about that
It's me
SHINKANSEN derailed at Toyohashi?
Find out what caused it.
This is what he said
He's going to do it.
He's serious
If the bullet train is destroyed, there will be many victims.
Imagine a bullet train going 200 kilometers an hour and flipping over.
It's like a plane going down.
Not a single one of the 1,000 passengers on board will survive.
You don't care about it?
I'm taking care of it
Can you?
But will the Metropolitan Police Department or the prefectural police follow my lead?
It's an unprecedented case. It's an unprecedented case, so we're taking unprecedented measures.
I'll talk to the Metropolitan Police Department and the Prefectural Police Chief.
I'm just glad it was only a derailment and no one was injured.
How did the SHINKANSEN stop?
200 kilometers an hour.
Even if it stopped suddenly, it would still run 2500 meters.
If you'd applied the brakes even a little later, there would have been over 1,000 casualties.
Why didn't KODAMA stop at the platform?
The automatic control equipment at the atc and
Did the monitoring equipment at the ctc central command center malfunction?
Nope.
There was nothing wrong with either of them.
I applied the brakes as instructed.
It didn't work at all.
It didn't work at all?
We found the cause of the KOIDAM derailment.
Tell me
About 70 meters from the point on the main upstream line to the secondary line was coated with cooking oil.
cooking oil?
That's why the brakes didn't work and the train slipped.
But if he'd smeared oil on the rails, wouldn't someone see it right away and think it was suspicious?
But there were no witnesses.
He was disguised as a JNR worker.
And then this envelope, which was left in this position here somewhere.
It says "Warning Letter" on the front.
I've derailed it as you predicted.
atc and ctc are useless with a drop of oil
The oil could have been applied 3,000 meters before the main line.
In that case, the following HIKARI would have also slipped and hit KODAMA
Over a thousand people would have been killed or injured
But I don't want to kill a single innocent passenger
The bullet train will be destroyed in 9 days
Executioner
Shinkansen Threat Perpetrators Continue to Execute Kodama Toilet Bombs Toyohashi Train Derailment One After Another
The police department wanted to apprehend the perpetrators as soon as possible.
I'm Yamazaki, Chief of the Police Department's First Section.
Thanks
I'm SAGANO, Chief of the Public Safety Section of the Metropolitan Police
We heard from the commissioner.
I'm AKASI, Chief of the Public Safety Bureau, Aichi Prefectural Police Department.
I'm Chief Nakano, Aichi Prefectural Police Public Safety Section Chief.
I've been briefed by the Prefectural Police Chief.
I'm Murata, Chief of the Investigation Department.
Now, I'd like your opinion on who the culprit is.
He's knowledgeable about explosives and the bullet train.
So he's a student radical... or an activist?
If he was a radical, he would have blown up or overthrown the Shinkansen.
These two warning letters aren't making any ideological claims.
They're just complaints about the pollution caused by the Shinkansen.
Perhaps the culprits are residents or their passengers along the troubled Shinkansen line
Residents along the line in 20 prefectures from Tokyo to Hakata?
In fact, the same accident that caused this derailment Happened two years ago at the shinkansen base in Osaka.
When they greased the points of the retractable line, the brakes didn't work.
Who knows about that accident?
It was in the Osaka and Nagoya newspapers.
If that was a clue, the culprit was probably someone west of Hakone.
The pollution problem is a noisy one.
The Shin-Osaka to Hakata line has only been open for a short period of time, and more than half of it is through tunnels.
So there are no serious problems yet.
So it's between Osaka and Shizuoka.
Osaka, Gifu, Shizuoka and Hamamatsu have their own pollution problems.
But the residents are working it out with the JNR.
That leaves Aichi.
The culprits' demands are almost identical to those of the plaintiffs in the Shinkansen public disclosure lawsuit.
And these two warning letters use the same brown envelopes.
They're made by a manufacturer in Fuji City and sold by a paper shop in Nagoya.
Did you check the oil on the rails?
It is made by a manufacturer in Chiba and sold mainly in the Tokyo area.
So the culprit could be a Tokyo resident.
But I doubt about Nagoya.
It's a risky bet, of course.
We've only got nine days left until the execution.
That's not enough time
How many residents are members of the Nagoya anti-pollution league?
About 2,500 households.
Of these, the lawyers have identified 575 residents as having been harmed.
These are the plaintiffs in the Shinkansen pollution lawsuit.
Then, please start interviewing those 575 people immediately.
You've narrowed it down too much.
It's a risky bet,
I want you to pay particular attention to those with knowledge of explosives and drugs.
drugs?
Nitrochryslin is an ingredient in dynamite, but at the same
But it's also a first aid kit for angina pectoris.
I understand, sir, and the Aichi Prefectural Police will do everything in its power to help.
I'd like to hold a joint investigation meeting between the six of us, if necessary, in the future.
Will you cooperate?
Thanks to the bullet train, it's only two hours from Nagoya to Tokyo, and we can always make a quick turnaround.
Thank you.
When the Shinkansen comes, all the babies around here cry.
And when you get sick, you go to an ambulance or a doctor.
This noise really disturbs business
Our profit has decreased, so I want JNR to provide a guarantee.
When the Shinkansen passes, it makes a sound like thunder.
I feel like I live near a construction site.
The Shinkansen makes my hands shake at work
Even if you put on a comforter, the sound of the Shinkansen echoes in your head.
Shinkansen is like a murderer
Hi
I'm with the Aichi Prefectural Police, and I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Please come in.
The bullet train's too loud to talk here.
You were an employee of Aichi Pharmaceuticals.
You were a salesman.
Well, I'm a salesman in the simplest sense of the word.
I sell drugs to hospitals and members.
Did you sell nitroglycerin?
No, I specialize in new drugs.
By the way, you're a member of the plaintiffs' group in the Shinkansen pollution lawsuit?
You know what,I can't see the TV in this apartment.
I can't even sleep without taking sleeping pills.
I hear you're one of the bravest of the plaintiffs.
If you lose the case, you'll jump on a bullet train with dynamite on your back?
What on earth do you want to ask?
There was a vicious threat against the Shinkansen.
So you think I did it?
You mean I used nitroglycerin to threaten them?
Don't get us wrong
I'm confused. I'm short temper but
But I'm a sensible member of society.
I would never commit acts of violence or vandalism.
We have a scientific basis for our demands.
With this, we won't even lose in court.
There's no need to threaten me at all.
The reality of life disturbance by Shinkansen
Nagoya University School of Medicine
This is an accurate survey of radio interference, etc., measured by instruments and questionnaires.
I see.
I Looked at this report from 4 years ago!
I'm not the only one who suffers from Shinkansen pollution.
I realized that thousands of people were suffering from Shinkansen pollution. I started a united struggle with them.
It's a U.S. military one, after all.
they're very good
The Aichi Prefectural Police have cleaned out 575 plaintiffs in the pollution lawsuit group.
51 with knowledge of explosives and drugs.
Eight with questionable alibis.
I'm hoping to find the killer in this one.
What kind of man would that be?
I studied criminal psychology.
I'm always trying to figure out the killer's personality.
I'd love to hear what you think.
Ten days' notice to destroy the Shinkansen.He must be a very smart man or crazy
But his modus operandi is quite ingenious, and the warning letter was well-written.
He's an intelligent man with a very high level of education.
I would consider him a college graduate.
He's a quiet, stubborn, and thoughtful person.
Age 25 to 35.
Occupation?
Well, if he's an office worker, he's a member of the elite, but he's also very dynamic.
He's creative.
he must be a freelancer
Is he an academic, a lawyer, a doctor or an artist?
If he's a lawyer, he'll fight the law.
If he's an artist, he'll use the press.
He's an academic with a background in explosives and mechanics.
That would put him in touch with radical students.
A middle-schooler could build a bomb.
I'm more suspicious of the doctor.
Why?
15 cc nitroglycerin.
This?
Nitroglycerin is hard to come by, but you can always find it in the pharmacy of any major hospital.
Doctors can get it out?
Yes
I am very interested in the professor and two students of Nagoya University School of Medicine who wrote this report.
Please investigate about them
This is Sarugatari, my supervisor for this report.
This is Shinoshima-kun, who was in charge of the survey.
He's a resident at our university hospital.
Did you write the report?
No, I just supervised it. It was all Shinozima-kun's work.
Akiyama stayed up all night many times and worked hard all by himself.
I just helped out a little.
It's as if he did it all by himself.
It's a very well-written paper, and I was so impressed with it that I didn't touch it at all.
Akiyama is indeed doing his internship here in the Department of Internal Medicine.
He's not in Japan now.
He's traveling around Europe.
Europe?
It can't be helped
Is there anyone who is close to Mr. Akiyama?
He don't have any friends, but have a girlfriend.
girlfriend?
Tomoko Kimihara, our pharmacist.
She looks lonely.
I checked the alibis of the eight plaintiffs in the pollution control group.
They were all in Aichi the day before yesterday and the day before that.
Professor SARUQATARI and resident Dr. SHINOJIMA of Nagoya University's School of Medicine are also clean.
But I'm fascinated by the doctor who wrote this report, Akiyama.
He's very logical and has a strong sense of justice.
The conclusion is also quite radical.
This man would do it.
If his girlfriend is a pharmacist. Nitroglycerin would be easy to come by.
But he's not in Japan. He's traveling in Europe.
Europe?
Europe
I see.
Now let's see if his passport has been issued. Find out if he really left Japan.
I'll do that
I'm into him
Do a thorough background check and check his relatives and friends in Tokyo.
Hiroshi Akiyama?
Here
This picture is definitely Akiyama himself, isn't it?
Of course it is.
The passport application process has recently become much stricter.
I'm Hiroshi Akiyama's father. Something about his son?
it's about the bullet train pollution lawsuit.
He has been very interested in the subject since his school days.
How many siblings does he have?
He's the second son of three, and the oldest son runs the family sawmill.
He cuts and processes finances from our mountains.
How big is your mountain?
300m2
this place is so nice and old
How about 3rd one?
She is my daughter. She's married to the eldest son of a banker and they have one child.
Do you have any relatives in Nagoya or Osaka?
Two in the lumber business and a manager of a jewelry company.
Someone in Tokyo?
Takeo Suenaga.
He's studying electronics at Waseda University.
electronics?
take out Mr. Akiyama's medical records?
And while you're at it, could you also take his EKG and X-rays?
That's a problem.
As a doctor, I'd rather not.
I'm involved in a very important case.
Would you be willing to help us?
It can't be helped
Get me the medical records on Nogami, who died the other day.
It won't bother the patient.
Which part of Europe is Mr. Akiyama in right now?
Paris.
The airmail arrived yesterday.
paris
By the way, do you have a picture of him?
The one I like best.
May I see ?
Mr. Akiyama, are you a suspect in something?
But he's irrelevant.
He's not in Japan.
I'd like you to accompany me to prefectural police headquarters.
Why?
It's a violation of the Explosives Act.
You took 15 CCs of nitruklycerin out of the pharmacy.
I have no idea
Isn't that a mistake?
Nogami..This is Akiyama's medical record
Hiroshi Akiyama's cousin, Takeo Suenaga, was investigated I found out that he's been traveling in Europe for the past 10 days.
However, when we checked the immigration office.
He never left Japan.
How about Hiroshi Akiyama?
He flew to Europe ten days ago.
I need a photo of the two of them.
Cousins of the same age.
They look a lot alike.
But Akiyama doesn't wear glasses anymore.
He went to the trouble of wearing glasses for the photo.
To look like Suenaga and pass himself off as him.
It was Suenaga who went abroad using Akiyama's name and passport.
Akiyama is in Japan.
What about this postcard of Akiyama to Kimihara?
It's postmarked by the Paris Post Office.
You can get foreign postcards anywhere
Akiyama wrote them in Japan and Suenaga mailed them in Paris.
Please summarize the results of the Nagoya investigation.
First, 15 CCs of nitroglycerin.
We believe this was stolen by Tomoko Kimihara, a pharmacist at a higher hospital.
Second
Postcard addressed to Tomoko Kimihara
Clear fingerprints of Akiyama were taken from the medical records of Yasushi Nogami.
After comparing the fingerprints with those on the warning letter, we can conclude that they belong to the same person.
Third, the handwriting on the postcard with the warning letter
Writing pressure inclination degree
and hiragana in particular have something in common, and we believe that they are all written by the same person.
That's all I have to say.
Certainly, the medical record is the deciding factor.
I know how hard Akiyama worked to treat patients for 2 years.
But Yasu Nogami died.
He must have been angry from the bottom of his heart.
So he got his knowledge of the bullet train from his follower, Takeo Suenaga.
Where the hell is Akiyama?
Tokyo, I'm guessing.
The oil on the rails is only available in Tokyo.
He's an idiot
He's leaving all these clues.
He's young and confident.
Six more days.Tokyo's a big city.
Ten million people.
We'll see if he can find Akiyama.
From now on... It's all up to us now.
This is A warning letter received by the president of Japan National Railways.
in order to fundamentally solve the problem of bullet train pollution
I derailed a train with explosives and repeated warnings.
But the JNR authorities have never shown any sincerity.
My five-day notice of destruction is not a threat.
I will stop the Shinkansen once again tomorrow morning.
Executioner
He sent the same warning letters to three newspapers and NHK, as well as the president of Japan National Railways.
Where are you going?
I've got representatives from all the companies here right now.
I'm going to call off the press.
I need your help.
Chief of Police.According to this letter of warning...
The bomber used explosives and derailed the train twice to sabotage the bullet train.
Why did you keep it from us?
We have a duty to report the truth.
You put the public at risk, but you kept quiet.
My boss force me to report it
Right
But if it is publicized to the public, there will be imitators.
And there will be many similar incidents.
can you please stop reporting on this warning letter?
But what happens twice may happen thrice, and the culprit seems to be very tough.
In this way, the bullet train will be stopped tomorrow.
And in five days, it'll be completely destroyed.
If there's a major accident, we're in big trouble.
We have to inform the public and protect their lives.
That's the responsibility of the press.
I ask you all to trust the police.
We won't let them stop the bullet train.
We'll catch the culprits in 5 days
How far along are you in the investigation?
takigawa
We have a lead on the culprit, and we're working on his whereabouts.
Please Recognize our efforts.
Let's do this
If the bullet train doesn't stop tomorrow, we won't report it either.
But if the culprit stops the train, we will definitely report it.
How about this?
I agree.
If you are credible, we don't report it.
If we know it's not working, we'll publish.
That way we can protect our position.
And the public will understand.
This is a matter of honor for the National Police Agency.
Don't let him stop the bullet train tomorrow.
I can't guarantee that.
We might lose to the criminals.
Why?
Even if the bullet train stops tomorrow, there's no danger to human life.
The game is five days from now, when the train will be destroyed.
We should win at the end.
That's what I think.
Shinkansen receivers are designed to prevent confusing signal waves
Shinkansen receivers are sharp, within plus or minus five hertz.
163.07 megahertz.
If it picks up this signal, the train will automatically stop.
The bullet train stops.
How did you get Nitro?
You must have given it to Akiyama.
I don't know.
Mr. Sada, the director of the Shinkansen General Planning Department, is here tonight.
I'm Sanada
First of all, please consider how Akiyama will stop the bullet train tomorrow.
The quickest way is to plant explosives on the train.
How do you stop it with explosives?
Train tracks, of course.
27 atc ground signaling rooms at the ctc central command center.
28 radio stations
25 edification stations.
If any one of them blows up The train will stop even if any one of them is blown up.
What if a simple tool was used to destroy the tracks?
In that case, the current flowing through the rails would be cut off and the train would stop.
What if he dropped a large obstacle onto the tracks from a mountain, a hill, or a high road parallel to the tracks?
It would be detected immediately.
The staff has protective switches every 250 meters. Every 500 meters, he'll use the phone to stop any nearby bullet trains.
The culprit could use that switch phone to stop them.
What are the alternatives?
There are countless ways.
It's a bullet train, safety first.
For example?
A single conductor, two meters long, placed on the rails.
That'll stop it.
The rails make a circuit every three kilometers.
When a train enters the circuit, the current short-circuits it, and you know where it is.
So even if it's just one conductor, the current shorts out, and that's where the train is.
And it doesn't move.
Therefore, all the bullet trains coming after it will stop to avoid collision.
Only one line
Three empty cans and three wet rags will stop it.
How is this possible?
In the middle of the track, there's a thing that emits an automatic control signal every three kilometers.
If you put three empty cans and a wet rag over it
The train can't pick up the signal and still stops
It's easy to stop
It's hard to find a way
We can all be prevented if we're vigilant enough about the tracks and the expedition.
But even if we put a cop every 100 meters, that's a lot of cops.
That's a lot of cops.
We don't need to protect the entire Shinkansen.
This is my idea
We've narrowed it down to two crime scenes in Aichi and Shizuoka.
That's where Akiyama know
But those two prefectures alone are quite large.
Narrow it down even further... to the forested areas of both prefectures.
It's harder to spot and easier to escape.
Why not aim for the forest?
If he's in the mountains, hills or cliffs, he'll be in plain sight, surrounded and inescapable.
Let's just ignore them.
Aichi and Shizuoka are only about 100 kilometers from the forested area.
That's enough to protect 2,000 police officers.
Please call the prefectural police in both prefectures.
I'm making a lot of bets, but it's the nature of the case.
I'd like to make one more bet.
The warning letter is postmarked at the Central Post Office.
I still think Akiyama is in Tokyo.
When is he moving to Shizuoka or Aichi?
He's going to stop the train tomorrow morning, so tonight.
He could be there already.
I'd say he'll be on the move early tomorrow morning.
It's easy to hide in the big city of Tokyo.
In the countryside, he's more visible.
He'll show up at the scene of the crime right before he does it.
I agree
What would he use next to leave Tokyo?
If he were to approach the bullet train quickly and make a hasty getaway, he'd need a small, fast car with good maneuverability.
How would he get there?
He can easily rent a car.
Then let's make a decision.
Akiyama will rent a car tomorrow morning, get out of Tokyo, and head to Aichi.
Find a rental car company in Tokyo and get Akiyama to rent a car.
Understood.
Then checkpoints on the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd Keihin, Tomei Expressway, and other highways.
Do not let Akiyama go west of Tamagawa!
I'll mobilize all the police officers in the Metropolitan Police Department.
Let me see your license
Go ahead
Hiroshi Akiyama?
I haven't seen him
Thank you
How was it?
There wasn't
Have you seen him?
I haven't seen him
Shibuya?
Akiyama is not coming?
Any car rental company?Don't give up.
He didn't come to Shibuya and Gotanda.I wonder how he escaped from Tokyo
Mr.Suenaga?
Here you go.
Safe drive
I'll drop you off at the Hamamatsu office after lunch.
Thank you very much.
163.07 megahertz
Signal radio wave with zero speed
bullet train...please get it
and stop
He stopped the bullet train.
You are lost.
We'll be sure to report it
We're going to announce every warning we've given the last two times, every destruction threat in the next four days.
It's for the public's safety.
It can't be helped
You must have had a lot of security.
How could the he has outsmarted you?
Takigawa
I'll explain
He is believed to have sent a 163.07 megahertz speed zero signal radio wave from his rental car while driving on the highway, stopping the bullet train.
You didn't foresee that crime at all?
We checked out rental cars in Tokyo, but we didn't get around to the rural areas.
We finally figured out what the killer was doing after the incident occurred.
163.07 megahertz is a zero speed signal.
Is this a JNR secret?
No, it's in a publication about bullet trains
Then you could have done something about it.
It was a total failure. There's no room for visitors.
There's no excuse for this. I apologize.
Apologies don't cut it.
What about the bullet train six days from now?
Can you prevent it?
We are trying to prevent it.
You can't say you're going to prevent it.
I'd like you to say you'll definitely prevent it.
I can't
You can't?
Because I hate the word "never.
You can't count on us
They'll lose again
I have a big announcement to make at the end.
big announcement?
The police have identified the perpetrator of this crime as 28-year-old Hiroshi Akiyama, a resident of Nagoya High School Hospital, and have issued a nationwide manhunt.
The car used in the crime was found in front of Hamamatsu Station.
But We still don't know where's Akiyama now
Police will...
I'll be away on a trip on the 23rd.
Please take care of my house while I'm gone.
Have a nice trip
Commissioner of Police
Are you really confident that you can arrest Akiyama?
200,000 police officers are currently pursuing his whereabouts.
It's only a matter of time before they arrest him.
We can't allow the anti-pollution movement to turn violent.
But even if you put out a nationwide manhunt, there are still 10,000 people who can't be caught.
The arrest rate is declining, but it's still the highest in the world.
I have no doubt in the high caliber of Japanese police officers... and their enthusiasm and hard work.
How can we count on you?
President of the National Government
The Central Pollution Control Council has already recommended that the noise level of the Shinkansen should be less than 70 lines in urban areas and 75 lines in small industrial areas.
Why don't you grant Akiyama's request?
The Pollution Control Council's recommendation is very sincere.
We will give it our full consideration.
But unfortunately, it is impossible to do so immediately with the current JNR's strength alone.
So you don't mind if the Shinkansen is destroyed in four days?
If a bullet train derails and overturns
At least a thousand people would die.
If another train were to collide with it. The number of victims will rise from 2,000 to 3,000 in one fell swoop.
It'll be the biggest accident in the world.
It'll be the biggest event in the history of the world.
Prime minister,Minister of Transportation
Can a government that controls the lives of its citizens allow this to happen?
I call for the total resignation of the cabinet.
We agree
This concludes our live coverage of the House of Representatives Committee on Special Programs.
Nice work, Akiyama.
He's a big guy for a 28 year old.
He's good medicine for the JNR.
Maybe they'll reconsider.
After all, they're up against something big. They're the Japanese National Railways.
It's more interesting than a bad boxing match.
How much?
1700yen
The government could not refute anything pursued by the opposition.Government Fails to Take Any Effective Steps to Address Shinkansen Destruction Threats
The seriousness of the pollution problem caused by the Shinkansen has been highlighted once again
The culprit, Hiroshi Akiyama, was born in Mukoda Town, Aichi Prefecture
News about Akiyama again?
It's too noisy
Young people these days don't have enough hardship and patience.
If they don't like something, they start bombing and demonstrating.
He doesn’t care what we are in trouble
Turn off the TV.
Akiyama went to Nagoya University Medical School.
Another drink?
I'll have it
Can I get one too?
Sure
You look lonely.
Do I look lonely?
What's your name?
I'm Fumiko.
I'm Miki
Nice to meet you, Miki.
You have nice skin and eyes.
You think so?
You don't have confident?
I don’t have, I'm broken heart
He was 3rd one. oh it's 11pm, time to close
Wanna go out?
Wanna come my apartment?
Is this your book?
Yes, I used to be a nurse.
Internal medicine?
Same as you,right?
You told me fake name
Hiroshi Akiyama
You're being chased by the police and have nowhere to stay.
You'll be safe here.
I make you trouble
Don't worry
I like the way you do
I don't want to be alone tonight.
Stay with me
You know, I used to think that all doctors were hypocrites.
That's what I thought.
So you got cheated out?
That's why I quit nursing.
I've only been a hostess for six months.
I've been a hostess for six months, and all men are jerks.
But you're so admirable.
Normal doctors ignore bullet train pollution.
They are selfish or something
I'm glad I met you
I'm gonna get drunk tonight.
Stay with me
The vandalism threats have caused a great deal of unrest within the JNR.
The union filed a motion to compel this morning.
We don't know what will happen on the day.
Therefore, unless the culprit is arrested beforehand.
Unless the culprit is arrested in advance, we will refuse to board the bullet train on the day of the notice.
The bullet train will not run at all.
That's not good.
Shinkansen is Japan's main artery and a pillar of the Japanese economy.
Shinkansen is not only for JNR anymore, it belongs to Japan, to the people.
We should operate
Why do you think so?
I will talk it over with the union and get them to withdraw their refusal to let me on the train.
But there's nothing we can do if the bullet train is stopped that day.
Takigawa-kun, who commands the Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department and the prefectural police.
Can he be trusted?
Don't worry.
Takigawa is the best man in the National Police Agency.
He's the only one who can solve this case.
We need him
I'm Hiroshi Akiyama.
Akiyama?
I know it's late at night and I don't mean to be rude, but I'm a wanted man and I can only move at night.
I need to speak to you
you're bold
You'll be arrested
Do you wan to notify the police?
I'm not police
You're challenging JNR. I will discuss it with you as the person in charge of
Come in.
I'd offer you some tea, but
My wife's in bed with a backache and the nanny's taking a bath.
You know how the residents along the Shinkansen line are suffering.
Mr. Akiyama
Japan was in a period of rapid economic growth at the time.
We had to build the Shinkansen in time for the Olympics.
It was a rush job, so there was no time to think about the pollution problem.
But the residents along the line have already been suing since six months after the opening.
You let it go for more than 10 years.
JNR's management is also having a hard time.
Currently, they have an accumulated deficit of 1.3 trillion yen.
And it will probably increase by about 100 billion yen every year.
It's very unfortunate, but the reality is that we can't even provide for pollution as much as we'd like.
The Shinkansen had a profit of 650 billion yen by 1973.
Can't you use the profit to solve the pollution?
If we reduce the speed of the Shinkansen to 70 kilometers per hour as you demand...
Sure, the noise will be 60 horns and the vibration will be 0.6 mm.
But it can't carry 350,000 passengers a day!
What about creating a 50 meter wide interference zone on both sides of the tracks?
It would cost enough money to build another Shinkansen just to acquire that land.
However, it is possible to acquire the land little by little.
From people who hurt the people along the line and get away with it.
It's an example of the vice of getting land cheaply.
Ideals can't be achieved in one fell swoop.
I'm going to take my time and solve this problem step by step.
I can't believe it
That's why I'm destroying the bullet train.
Nothing can be changed
If nothing changes, another Akiyama will come out.and do the same thing until the JNR regrets what it's done.
I'm sorry, but I'm more troubled by this than you are
Japan's problems are full of contradictions. Do you really believe that Japan's problems can be solved only by simple idealism like yours?
I am not an idealist.
I'm a doctor who can't even save a human life.
Mr. President, have you ever lived with 100 horns of noise?
Let you listen something.
My patients have died because of it.
Three days from now, 12:00 noon.
At 12:00 sharp, I'll be done with the plan.
This is your last notice.
You're going to do this by any means necessary?
You're not going to fight us in court?
I don't trust the courts.
The powers that be will intervene.
Mr. Akiyama, I think your request is correct.
I'd like to do the same if I could.
But let me make this clear.
Destroying the Shinkansen is a criminal act.
You don't want innocent passengers to be involved.
If you're worried... Please don't let any passengers on board.
We can't
Then I'll have you take responsibility.
Of course I'll take responsibility.
But how about you?
I don't care what happens.
I can't believe he even went to the JNR president's mansion.
That Akiyama guy's got no respect for me.
He's very active
Tapes.
recording Tapes.
Tape?
Akiyama taped his conversation with the President and brought it to TV Tokyo.
They're going to air the tape today at 3:00 p.m. on TV Tokyo.
Akiyama just wants to use the media to spread the word about Shinkansen pollution.
Let's leave him alone.
But he's a wanted criminal.
I don't know if it's okay for him to move around so much and do whatever he wants.
What do you think?
Sure, he keeps winning, and he's lucky.
But luck doesn't last forever.
It's time to fall out of luck and lose.
You're so carefree.
Anyway, I'd like to meet with the station's programming director and the director of the TV station to get them to stop the show.
Come with me.
Mr. President, have you ever lived with 100 horns of noise?
Let you listen something.
My patients have died because of it.
Akiyama is the single most talked-about person in Japan today.
It's the real voice of the President of the Japanese National Railways.
We want this tape aired.
How did you get it?
Akiyama called me, the director, just after 9:00 a.m.
If you want the tape, it's in the coffee shop in front of the station.
He said to pick it up under the name Miki.
This is it?
That's right.
Who left the tape with you?
Akiyama himself.
To be safe,I showed the waitress Akiyama's picture to confirm.
But if this is aired, there will be distrust of the police.
And social unrest will increase.
The president will want to take this off the air.
Anyway, I'll have him pick up the phone and you'll talk it over.
I didn't know we had it on tape.
But there's no need to stop the TV station from airing it.
I take full responsibility.
I want you to do everything in your power to stop the crime the day after tomorrow.
I beg you.
We left Tokyo at 9.20pm.
You did a great job driving for more than 5 hours!
Where are you going now?
Sakanozaka Tunnel.
Nothing has changed.
It's the same as it was in the old days.
This is Saka no Saka Next to Nukatamachi.
This is where I was born.
There's a sawmill on the outskirts of town.
What are you going to do now?
Do you want to go to the motel Royal Plaza in Nagoya that we decided on earlier?
Why don't you go ahead and stay there under an assumed name?
I'll come back later.
I'll be waiting for you.
Who?
It's me.
You're late.
I had to return the truck to the sawmill.
I couldn't get a cab.
What do you use a bulldozer for?
You don't have to know.
Drop a stone down the hill?
I'm exhausted
Let's take a bath and go to bed.
Hello?
Takigawa
It's finally tomorrow, isn't it?
What's the security plan?
Akiyama says he'll shut down the bullet train for at least two days, paralyzing it for at least two weeks.
The question is how.
It's got to be a train derail and overturn
If he does it, at least 1,000 people will die.
I don't think Akiyama would kill someone.
But he's cornered, and there's no telling what he'll do.
But what kind of method would he use to derail and overturn a train?
Drop a truck or a car on the tracks.
And hit the bullet train?
If he drop it early enough, the warden will spot it and stop the train immediately.
If the obstacle is an electric double-acting object, the moment it is dropped, the electric current in the circuit will short-circuit.
The bullet train will stop and won't collide.
At 200 km/h, the train will run 2,500 meters even if the brakes are applied.
He could drop the train when it approaches within 2,500 meters.
Or hit the train itself while it's in progress.
Takigawa. Make sure you prevent the train from derailing and capsizing.
Now, this time, instead of the forested dirt.
We'll focus our security on the mountains and hills, where there are more cutouts.
It's easier to drop obstacles, and Akiyama won't mind being arrested.
Where do you think the crime took place?
I still think Shizuoka and Aichi prefectures.
I'm thinking Shizuoka and Aichi prefectures.
We'll be on high alert in those areas.
Mishima Tago, which has many cut-through sections, as a priority area.
Hoshigoe Tunnel and Saka-no-Saka Tunnel on Mikawa Bay
Okehazama Tunnel near Nagoya.
In both cases, two officers each at the exit entrances to the tunnel
Along the line will be 2 policemen on each side every 100 meters
How many police officers will be mobilized?
80,000.
That's a lot of men.
I'm going to Nagoya with Mr. Nakano and Mr. Murata
It's Akiyama's hometown. He knows the geography. It's an easy place to execute.
I guess I can really trust you?
It's time to return the favor.
Don't worry.
Two days in there, we gonna look suspicious
Let's move
You want to move on to another motor?
yeah, they don't see any customers.
Tomorrow at 12:00, are you sure you want to do?
Yeah
You're gonna get caught, and you're gonna go to jail.
I'm ready.
Stop it
Why?
I love you so
I want to live with you.
I can't
Why would you want that?
Yeah
You just played me
That's better
We shouldn't be more than that.
Results of Collective Bargaining
The union has withdrawn their refusal to let me on tomorrow.
Okay.
Thank you very much
But there's one condition.
The Japanese National Railways, the labor unions, the pollution victims, and representatives from the four companies.
We'd like you to form a special committee to come up with a real solution to the pollution problem.
Of course I agree.
Tomorrow the police will be on full alert to prevent any accident.
can you do it?
I assure you I'll take care of it.
Thank you very much for your time.
The bullet trains will continue to run as usual.
Tell that to the PR director.
Security in Shizuoka is complete What about security in Aichi?
We've mobilized all the former detectives of the Aichi Prefectural Metropolitan Police Agency to be on high alert.
I always think about the quality of our officers.
Many of them are good, but many of them are idiots.
Which one of them will bump into Akiyama?
It's all luck.
There's nothing we can do.
he can be apprehended with the slightest clue.
A good cop can find him, but a stupid man can miss him.
If you see anything out of the ordinary. If something unusual happens, will you let me know right away?
The streets are full of cops.
What course did you take up the hill?
I took a cab from the Komaki interchange to the highway.
The cops at the entrance took a look at the wanted photos.
Same thing on the way out from the Toyokawa interchange.
I knew it. Route 1.
Through Kityu and into Okazaki.
Route 1 has the toughest checkpoints.
They look in the trunk and under the seat.
That's why it's okay.
The cops won't think we're going down Route 1.
Shall we go?
Hello?
2411391
You sure to go?
Hello?
Is it a blood center?
I have a 9:00 a.m. surgery at the First Hospital in Midorimachi, so I need 1,000 cc of type A blood at 8:30 a.m. I need you there at 8:30.
To where
To Dr. ONOMI of surgery
9 o'clock at Meitetsu's Miya station.
9 o'clock
Where to?
Emergency blood transport to Okazaki Hospital
You have to wear helmet when you drive an emergency vehicle.
I was in a hurry. I forgot.
Be careful next time.
Okay, go.
Go left, go left.
Stop
Sorry
What?
surgery is at 9:00 a.m. Can I go to the
Where's the hospital?
It's right there, Okazaki Hospital.
What's that bag?
This?
What's in it?
I was told to deliver it as soon as I got to work.
A change of sweaters and a book to read on the train.
Don't need to open,
Go
Thanks
So nothing's happened yet?
Well, the only incident was the theft of a blood truck.
blood truck?
It was used to transport blood from a blood bank to Midorimachi First Hospital.
The hospital doesn't remember ordering it, and it's not scheduled for surgery.
And there was no surgery scheduled.
The car was stolen during the dispute.
That's it.
Akiyama got in the blood truck and drove through the checkpoint.
Please get ready right away.
We get it
he is a doctor.
Good idea
Police car
Go left and stop,This car is safe.
When I get into GAMAGORI, I  buy me a bike and a work thing.
Then work shoes and a yellow helmet.
The dirtier the better.
The blood truck was abandoned in front of Miyagi Station on the Meitetsu Line.
Fingerprints in the car confirm that Akiyama was the driver.
He's now within 17 kilometers of GAMAGORI and TOYOHASHI.
We are finding him
He might change cars.
Stay alert from Kiyu to Hamamatsu.
I get it
By the way, Akiyama's parents live in Nukatamachi.
Yes,
I'd like to go there.
Why are you going there?
He has three hours to stop the bullet train before noon.
We've done what we had to do, and there's nothing to do here.
But
I've been thinking only about Akiyama for the past 10 days.
He's more like friend now
I'm just trying to get a sense of who he is
Thank you for everything.
You can leave now.
Don't follow me or you'll be an accomplice.
I don't care.
I knew it all along.
Stupid
I love you
Go home
Go back to Tokyo.
Good luck, I won't forget about you
See you
I am so sorry.
I've been confined to my house since he was declared wanted, and now I'm under house arrest.
How did he turn out like that?
He used to be such a sweet, cheerful boy.
Did he come back here from time to time?
Not at all.
He used to come back every summer vacation when he was a student to help his oldest son in the lumber business.
He would move trucks and bulldozers.
Trucks and bulldozers?
Where is it?
I'd like to take a look at it.
Where are you going?
The road's closed from now on.
Oh my god,I came here to get that Bulldozer.
You can't just throw him out there like that.
We've been trying to find the owner since yesterday.
I'm sorry, I'll move it soon
Go
Thank you for your hard work.
What's up with you?
I was told by that police down there
That Bulldozer.
Get it out of here.
This one doesn't work... it's got a chain wrapped around the controller.
It's wrapped around a wire too!
I'm so screwed!
I have to get the keys from the director!
What group are you with? I haven't seen you around
I just came from Toyohashi today
Harada Civil Engineering
You look like him.
Who?
The culprit.
Don't joke about it.
I've got kid and wife
Here it is
There's no bulldozer.
They are always lined up here.
How much does the bulldozer weigh?
About 10 tons.
Come
Contact Mr. Murata
Find me a bulldozer near the Shinkansen by helicopter.
Let me radio in.
Hello, please, Chief I, President of the General Command Center.
We found bulldozer  in the Sakanozaka Tunnel.
Tomoko Kitahara is still in detention?
Ask Murata to bring her out there
There's nothing I can say
Nothing
Get in the car
Akiyama
Bulldozers are abandoned and can't be driven.
Destroying the bullet train is impossible.
Why don't you just give up on the plan and come out?
Can you catch me?
Akiyama
Kimihara
I'm trying to help Mr. Akiyama.
He's going to drop a bulldozer on the tracks.
Please tell him to stop!
He listen to you
Hiroshi
That's over
Please get out
The engine started.
It's not supposed to run.
It's radio controlled.
Hop in the driver's seat.
Pull the key out of the engine.
Get the police car to close it.
Jumping into a bulldozer from the top of the car
Jumping into a bulldozer
Pull the key out of the engine.
Akiyama
The bulldozer won't work anymore
so come out gracefully like you.
Akiyama
THE END