Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Doshaburi / When It Rains, It Pours (1957)
Thank you very much.
Hurry up, or you'll be late.
Mother.
Present for you.
I got a little raise this month.
That's great.
What's this?
This is so great.
I can still use my current purse.
Old wallets are bad luck.
Why?
All the money goes out.
You know, that's funny.
Wake up!
or you'll be late.
Bros!
It's too early.
Wake up!
Damn it!
What are you doing?
My hair's a mess.
Let's go!
You are stupid.
I'm going.
Can you get home early?
It could be.
Your father's on his way back from Hokkaido.
I'll be home soon.
I'm off too.
Take care.
Please serve fish.
Damn it!
Thank you very much.
(I'll wait for you at that restaurant)
There's something I wanted to talk to you guys about today.
I asked Sudo-kun to join us.
Have a seat.
Be relax.
Actually... it's about you two.
No, it's not a bad thing.
Right,Sudo?
He's very concerned about us, and he's aware of our relationship.
There's a rumor going around the company about you guys.
How about a workplace marriage?
Let me think about it.
I've known him since he was a little boy.
He was crying boy.
Don't talk about that.
And, you know, his mom asked me if I could help him find someone.
You sure you don't want me to handle this?
I'll leave it to you, sir.
Ok.
I'm sorry to worry you.
It's nice to see young people being so active.
I envy you guys.
Your place is an inn?
It's a small place, but we've always had a lot of regular customers.
I think its good business practice.
There are a lot of strange guests these days.
How's your parents?
My father died when I was a kid.
I'm sorry.
By Cerebral anemia.
You were raised by your mother, weren't you?
Yes.
Hey, three mugs.
I can't drink anymore.
Just one more for us.
Thanks.
She can drink.
How much can you drink?
She can drink 5 mugs.
5 mugs?
Let's toast for your work place marriage.
I can't drink 5 mugs.
He was surprised.
Exemplary workplace marriage.
I worry..
For what?
You're so happy, it's kind of scary.
You worry too much.
I got drunk.
Are you alright?
Let's get some rest.
I want to be a good wife.
I want two strong boys and a beautiful girl.
Let's go see your mother now.
We'll surprise her by telling her about today.
We can't.
Why?
I've never been to your house.
Not tonight.
I'll tell her all about it.
I'll call you one of these days.
Wait till then.
Good evening.
Welcome.
Do you have a room where I usually stay?
Please come in.
Come in, boy.
Take them to Kiri room.
Please come in.
It seems your business is busy.
Thank you very much.
This is a souvenir from Hakodate.
This is awesome.
You like it.
Thank you very much.
I'll serve you a sake.
Have a seat.
I'm so tired.
Can you rub my shoulders for a minute?
Thank you.
The bath is ready.
What do you want?
I'm starving.
Let's get something to eat first.
He's so selfish, isn't he?
Thank you.
She took different boy.
Who's she?
A madam?
I have no idea.
I'm home.
I've brought these today.
Oh dad is here?
He's just come.
I can drink again.
Serve him.
Welcome home.
Where have you been?
Pachinko.
I walked there.
I got this for 30yen.
How about eating this.
Have a drink?
Thank you very much.
Where's Matsuko?
She said she was going home early today.
What's the hell?
It's spring.
A customer ordered tamagoyaki (fried egg) and unadon (bowl of rice topped with eel)
The woman is strange.
You have a bad idea.
She sleeps with a guy every night.
Hello?
This is Kotobuki.
Our customer ordered tamagoyaki (fried egg) and unadon (bowl of rice topped with eel)
I had a dream about my father.
What dream?
You were dancing with the Ainu.
That's a weird dream.
But your business is romantic, too.
You roam Hokkaido, buying bear pelts.
Wait Yamada.
I was kidding.
Stop doing it.
Get your hands off of me!
Wait Yamada.
I leave the fee.
It's not very educational.
I think you're right that buying this house and letting your mother run the business was a great idea.
Sarcasm?
I'm just being honest.
I'm grateful.
This business is the only reason we are able to eat without any inconvenience, apparently.
But sometimes I wonder if I'm doing the right thing.
Seeing so many strange customers drives me crazy.
You don't have to talk about it now.
Your father comes by once in a while.
He might be right.
But that doesn't mean there's nothing we can do about it.
Let's keep the world interesting.
It's time to go.
It's time he leaves.
Why don't you stay over?
Just tonight.
Don't make him confuse.
See you.
I wanted to see Matsuko.
Say hello to her.
I'll come next week.
Take care.
See you.
Oh Matsuko?
Oh dad.
I've been waiting for you.
Sorry I'm late.
Did you go to movie or somewhere?
No.
I'm so happy about something that happened today.
What's that?
I'll tell you about it.
I'd like to hear.
Let's walk to the park.
That's good.
I'm just glad you guys are happy.
I made a lie.
What?
I told him you died.
I told him that.
Oh I see.
I told him you died of cerebral anemia.
What?
I would have preferred another disease.
Sorry.
It can't be helped.
It's hard to tell my mother about this.
I'll tell her later.
Dad.
I don't know if it's gonna be okay.
It's going to be fine.
If you really love each other.
I wish you the best.
Thank you. Good night.
Good night.
Excuse me.
Do you have a neighbor named Abe?
Abe?
Tame Abe.
Oh Otame.
She run inn.
It's a inn but just small.
It's over there.
They are busy.
When I look at it this way, I see all kinds of people coming in.
People like street girl, gang,Madam etc.
They look so nonchalant, like they're walking into a buckwheat noodle shop.
You'd be surprised, wouldn't you?
I want you to be more flexible.
Just 3.
Thank you very much.
Kameyama is crazy about this.
I'm mad at him.
I'm in trouble.
Get along well with your suppliers.
Unlike your business, it's hard to make a day's wage.
We have a hard time too.
You can keep this as collateral.
You don't have to do that.
You look happy.
Your husband buy this house for you.
Your kids are nice.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
There's a room available.
Please come in.
You have a guest even in the noon.
Don't look at her.
What kind of person is she?
It's a strange world.
Come in.
It's nice weather.
Are you alone?
Someone will come later?
I'll serve you a tea.
Let's have a nap before sex.
I don't have sex with you.
Hey, you dance at bar.
You damn it.
She's kind of weird.
I see.
I'll serve her.
Excuse me.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm starving.
I need to talk to you.
What?
Let's talk in front of your father.
When your father died, he made a will that you be raised to be a man of honor.
I know.
I'm relying on you alone.
Okay, then.
I firmly declined the Chief's offer on the phone earlier.
I absolutely disapprove.
You didn't even ask me for a word of advice.
I don't need to talk to you.
You lied to me.
What?
Her house run Love hotel.
Her mother is kind of mistress.
I can't believe it.
She told me they run old inn.
There must be some kind of mistake.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
I've never been so embarrassed in my life.
She didn't have to tell a lie.
You are ignorance.
You don't know what is the world nowadays.
I'm mad at your chief too.
He is making a fool of me.
That's enough.
Sorry I'm late.
Did you wait?
40min.
Sorry.
Give us 2 mugs.
What do you want to talk?
You seem annoyed to see me these days, don't you?
What are you talking about?
Your Chief told me today.
He said you're in a relationship with someone else.
I heard she's the daughter of an executive from a very nice family.
She's younger than me.
Why didn't you tell me?
Here it is.
Never mind.
I'm bad.
Why you lied to me?
About your house.
You should have told me earlier.
I was going to tell you.
I just couldn't say it.
Why don't we talk about it over dinner?
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
It's none of her business.
It's up to you.
That woman or me?
That's what I'm asking you.
You need to clarify.
It's too late.
It's ok if you go home first.
I'll send you off.
So come to my home.
Meet my mom.
Onsen Mark
You don't know that.
We get all kinds of visitors.
Come on, I'll show you.
Well, I guess we can't get married... time to say goodbye.
Let's say goodbye.
Oh my god.
Welcome back.
You're late as usual.
Hey, Dad bring something nice for you.
She's a funny girl.
Are you upset today?
I'll give you this.
Try this on.
Good.
This ring is a gift for you.
I was waiting for you to come home so I could tell your mom about the other day.
Forget about that.
Why?
I'll talk to my mom.
I'll talk to her.
All I have is my mom.
Oh yeah.
I'm supposed to be dead.
Anyway let's have a drink.
Where takenosuke's been?
We have to go home.
It's better late.
Our dad is at home today.
Oh yeah.
Kids are so difficult when they grow up.
How's their kids?
I'm always at Nihonbash home.
Over here it's their dad once a week.
I feel sorry for them.
I'd like to be their sounding board.
but Something's just not right.
Probably because I feel guilty.
But the kids are very dependent on their father.
When they get older, a female parent isn't good enough.
I'm an unreliable dad.
What's wrong with Matsuko..
What's wrong?
She's 24?
25.
Oh right.
Matsuko was already born when you were 25 years old.
Takenosuke was in your stomach.
Time goes fast.
25 years.
I've put you through a lot.
Let's go have a drink.
I wanna drink too.
Can you drink lately?
Yes kind of.
I wanna drink more.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Dad, you have no right to say anything.
OK.
Well, if that's what you want, I won't say anything.
I'm just trying to get to know you guys as best I can.
You're all grown up now, and you're gonna run into things.
I'm just trying to be a sounding board.
I know exactly what you mean.
Well, then you're gonna have to tell me everything.
In your long life, you will encounter many problems that you can't handle on your own.
I will handle it myself.
I don't need anyone else to take care of it.
Watch your mouth.
She's in bad mood.
Let's talk about it later.
I'll see him off.
It's your job.
You take a bath.
I don't take a bath at home.
You're going out.
You take a bath.
Take care.
I'm going.
I'll take a bath.
Good evening.
Is there room available.
Hey.
I know you are there.
Sis
(It's some kind of spell)
God told me that he ran toward Tatsumi, but he'll be back shortly
Tatsumi?
North or south.
Either way, he's going home soon. You shouldn't worry too much.
Busy, busy.
Welcome home.
How'd it go?
the police are really unreliable.
Welcome home.
I've been looking all over the place, but I can't find her at all.
Sorry.
Don't get me wrong.
Is there anything else that comes to mind with Matsuko?
For example, did Matsuko's behavior seem strange or something?
Come to think of it, she ran away from home, got strangely frustrated, got into a fight with her dad.
she has a relationship with a man.
It must be so.
they might have eloped.
They are together.
Shut up.
Do you know any other guys who dated Matsuko?
I don't know anything about that.
Even if that were the case, I don't think she would elope.
I don't think she would do something like that because she is very serious.
She's not like us.
We eloped before, didn't we?
Shut up.
You talk too much.
I wonder where she went.
You have a guest.
It's been a while.
How did you know here?
Ueno-san told us about your location.
Oh Ueno.
I told him not to say anything.
Wanna drink?
You've changed.
I've been living like this for two years.
I'm not supposed to change.
I've missed you.
What's the hell?
Let's dance.
What's the matter?
I don't want to dance.
You're a funny guy.
Business trip?
Kind of.
You keep staring at my face.
I need to talk to you.
I don't wanna talk.
Have a drink.
Here.
Thanks.
I can't help it... you're drunk as a skunk.
You changed yourself too.
I'm leaving.
I'll see you some other time if we have a chance.
See you.
Don't make fun of me!
I'm leaving.
What are you going to do with me?
I could still see it from my window.
You know?
That symbol is still a dark memory in my mind.
I know that now.
How you hid your business.
It's too late for that.
You have a wife.
You're going to have kids.
But ever since I was found by the authorities in that cabaret.
I knew you'd come for me one day, and I knew this would happen.
I can't go back to Tokyo anymore.
Why?
I need you to hide me for a while.
Someone chase me.
What's wrong?
Did you do something wrong?
Did you have something to do with this?
Only lower-ranking employees like me are arrested.
I wanted to see you one more time before I got caught.
What are you thinking?
About your wife?
or baby?
Don't say bullshit.
You still think of them when you're away like this, don't you?
I know what's in your heart.
You want to go back to Tokyo?
You want to go home.
It's written all over your face.
I want to go home.
I don't want to spend every day in this cramped place.
The police will arrest you as soon as you leave.
I won't return you alone again.
I won't let you go this time, no matter what happens.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm going to work.
You don't have a cigarette, do you?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
There's a ham in the cupboard.
What's wrong?
The police are just investigating the family register.
You really don't know this Sudo guy?
No.
And my daughter is with the Sudo?
She's just hiding him.
The man is still at large on bribery charges.
I think he's going back to Tokyo anyway.
If he stops by your place, or if you know where he is, please give us a call.
I heard he was hiding out with your daughter in Kobe for quite a while.
He flew to Kyoto, apparently, when he was spotted.
Are you sure he hasn't come to your house?
No.
Thank you very much.
She fell for the wrong guy.
After two years, we finally find out where she is, and now this.
Well, it's a good thing she's okay.
The guy is called Sudo?
The man has a wife and a newborn baby.
I think she has a very deep relationship with him.
Don't worry too much.
I'm going to Kyoto at the end of this month.
I'll see what I can find out.
Thanks.
Cheer up.
I'll ask God.
Oh again.
Stop doing it.
That god is of no use.
Don't ask the god.
Look at that.
As God told us, we purchased a lot of that product.
But they doesn't sell out.
Because you bought a bad product.
You have an old way of thinking.
Don't blame others.
Please eat.
Don't worry too much.
Cheer up.
I know Matsuko would have had a hard time with that.
A woman's failure with a man is a life experience.
I've been having a hard time since I married him.
Don't say that.
Have a drink.
She likes Sushi.
She likes Wasabi too.
She's really good girl..
Give me a beer.
I don't drink coffee.
you haven't paid your accounts receivable yet.
What are you doing?
Come here.
We don't go to school because the weather is nice.
I'll play you some good music.
Can you hear?
It's noisy.
Oh.
Is this fine?
What?
You said it was noisy.
I mean this article.
What?
Why don't you at least read the paper once in a while?
Our tax dollars are being spent by government officials.
You pay tax?
Taxes on cigarettes and beer are rising rapidly.
So don't have a beer.
Shut up!
The love hotel business is becoming more difficult.
Will taxes go up?
It seems that the operation of love hotels near schools will be prohibited.
Do you also manage a love hotel?
If you come, I will give you a 200 yen discount.
You're dirty.
This.
Shall we go eat this ramen?
Treat me.
Let's go to cinema after we eat ramen.
Will you also pay for the movie?
You have money, don't you?
You're so smart.
Let's go home then.
I'll pay.
I see.
You'll pay for me later.
You're so smart too.
Let's go.
His wife cries every day
And she has a child.
I really don't know what to do.
I’m sorry.
He was a serious boy.
He was loved by his superiors in the government office.
I, too, have been looking forward to the future.
You know what they say about the woman behind the crime.
He became corrupt because your daughter lured him away.
Are you saying that our Matsuko seduced Kazuo-san and got caught up in corruption?
I can't think of anything else.
I have a letter from Kazuo.
A letter?
My son would like to come home, but Matsuko won't let him go and he's in trouble.
If you like, I can show you this letter.
Perhaps because I raised him with my own hands, he's a bit naive.
he was controlled by her.
Does the family of the daughter who does this kind of dirty business have a relationship with a man who has a wife and children?
Mom.
Our father is here.
The postmark is in Tokyo, so he must be somewhere in Tokyo.
Tokyo?
When Matsuko arrives, please ask her to return my son to me.
It seems your husband is here.
I don't want to disturb you.
Don't worry about it.
Matsuko chose to live her life the way she did, and I'm sure she won't regret it.
And even if she does, she'll take care of herself well.
It's not your fault, so there's nothing to worry about.
She'll come back soon.
Get me the coat.
Are you leaving?
I'll come here A FEW DAYS because I'm curious about Matsuko.
Is there room available?
Our guest will take this room.
There's another room available.
They want to stay this room.
Come in.
That's terrible.
I've been studying so hard.
You move?
That's mine and Matsuko's room.
Don't use it for business from now on.
I get it.
I want to go with dad.
Where?
Anywhere.
I get it.
The stores in Nihonbashi are closed this Sunday, right?
How did you know?
I checked it out.
Ok?
This holiday...
I have a union meeting.
How about the night?
We're going out to Hakone for the night.
That's boring.
Don't act like kids.
He's busy.
Never mind.
Let's go with Takenosuke and mom someday.
Here's your allowance.
What are you doing?
It's ok.
I'll see you off.
I wanna go to the mountain.
This is so great.
I need a camera, too.
Why don't you buy it?
I don't have any money.
Poor guy.
Let's go eat at the cafe.
Oh yeah.
What do you want?
Kid's lunch.
You are mean.
This.
I thought he went to Hakone.
You shopping?
Nothing.
I thought your mom was with you.
I thought you went to Hakone.
Thank you, ma'am.
Let's go,Dad.
I need something to eat.
Let's go to a cafe.
You're an idiot.
Don't cry.
It's not our fault.
We were born under such a star.
Our dad didn't mean to lie.
He had his own plans.
Bros.
Don't you regret it?
They're our father's children, we're his children, too.
You know that.
Are you okay with that?
No..but It's all right.
I hate you.
Hey, let's go see a movie.
Bath is empty.
Take a bath now.
It's heavy raining.
I will show Kirinoma's guest when they arrived.
Thanks.
I worry about Ume.
She's probably at her friend's house talking.
Shall I pick them up at the station?
It's heavy raining.
You don't have to go.
I wonder if the water will run again.
Where's Ume?
I worry.
Something must have happened, today?
Maybe you got in a fight.
It's nothing.
It's not our problem.
It's still our problem.
what does it mean?
What time is it?
She told me to leave from work at 10 pm.
Shall I call them again?
When you called earlier, they said she'd already left the store.
She left early, they said.
Bros.
I need your voice.
Yuriko Hanagumi
Call as Miyamoto.
5497-567
Yuriko
Hello?
Wakaba salon?
This is Miyamoto.
Is Yuriko from Hanagumi there?
I see.
She's there.
They told she left when I called them.
Is Yuriko there?
It's me.
Okada.
Never mind.
Don't say excuse.
Liar.
You didn't break up with Miyamoto, did you?
I'll say goodbye to a woman like you for tonight.
And then... those kimonos you collected at Mitsukoshi the other day, I'll take them back.
You are an idiot.
Then?
Because it's boring. I came home after playing pachinko.
Why didn't you come home with her?
I didn't think it would come to this.
You could've told me.
I'm sure you wouldn't be happy to hear it.
She must be on her period today.
I'm bad.
Come here.
Sorry but call me a woman.
Young woman.
We can't have suck a service.
I see... well then...
He's an asshole.
Shut up!
Is she back?
Mom.
Matsuko..
It's been a while.
Where have you been?
I'm not alone.
Come in.
You meet him for the first time.
I'm Sudo.
Anyway come in.
Tell Hatsue to get ready for the bath.
You don't have to go home?
Not yet.
We can talk about that later.
This used to be me and my sister's room.
It's the same.
I don't want to bother you.
Want to go home.?
I can't.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
It's been ages.
I've changed, haven't I?
I don't think so.
Please take a bath.
Thank you.
Wanna take a bath?
You look down.
You can leave if you want to.
No one's going to say to leave.
Are you going to rest now?
Cheer up.
You'd better get dressed.
Don't do that.
He'd rather sleep than take a bath.
I'll wake him up later.
I'm sorry, Mom.
After all, this is the only place I could stay.
What the hell is going on with you?
Can we please talk about this tomorrow?
I'm tired.
I'm worried about you.
Take this.
You won't catch a cold.
Thank you.
Where's Ume?
She's still out.
Has she started to fall in love yet?
She's not like you.
Ironic?
It tastes good.
You're really getting strong with the booze.
I've been practicing for two years.
Can I stay here for a while?
I know you don't have anywhere else to go.
Here's your home.
Watch out.
What's wrong?
What did you do?
No!
What's wrong?
She wanted to go home, so we sent her home.
I'm sorry to bother you.
She was so drunk she started crying.
Why you drunk?
I hate you!
We're leaving.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Good night.
Ume.
What's wrong?
You've got to have that kind of energy.
Let's have whiskey.
Stay strong.
I'll prepare the bed.
Let's have whiskey.
Yeah.
I like you.
I hate mom.
I hate dad more.
Umeyo.
Do you remember me?
Sis!
Don't drink.
I wanted to drink.
I like to drink.
OKOK.
Let's have whiskey.
Come on, Sis.
We are mistress club!
Good night, ma'am.
Good night.
She's sick.
You've been in Kobe ever since you left.
How did you know I was in Kobe?
I heard about it from the police.
How did you end up like this with someone being chased by the police?
He has a wife and kids.
Police told you so?
I beg you, break up with him.
Mr. Sudo may regret.
How do you know that?
I beg you, break up with him.
OK.
Really?
But I have a condition.
Conditions?
Your will leave our father.
It's our father's fault for making me the way I am.
Can you leave him?
If you can't, then I can't leave him either.
It's the same thing.
You drunk too much.
That's fine.
I'll pay for it.
I'm worried about your health.
I don't care what happens to my body.
I have to be clear.
I can't allow two people to share one man.
What?
You can't get him.
He's mine.
I won't give him back.
But he is...
What's wrong with him?
You said some strange things earlier.
Something about Sudo having regrets.
Why did you say that?
Speak up.
Did you meet the people at Sudo's house?
What did she say?
Matsuko.
He wants to go home.
He miss his home.
That's true?
Mr. Sudo sent a letter home.
I can't believe it.
That's true.
Her mother brought it .
Her mother brought it all the way here to show you?
Matsuko.
I beg you, break up with him.
Mom.
He's the one who ran away from the police.
That's even worse.
I'm not like you.
I can't just walk away from someone, no matter who they are.
I don't care if he's a thief or a murderer.
If I love someone, I'll be with him until the day I die.
I won't let him go even if I'd dead.
It's a wonder you had a child like me.
I wonder if I'm really your child.
Sis.
Why don't you come upstairs for a minute?
Why?
I hear something strange.
Please come.
Look at that.
See?
What's wrong?
Where's spare key?
Which room?
Your sis..
What's wrong?
I have no idea.
Sis.
What's wrong?
Is it forced suicide?
Call doctor.
What's wrong?
Sis killed the guy..
Matsu..
Stay strong.
Mom!
Hello?
They can't be saved.
Sis..
Bros...
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thanks.
Kazuo was killed.
My only son.
He has a wife and children. It's not easy to kill a man like that.
Husband's mistress and her daughter are so terrible.
Did Matsuko leave anything out?
She said she would never let go of the person she loves.
She said she was a winner because she would be with him till death.
she is strong-willed.
I found her diary from two years ago in her purse.
When I read it, I understood exactly how she felt.
What did it say?
I was thrown away miserably by that man I trusted so much.
The only reason is that our mother is a mistress.
How is being the daughter of a mistress a negative thing for a human being?
I have a father and a mother.
Why am I not allowed to have the same kind of happiness as other people in the world?
When Sudo left me, I wanted to curse my father and mother.
But my father and mother are kind people to me.
I don't hate anyone
I will live on my own.
All I can hope for now is that my sister Umeyo will not have to repeat my misery.
The sight of her innocent sleeping face weakens my resolve to leave home.
Umeyo.
I wish you all the best.
I'll be praying for you.
she's great
She's so upset that she won't let anything happen to us.
I didn't know.
I guess she couldn't forget the first guy.
Apparently Mr. Sudo wasn't as serious as his sister.
He got a wife from a good place within six months.
I feel sorry for sis.
Sudo was bad man.
It was ok if he was killed.
Mon.
What?
Pleas leave from our dad.
Umeyo.
I've been thinking about that for a long time.
I will start working from tomorrow.
Please do too,bros.
We have to look after this house.
that's too sudden.
I think this is a very good opportunity.
I know how you feel but...
But too soon.
We were doing that, and we were screwed for life.
Let's do our best on our own.
I'm sure she felt the same way.
I came here thinking you'd miss her.
Sure enough.
They say if you cry too much, Buddha won't become a Buddha.
Where's hatsue?
she is going shopping.
I see.
I wanna hot tea.
Do us a favor.
What?
Let us live on our own.
By yourselves?
I don't understand.
I want to support my mother on our own.
You too?
We want a brighter, healthier life.
We want a righteous life.
We want to quit this business and we want to work.
I'm not as fastidious as Umeyo when it comes to the difficulties of the world. But I still feel sorry for our mother.
Dad.
I was so frustrated today at the crematorium, I wanted to punch her in the face.
But it's frustrating but that's the way it is.
She's your mistress.
Do you agree?
I told our dad.
I'll follow our kids.
Our children have grown up so much!
Don't ever worry.
We'll do our best.
Let's do it, Dad.
I'm graduating next year, but tomorrow I'm walking to find a job.
I think it's better for me if I do that, so I can be myself.
I see.
Have you all thought that much?
I'm sorry I made you all feel so low because of me.
Maybe it was really me who let Matsuko die.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I was weak.
But you have to believe on this.
Your mother was never a common Mistress.
I had no choice but to keep her away from me.
I may have made you guys miserable, but it didn't have to be that way.
We were going to be a couple to begin with.
Don't say that.
We may never get a chance to talk again.
Your mother went with me to work at a store in Nihonbashi.
Then suddenly it came to me that I was going to get married to the store's daughter.
I was very confused due to my work.
Your mother noticed this and went away.
Matsuko was already in your mother's belly at that time.
I didn't know that was going to happen, but I ended up with my now wife.
I had a duty to them, and I just couldn't say no.
I got married, and about a year later I ran into your mom.
I couldn't contain myself any longer.
It bothered me and it bothered her.
Until today, I've tied your mother down.
I had no choice but to do that.
That's all.
That's the history of my mistakes that made your sister and all of you unhappy.
That's unfair.
Under no circumstances is it very sinful for one man to have two wives!
You're too selfish.
No matter how much you suffer, your sins will not go away.
It's too late to sat that.
Shut up.
You are man.
Since you are a man, you listen to what he has to say.
Do you accept the existence of your mistress?
No, but Even when it's unavoidable, if you really love each other, you can forgive.
No at all.
You shouldn't be with another woman even though you have a wife.
But you know what, I don't have any real experience, but love isn't so cut and dried, is it?
Are you willing to kill someone as long as it's serious?
Are you willing to sacrifice other things to achieve love?
Is it okay to deviate from society's morals?
Stop saying that.
Umeyo is right.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
I'm old-fashioned.
Takenosuke,Take care of Mom.
Ok?
I'm going to assume that our father is dead.
Umeyo too.
You guys need to take care of yourselves.
I want you to grow up.
Okay?
Dad.
Get out of the front today.
Mom, take him there.
Please.
Takenosuke.
You're going to the mountains again this summer
Have a drink.
I can't leave from you.
please say you won't break up with me.
Please take me anywhere.
I can't live without you.
I wanna stay with you.
I can't leave you like this.
I need you.
Don't say that.
I don't want to leave from you too.
I want to run away together.
So.
Let's be people that Umeyo and Takenosuke will never laugh at us again.
We were weak.
We have been living with a spoiled way of thinking.
I'm happy with it.
What if I make your children unhappy?
I'm in pain.
But let's start fresh around here, shall we?
If you need help, I'm here for you.
If you're not in the business now, you'll have to think about something else.
Don't worry about the money.
We'll help each other as human beings, even if we're separated.
Cheer up.
Let's put up with it for the sake of the kids.
It'll be like a memorial to the dead pineapple.
You got it?
Please.
I can't.
mom isn't coming home
I wonder what happened to her?
I feel sorry for our mom.
Don't say that.
Why?
I feel like we killed her.
It's mom!
Mom.
We were worried about you.
Where have you been?
I was just down the street from your dad's house.
Okay.
Let's go home.
I'm quitting the business.
Let's sell the house and live together in a quiet place, just the three of us.
Let's start all over again from the beginning.
I finally made that decision.
We'll be fine for sure.
I'm with you.
Hey!
THE END