Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Excuse me.
Do you need something to drink?
I don't need.
A passenger apparently wants a Martini wine.
This is the fourth cup.
He's still sober.
He's amazing.
Sorry I kept you waiting
The airtrip is very tiresome,
I need this Martini to help pass the time
Well, I will try to cheer you up
Oh, please
Now, guess
In a shower, one person is having a shower
Now, there is one person, right?
Right
And now.
There are two people taking a shower
That's right, exactly two
And now...
Three?
That's right
And now...
Four
No, it is not
You certainly have four persons Why?
There are five persons
But you have four
Look, this person is picking up his soap
Did you get it?
Oh
Nice talking to you
Thank you
Fukuzatsu na Kare / A Complicated Man (1966)
How was the NAL service?
I hear it's better than before
I saw a good looking crew.
He's tall and smart.
He worked very nicely.
Oh He must be Idohori-kun.
Idohori?
He has unusual name.
Judging by his name, is he from Okinawa?
You're silly.
That's just his nickname.
His real name is Geroge Miyagi
What? Is it nickname?
What do you wanna eat?
Anything is fine.
Help me.
He's careless guy.
Why?
Just call him Idohori
I can't imagine how much he's done bad things so far.
He's good-looking, but when he's broke, he works digging wells.
He got 1000yen to dig 1m.
The rookie dug deep, so he was drenched from head to toe.
He ended up to catch a cold.
I didn't know that.
I can't believe he did that job.
He even talks about it proudly.
Oh yeah.
Didn't you have a relative who worked at the Nihon Shimbun?
He's the brother right above my late mother,
and he's currently the head of the business division, you know.
Oh, right, Mr.Suga?
He was the London correspondent, wasn't he?
Nearly ten years ago
I hear that Mr. Ido-bori was wandering around Europe and was taken care of by Mr. Suga.
You might be able to learn something about him.
Hang this there.
I'm back
Oh Saeko,Well come back.
Did you have fun?
Yes a lot.
Good to know.
Are you holding an exhibition in the UK?
Yes.
It's convenience.
Do you know of Miyagi?
Put it there.
Miyagi?
Who?
He's flight attendant.
He's crew for NAL
He lived in London
London?
Oh he must be George
I heard you took care of him very much.
It was not much.
He studied at Wimbledon University,
He was expelled for some reason.
He came to me way,
He came to the London branch office near Big Ben.
Are you promising to be a camera assistant at home
and work diligently?
Yes, I'll do my absolute best.
By the way, what's your favorite thing?
Yes, it's a girl.
You're honest.
I'm sick and tired of Japanese people who lie.
Don't think about girl while working.
Sure.
So I hired him
He spook English well and was well mannered.
He was good to us.
He happened to cause an industrial espionage scandal while I was away on a reporting trip.
Did he?
The company is a factory that makes comet machines, and he secretly took photos of the equipment there.
There was a risk that this could develop into an international issue.
I asked him like this.
Who exactly bought you?
Nobody is buying me.
Did you do it of your own volition?
No.
Who told you to do that?
Who asked you to do the photo shoot?
You can't say it because you feel bad.
OK
You can rest until I get to the truth.
OK?
I was certain he was an accomplice.
After further investigation, I found out that a cameraman, desperate for some pocket money, had accepted the job from a certain businessman.
It turns out that they had disguised it as a company recruitment opportunity and made Miyagi-kun work for free.
So, even though I looked after him, I may be the one responsible for causing him incurable emotional wounds at his most crucial time.
Are you still in a relationship with him?
I haven't seen him in a while, but he's very loyal.
He called me and asked if I would like to have dinner with him.
I think he'll be here soon.
He may suddenly have work to do that requires him to fly.
No way.
He's not a fighter pilot
Welcome.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
You haven't changed at all
I'm sorry I haven't seen you in a long time.
Come in.
It's been 10 years since I last saw you
But you haven't changed at all
Not at all.
Ah, take it easy, take it easy.
Oh, excuse me
Ah, let me introduce you
She's My niece Saeko Morita
I'm Miyagi
Excuse me, but weren't you in
San Francisco by NAL two weeks ago ?
Yes I was
you remember that well?
I remember most of the passengers.
You have an amazing memory
Hey, since it's all ready, please carry it over
Yes
You might be tired of eating tempura by now.
I love it
You can eat it anywhere in the world now
That's right, you liked fish
Whether it's from the sea or the river,I love it.
Do you like the fish in the well?
Fish in the well?
Are there any fish in the well?
Since there is water,
there might be some.
haha, I understand now
You seem to know various gossip about me
I don't mean that
Oh, it's not good to hide things, you know
I know exactly who said that.
But in this case, I might just confide a secret that I haven't told anyone yet, just to you
Can you absolutely keep this secret?
If this gets out I'll be fired
I will keep that secret
Right now, I'm out on bail.
What's the hell?
Let's dance
Why did you do something like that?
Because I was lonely
You shouldn't have the right to do something like that now.
Don't make fun of me.
You actually have someone, you know
He's been cold lately
It's none of my business.
George, do you remember?
In the beginning of us.
Hey George, let's go somewhere tonight
We can't.
You have a husband, don't you?
Don't worry, don't worry
You know, we were apart like that four years ago, weren't we?
And it was only for a month
I didn't really understand various things back then
Let's dance, George.
George.
I can't forget you
Don’t do that.
Will you go and apologize to her like this?
It's none of your business.
You know, it seems you're quite close with her too, huh?
Excuse me.
it was you after all
Come in.
Never mind
Has the company found out about that?
No, don't worry.
Do you still not want money?
No, not really
What about your position?
It must be boring even if I become important.
It just binds me up because my actions are restricted
Meeting a young man like I
feel like taking a refreshing breath
These days, young people are so timid and pathetic
Money, fame, and success
Japan's future looks bleak.
Thinking about it, just having someone
like you around enriches my heart
However, I do have a fondness for women
Most failures stem from that
Isn't it quite nice to like women?
You're still young, after all
If your heart is moved, go ahead and enjoy it as much as you like;
There will come a time when you get tired of it
You think so?
I've been doing it since I was 16 in England
I can't do that yet
Do as you please
By the way,
Haven't you made up your mind yet?
What do you mean?
I told you when I helped you
If I save you, you will follow me
However, I should have firmly declined at that time
Indeed, you refused
But I saved you
I'm grateful for that
However, since I declined,
your act of saving me
is solely your own will
You're right.
So I'm not pushing you
but that's fine
Your feelings will probably change eventually
I'll come again someday!
Hello, is this Morita's house? Is Saeko there?
Saeko?
We don't have anyone named Saeko here
Hello, is this Morita's house?
Is Saeko there?
I'm Saeko.
Who?
Kacchan?
Where are you calling from?
If it's from some bed,
I won't accept that
Hello
This is Morita.
May I ask who is calling?
This is Miyagi
Is Saeko there?
But I believe she has already gone to bed,
so please wait a moment
Hello, is this Saeko?
what? Isn't this Saeko?
My sister hasn't come home yet,
but no, I am not Saeko.
Is there something urgent?
I will just let my sister know that you called
Hello, is this Suga's home?
Yes.
I'm George Miyagi
Actually, I have a request that I would really like to discuss
No, it's a request for my entire life
I'm really sorry for being out so late last night
No, no, I thought that if it continues like that, it wouldn't be just a simple matter
I quickly called Saeko out for lunch today
I explained it on your behalf.
Thank you very much.
what did Saeko-san say?
Surprisingly,She was in a good mood
So, did she agree to my plan?
I think so.
they were even scolded
She felt more sorry for the girl who slapped than for the girl who was slapped.
So, about last night's phone call?
It really was Saeko
She doesn't have any siblings, you know
But the fact that she went out of her way to answer the phone probably means she wanted to hear your voice, right?
Thank you for everything; I really appreciate it. I'm sorry for causing so much trouble, and when I get back,
I will come to express my gratitude eventually,
but I don't have time today,
Wait Miyagi-kun, I have something that I brought from Saeko
Thanks.
You don't read?
I will read it on the plane
Thank you very much for your repeated kindness
Well, Saeko
What on earth does this mean?
You called me to Haneda all the way to Haneda
Sorry.
just to see him off?
I don't mean that.
Just something.
It seems you have something to discuss
shall we have a drink somewhere cool and talk about it in detail?
However, I have guests coming over to my place today.
I have to hurry home
that's a busy matter
Is it one of Dad's customers?
No, it's the Indian lady I met at my Arab embassy party
Shall I send it to you?
Thank you very much.
I've completely forgotten about yesterday
Please don't worry
If we have the chance to meet again,
I believe we will surely have a fun conversation then
Morita Saeko, Dear Idohori
what are you doing, grinning to yourself?
I see, it's a love letter
Do you need another glass of wine?
how about going for a swim after we land in Honolulu?
Sounds good!
I want to go surfing for the first time in a while.
but you should really give it up
Why? You're a strange person
Please.
Thank you very much.
Actually, there was someone I wanted to meet when I came to Japan
It's someone I met at a nightclub in Cairo
I was watching from the back seat inside the tent
A foreigner sat next to me
He looked very lonely
That person was a boy on a Japanese ship, and his name was George Miyagi
Huh? Miyagi?
Yes
And then suddenly, he became restless and called the boy
When he stood up to leave
that turned into.....
I see
If you don't mind, please tell me more
Idohori!
Hey, how are you?
It's been a while
When did you arrive?
I came yesterday
Aren't you going to join us?
Are you in a hurry?
Not really,
then it's fine. Let's have some coffee
Yeah.
By the way, how's everything going?
I'm doing well
I actually have a surprisingly domestic side
And my husband loves me too,
so that's great
But I guess you're bored in the banking job
that's the thing—my husband is really dedicated to his work,
When clients from the main office come,
he shows them around, and if they don't come, he gathers his subordinates at home
I'm always in a flurry, but I don't mind because there's no such ideal husband
He's kind and considerate
I can't believe I came all the way to San Francisco to hear your boasting
What about you?
Me?
Are you hunting women?
I'm actually in love right now
In love? Who is it?
Is it someone from the same company?
No, it's not like that
Could it be that person is SM?
SM...
that's right, exactly
So it was Saeko after all
But why would you say that?
It's obvious, isn't it?
She was a classmate from college and I met her last month.
So it was you after all
You were the one who taught her about well digging
But you didn't tell her my secret, did you?
What secret?
Don't tease me.
You and I had a fight and broke up
but I haven't even talked about that with anyone at the company
It's the bare minimum of etiquette towards you, isn't it?
If that's the case, I appreciate it
Of course, you haven't mentioned this to Saeko, right?
Of course, I swear.
Is that so? Thank you
There's no need to say thank you. it's just that I haven't talked yet
Are you talking about an exchange?
Yes.
money?
Don't underestimate, okay?
I have more money than you
Well, think it over carefully
Other than the money
But you are married.
It's none of your business.
I just want to steal you away for a bit
At this point, I don't really want any affection
You intend to tell Saeko-san about this deal, do you?
Do you think I'm such a cowardly woman?
We are fair now.
What do you mean?
The deal is done, right?
But still, the one who has the advantage is you, holding onto my secret
Men's reasoning is so simple, isn't it?
It's not like that.
I've created a secret that I absolutely want you to protect
For your husband?
For Saeko
For Saeko?
Promise me that you will never tell Saeko about this
I never expected you to come out so honestly
it's quite ironic?
Oh no, that's not
we made your tea.
Come in
Shall I bring your meal right away?
Please do that
How about drink?
A beer would be fine?
Yes
I understood
What is this?
This is a small stone from the river
I picked it up because it's pretty
The other day, I invited a lady from India
named Madam Zaruzaru to my house, you know?
I heard something from her at that time
A love romance that lasts just one night with you
I heard you might have gotten married
So, is she in Japan?
Do you want to see her?
I guess so
But I feel like it's better to leave old memories undisturbed
So, can you endure it?
Yes, I can.
I envy men.....
for being able to cut off their past so easily
Do you have a past too?
You shouldn't treat me like a child
I apologize for that
From a woman's perspective,
I think if the other person were to cut
off the past, you might seem insincere,
but that's not the case.
Excuse me.
I wonder what happened
This area sometimes has a strong wind blows
I'll take care of it.
You seem like a mysterious person, don't you think?Yes,
Me?
why?
I think you're a very complex person
To me, there's nothing mysterious at all
Still, I believe it's better to have a little mystery, whether you're a man or a woman
No, but I've actually suffered losses because of that until now
But
it's really true
I've lived my life naturally as I felt since I was a child
But that becomes a mystery to everyone, which is a problem for me
Because there are no connections to my past at all,
it seems that people think I'm a silly and extraordinary guy,
but that actually troubles me as well
it's true
I'm sorry.
You tried so hard to excuse yourself.
Is that bad?
Because it feels like you
were being a spoiled child
Yes, I'm a brat.
It's not good.
I wanted to see you.
I was scared that if I couldn't see you,
I felt like I was going to be no good for some reason.
Well, I'm going to take my leave now
Are you heading home?
Huh? That's too bad
Then let me see you off
I'll see you again before you board.
So, tomorrow,
so early?
It's not tomorrow to board, but I can't wait, is that okay?
Alright.
then I'll go settle the bill for a bit
Oh, you forgot the apples.
Saeko?
Yes
I'm sorry for being late
Where have you been?
I was treated to dinner by my uncle
Well, let's go. You lied to Papa for the first time, didn't you?
I called Mr. Suga
Well, it's fine. You're old enough to take responsibility now
I believe in you
The meal is ready
She said she had already eaten her meal
I see.
Actually, I suddenly have to go to Rio de Janeiro as a representative of the industry
And I would like you to accompany me again
Well, when?
It's quite sudden,
you see
If we don't leave the day after tomorrow, we won't make it
So until when? Huh?
It might take almost a month
That long? That's a problem for me
Have a nice day.
Are you Mr. Morita's daughter?
Yes.
then you know Miyagi-kun, right?
What's wrong?
Well then, let's talk while we walk
What is your relationship with him?
I don't have a deep relationship with him
You haven't seen him that much yet.
No
A young man like him is quite rare these days
Once he decides he wants to do something,
he pursues it wholeheartedly without worrying about what others think
It might sound like he's a very simple man,
but on the other hand, he is quite sensitive to feelings and has a surprisingly sentimental side
In a nutshell, you could say he's a manly man
Anyway, it's a waste to leave him as just a purser
Well, no matter what anyone says
What Japan is most lacking right now is neither money nor goods
It is precisely human resources
Just like Miyagi-kun
Do you know him very well?
I think I know Miyagi-san
The important thing is that
he is currently in the middle of hunting
So, it really is true that he is in the middle of hunting, isn't it?
he is in the middle of hunting?
Legally, it should be referred to as a suspended sentence,
but it seems he prefers the term 'in the midst of predation.'
In any case, it's just a matter of waiting one more year for divine judgment
Why did he end up in this situation?
Because he was caught for illegal handling of a disability and a pistol
When?
It's been a little over three years now
At that time, he was working as a bartender at A bar in Yokohama
A night.
He heard from one customer that he was troubled because a bad foreigner had defaulted on nearly 10 million yen
He went to where the foreigners were and argued with them in English.
But the foreigners outnumbered him, so he was overwhelmed.
It happened while he was being transported somewhere in a car.
Don't move.
That was good up to there
but the next morning,
the police came to his lodging,
and as a result,
it ended up in court
You know quite a lot of detailed things, don't you?
Well, I had a lawyer assigned to him, you see
You?
That's right
He's a man worth doing that much for with pleasure
Well, I just tent to chatter away without thinking, so excuse me
Sorry for keeping you waiting
What would you like to drink?
I'm not in the mood to drink
What are you thinking?
I was just wondering where you would take me today
Well, I haven't decided yet either
Shall we go to Jindaiji, or would it be more
stylish to stretch a bit further to Tamabochi?
Do you like cemeteries?
hat sounds nice.
it makes me feel like we could live twice as long,
just like the Buddhas
If young people go, they'll surely be happy
Walking like this, it feels like we're looking for an apartment together,
A place we could live in forever?
I suddenly decided to go to Brazil
Huh? What are you going there for?
I'm going to help my father
When?
Tomorrow
and I might end up staying there for almost a month,
for almost a month
but I really don't want to go
but this time his the last trip,
so he absolutely have to take you with me
It's so terrible that I can't see you for a month.
My heart aches too
It's tough for me too.
It's awful that things have turned out this way
I won't let you go as it is either
I don't care what happens
I think you feel the same way.
Let's be alone somewhere.
We can't do that.
That's your company's airplane? Huh?
No, that's not it
That's a U.S. military fighter jet
So, they might go to Vietnam someday, huh?
Well, compared to that, I have to endure it
Even if I can't see you for about a month,
won't you send me a letter?
Sure.
Is there something I can help you?
No
This is a letter for you
Thank you
We met again
To San Francisco?
Yes
Let's go that way
I'm so happy
because I didn't expect this
I didn't think we would meet
like this either
When I found out I could take this flight
To be honest, I was wondering what to do being in first place, unable to even talk to you
Just looking at your face is too painful
Oh, what's wrong?
No, it's nothing
By the way, what are you going to do?
I have to go out for business,
but I'll be down writing letters or something
Mr. George, I saw your illusion today
In front of the hotel,
wearing a brown suit,
I couldn't help but exclaim, and my father became suspicious of me
Rio is a beautiful city
Blue sea and white sand
People who are close to each other everywhere
It seems like everyone in this town is in love
How happy I would be if I were with you
Hello,
how did you manage to come all the way here?
If I want to meet you, there's no place I can't reach
Is your job okay?
I took a week off forcefully
So, I asked a friend from the airline here
to arrange the tickets up to this point
Well, what did you write?
A letter for you
Don't see it.
Why?
It's still unfinished.
You are here,
why not just say it out loud?
Come on.
Well, Rio is a beautiful city
And then?
How happy I would be if I were with you.
I'm the same way
We can meet for a full five days, you know
But I wonder what my father's schedule looks like
Well, I guess that's a problem
I came all the way here thinking I would guide you,
but let's go out for now
I'll bring my jacket so please wait.
I'll think about this.
You could become my long-lost friend
And if we say we just happened to meet in Rio, I can formally introduce you to my father.
No way!
Don't tell such lies.
He took break.
Idobori-kun is really into her.
I can imagine there are quite a few people in my
circle who would be disappointed to hear this rumor
Are you one of them?
Not at all, he's fine as long as we're just dating
I'll find a good person eventually, just like you
Well then, it's in front of the gate at 1 o'clock tomorrow
It's better to write the letter later
Oh, just a little bit
That's not good
It's disappointing that they came all this way to represent the industry
Ah, I understand, I understand
I'm going now
Have a good time
Stop it....
Saeko.
I was really scared
After all, I didn't understand the words
and I was wondering what to do
But I'm glad we met
But I didn't know you were that strong
I was bad boy in old day
Did you used to fight a lot?
No, that's not it
I was doing boxing
Well, when? Where?
It was at a camp in
Tachikawa
I fought against an American
That's also a fixed match set up for me to lose by knockout, isn't it?
I also hated the idea of a fixed match,
but I couldn't win against obligation
I reluctantly took it on
Around that time, I had a passionate patriot fan at the Western-style bakery in Tachikawa
She had no idea it was a fixed match
George, I don't want you to lose, so do your best!
If I lose, I might die.
probably due to the frustration of being toyed with by American soldiers on a daily basis
She wanted to let it all out with my victory, right?
George, you did it! I'm so happy
What's wrong?
What happened all of a sudden?
But that woman was beautiful, wasn't she?
You are stupid.
What happened after quitting boxing?
I did various things
Boat racer,The bellboy at hotel
Bar staff etc
How about bartender?
Yes, I did
Before joining  in NAL
You knew that I used to work
as a bartender
Oh, that was just a guess
Oh, I have to go home now.
Really?
because my father.....
I'm sorry
It's fine
Well then, I'll be waiting in the hotel lobby tomorrow
If we meet there, we shouldn't miss each other like today,
and around one o'clock would be good
I get it.
I was surprised
I'm sorry.
My father just wouldn't go out, so I was quite anxious about it
I thought you might go out together too,
so I was a bit flustered at the entrance
I suddenly got a headache
I see, let's go out today
I'll show you the face of Corcovado
Yes
this is the apartment I'm renting
It's more economical than a hotel if it's for a week
Well, I can't go
Why not?
I can't go
I can't enter your room until I get married
You're saying that again, huh?
Tomorrow, Meet my father to get approve our marriage
I can't enter your room until I get married
So just understand
I want to go to your room without any worries
What if your Dad says no?
I won't let him say that
How can you do that?
I will definitely make him understand
by tonight, no matter how long it takes
So
I understand,
I'm sorry about that
I'm being selfish,
Dad.
I have a request for you
Hello, could you please talk to Mr. George ?
What? He's not there?
Really? Thank you very much
What's wrong?
You don't mean he's already moved out, do you?
Hello? Oh, George? When did you come?
I really want to see you.
Wait for me at our usual spot
Stay way
You are cold
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong at all
You're cold, it's like you've changed
What about Saeko?
You've already gotten tired of her, huh?
It doesn't really matter, does it?
I guess I was better after all
If that's the case, I wouldn't mind being with you
I've been thinking for a long time about whether I should break up with my partner
If only you had that idea
George, I'll let your secret wife know, ok?
Do whatever you like, I don't care
George.
we've talked quite a bit about it
It seems that Dad has completely lost his emotions
I also provided a detailed explanation about Miyagi-kun's character
The reason he didn't show up at the hotel
Because he has something to hide,
that's for sure, He thinks like that.
Anyway, putting that aside, I think I will try to meet George once, what do you think?
Come in.
You're here.
I thought you would come
That's quite a power-saving approach
What were you thinking in such a dark room
without turning on the lights?
I suppose everyone already knows that, right?
Well, that's true
By the way
You came here thinking that today I
would finally make up my mind, didn't you?
I can understand at least that much
Actually, you came at a good time
I always come at the right moment in life.
There is such a thing as the right timing, and I don't let it slip away
It's not easy to patiently wait for that right moment to come
But you are a person who is worth enough for me to do that
It's pointless that you praise me.
I truly believe that, of course, that person too.
Who?
Well, it's not the time to mention the name yet
But
can you really just watch in silence?
He is deeply in love with you.
That person is deeply pained by the recent conflicts among the same ethnic group in Asia
He wants to somehow bring peace to this Asia; there is no time to waste
Thus, he was able to strengthen his resolve to avoid taking action
That person chose you as one of his assistants
Could you please speak a little more specifically?
It would be best to hear that directly from that person
I understood.
Even though I am not in a position to marry a woman among good house,
I was able to smoothly join NAL company thanks to that person's recommendation
I can say it now,
but that's exactly right
I knew it.
Do you value
your life right now?
Right now? Right now
Speak frankly
I don't particularly think it's precious
Alright, the time has come
What is it?
You've changed your mind.
It can't be helped
Let's acknowledge that I've changed my mind.
I come to your room
There is a guest
Please come in.
Oh, it's nice to see you again.
What do you think?
You didn't have the courage to propose to this young lady
I'll show you the reason for that
You took on that burden when you did ship's
laborer
However, just being embarrassed alone
won't communicate anything to others
If you boldly show it, everything will change and
you'll be able to let it go
What do you think?
Now you understand, right?
He is definitely not a careless man who puts on a facade of control
He truly loved you with all his heart
However, he did not have the courage to confess this
His propose will be decline if he did confess about this,
he would not be able to accept a marriage proposal
He got a tattoo just because he was young.
Youth always seems to carry some
form of punishment later on, doesn't it?
However, if you intend to stick with someone like him, that's a different story
George...
what do you think?
Will you follow him?
Yes, I will
Your answer is too quick
Can you think about it a bit more?
Okay?
you will also have children
However, children cannot go swimming in the pool with their father
First, will you tell this secret to the child or not?
Will you regret it when that time comes?
I won't regret it at all
I see
Right now, you probably love him with pure feelings
However, I did take the liberty to look into your upbringing
So, if I may say so,
You won't be able to live with such a tattoo man forever
Will you cherish your dreams with him forever, or live in a long, long disillusionment and suffering?
You are standing at that crossroads right now
What if I say my feelings have been
decided from the very beginning.
What do you mean?
I love him.
but  you should go home today.
At least think it over for one more night
And once you've made up your mind, you can come back here again
Even if tomorrow comes
He won't run away or hide
I promise you firmly.
Even after thinking about it all night,
my feelings won't change
In that case, it means that your love for him is genuine
Please go home.
He will probably be waiting for you to come tomorrow
She is going home.
It's someone you will never meet again
Come here and see her
That's enough now
Just hearing her words makes me satisfied
I understand very well that I can't make her happy.
For the first time in my life, I truly loved her.
But if truly loving
someone is this painful,
I never want to go through something this painful again
Never.
That's right.
You've graduated from the world of women
From today, a life of battles and adventures begins before you
for the Asian people.
Come on, let's pack our bags.
Let's move out here and go to that person
You don't like it?
No, the bags are already ready
I intended to do that from the very beginning as well.
Let's go.
THE END