Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Adultery / Furin (1965)
Our ancestors didn't used to have a unit of husband and wife.
When they felt like each other, they enjoyed having fun together
They resolved their sexual arousal.
But world population had been increasing
But the protection of private property and religion created a taboo on sex.
That's how we got the unit of husband and wife.
People began to have sex to adapt to a demanding social life
Every human being has sexual desires.
But I wonder if it's morally just to have sex only in the context of a married couple.
It's beautiful to have sex without thinking about the marital relationship.
Marital sex is as boring as livestock.
People are solemn about sex.
As a result, the once energetic young man becomes a boring father in the home
Therefore I really hate a unit of husband and wife.
This woman visit me twice a week,She knows about what I think
She comes Tue and Friday these day, and She goes back in home at Omori at 8pm
Hi
Welcome home
Hello
I got a call for you at 3 pm from Sato,Kobunsha
About bank?
He told me to visit you 1 pm tomorrow
Wanna have a meal?
Yeah
I cooked your favorite dish, Tonpoloo
Want beers?
I have a work, so I won't drink
I'm sorry.
I've already prepared it
What's wrong about your ring?
My father bought it for me
It looks like engagement ring
No one wear it in their right finger
It must wear in their left middle finger
Oh I see
I was asked about match making last night
I was not into it.
So my father got angry with me
But I think your mother worries about you
My mother only obeys my father, so she is on my side.
So I feel relieved now
She wanna get married with me?
No way.
All the women I had relations with ran away in disgust at me.
But at the time I was....
Let's get married with me
So Can I?
Seiko
You really get married with me?
I told it by mistake
I regret it
At the time I found her old-fashioned and charming.
I just wanted to have sex with her once
Can you meet my father once?
Or shall I bring him to here one day?
I'll visit him some day
I broke dish
I've been avoiding her for two months since that day.
I thought she would run away from me.
That day I won the Sexual Aesthetics Newcomer of the Year award.
Congratulation
Thanks
I read this
Tell me what you think about this book
What I thought?
I feel misters
I wonder why you late about marriage
Perhaps my parents were the cause of it.
Your parents ?
My mother was fed up with my father's affairs.
So they don't get along well
But she have to have sex with him because they are husband and wife
I used to despise them as children for being like cattle.
That's the reason why
I feel sorry
i want to fix your mind
It's impossible to fix it
I think I can
I want to help you who have an unhappy way of thinking
you should use a cutter
I lost it
You should go home
Don't worry
But
You should change your socks every day
I know
She left this
You are careless
Oh you
I thought the dry cleaner came
They come late night?
It's been a while.
Come in
this room is very nice
Why you say that?
You won the Rookie of the Year award, so you're popular with the media.
No way.
I sometimes work as a translator
This room is very nice and this sofa is also nice.
This is the sofa in my country house
I got this because my grandfather died
But you look good.
I wonder if I marry you
I'm kidding
Actually I'm in trouble with being proposed
He's UPS reporter
He's American?
He's sent to Vietnam now
Look at his photo
Are you surprised?
I think forefingers like your figure
How old is he?
He's 29
He's same age with me
I am amazed that you have an international marriage.
i haven't decided that yet
So I'm here to talk with you about that
i decided the answer
I know what's on your mind.
i read your novel,aesthetics of sex yesterday
I think the novel is written from a man's point of view.
Why?
Today's society is male-dominated.
Women were despised if they asked for sex
don't worry about people like that
Sexual experience has nothing to do with human nature.
I think the experience of sex should be more respected
See?
Experience is preferred in any workplace.
I think it's very bad for a woman to become a wife without having had sex.
I think it's worth more without virginity
I think it's very prejudiced to be obsessed with virginity
I wish the men of the world were like you.
men are egoists.
they force women to do things
That's right
There seems to be a fire nearby
Oh there's a fire
It's very close
Where?
I'm sorry but it's beautiful
No
you just empathized with me
Yes I did, but I can't
Why?
I’m on my period today
Trust me
No
You can't
A new sensation hit me in the dark waves
Exactly it was a stone like a small jewel
I can't live without her
Seiko seems to be back
Oh I see
Ask her
i don't want her to hate me
Seiko
Can you come?
Have you decided a date for Sabori-san and your father to meet?
Not really
We asked you about it
He misunderstands that i don't care about you
It's not your fault
I read his book so I know what he thinks
he doesn't want to get married
Is that so?
It must be
He said couple sex is the same as livestock sex
He thinks it's better if we don't get married and get comfortable with each other.
you have to care what people think
Having sex without getting married is like an animal
i feel so ashamed of you
you guys think about us a little more
Don't worry I will definitely marry him
Since that day, she has come to stay at my house from time to time.
She works for a magazine, so I don't have time to see her outside.
there are economic reasons too
I'm going out
It's early
I'm busy today
Please warm up the fried egg and eat it
Can I go back after 9pm?
It's late
She's going to see you today
Oh Tuesday..
don't fall asleep.
See you
This is Maki's
This is too tidy up
Seiko might find out
Hi
I'm sorry I'm late
There was a demo on the way
You dressed up.
Did you go to match making?
There was a tea party
I thought you had gone on a blind date.
I decided to take a tea lesson from tomorrow.
Why?
I thought I had better have a job in hand.
You have a job in hand?
I decided
You'll leave your home?
Originally I don't want to stay at home
I think you'd better not offend your father
It can't be helped
Here are ginkgo nuts and baking powder. What kind of dish did you make?
I wanted to make hotcakes
don't lie
You intentionally soiled the dishes you washed again.
Someone is using my red chopsticks, so I'll take another one.
don't worry i won't ask you anything
It makes me sad when you cheat
She finds out everything
my plan failed
Wait..Maki might be..
she may be planning something
That's what I thought
Maki is trying to make his presence known to SEIKO
What's wrong?
Even though you're an adult now, you call yourself a child
don't do tricks
What?
Don't pretend you don't know
What's wrong about this handkerchief?
I know this is yours
This is not mine
It has the initial S
My initial is M
I see
it belongs to your other woman,right?
Your other woman is doing all sorts of tricks
All the cabbage that I put in the refrigerator is cut.
it is cut in two with a kitchen knife
I felt scary
I never told you about it
why do you sometimes cut cabbage in two?
it rots quickly
You're too sensitive.
This is my way
Your way?
I usually take cabbage leaves and cut them
I learned how to cook from the north, so I cut it like this
I can't prepare the dish unless I cut the cabbage in two.
I won't cut in two if you don't like
Please stop cutting the cabbage because it will get old.
Ok
Maki seems to have misunderstood about cabbage.
Shall we have a bath?
I wanna stay here to listen to the music
The bath is ready
Let's get in together
Who is it?
What's wrong?
Today is not..
I'm about to take a bath
I'm tired from staying up all night translating
This is my father's paper knife.
I'm here to give you this
Please use these scissors for your work as well.
You didn't bother to bring it in the rain.
Anything else?
I need to talk with you something
What?
Next time ok
Tell me now
I got pregnant
You're kidding
i don't care if you don't believe
You'll find out later
What the hell?
are you going to have a baby?
Sure
I want to have your baby
Who?
dry cleaner?
Female?
Old woman
Wash my body
Damn it.
Seiko got pregnant
We'll have a baby
I must stop her
Seiko eventually decided to have an abortion.
She thought it was wrong to have a child without being married yet.
I think she was emotional then
We've done.
It's okay to come back in 2 hours
Another woman always comes after I leave
i got terrible.
what are you going to do?
I want to know
Tell me you hate me
I took the liberty of having a date with you.
I'm so sad.
I feel like going to die
I can't go home
My parents wonder why you don't come to my house
I have a very bad reputation because I stay home without getting married.
my parents want me and you to live together
But I don't wanna force you about it
i feel like killing myself
So Tell me you hate me
What if I tell you it?
do you have the chance to marry another man?
No way.
I don't have
If you tell me clearly that you don't like me, I can make up my mind
I don't hate you
Lair
You're suspicious.
why don't you believe me?
because you won't live with me
Ok..then, let's live together
To be honest,I have to compensate SEIKO for something.
About The abortion this afternoon.
But I definitely can't get married with her
We won't get married for sure, ok?
We live like siblings
We're not husband and wife
But we live together at a house
Yes, that's what you want,right?
Are you Sabori?
I'm Takayama
Thanks for taking care of my daughter
Seiko told me about that.
We all family feel at ease
Thank you
Thank you in advance
But we won't get married
In short, we pretend to be husband and wife
I see.
Thanks for understand me
You are lair
Why?
You told me you hated a unit of husband and wife
But you made a promise with her
Don't get me wrong.
We just live together
You listened to our conversation just before
It's husband and wife if you live together
The aesthetics of sex have been corrupted.
You're loser
Am I? no way.
I had no choice but...
Don't give me excuses.
I don't give you excuses.
You will get to know later
Don't be upset
I hate lair
Maki
I'm going home
I sold the apartment, and bought a house in suburb
It's convenience for me if there are many rooms
Seiko sleep downstairs
I use upstairs for my work too
You are still working
Please take a break
What's that?
I put on this because I had to address to neighbors
Hi
Oh it's me
How's your new house?
It's boring
Really
By the way, shall we meet tomorrow?
Sorry, I'm busy
I need to think myself
No.
See you
Maki refused to meet me for a week,
but I end up meeting her
I can't sleep well these days
I see bad dreams
I work too hard and eat ramen outside
and I'm lonely at home
I feel like killing myself
I imagine you guys enjoy your life
I feel lonely
In the end, I love you
He sends you letters?
I got.
He write sweet words
But I really miss you
I want to smell you and hear your voice
I wanna feel you
How about meeting with us once?
we shouldn't care too much
We need some changes
I had a lot of bad experiences
I don't think I've ever had a worse experience
She also had a lot of bad experiences too
I think she understands me
But I worry she wanna meet me
Leave it to me
But I don't have a wife
As I told you, We live like siblings
I don't trust you
Anyway I will invite you later
I persuaded her over time.
She finally accepted it
Maki is coming at 3pm
Ouch!
Calm down.
Don't worry
Seiko, you see?
You mean, we're not husband and wife.
Don't pretend to be my wife,right?
Come in
May I?
Listen,
Don't show how you are great
I know.
I'm not stupid
You're not
I'll introduce her
Calm down
Wipe up
I'll wipe
You got your clothes dirty
Don't worry
This is cheap
Hold on
It's true that you are not husband and wife.
What?
I couldn't believe it
I found out it when I saw her ring
Ring?
She wears on her right finger
her right finger?
Yes, sure
This might be smaller but please change
I'll wash your clothes
Thanks
You had better wash your clothes quickly
Please go another room
You have a hard time
Yes I do.
You have hard time too
I think Sabori have a hardest time
Yeah, but it's his fault
Thanks for everything
Come back
I'll wash your clothes
I'll wash by myself
Don't worry
I don't understand this situation
Fake or real?
I think they are acting something
I see.
He can tell it's mine by looking at the initials
He's really careless
I have another story about him
When I visited his apartment first time, he misunderstood me as his sister and gave me a apron
And he told me I was dry cleaner
They were talking each other a lot during the night
These women are eager to talk about the past.
They talk about each other's misfortunes and balance each other out.
I’m sure they will against each other later
I have to prepare for it
Let's take turn
You have a nice figure
You have nice skin
What's wrong about this?
I was injured as a child.
I'm sorry.
When was it?
When I was 6.
It was serious
Hold on.
I'll wash you
Let's wash each other
Are you bored?
You thought we talked badly about you?
Did you finish your talking?
Tomorrow is Sunday.
She'll stay over here tonight
Oh no
I can't?
I don't wanna go home
It's ok.
He always sleeps alone here
I'd like to stay over
Good night
Come with me
Hold on.
You should care about me
I'll sleep downstairs from tonight
You can sleep in
Thanks but I'll get up with you
Ok then I'll sleep in
By 9 am
We can sleep by 10 am
I need to get on plane at 10 am
Oh I forgot.
I need to sleep now
Good night
This is better
I'll be back around 20th
Maki will stay here while you are not here
We don't feel lonely each other
That might be good idea
Can you give the front door key to her?
OK
Have a safe trip
I went home a day early.
I worried about them so
I finished my work quickly
What's wrong?
Saruoka.
I have to do something
I'm leaving here
You are strange?
Are you going to meet a women?
No way
He's bad
Maki?
You're late
Oh I thought you were going home tomorrow
you are very drunk
Never mind
Did you notice anything unusual?
My dad and mom visited me
My dad asked me who is Maki
I had a hard time explaining to him
Honestly you could have said she was a common-law woman
Don't say about her badly
It seems that she and the foreigner are planning to get married
get married?
those who marry are fools
Maki sleeps there
She won't come back
You should change into pajamas
It can't be helped
Where have you been?
You look weird
I finally find out
You said you don't have a physical relationship with Seiko.
But you had sex with her while I was away
But of course.
You're husband and wife
I saw you.
Where did you go with him?
To hotel
I just ate with him, danced with him, and drank brandy at the bar.
Why you slapped me?
Trust me
I'm disgusted about your lie
why are you making rice balls?
For Maki's lunch box
do you always make for her?
She likes my cooking
She says she kisses and eats before she eats
that's ridiculous
You don't know how she feels
For what?
I return the key to you
Are you coming back early today?
I'll back home late
i am waiting for you
Thanks
Do you want meal?
Come here
I was still awake last night when you hit Maki.
I felt so complicated
don't think about her anymore
I felt so sad when I held her for the first time in a long time.
She serves me very seriously
But I feel no desire for her.
If I don't see Maki anymore, you'll be happy.
In that case, I won't see her anymore too
It's a pity that I won't be able to meet such a good person.
If you will allow me, I would like to be friends with her forever.
i don't care about your relationship
I tried to get them to get along, but this was too successful.
Hey
That woman
She fled from Osaka to Tokyo.
She looks like Venus de Milo
She's lesbian
She's lesbian?
With who?
Here's Madam
She is very nervous and seems to have been deceived by many men.
i think she has a mental problem
Wait
Are people with neurological disorders prone to homosexuality?
Have you read Kane's book?
According to her, people with neurological disorders are more demanding of affection.
Those people seem so devoted to men
But Those people commit suicide when she feels uneasy about being rejected, so it's the worst.
Those people's in pain, but Those people seem to enjoy it
But when they feel anxious just before, their demand for affection turns to women.
so they become homosexuals between women
Is homosexuality in that case psychological?
At first it is psychological, but gradually they come to seek physical relationships
They bathe and eat together
They hug each other when they sleep
Hey wake up
wake up
i sleep in the middle of you
I envy what happened last night
Why you didn't stay out tonight?
he suddenly returned to America
He left you?
No
his mother seems sick
is she in danger?
She said she had surgery and is doing well.
He worries about her mom a lot
He's mom's boy
I'll forget about him
she is sleepwalking
No
i hate living with you
I'm going home tomorrow
Stay here
No no
What's wrong?
I can't sleep
Back to the room
i believed in her
please believe in her too
I get it.
Let's go back
i will hold your hand.
i think you can sleep
come
Why I am not happy?
I have two girlfriends, so I think I should be happier.
i feel anxious and lonely
I'm not lesbian with Seiko
You don't love each other?
What do you mean?
I mean did you have sex with her?
I wanted to be by your side, so I made friends with her.
you told me to get along with her
Yes but
Recently, Seiko has been acting strangely.
Because of you
I've been having a lot of trouble lately
Living with you makes me feel lonely
I'm taking sleeping pill everyday
Excuse me
There's a call for you
It's me,Maki
Can you come to our house?
I can't live without you
Please come back
I'll listen to you
please don't leave me
if you don't come back i will die
Please come back
Thanks.
I like you
Please come back soon
do you live here again?
What should I do
From tonight I will sleep on the second floor
We have fun after Seiko goes to bed
Were you sleeping?
there is a thrill
Where are you,Maki?
Maki has been gone somewhere
Seiko
Maki?
Maki is missing?
I will find her too
she's on the ceiling or in the bathroom
I hurt my back and it hurt all day
Seiko went to her parents' house in the afternoon.
she didn't come back at night
Seiko didn't say anything about what happened last night.
By any chance
what are you worried about?
What should SEIKO-san do if something happens?
What?
From police
Hi, I'm Sabori
Oh you..where are you now?
i am in front of the station
can i go home now?
What?
Come back soon
We are so starving
What?
i have to pick you up?
Where have you been?
you are terrible.
I was walking around Shinjuku for the sake of you two.
I won't go home
Seiko, wait
I don't wanna go home
Why?
That's not my home
We moved there together
We live together like brothers,right?
I don't wanna go home anymore
will you go back to your parents house?
Where are you going?
I have a place
i feel so guilty for this woman
she's been trained to be a seriously average wife
We'll register tomorrow and become my legal wife
So please come back
You don't like?
OK?
You should treat me nice sometime
I know
Seiko got settle down
But I have to settle Maki too
Maki
Come here
I had to complete our lives
I've used my stamina all night long and I'm already feeling my limit
Seiko is taking a bath now
she's going to relax tonight
I see
We can have fun for an hour
Go downstairs
I’m thinking something
I should have been more interested in food than women.
We decided to have a meal together because of Seiko's birthday.
Are you sure to go to Paris?
You shouldn't go.
It's boring
this is a business trip
I also have a map of Paris in my head
But it seems expensive
I'll save my money
Oh Sabori
Hi
you are eating with beautiful women
I heard that you are married and live with a woman.
You are going well
Kimono woman is your wife?
She is your mistress?
You have put sexual aesthetics into action.
Don't look down like that, please introduce me to a woman.
Get up
It seems that Maki is going to get her passport today.
she really wants to go to Paris
She may not come back to Japan after meeting a good man in Paris.
Can you stop her?
Leave her alone
i don't care where she goes
I can't live without her
Can you stop her?
Please
I will travel for a while.
Please don't look for me
I want to escape reality.
From Seiko and Maki too
I want to get away from relationships.
You have to go to the apartment tonight?
I haven't come back for a while.
I need to tidy my room up before going to Paris
And I have to pay for the rent
You shouldn't go to Paris
Please stay here tonight
I don't wanna be alone
And It's too late to go there
I will stay over there
At the apartment ?
You stay there alone?
Sure
Do you doubt I stay there with Sabori?
I don't doubt you
That's good.
Anyway I have to go
Wait
I listen to you
Don't leave me alone
Don't worry, just one night
I'll be back tomorrow morning
I can't sleep without you
Please Maki
What can I do...
I'll give you my sleeping pills.
Take 2 tablets
I'll be back tomorrow morning
I'm back
To Sabori,Maki..Good bye
Seiko
I'm Maki
I'm relieved she's ok
If that newspaper ad hadn't been read by you, I wasn't sure how to let you know.
But all is my fault
Seiko hit her back and she can't walk
She hit her back? at where?
At the stair.
She told me just before. She felt down
That staircase has a high angle.
I've felt down before
But I wonder Sleeping pills has something to do with stair?
She took sleeping pills and slept upstairs
She suddenly became distressed and tried to drink water.
Then she felt down
Why she tried to sleep upstairs?
I don't know.
Doctor told me don't make her talk a lot
This was happened because I went back to my apartment
I don't feel like going to Paris now
I will stand by her, and look after her until she gets better
Sabori is here, so I have to leave now
Sorry to bother you
Not at all.. well...I need to talk to you
i think her suicide is a lie
The doctor said she didn't take a lot of sleeping pills.
But
I know her very well
When my child was born, Seiko was 6 years old
Everyone was interested in the baby, so Seiko got jealous and cut her hand with a knife.
She misunderstood that everyone was interested in her
I saw the scar in her arm
That's it
I thought she didn't need to fall down the stairs
It's an accident that just happened
It is also an accident that the injury when she hurt herself when she was a child became suppurated.
Then see you
After half a month, Seiko was discharged from the hospital.
Her spine is braced and it is not yet known when she will be able to walk.
I made a promise to move here with Seiko.
You'll move in?
I'll be her nurse
You'll live here again?
Of course
To be honest, I don't wanna have sex with you anymore
I would offend Seiko.
Can you put it up with it?
i found a good solution
I have a favor to ask from you
Tell me
I heard that you were officially registered a long time ago.
Yeah
I also want to register marriage with you
The Japanese Civil Code only allows one married couple.
I want you to adopt me as your adopted daughter
adopted daughter?
You'll be my dad
I'll be your dad?
We can't.
We are only 4 years apart in age
Seiko said that if I'm not legally older, I can become your adopted daughter.
Seiko said that?
Hold on, I look up the law book
I'm 1 yrs younger than Seiko
I think this is an good idea
Look
Article 736
Between spouses or their relatives or their adopted daughters
According to the provisions of Article 729...this is about divorce
Unable to marry even after kinship ends
In other words, if Seiko-san dies, I won't be able to marry you.
If the adoption is terminated, we cannot get married.
Is that Ok?
Yes no problem.
I feel easy going
About the adopted daughter?
I know you are against it
I know how you feel.
I talked with Maki just before
how about you get married?
No way.
I would rather live with Mr. Success than live with him.
I want to live with you if possible
But I don't know when my health will improve
I wish I had died then and everything would have been fine
that's a terrible idea.
I'm not going to marry him after you die
Even if you don't think so, it could be
i have never thought of such a thing
Let's adopt MAKI anyway
Really?
you made a decision?
Are you sure?
Yes if you are ok
I don't mind if you decide it
You should take good filial piety when you become an adopted daughter.
Of course
I have suffered a lot from you, so from now on I will be selfish.
Sure
Right,Dad?
Don't call me Dad
I'm still 29
But you will be a father in six months
We have a daughter, I hope we'll have a boy
Let's sunbathe a little on the porch for your baby
Take me to there
Please take her on the porch
Maybe her suicide this time was her made-up story.
In other words, Maki and I were successfully deceived by this Seiko
No way
i have a sexual aesthetic
I have a sexual aesthetic that was endorsed as revolutionary sex
But...
THE END