That's terrible
The winds are 50 meters high, so the strong winds will blow us away.
It's bad enough that we went there to cover the event and there was a typhoon.
But you filmed well
There is another one
What's this?
This is night view in Ginza
We don't notice these neon lights on a daily basis.
Lots of neon for store signs and building ads.
What do you wanna say about?
What if bigger typhoon attack Tokyo?
These days there are a lot of dirty neon lights and advertisements on top of skyscrapers.
They disturb our lives.
They are at risk of falling down with the wind.
You are saying too much
You think so?
There is nothing we can do about natural disasters.
We should be careful about that
Current neon can withstand wind speeds of up to 60 meters.
So Don't worry
Hold on, Neon and Typhoon..seems interesting
Typhoons come just when you've forgotten about them
Typhoons with wind speeds of 60 meters or more are possible.
Wind Velocity 75 Meters / Typhoon Reporter (1963)
Now we are going to have a lighting ceremony for the neon building.
The daughter of the Marutaka company responsible for the construction turns on the switch.
Next, a representative from TOZAI Pharmaceuticals's Fujikawa will address the audience.
I'll address you
Today is the 30th anniversary of TOZAI Pharmaceuticals!
It's also the anniversary of the new pharmaceuticals.
Our neon building was completed to commemorate this event!
I really appreciate you guys
Thank you for helping us
I really appreciate what you help us.
we want to help you guys too
We will continue to make efforts to develop new drugs
Please enjoy our neon tonight
Thank you for having me here today
I'm relieved that the construction will be in time for the lighting ceremony
I was not going to get fired.
Our workers worked so hard
Yamaguchi's design worked it
Asanuma took to control the site
It is thanks to him that the construction was completed on time.
I'm shy
Give me easier work next time
You're funny
Let's toast
Welcome
I happen to see u
Are you here for congratulate me or scolding me?
What should I say first
Let's be friendly today.
No matter what the weather, this neon stays the same
I hope so
He's here again
Come
Thanks for coming,Tamura
Congratulation
Thanks
I forbid you to associate with her if you bully me
You're good at joking
Please have fun
Serve him
I got a big fish for you
It was so nice fish
He asks me if it's okay if a typhoon with winds of 60 m/s comes.
He's always cuddling with her
You get upset about that?
I'm not good at taking care of women.
Not like you
Me? why?
You have a nice wife
Wife...
Please stay little more
I wanna see something before seeing my wife
What wanna see?
Neon
Look
I like how it changes from purple to red
Stay strong
Wait
What? the neon got burn?
You got shot?
It's me
criminal is on the run
I don't know the number
It was hard to check it
Ok I get it
Go to police,Kagawa
You go too
It's dangerous to shoot at midnight
What's wrong?
I can't believe the neon lights I saw 6 hours ago
It's someone's harassment
Marutaka Company and another company bid on the construction tender
Endo
they raced to the end
I was thinking about that too..but I can't believe Endo company did it
It could be
I heard that ENDO worked behind the scenes
They are Yakuza from Manshu
Marutaka got famous about this work
Marutaka will take an advantage about Neon work
It's ridiculous to interfere just for that reason
We need to investigate it
Connect to Nagoya branch
I feel weird
Tonight's case is your job.
Nogoya51568.
it’s urgent
Hi, I'm Kitaya
It's me
Oh boss
I’m on schedule
I will arrive in Kobe tomorrow morning
Did you book properly?
It's fine
I made it.
I look forward to reading tomorrow morning's paper
Oh Tamura
You had a hard time
Where's dad?
He went to the hospital with Mr. Yamaguchi.
did he say something about tonight?
Did he say someone interfered?
No
Let's see Nagoya Endo company
he didn't say anything
what do you think about it?
i don't believe it
you really doubt them
Forget about this
Why?
ask my dad as interview
He's coming back
how was their condition?
They're ok
You had a hard time
I had
who do you think is the culprit?
I was asked about it by a newspaper reporter at the hospital.
Tamura says that the culprit is Endo.
what do you think?
I have no idea.
it's a police job
I'm mad at seeing that destroyed neon
we shouldn't be quiet
Don't be mad
We're not Yakuza
But we must draw the line.
We have to find solid evidence that Endo did it.
It's not good to speculate.
leave the culprit to the police
we have to remake neon again
what is the construction cost?
Consult with TOZAI Pharmaceutical first. but We will do it whatever happens
I don't care if the company goes bankrupt
That NEON has a one-year warranty, so we are responsible.
i don't worry about money
Ok?
Please do your best again from tomorrow
Sorry to disturb you
Won't you guys pay for the construction costs?
Of course not
We paid 50 million yen that cost to Marutaka Company.
There is a one-year warranty, so any accidents during that time are their responsibility.
You're so cold
This is a contractual issue between companies, so it can't be helped.
I've been criticized for building this neon.
I have been criticized a lot because I spent too much money.
But last night's incident was an unforeseen disaster.
Marutaka company accept it.
It's none of your business
Mr. Maruyama came here earlier and said that he will complete it in the middle of next month.
i have a meeting now, sorry
What's wrong?
I'll go to the site
the doctor said you should rest
I am worried and responsible for NEON
I'm going
What's wrong?
Ok I won't go
I just designed it so I don't have to go
I'll sleep
You should go
You sure?
I know how you feel
You are so sweating
I haven't been home much since I got married. sorry
Don't worry. please go
What's wrong?
Are you ok?
i feel dizzy
You should rest
Is Yamaguchi here?
Thanks for coming
Welcome
Thanks
You had a hard time
Please rest
they are so cruel
I'm glad that the only people injured were me and Mr. Asada.
Do you also think that Endo interfered?
I can't say clearly but I think so
WE and Endo Company have been on bad terms for a long time.
Whenever we made a bid, he always made a bid too.
They couldn't beat our president, so they always lost and ran away.
They said they would merge with us a year ago.
Of course our boss refused.
I didn't know that
I think our boss will have a lot to worry about from now on.
Repair work will cost 50 million yen
we have no profit
our company may go bankrupt
Don't worry
I will see the site from now on
I'll see it for you
You can go for me
Thanks
don't be humble
I feel hot
I'm still single
I'm sorry
You've been having a hard time with the restoration work since this morning.
I will do my best for the company
I support you guys.
I thought you dislike NEON because you are a typhoon reporter
You're right
But I'm annoyed by the background of this incident
Please Write a special article about our company's neon
I'll drop you off at the site
Really?
Do you care?
You have other drivers, right?
I’m worried about her being kidnapped
it's a good time
What can I do for you?
That black car was found
Where?
In Kofu
Kofu?
They abandoned the car near the station.
Please go to support Mina-chan
Ok but...
Please write an article about the typhoon later.
Prioritize this case
I'm counting on you
Leave it to me
Kagawa works for the Metropolitan Police Department, so you might know about ENDO from the car.
I'm back
Thank you for your hard work
What about Marutaka Company?
They panic a lot, but it's okay
They are working again from this morning
Really?
they don't give up easily
They are obstructing our advance into Tokyo.
I will defeat them by any means necessary.
I know
In doing so, we are...
Get the phone
This is Endo Industry
Who's there?
Police?
Our boss is out now
i am the manager
What did Kuroki and Maruyama do at Asama Onsen?
I don't pretend I don't know
we fired them a month ago
They are too dangerous
we have nothing to do with them
is the fingerprint ok
they saw your face?
No worries
I heard that a black car was abandoned in front of the station.
i thought i was lucky
you should give up
Employee Caught at Asama Onsen is a Substitute
It can't be helped because they confessed themselves and had pistols.
The black car is the stolen car..
Damn it
This case will remain unsolved.
The incident may have just begun.
just begun?
Endo will definitely take the next action
I see.
I'm frustrated tonight
Let's go back
Yes
i will take your stress away
she is very nice
That's good service
please work there
On my god
What are you doing?
Work harder
Don't look at it.
Go back to work
Hello
Did you get better,Yamaguchi
work makes me feel better
your wife is angry with you
The situation is worse than you think?
Gunpowder destroyed all the neon signs
We have to redo everything
But you have a deadline
If it's a simple construction, it looks like I'll be able to make it on time
But if a typhoon comes, it will be a big problem.
He's here again
Thank you for your hard work
Oh you are here too
Put this away
Please eat this
Let's take a rest
I have to work
It's sweet time
Come to eat
Thanks
Please eat
I'm lucky
Do you like sweets?
Yes
That's sweet bum
This is meat?
Please eat a lot
Bring it to me
Yes
Thanks
That's good
Where are you looking?
Your fault!
Oh you're Kitani
Excuse me but who are you?
I'm Teruko Maruyama
From Hakuba mountaineering
Hakuba mountaineering?
Yes
are you the dark skinned girl?
Yes I am
This is a very odd coincidence.
You look different
you haven't changed at all
I'm dumb, so I'm the same as before
No way
You look great
i am happy to be praised by you
Smoke?
No
You're still serious
This store is no different too
I often come here too
We made a schedule here, didn't we?
Iced coffee,2
you were so stubborn
you ended up sticking to your plan
Are you in Tokyo all the way?
Since I came to Tokyo recently, I am at the hotel now.
What do you do?
I am a manager of a small company
here is my business card
You're executive
Just job title
have you married yet?
no one will marry me
You are too picky
Thanks.
How about you?
no one will marry me too
You are too picky
Oh my god
i want to date you from now
Go ahead
do you have time tomorrow night?
i can make time for you
i want you to meet someone
It's been seven years since I met you
You belonged to the swimming club and I belonged to the mountaineering club.
we always acted differently
Kappa and mountain man met for the first time in 7 years
Thanks to her
you should thank me more
Yes we do
I invited her to join the swimming club, but I understand why she didn't come.
What kind of company is Kono Akatsuki industrial?
This is a new company that does anything
But you're not a funeral or pawn shop director, are you?
no way
We used to go to the pawn shop
The shop behind the school?
they took good care of us
my watch was taken to a pawn shop
Really?
Don't pretend you don't know
this was a memento of my mother
he cried to me and asked
tonight i will treat you
Let's have fun
You drink nicely
Is the job of a journalist interesting?
i like doing this job
he is called a typhoon reporter
typhoon reporter?
That's dangerous
Suppose a big typhoon like the Isewan Typhoon comes to Tokyo.
He's started
An even bigger typhoon may come to Tokyo.
How would you feel if a typhoon with a wind speed of 65 meters or more hits Tokyo?
At high tide in Tokyo Bay at storm surge
What do you think will happen if the levee breaks?
If so, 60% of Tokyo residents will be held and 30% will die
160,000 casualties in Tokyo died in WWII in 10 months
A single typhoon causes twice as many casualties
Clam down
The citizens of Tokyo must seriously think about the countermeasures.
There are three government agencies related to the reclamation work in Tokyo Bay.
More than 10 companies are contracting the construction.
I don't think you can do the right job in that situation.
I see I see
He always gets excited when he talks about typhoons.
I understand he's typhoon reporter
By the way,
what kind of hostess do you like?
I don't want
You dance,right?
I won't
But let's call
Teruko is here
I can dance
But
Ok I'll leave
Oh I have to go
where are you going?
I'll see you soon
See you
You'll stay here?
Yes
Shall we dance?
What's wrong?
I feel I ended up being in Tokyo
I'll do my best
I am currently working on a plan to be a company
If it goes well I will be promoted
Then....
Is it definitely Akatsuki Industry?
Yes for sure.
The other day you said it was the beginning
I have since contacted the Nagoya office to find out.
That’s good to know
Endo took over Akatsuki industrial for advancing in Tokyo
They use violent
Akatsuki industrial is small company but has carrier
ENDO interferes with Marutaka and Endo use Akatsuki industrial for advancing in Tokyo
I've heard of the name
I didn't know Endo took over
I'm sure about that
If so, is there evidence that Akatsuki industrial interferes with Marutaka?
I haven't got the evidence yet, but I'm really sure
I see..Endo did it
You seem to get lost weight
I was busy
Welcome
Where have you been?
You always go outside these days
You're scary
Serve him
You are too serious.
What happened?
Endo broke our NEON as I thought
You sure?
According to Tamura, Endo used Akatsuki industrial in Tokyo to do it
Akatsuki industrial
What happened?
She's selfish
I am currently working on a plan to be a company
If it goes well I will be promoted
Thank for coming
Have a seat
What happened?
You have something to do with ENdo?
ENdo?
Nagoya ENdo
They interferes with Marutaka
I have no idea
It can't be helped you reply like that
You're rude
I have the evidence
You can't escape
You are not Communist.
Give me a break
You didn't know Teruko's father was a president of Marutaka?
You didn't know
You didn't do that if you knew it
She knows about that?
She knows
I'll definitely solve this
Can you think over?
I'm your friend
I took him to here
Come in
Are you sure anyone will find this
That's what I wanna say
Listen, I have money
Work perfectly
I know
Be careful about Marutaka
Laborers for wiring work are hard to gather.
OKOK
We're in trouble
The way we're doing it now, we're not going to make it in time.
Change the power distribution design and cut corners.
No way,we can't do that
This is just repair
we can't do that
Please
Don't get mad, we need to think about this
What should we do then
He's here again
He's insist
He's annoying
What's wrong?
Power distribution engineers interfered in this morning
Hi Tamura.
Is the news in the newspapers the work of ENDO?
I haven't got the evidence yet
What?
You wrote this,right?
Why you didn't write clearly?
What the hell, what? our president?
Our president got mad now
I'm frustrated with him
He never complains, so everyone likes him.
He does not listen to us
Asamuma
What are you doing?
Go back to the site
Look
There are new workers today
Work as fast as you can
I know
Did you read this?
Yes
You don't do anything?
For what?
Endo
Endo?
They interfered with the timing of the construction deadline.
Newspaper doesn't say Endo does it
You are still young but get mad?
Go back to the site
Damn it
Hurry up!
A Reporter came and ask me a lot
I wonder Marutaka find something
Anyway, watch out about Marutaka,OK?
Are you okay with the worker buyout thing?
That Umehara?
Don't worry, I owe him a lot
He won't tell it to anyone
We have a guest. sorry
Have a seat
What's wrong?
Can you go back to Nagoya now?
Nagoya?
What's wrong?
If I had my druthers, I would have noticed this when I met you near the construction site.
You are talking about the news.
That's fake
We have nothing to do with that
I guess only Tamura's agent write that
He's mad these days.
This is the list of executives of our company
Don’t pretend you don't know.
I know Endo is behind you
Endo?
No way
I'm working hard on my job
You get misunderstanding something
I haven't met him
Kitani
Don't make fun of me
Hold on
What the hell?
Oh daughter
Why you are here?
I'm here to talk with him
Get out from the site now
We are talking about that with her now
I'm not asking about her
My answer is same
I refuse it
Answer
I know you have something to do with Endo
Get out from the site now
Sorry.
Bring medicine
I'm OK
You guys go home
You have dishonored my father.
I can't accept this
Our enemy is someone behind Kitani
Sorry to disturb you
Sorry
I'm OK
I'll keep secret what happened
Does it hurt?
I'm OK
What's wrong?
You wanted to help him even if you were injured?
It was just happening
I thought you loved Tamura all the way
But Actually you love Kitani
Don't say bullshit
Does Tamura really hold the assurance?
I think so.
So He wrote that on the news paper
His article is problematic.
That is the article I want to fight with Dawn Industries.
They'll interference again for sure
What are you doing,Umehara?
Work hard
We have all the materials for the NEon
Code is missing
Why?
They ask me to pay first
We have money
Call them to bring it
I get it
Where's Asanuma now?
You sure that he went to Yanagibashi's bank?
I'm sure
He and Kawakami went there for the loan
Kawakami is a moneylender
I see
moneylender
However, please entrust your house in Aoyama to me as collateral.
That's fine
you had a bad experience
I have to complete this task for my pride
I see
Please keep our promise,Maruyama
I'll trust you
Can you stop it?
Stop it
You?
As a result of forensics, Mr. Moriyama was sitting in the back
The driver was shot dead inside the trunk
Nothing else is found because the sea water has washed the inside of the car
nothing was found?
Non-victim fingerprints found on door
Related to Endo?
I can't tell
All of Maruyama's belongings were taken.
I think it's the work of robbers
Daughter. you keep staying here?
What should we do?
Go to the site
Please complete Neon by the deadline for my father
Let's go,Asanuma
We're going
Thank you
Did you know who killed the president?
Not yet
According to the investigative headquarters, before he was killed, he met a man at Yanagiya's restaurant.
They are investigating who was he
Teruko
i can't stand it anymore
You might end my friendship with Kitani
Is that Ok?
It can't be helped
Do you still love him
Stop talking about him
I’m just a journalist
i may not be able to help you
But if you have trouble, please consult me
Don't think too much
Take care of yourself
Are you going to buy back Mr. Maruyama's mortgage from me?
Yes
I want your reply now
is this check real?
You can call your bank to confirm that
I get it.
This is my business
Since Mr. Maruyama is dead, there is no point in owning his house.
I was going to turn it into money someday.
Let's deal with me
Do you want us to stop this construction?
it's a silly story
80% completed
Why you want us to stop?
I am very grateful to Mr. Maruyama, and I am very sorry to tell you about this.
If another incident comes, the impression of our company will be bad.
it has nothing to do with construction
It's not irrelevant because I'm requesting an extension of the construction period.
we are waiting for the materials because the materials have not arrived
Anyway we can't wait anymore
We have to complete it on time,right?
It's too late
Please complete within 3 days
3 days?
That NEON was completed once
The company's pride was destroyed by that incident.
It's so embarrassing to leave the neon broken garbage
We can make it
Let's do it
3 days are enough
As you hear, we keep our promises
Please keep our promise
We want to advertise immediately
we keep our promises
Tamura
What?
I have a letter about an article you wrote
Read them
Most say it's not good to blame Akatsuki Industry
I believe this was written by Akatsuki Industry
It could be
Would you rather post the letter or ignore it?
Let's post this
I will write clearly that it is Endo s fault
I will write all the investigations of this investigation, including the sabotage case and Mr. Maruyama's murder case.
Let's do it
Then we can defeat Endo Kogyo with the power of public opinion.
But be careful about them
They are too dangerous
So be careful
Tamura, phone call for you
I'm here
I can meet you tonight
Welcome
I was going to call you up
it was convenient.
Wanna drink something?
Cut it out,Kitani
For what?
Don't pretend you don't know
Leave from Endo
That's rubbish
you wrote a lie
You bother me
you think you are innocent?
You wrote a certain industry
That's funny
i didn't write the company name for you
I actually intended to write clearly as Endo industrial
The newspaper company's information network is very reliable.
I see
You've become a very dirty man in 7 years
It doesn't matter if it's dirty or clean
Humans always change in 7 years
Have you ever thought about Teruko's feelings?
don't talk about her
failed negotiations
It could be
You have no intention of quitting your current job?
No
You're not going to dismiss the article, are you?
I'll write clearly Endo
Hold on
let me think for three days
three days?
two days ok
What do you think?
I get it
this is our last friendship
Hold on
Have one drink
No
Leave me alone
The weather is bad these days
According to the news, another typhoon is coming.
Every year around this time, a typhoon comes and messes up the outside.
Japan really has a lot of typhoons.
Do Truk Islands really exist?
A typhoon with a maximum wind speed of 45 M comes to Japan from there.
We should be careful
It would have been very difficult if it had been a dump truck instead of a truck.
did you come here again by plane?
That's cool
i want to get on a plane too
i have to win the lottery
I have never won the lottery
But I won 50 yen last month
Please leave
For what?
do you guys take a bath?
I will go to bed immediately without taking a bath this year
I see. please take a rest
Good night
Hey
do not ever mention my name.
Are you going to stop interfering with the construction work?
No way
Tamura will pursue further
Beat him
Bring Konishi tomorrow
Even if Tamura is killed, the people at the newspaper company will know.
You don't listen to me?
I don't mean that
Tamura has been my friend since I was a student.
So what?
i fought with your father in the war in China
your father committed suicide on correction day.
I brought your father's remains to Japan.
I took care of you and sister and paid for the tuition up to the university.
I gave you money for your mother's funeral
you have to thank me
Yes. it's me
What? typhoon?
wind speed is?
The wind speed is 45 M, so there may be damage.
Can you come to the site?
I feel sorry for your wife
I'll be there soon
Is typhoon coming?
It seems big.
Turn on the radio
I really hate Typhoon
Typhoon No. 12 developed and the central pressure reached 918 mbar.
The typhoon has a maximum wind speed of 45 m/s and is accompanied by heavy rain.
we don't know where the typhoon will land in Japan now.
The scale of the typhoon is believed to be larger than the Isewan Typhoon that came last year.
We're going to the site
Please
we prepare for the typhoon
Thanks
Take care
Will Typhoon No. 13 come to Japan?
is there another typhoon?
Typhoon No. 13 has occurred
Where?
Right behind Typhoon No.
Oh two typhoon
No.13 is small but Typhoon No. 12 has a maximum wind speed of 55 M.
Where is it going?
There are three possible paths
Course from Okinawa to Mainland China
Course to go to south Kyushu
A course that goes all over Japan from Kyushu
Now is the season for typhoon reporters
If that typhoon makes landfall in Japan, it will become the biggest typhoon, even bigger than the Isewan Typhoon.
is there a typhoon?
If you come, we will suffer great damage.
If it comes to Tokyo, it will be around evening tomorrow.
It is dangerous to work halfway
Where have you been?
I was in toilet
You've been acting strange lately.
No way
You instructed the illegal construction, didn't you?
Endo asked you?
Or Akatsuki?
I don't know anything
never come here again!
Really?
He's basted
We need  more workers
It's me, what?
You need more workers?
we want perfect construction
Can you handle it?
Sorry for being late
Tell me how is the site?
they were doing emergency work
We'll see how it goes
I got a mortgage on MARUTAKA from Mr. Kawakami.
Tamura is the problem
Typhoon No. 12 increased in strength and the maximum wind speed reached 60 M.
Heading north after passing through Okinawa
It is currently unknown whether the typhoon will make landfall in Kyushu or mainland Japan.
The Kanto region will enter the storm zone at night.
The promise with Tamura is until tomorrow, right?
Yes
OK
Shiodome 10 people ,Ao 5,Take 10,
A total of 25 people come to help
Thank you
That's enough
Leave it to us
I'm counting on you guys
Kyushu will enter the storm zone and there will be a lot of damage
Typhoon No. 12 is moving north at 50 km/h.
Typhoon No. 12 is expected to make landfall through the Kii Peninsula.
Be careful with fishing boats
He's coming
Damn it.
Tamura!
Hey, what are you doing?
About 25 people go to the construction site.
They won't give up
He's coming
Really?
I have to go
I mean, Typhoon
Typhoon No. 12 recorded a maximum wind speed of 60 M on the Kii Peninsula.
Typhoon No. 12 is getting bigger and continuing northward.
The center of the typhoon will pass through Tokyo at around 6 o'clock tonight.
There is no risk of high tide as it is not at high tide
The wind is very strong, so please reinforce your house and secure drinking water.
Be careful as power outages and flooding may send
This is the current situation
how about the army?
They are waiting
Kamata region situation?
This is the countermeasures headquarters
Typhoon No. 12 suddenly changed its course to the north off the coast of Enshunada.
The Kanto region is likely to be out of the typhoon zone.
Typhoon is not coming
Typhoon is not coming?
Kanto region will be safe
It was close
Oops
Please don't worry and keep working
You can sleep well tonight
I'm worried about another incident happening
I'm going home earlier
You run away
I wanna drink
do you want to get drunk alone?
Let's call to Yocchan
Hi, oh Kagawa?
What?
The typhoon changed its course?
The typhoon has increased its speed and is now 45 kilometers per hour.
Wind speed is 60 M
Lands in mainland Japan around 10:00
Landing point is Tokyo exactly
The high tide in Tokyo Bay is at 10:10.
I will be big problem.
I'll call you later
He's coming
We shouldn't have been optimistic
Let's act as planned tonight
How about you?
I'll stay
Hi
Are they doing construction when the typhoon is coming?
Marutaka?
Really?
I see
So Tamura is going
He's my friend
I have to do something
A storm would be convenient, so go after him right away.
blackmail him
If he throw away the articles so far, say you won't kill him
He's your friend
Kill him if he refuse
I ask konishi to support you
He will watch how you solve
We have to make it by tonight.
We are about to complete
You guys don't know how Typhoon is scary
Get them away, and we will save here
Only a portion of the power distribution system remains.
Watch out.
What if Neon fall down
That Neon is like my child
You don't know how we feel
It's impossible
You have to run. It's not safe.
Leave from here
You get out
You stupid
Leave from here
You must lead them
I'll leave it to you
Save them!
You say Neon will be fall down
But I wanna see how it goes
She's saying right
If My dad is alive, I'm sure we won't leave
You don't believe what I say?
I wanna do what I want
Don't waste time.
Leave from here
You're crazy
Go home
Tamura
I need to talk with you
What?
You want to reply?
You decided to leave from Endo?
Can you leave from that case?
I can't
I'll write the truth
You don't listen to me?
You should wake up
You insist.
I'll write the truth
I'll write about what Endo does
Hold on
You're going to die
You show how you are.
That's what is Endo doing
And you are his dog
You leave or not?
You leave
Don't say bullshit
You are under control by Endo
It's none of your business
You'll be arrested
That's matter of time
I'll expose everything what endo did
You don't have to
Konishi
Tamura
Next your turn
You'll be dead
You
Don't get angry
Boss told me to kill you guys
Don't say bullshit
I believe in him
Boss told me to kill you guys.
and promote me
Tamura
You OK?
Hold on
Sorry
You OK?
I'm OK
BE patient
Sorry
Thank,Kitani
Feel better?
Kitani
Tamura.
You OK?
Kitani
Teruko is on the roof
She'll be in danger.
She doesn’t listen to me
Save her,KItani
Teruko
Where are you?
Watch out!
Kitani
You OK?
Teruko
Tamura is nice guy
He's so kind
Kitani
Leave from here
You should give up
Be strong
Kitani
I finally understand how Typhoon is scary
What you said was right
Humans cannot win against the forces of nature.
A typhoon is a natural disaster, so it can't be helped
I don't think so
Typhoons are not natural disasters but also man-made disasters.
man-made disasters.
We must always take steps to prevent that.
I'll keep writing the post
To prevent a disaster like this from happening again
that's one way to comfort the victim
Typhoons are not natural disasters but also man-made disasters.
We must prevent it
A typhoon with a wind speed of 75 meters or more may come.
THE END