Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Gorotsuki Inu / Rogue Dog
(Inu/Dog Series #3)
I'm going on another trip.
I'm thinking of getting a wife and settling down
But I'm good guy and good rider
I want to play some more
It can't be helped
She's a good woman
Shit
It can't be helped
Can you help me to ride?
Go ahead
Why am I so popular with women?
It can't be helped.
I'm good guy
That's what I thought.
This is great
you have a fake
I'm coming to see you tonight
I'm Fukuda from the North Kobe group.
Thank you for your help
It seems like you guys are worried about something.
That's right.
Our boss is gone and business in Osaka is currently very poor.
So we came to another place
If the police come, you're over
don't worry about it
I don't want to get too involved in the issue right now
This is a very interesting pistol bullet.
Who's the hell he is
Here it is
This is great meal
That woman ordered this dish.
Have a hearty meal.
I see
It's been a long time since I've seen you
Are you Tamako?
I don't know you
My dead wife's name was Tamako.
Looks and is about the same age as you
I miss her
Why she died?
she died in a car accident
she was hit and run.
So I'm searching all over the country for the culprit.
Your dead wife looked like me?
Kind of
There's one thing that's definitely different.
don't say bad things about me
Face?
No.. it's boobs
She's got nice boobs
I've got nice boobs,too
nothing compares to you
Then try to touch mine
Then let me touch yous
You've got nice boobs too
They are well balanced
When she died of pneumonia, she took my hand and put it to her chest.
You just said that she died in a car accident.
Oh shit
Thank you
Don't pick on me
This is what you do when you make fun of someone
I love you
Are you sure?
Well, if that's the case... there's only two things I wanna ask
Number one, that woman who brought me here... who the hell is she?
She's been here for over a month.
She's a rich widow from Osaka, YOKO MISAWA.
She's staying alone?
Yes
She's a rich widow
Don't play her
Don't get jealous.
She might fall in love with you
I'm jealous
Don't fall in love with me
I wanna ask you one more things
Where's the gambling place tonight?
I have no idea
You're too honest
I love that kind of innocence.
You think so?
Ok I'll tell you
It's a place called Kura, which is located in a separate annex.
I see
Han
Cho
Decide!
Ok
Ready?
Han
do you continue?
Bid please
What's wrong?
You cheated on me
I’m very angry with you
I'll play with you later
Really?
Yes
I'll wait
You're here
thank you for waiting for me
You look so nice
I want to hide here tonight.
I don't know if I'm bothering you.
You rented this room for me.
If you want to hide, I've got the perfect body to do it.
I'm so glad you did.
I'm counting on you.
you're quick to hide
I hear you're a rich widow.
Yoko Mita
Kamoi,How do you know my name?
I asked maid
How do you know my name?
I checked in under a false name
You're Daisuke Kamoi for sure
you didn't know?
You cheated me
your age and style,
I heard you ran away to KISHU.
Who told you?
Even police does not know
You disappeared from Osaka
Are you related to Osaka?
Are you a member of yakuza?
No
I didn't know.
I didn't even know MISAWA was murdered.
I didn't know he was a gangster... and that he owed money to them.
They killed your husband.
What's your business?
Money lender?
He had a legitimate financial business in Kitahama.
He didn't know that he was lending money to a gangster.
We couldn’t collect the money in the usual way.
We hired another collection specialist.
Then the problem got bigger.
I get it
But dead people don't come back to life
He's probably having an affair in heaven right now.
You're such a cold person
that's one of my charms
Please... strike at my master's enemies.
No, I'll be your master's enemy
Hold on
I can't stop once I run
My heart's racing, and yours, too.
Let's cool it down a bit before we talk.
He's late
What's he doing?
I'm tired after hitting anything,
There's a bar called SUMIRE in Shinsekai. The office of the 16 groups is on the second floor of a bar in Shinsekai
They commit various intelligent crimes
There are three executives,Inatori,henmi,Kawakami
You want me to kill them?
Or they'll kill me.
They'll kill me the same way they killed my husband.
I'd go to the police.
They won't listen to me if I tell them I financed the gang.
Inatori,henmi,Kawakami
Yeah, I'm starving.
I'm serious.
I'm serious, too, and I'm serious about my desires.
Leave it to me
are you kidding me?
I'm not,wife
wife?
Trust me
It can't be helped
wife?
Thanks
You've got nice shoes
feet are important
you look like a playboy
How do you know?
You can tell what kind of man he is by looking at his shoes
So I'm playboy?
Your shoes are starting to break down
Don't pick on me
Don't get me wrong
I see
Nice joke
pay for the space
What are you doing?
You're kamoi
You're back in Osaka
You're popular
I can beat them easily
Thank you very much
Here's change
Take it
Come to my bar
What's wrong?
Yakitori is gone
Yakitori?
Welcome
Why you are chasing me?
We are ex Tenchi and Gamo group
You did something to us
I see.
Are you on probation?
please work well
Our boss was arrested because of you.
Give him some tsukudani.
What's the hell?
Come with me
They are chicken
It's not because of you
What?
Oh you, It's been ages
You look so nice
How's your salary?
So so
I'll treat you a meal
What meal?
Of course, Udon
you love udon
I want to eat steak once in a while
What are you thinking about?
Nothing, just women
She's nice
I like udon noodles because it's connected to my sense of life.
Your sense of life?
Tap it, stretch it, make it long and thin
This is my life
I see.
And on top of that, it's elusive.
Kamoi
Detective Miyamoto committed suicide
He was killed by a pistol master like you.
pistol master?
Is he better than I?
It could be
He is Shuji Inatori from 16 group
16 group?
2F at sumire bar?
Do you know?
I've heard that name a little bit
Shuji Inatori is missing
will you look for him?
I don't want to work for your salary
you don't pay me
You're right.
I don't pay too
If you were in illegal possession of a gun, I could arrest you.
Unfortunately, you don't have one.
What do you order?
Hold on
If you're in Osaka.
The current Tenjikai and GAMO gang are a pain in the ass.
If you'll just take my word for it...
I'll talk to them myself.
I see
I see you're afraid.
You heard there was a gunslinger who is better than you.
That's why you're so pissed off.
I know how you feel.
You can't do anything by yourself without a gun.
Hold on
I'm better than him
It can't be helped
Well, I'd like to meet him.
But you don't have a gun
I'm strong without a pistol
I see, give me a soup of Udon
I want to eat that soup
I won't help for you
I want to defeat that Inatori
I want to have a pistol duel with him
I'm looking for a pistol later
Just in case
I know
Is she madam here?
I'm looking forward to it.
mayumi,I just got a call.
Inatori wants to see you.
Mr. Inatori is back in Osaka?
Don't listen to him,ok?
Henmi
What are you talking with her?
I'll take Mayumi to Inatori.
No, I'll take her
Inatori asked me to take her
I won't go
Henmi, you fall in love with her?
She’s our business tool
She's not just yours
You just have to stay with him for a while
Hold on, I need to talk with her
If you don't go there, we can't get any share
You have to listen to him
Mr. Inatori, using me as a tool.
It can't be helped
We need money, then we can use the money
Don't throw me away
Let's go,Mayumi
Get away
I saw you in the evening
I don't know you
Police asked me so
I see, ok I don't know you
By the way , wanna have a drink for our sake?
What are you talking about?
Just one drink, ok?
OK let’s go
What's wrong?
Don't wanna enter?
This bar is our enemy's
16 groups have managed this store since TENCHIKAI and GAMO disbanded.
We can't go
Don't worry, I'm with you
Defeat 16 group then you should manage here
Can you help us with your pistol skill?
Of course I'll help you guys
What's the hell?
16 groups's bar is here?
They talked about killing your boss
So I took them to here
You cheated us
It's too late to make excuses.
What's the hell?
They are our enemy
I heard their talking.
They talked badly about you
You cheated us
It's too late to make excuses.
Leave it to you
Who are you?
I'm just stranger like nasal mucus
You're not our enemy?
No way, I like you
You cheated us
Thanks
What's wrong?
Where's mayumi?
Still at work.
Bros
Thanks for your help
I don't like to ingratiate myself.
I have a college degree in economics.
Are you good at economic?
Well, I'd be happy to work for you if you let me, but...
I'm good at keeping the books.
I've been involved with a company that's in violation of the Foreign Exchange Control Law.
Can you do it?
I see  I see that’s alright
I'm good at it
I'm going to pull out the core of that apple
What?
I also took apple seeds.
But Don’t be surprised
I can show you more
Which guy is Inatori?
What's wrong?
He's police's dog
Me?
What are you talking about?
I hate polices
Tenchikai told us
I know they are lying
Don't tell a lie.
he's our guest
He's pistol master
He told us to help us
Yeah, I'm not police
He's passed out
Get the pistol
What's the hell?
I feel dizzy
What company?
company?
What do you mean?
I am a victim.
How about you?
This is my business card
Manager, First Sales Section, Kansai Boeki Kaisha, Ltd.
Thanks
I was tricked into coming here by a young woman.
I was forced to take sleeping pills and my important documents were stolen.
Where the hell am I?
Stay down
I have a pistol, stay down
I wish I could have a pistol
It can't be helped
I'll smoke
I was ordered by the boss.
Now I'm giving you orders.
It's your job to kill him.
It's not a good idea to use people to make profit.
What if I kill him?
If you kill him, there will be more trade jobs in Kansai.
It worth 40 million yen
Use this pistol
Police chase Kamoi
Don't worry about you
Let's all share the profits of this work.
Boss,Inatori, you and me
Let's get big money
Be sure to kill him, I'm watching you
Bear in mind
If that's the case, I'll do it.
Boss called to release Kamoi
Why?
He's not either police or Gamo,tanchi's guy
Why boss know?
I should ask him
The boss's orders are absolute
Release him
Release Kamoi
I wanna go home
Don't kill me
Give me my pistol
Stupid, you should thank to us, you are alive
Go
Boss is Inatori?
It's none of your business
Give me my pistol
later
When?
Tonight
Take him to your house
This is Boss's order
I trust you
What are you going to do with him?
We'll release him later
Hold on, I need my pistol
I'll pay you back later
Hold on
Are you a police officer?
It's none of your business
Anyway, I know for a fact that you're trying to destroy 16group.
Go to this place, I'll give you the pistol
I trust you
Go
See you
I don't have a pistol, so I feel lonely and feel like I'm going to catch a cold.
I’m looking forward to tonight
Too early
Wrong person
Come in
He'll come back soon
Whose house is this?
did you come here without knowing?
Here's Shibata's houses
Is this his house?
What do you think about this?
I'd rather play...
That person went shopping with KING in hand.
That's ridiculous
Place like this
Please don't do such things without permission
Sorry for keeping you waiting
You're a shoe shiner, aren't you?
You're the playboy
I didn't know this was your house
Come in
Here's my house
Sorry for keeping you waiting
I'd rather play...
Why did you come here?
A beautiful woman asked me to come here and wait for someone.
Mayumi?
Yes bar sumire's woman
Get out from here
Why?
Get out from here.
don't come to someone's house without permission
Don't get upset
It's none of your business
She is my daughter
Get out from here
I'll wait here until she comes
Wait
Get out from here
He's so short temper
Come here, there's a problem
What's wrong?
He's down
King is on his face
Please don't die until the shogi game is over.
please contact a doctor
He's alive.
mayumi?
I'll take her
Stay strong
I contacted mayumi
When I came he died
he said he didn't feel well in the morning
I forced him to play shogi.
He asked me to take care of Mayumi
yes. that's right
Give him this pistol and come right back.
you are going to the wake tonight,
Kawakami and Inatori does not know we are together
Please come by 9:30
I'll be waiting here with my train ticket and luggage.
mayumi
I happened to be present at his death.
Dad
I was Bad girl.
Forgive me....
He worried about you
He asked me to take care of Mayumi
I want to marry her after the funeral is over.
What are you talking about?
He told me
no evidence
he can't talk because he's dead
Dad
I want to live seriously for you
Don't worry
I’ll look after her
Thanks
Thank you for taking care of the rest.
What?
Hold on
I think you should clean up after yourself
let me go
Oh this is
I missed this
This works fine
Thanks
But... leaving your parents' funeral to the neighbors and going home...
This is unforgivable.
He's not your real dad.
but...
you call him Dad.
He raised me.
You know what they say about a godparent and a foster parent, don't you?
I'll raise you as your husband
you should get out of that group
You should be careful
You don't have to worry about that.
Could you represent us at the farewell ceremony?
Wait a minute
Wait a minute?
I thought you were going to be her husband
I was just asked
I hope you are not bad man
Do I look?
Where she's gone?
Get your hands off of me!
I’m sad
What are you doing?
I've done. let's leave from Osaka
What's wrong?
Go ahead.
I was ordered by the BOSS to join the MAFUJI-gumi in Hiroshima.
So?
I killed kacho with that pistol
I thought you didn't kill him and you were going to ask me out and run away.
I'd killed if I didn't kill him
I don't want the share
I wanted to get out from 16 group with you but
You don't like?
I killed him, you don't wanna stay with me anymore?
you wanna stay with me ?
Henmi
Help us
Fire?
Yakuza's fight?
Which group?
He was killed by pistol
By yappa
Ok let's bid
Did you confirm?
What's the hell?
She looks nice
she's already dressed
yes really
What are you going to do?
What's wrong?
you are a murder suspect
Don't lose any sleep over it.
I just got here.
Ok it's not you
you don't have the pistol
you are a really nosy bastard
What's the hell?
You're too noisy
I wanna fight with you
Just bring it
Ok come
Look, I'm stronger
I've seen this before
Yours?
Don't say bullshit
That one came out of some guy's heart today.
This guy.
This is Kansai-trader
Where was he killed?
How you know about him?
Well.. I haven't seen him
You're lying, you just told me kansai trader
I forgot to tell you
you just told me
That's strange
Oh you told me
me?
You showed this and told Fukushima trader's guy
He was killed
I feel sorry
He was floating in the Kizugawa River.
You killed him and throw away?
Stupid, I don't have the pistol
The person who shot was died
What?
The person was taken away with a woman in the ambulance earlier.
boss
What do you think was the cause of death of Sales Section Chief Arima?
shot dead
That's bad
And we don't even know who did it.
I came to thank you for that.
I don't know if I've ever taken care of you before.
I don't know.
Isn't the president of the company relieved by the Chief's death?
If Chief took those documents to another company, it would turn Kansai Boeki Ltd. upside down.
Mr. Arima was in charge of exporting our new product, Leon, wasn't he?
He planned to dump the product in order to boost exports... at the behest of the president.
On the surface, the company obtained an export certificate from MITI under the guise of exporting at a fair price.
Receive remittances from foreign buyers at the correct amount.
Then?
Sneak in a rebate for the lower price.
Foreign currency is obtained in Hong Kong
Paying yen as money to buy foreign currency
That's a violation of the Foreign Exchange Control Law
What happens if the police and the industry find out?
What will happen to Kansai Boeki's position?
Do you have any proof of extortion?
Kobe, Hong Kong. Here's the contract: COPY
Signed by the president.
Company seal
The murdered ARIMA was taken while he was with a woman.
woman?
Yeah, except for his wife.
So you erased Arima for me?
I want the share.
50/100,000 dollar
That's a small price to pay for this.
What if I turn down?
You're not like Arima.
HENMI, the man you counted on, is dead.
Let me help you with your grief.
You're the one who killed HENMI.
What are you talking about?
You kill one, you get more SHARE.
Don't say bullshit
Oh, come on, I didn't kill Henmi.
I was investigated by the police, and I have an alibi.
And now he's been released with an alibi.
It's not true.
You killed HENMI because you wanted SHARE.
Go to the police and ask them.
If you don't have HENMI, you might as well be my bitch for the rest of your life.
You have a nice figure
You used my pistol and kill him
You made my pistol dirty
I didn't use it.
Henmi used it
you have something to do with it too
my pistol is upset
When did you get out of the police station?
I took your dad's funeral out with the neighbors.
Funeral money was paid with the disposal of household goods and the power of the apartment
There's nowhere for you to go now.
Hold on
You gave me the pistol that killed someone
It's like a father who's daughter is defiled before her wedding.
I don't have anything to do with you anymore
Henmi was killed on the orders of her boss.
Boss is Inatori?
No
I don't know what he's like.
I like most women.
but I don't like women who made my pistol dirty
I will apology to you for Henmi
You are like his wife
Please pay back for him
Kawakatsu did it for money
do you want to be my wife?
I love you but I can't
Use this and kill him
Henmi used this and Henmi  was killed
Because of this, I am suspected by the police.
I owe this PISTOL a debt of gratitude.
See you later.
Come in
I didn't kill Henmi
you don't have to hide it
you are very reliable
How many times have I told you?
I play pistol, but I don't kill.
I threw everything at you!
You said you'd take out 16 groups.
I'll take care of you, body and soul.
Do you know that the BOSS is above Kawakatsu and Inatori?
Boss?
You're kidding me.
You're trying to scare me.
I'm serious
They all clearly said BOSS.
Oh, my God, you're going to help me.?
Don't worry
I will protect you.
You threw everything at me
He ran away
I'm surprised you're still alive.
I'm good at defending too
Protect or be attacked, Kurokane no
Looks like the Grim Reaper has finally latched on to you.
That's what it looks like.
the guy who hit it from behind.
I've seen him before.
In the bathroom at the SHIRAHAMA
He'll go after you in the bathroom.
He's looking for you.
But you know what?
I never once take my eyes off your skin... or your PISTOL.
Oh here's police
The bathroom is always a special sight
You inquired at the inn where you and the woman were staying.
The man who apparently targeted you was staying in the annex.He calls himself Yasuo Takagi, the broker.
That must be fake name
You think the guy is Inatori?
Can you see that picture of Inatori?
We have his fingerprints, but not a single picture of his face.
he is very cautious
The only one in the police force who knew about it, Detective Miyamoto, was shot and killed.
That's bad
He is very intelligent so it is very difficult to control him.
You know what he looks like?
Yes
so why don't you cooperate?
You came to me, so cooperating us
I'm Kimura from Division1
Come to here
Hold om
I don't wanna see any polices, I'm leaving
I treated a meal last day
It was just Udon soup
Kamoi
As a matter of fact, I have chest Disease
I kept it hidden within the police force until I took on Miyamoto's enemies.
I'll die soon
I wanna work for Miyamoto
You look sick
I see
I have no choice but help you
Please
OK I'll help you
Take care
Thanks
I'm willing to help you
It's Montage
The forehead, the eyes, the nose, the mouth.
The hair, the eyes, the nose, the mouth.
I want you to pick out the one that looks like him.
I don't know.
You're like a schoolteacher.
Oh yeah
Yeah, like the hair.
The eyes are like this one.
Sharp like that.
Is it similar?
I don't think so.
That's funny.
The kids will love it.
Be serious
I am
The lips are so different.
It's more like sharp
eyes are like a woman's,  like a melt-in-your-mouth slit
Oh He’s me
It's a familiar face
It's me.
I've been looking in the mirror since I was born.
I was dancing in my hotel room when he came after me.
This is funny from me.
Can you be serious for a second?
Yeah
I'm serious now
Not like him
He should have worn more austere glasses.
Yes he is
I wouldn't say it's conclusive.
It's almost exactly like this.
What do you think?
he looks like Mr. Inatori.
Oh dear, why she's here?
She wants to revenge for Henmi
Why don't you arrest Kawakatsu?
He has Alibi
She was a runaway from home and was picked up by HENMI.
He was picked up by HENMI and worked as a liaison for 16 groups while doing business at a bar.
I see.
Let's go home
You go home alone
She has something to do here
Why? I thought you match making with us
You are always being playboy
I'm sometime serous for women
Police
You'll die soon, so you should listen to me sometime
My sick...
It's lie
Sorry
What?
thanks for your help.
Cut it out
If you get out of line, I'll arrest you.
I've got the arrest file.
I'm gonna get you some sort of a rap sheet.
That's not funny.
See you then
You're in danger if you work with him.
What's the hell?
You guys must be 16 group
Stay down
You pretend to be police
Get in the car
How did you know I was at Police?
You cheated me
What did you talk to police?
I don't give a shit about you.
About me,right?
Wait
There's no benefit for you if you kill me
You're not going to get any more money.
Don't say bullshit
I know Mayumi ask you to kill me
I hate to kill people even if my lover ask me
Don't say bullshit
We heard Mayumi went to police so we were waiting for her then you came out
You are stupid, Me and her has nothing to do
Put your pistol down
Not bullet, Put your pistol down
Hold on
I'm good at dumping women, not so good at dumping pistols.
Anyway please take care of my pistol
Thanks
Stay down! I will shoot him
Don't come, It's danger
Hey why did you come?
Bros
Who killed him?
Kamoi
Did you kill him?
What?
Don't say bullshit
I don't lie like you.
I'm arresting you for illegal possession of a firearm.
Stupid, Look after Mayumi
mayumi?
she has injured her leg
Wait
Leave it
Help me
Ms. Shibata
Your visit
I looked for you
You're too noisy
Don't say bullshit
How did you know she was here?
The bar is closed.
I went back to my apartment
Neighbors were asking the police to protect her.
They informed me that she was in the hospital here.
I see
I've been on the run from the police.
I also lived in different places.
Did you do something bad?
No
nasty guy is chasing me.
You know what.
I'm here to tell you that I didn't kill Kawakatsu
Trust me
You can't?
I don't fire bullets that kill people s
I can't avenge your enemies.
Kawakatsu got what he deserved.
That's all
Who's the boss?
Forget it
I'm glad you're doing well.
See you
Hold on
You know what?if I've been hanging around here, that police come here
I don't like this police hospital.
I want to talk to Kamoi alone.
Hey
She wants to talk to me
Get out of my way, old man.
I don't give a shit.
If you get in the way of someone, the horse will kick your ass.
I don't care if I get kicked off.
This is a hospital. I can stay here.
Get out of my way, old man.
I love hearing you talk about this.
I think it's a good story.
He's useless never mind
Tell me
What is this?
A note on a phone call from the boss.
I don't know how he knows I'm here
This is a trouble
You called the police?
He said no to tell them
So Inatori and this gang leader are the only ones alive now.
I don't even know what he looks like.
I don't know when he will come here
Call me as soon as you get out of the hospital.
you will be killed like Henmi and Kawakatsu
That's why I'm scared.
where does he always call from?
do you doubt me?
i have nothing to do with it
She can't help but think that you are related to them.
You see a man, you think he's a thief.
I see
Count on me
Hold on
Where you going?
To USA
just in the neighborhood.
You are strange
I'm gonna need to inspect your attire.
Go ahead
I threw away the PISTOL.
Sorry, I paid you back
Pistol is here
See you
hey
Look after Mayumi,
Your salary goes down
How are you, bros?
I forgot your name
what?
Today I have more business to do with chickens than with eggs.
Hold on
What did he say?
Today he has more business to do with chickens than with eggs.Wanna stay with us?
He must be Kamoi
Chicken and duck are sukiyaki dishes
You are reserved?
I'm here to see a guest named Inatori.
I'm afraid he's not staying with us.
Guest 236 room
He's on a yacht on the beach, sir.
It's connected to the pier behind the hotel.
It's easy to find?
The My name is Red Wing
Okay
Don't threaten me like that.
I'm not threatening you.
I mean it
Get your hands off of me!
I'd rather call you Yoko but not boss
I owe you for your plan.
I'm the one who set you up as the boss in the first place.
Ostensibly as a moneylender so I could get information about the company.
You've taken all the money your friends have accumulated.
You were going to cut us off.
You gave Kamoi a lot of information.
You tried to kill me
It's for your own protection.
If I don't do it, you do it.
I hired him because I was afraid you'd erase me.
I'm not as stupid as you think
I'm the one who killed Henmi and Kawakatsu
Next is you but I won't kill you
Give me 50% of the share and your body
No matter how much you don't like it, I always get what I'm after.
I'll give you money
I don't want belong to you
You've changed your tune.
Kamoi changed you?
If it's money, I'll give you all of it.
Get out of here.
Mayumi will come here
Mayumi?
I used your name to call her
As soon as we get rid of her, all the evidence will be gone.
Get big money then fly to Hongkong
I'll make your trip a pleasant one
This is how it was supposed to work.
How did you know here?
From mayumi
you do a very difficult job.
I heard all your stories
if you really love me i will forgive you
I was scared.
I'm not going to play that hand.
It's time for us to battle
Ready?
throw the pistol into the sea
I was a little earlier
You look great
Don't move or shoot you
throw the pistol
I want you both dead.
I'll call the cops and tell them you shot each other
You better not be joking.
I'm going to shoot you.
Thanks for your help.
Come on
Go right
What's wrong?
Watch out
Stay strong
Damn it
Watch out
Why you don't shoot?
I'm gonna win this time.
I don't know about that
Ready?
It's just a scratch.
Hey Inatori!
You're under arrest.
Who are you?
We are from the Kitayama Police Department.
Detective Kimura called. We're here to help.
Did I hit police?
I’m sorry
I hit police.. I need to leave
Detective Sano, wait
Detective
Detective ?
Me?
Kimura said Thank you
That shobokure
He told you I'd be police?
That woman... she was wounded by one of their pistols.
Go patch her up.
They're only flesh wounds.
I'm not going to shoot a pistol that's going to kill somebody.
All are under arrest
Take care of the rest.
I feel good...
See you
You're fine
Thank you very much.
Henmi is glad too
I'll go back to my country and protect my father's bones.
Hold on
I'll go with you.
If you want to go, give me your pistol
Don't say bullshit
Then I'll arrest you
I don't have
Let's protect this bone in Osaka, just the two of us!
Tears of humanity
That wasn't the deal.
I'm sorry.
I've never been dumped before in my life.
She left you because she liked you.
It could be
What are you going to do?
you are underpaid.
i don't want to be in your care
I don't want to eat udon every day
Bros
I'm glad to see you
I came from Osaka to look for you guys.
I'm confident in my body.
i want to be a strip dancer
please introduce me somewhere
I'd happy to be with you
Hold on
I'll talk to you later.
See you in 4 yrs
Take care of her
See you
Don't leave from me!
Wait
See on your back
THE END