Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Okay.
Well, I'll be in touch later.
Is it okay if I call you at that late hour?
Thank you. Excuse me.
Thank you.
Did you catch the last bullet train?
Yes.
Have you decided on a place to stay?
No.
I just thought I'd walk around.
What are you talking about?
It's too cold.
You'll go to die.
I'll go to die?
Is this an old inn?
You don't like it?
There's only one in Yuzawa.
We left it just the way it was.
I like it.
I've decided on the top of the house, the third floor.
He's not back yet?
Call me when he back, 83201911.
Take your time.
Tell him to call me.
I'm Ukiko Kawamura.
Excuse me.
Hako Kirameku Hate / Beyond the Shining Sea (1986)
Visiting?
Is Tsuguro here?
My brother is out right now.
He's not here.
I wonder where I can find him.
I'm Kawamura...
Let's go.
I'm so sorry.
You are  his sister,right?
You can't just barge in here like that.
People are watching us, and workers are listening.
I'm embarrassed.
My brother is taking his friend to the slopes right now.
Please go home.
Which ski resort?
Joetsu Kokusai in Osawa.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Are you going to Osawa?
Yeah, just to take a look.
I told him about the phone call, but he said he didn't want to see you.
But he called the inn later.
It was something wrong.
Good-bye.
I'd like to call for a guest.
Mr. Imaizumi from Shiozawa.
If you are here, please come to the hotel lift.
Excuse me.
Yes.
You look so nice.
Your friends are coming.
He's coming, for sure.
Can I ask you a favor?
Are you drunk?
I feel good...
I need you to deliver this.
A letter?
To hotel?
To Shiozawa.
There's a house behind the Reverend Suzuki Memorial Museum called Imaizumi.
Yes there is.
Tsuguro at the house.
I know of him.
He's the second son who went to Tokyo.
He got into a prestigious firm, went to New York or something.
But he got fired because of his girl problems.
I quit the company because of this.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
You don't have to answer her.
Excuse me.
Hold on.
This is not a good way.
Pills?
What kind of pills? Sleeping pills or something?
What was she like?
She's in her white pajamas, drunk and feeling good.
She's asleep and waiting for you.
I took a few pills, so there's no rush.
May you be at my bedside when I wake up.
Ukiko.
A little bit of medicine... that mean she's going to kill herself.
I'm in trouble.
I'll call you.
tell me your number.
Don't do that.
If you call, you're gonna be a part of this.
Excuse me.
She's completely sleeping.
She won't wake up at all.
Police...
I'd better to call police.
Calm down.
Call a doctor first.
Call Dr.Fujimaki.
She might be kidding.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Don't make a fuss!
What's the hell?
She's so serious.
She's going to kill herself?
Don't go.
It's none of your business.
This is a matter of life and death.
Stay away from her.
Don't get involved with her and you won't even be here.
Should we pretend we don't know?
He does not know of her?
Shut up!
I'm thinking...
Are you Hirono?
Thanks for coming all the way out here.
Is Imaizumi here?
He's not here.
I remember she washed out her stomach and took out everything she drank.
The doctor said she would be cured after another day and night of sleep.
I don't wanna see her.
I came here to be responsible for her face if she die.
Don't say that.
You said you broke up, but you were married with her at one time.
I'm in a very difficult position.
Don't look at me.
Her mother's coming.
I called her before I left Tokyo.
She's coming from Tsushima.
It's too far.
She can fly in and take the Shinkansen from Ueno and she will arrive before the evening from now on.
Where is the Nishijin ryokan located?
It's at the west exit.
Behind the station.
Thank you very much.
Give me this.
Toru.
She's alive.
She's sleeping peacefully.
I see.
Snow country is warmer than I thought.
She's alive.
Excuse me.
Imaizumi was not here.
Tell her when she wake up.
These are delicious!
Glutinous rice is the real thing, you want some?
Can I sleep a little longer?
Go ahead.
Get well soon.
Mom.
You are a pathetic woman.
It's really stupid to be with a young man like that.
In the end, he didn't come and just delivered the money to his sister here.
He delivered just 100,000 yen.
You are already 30 years old.
You were dumped by your husband and went out with a younger man.
I'm so frustrated.
Your life is trash.
You'd be better off just dying like this.
No way.
I didn't mean that.
You can't what?
Let's go back to the island together and live
I still have a headache.
Living on a small island might not be so bad.
You're not child anymore.
Your brother is waiting at the restaurant.
Mom, I'm going for a walk.
I'm trying to figure out how to say hello.
Hello.
Shota.
How did you know it was here?
I heard you're in a high place.
Thank you very much.
You've grown up.
I saw you two years ago.
How long are you going to be here?
You'll have to stay with Grandpa's family.
I don't remember such a big broadcast.
This is music at 6pm, and it's different music in the morning and at night.
What song is the morning one?
Well.
Tell me.
The song like this.
Are you still there?
That was supposed to be the 4:00 ferry.
Our father left with that intention, too.
Can you visit me?
I've got some more work to do.
I need to go?
I get it.
Sorry I'm late.
Shota said he went to Grandpa's first.
Auntie, it's been a while.
Last time you came, you were with your husband.
Is he fine?
Yes.
Take your time.
I'm sorry to inform you that I've caused something stupid and I'm going to be taken care of by you.
Please accept my best regards.
I've just seen the sunset sea here.
Bros.
Ok.
If your voice sounded muffled, clingy, or pathetic...
I would not have let you in the house.
Well, thank you.
I'm relieved.
You look nice.
Let's live together.
If he wasn't good, we were going to kick you out.
You saved my life.
If you'd gotten rid of me, I'd have jumped into the ocean this time.
What's the hell?
You haven't changed since you were in college.
Anyway have a meal.
Eat fish, breathe in the sea air, and your blood and body fluids are replaced with pure water.
It tastes good?
When you're alive, the first thing that comes to your mind is how good food tastes.
That's happiness.
Then what will be the next happiness?
That's what Ukiko came to find out.
The word “rough” is written “rough” in the kinetic word “rough
Is this fish really that scary?
This fish doesn't move all day.
I feel sorry for him.
I'll bring this tank when an important guest comes.
I am taking care of this fish.
You gonna eat this fish?
Hiroko.
Why didn't you call me before you came?
What's the hell?
But that is how you are.
You are very stubborn.
Bros.
Her personality is completely different from Ukiko's.
Dad, you're comparing me to Uki.
Now that you compared me to Hiroko, I'm a zero.
I'm less than zero.
Oh no.
This was my room before I was married.
I thought the bed would be better, so I cleaned it up.
I'm sorry... to thank you for everything.
Thank you very much.
Since my father collapsed, you've been taking care of him, and you've been a big help for me.
I understand you've been through a lot.
It must have been hard for you.
I know how you feel.
Good evening.
I've come to pick you up.
Oh, Mr. Atsumi?
Please, come in.
It will be a long journey.
We have prepared a meal for you.
Come in.
Hiroko.
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble.
Did you really not want to see her face?
I know.
Since you didn't have any work, you worked overtime and then killed time at a coffee shop.
I didn't know how to greet.
You were good just the way you were.
I can't.
What happened to that bright, innocent person she used to be?
Do you remember?
We used to go to the beach in the summer with her and her husband.
Tsukue Island?
We went on a boat.
There were only us.
It's been a little while since Shota was born... seven years ago, I think.
We were returning to the pier after a day of play.
Ukiko suddenly said she had to pee.
Oh yeah.
I pulled her hand and told her to go to the grass.
She walked right into the water right in front of us.
She sat down.
She was so close, I could hear the sound of pee.
She seemed to be embarrassed.
She laughed about how great it was to pee in the ocean.
I was so envious of Uki back then, she was so carefree.
She said it was thrilling, like having her ass licked by a whisper.
May I have some?
Our dad are too glad.
I kind of worry.
He'll show you how he can change Uki by himself.
No matter what you do, human nature will never change
We can't do this.
Uki has just arrived.
Stop it....
Where are you going?
To the fish market.
I heard that fish from all the fishing ports gather here at the market.
Don't go there.
It's not a place for people like you to hang around.
What do you mean?
As long as you live here, there are certain things you must refrain from.
By “refrain” do you mean forbid?
Yes,that's it.
Do not walk the streets in your house clothes.
No loitering around aimlessly.
Do not behave in a conspicuous manner
Is that all?
And one more.
Do not contact past acquaintances by phone, letter, etc.
You have to keep up with them at least.
Are you saying that you are doing this like a fish?
I won't ask how it happened.
It's not a good idea for a person who is a homemaker to fornicate with another man.
You have extra time to waste, you do it.
OK.
You, however, end up having secret times, secret actions.
And the result of that is that you end up in trouble with a young man.
Something like that.
That's what I think.
I get it.
I'm sure that's all that matters to you.
The coldness of your hands
Excuse me.
Uncle.
I've found my purpose, albeit a small one.
May I come into town?
I don't understand a word you're saying.
I'm going to buy some inconspicuous everyday clothes.
That's good.
I also found some of Hiroko's old oil painting tools.
So I want to buy some paints and brushes.
Do you do oil paintings?
I have no idea.
Maybe I'll paint my uncle's face one of these days.
I'm going to go now.
Hold on.
I'm off to the weekly Saturday town council meeting in half an hour.
Come with me.
There is not a single house or factory in this area.
Not a single yakuza out of a population of 41,000.
Really?
Not even a gang of yakuza?
They always fought them off at the water's edge and never let them take a step ashore.
It's as if you fought them.
I fought them.
After I work in Kyoto,
I worked at a youth office in Nagasaki Prefecture.
It was hard work.
Thanks for taking care of them.
Welcome.
That's what I thought.
You are here.
You work here?
I hear strange woman is watching our student.
You don't feel comfortable to live?
Well, we've made our peace with it.
He let me out for shopping or something.
I can show you around if you like.
By car.
For a change.
Are you sure you want to do that?
You worry about your uncle?
No.
You didn't say anything to me when I got there.
I think you were trying to avoid me.
That's because if I said anything...
I would've said something really strong.
What do you mean, “something strong”?
Where would you like to go? Anywhere you want to see.
Well.
I already know about the setting sun, so where the sun rises.
If that's not possible, I'd like to go to the cape to the east of you.
You miss the mainland already?
I don't think so.
Hello? This is Omi.
It's me.
Are you sure?
Yes I know.
Who was it?
My friend from Hakata is here.
I lied to my mother and came out.
It can't be helped. Your uncle is very strict.
How about you with Hiroko?
I didn't say anything.
I go straight away from school.
I wonder which way the sun rises?
That area is east.
Have you ever seen a sunrise?
No.
Hakata is that way.
Can we see Higashimatsuura Peninsula today?
Let's go further out.
Watch out.
Don't worry.
You scared me.
Why?
You thought I'd jump in?
No.
Is this screen cliff?
Sakyobana.
Oh, why? That cliff looks like a folding screen.
You see, it's a black folding screen.
But it's not.
Oh, it's beautiful.
The only time I get to do this is on Saturday afternoons when my uncle's not around.
Here it is.
screen cliff
Where?
That white cliff.
I'm pretty sure it's because it's crumbling in the middle.
Are you sure?
It's kind of disappointing, isn't it?
But what's interesting is that the fossil from there is apparently a freshwater fish.
right in the middle of the ocean?
Yeah.
An American paleontologist discovered it in Taisho,
He named the fish Ikius nipponicus after a living creature.
Ikius nipponicus?
It's like being a Japanese living on a living island, just like Atsumi.
People try to avoid me.
No, they don't.
I'm not like that.
I'm a teacher.
My father is a teacher too.
My wife's father is a teacher too.
On this island, retired teachers...
They all buy boats and go fishing every day while living off their benefits.
That's where I'm headed
To someone like that, you seem like you're from another world.
You do what you want, when you want, wherever you want.
I don't know how to put it.
You always make me feel like I'm in a good mood.
And I betrayed it myself?
Yes you did.
You have betrayed us in a way that cannot be undone.
That's all.
I said, in my strangely logical, teacherly way.
You haven't changed.
You think so?
I'm glad I came with you today.
Thank you.
I feel like I have an ally for the first time.
Ally?
What would you do for me?
What do you want from me?
Would you do anything for me?
Not anything.
I'm kidding.
I don't need you to do anything.
I just need to know that there's someone out there for me.
That's all I need.
I wish I could do something for you.
It's okay.
If I can't help it, I'll become someone else's mistress.
No.
You should be more firm.
You look like a schoolteacher.
I'm a teacher.
Now too?
Yes I am.
Which part of you is a teacher?
Stand up straight.
It's important to restart your life.
Stay strong and live on such a small island.
People on the island think you are strange.
Uki.
Where will you go?
We'll go to shopping.
Atsumi told us to go there.
Good for you.
Let's go together.
Shota.
We're going..
Their families were good friends.
Where have you been?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Fish?
I went with a young guy named Arai.
He's new here, and he likes to fish.
Nice turnip fish.
it's not rare.
Please give it to our neighbors
What a waste!
I'll take it to my uncle's house.
I told you it's not rare.
I think I gave Uki some turnip miso soup when I was there
I'm tried.
I'll go by scooter.
I haven't seen their faces lately.
I'm off.
Good evening.
Fish delivery.
They're heavy.
They are for you.
Thanks.
How are you?
I'm fine.
This is nice fish.
Atsumi went to sea.
Let's cook miso soup.
I'll cook for you.
In the past, when a child was born, everyone drank this miso soup.
In other words, it's a fish for women.
Where's dad?
He went to Saturday Council Meeting.
He'll be back soon.
Where's Atsumi?
He went to the sea and is tired and drinking alcohol.
My mistake.
Did I make you feel bad?
I'm sorry.
I feel bad.
Dad.
You're here.
Don't bully her.
She's not fine.
What?
At first I taught her the rules, but recently she's started to recover.
She's not complaining about anything.
She seems to be a sick person.
She seems to be a sick person?
I worry.
Ukiko?
Yes.
Stay like that.
I made a milk tea for you.
You didn't even eat dinner so I was worried.
Thanks.
How are you feeling?
I got better after I went to bed.
Do you see anyone?
No.
That is not pure-hearted
What do you mean?
I'm just worried about you.
I thought you were pregnant.
What?
That's a natural thing when a man and a woman are together.
Of course, I have no idea who that man is.
Just in case.
I'm glad you're not like that.
Have a drink.
Watch out.
Let me go to Hakata once.
I feel like I'm suffocating in here.
Ok Go ahead.
Kawamura.
Shiomi.
You looked a little different. I thought I had mistaken you for someone else.
Are you still in the Steel Department?
I am currently working as a secretary.
I thought you were in Tokyo, but you're here?
I've been through a lot, but now I'm on the island of Iki.
the island of Iki?
Really?
Four?
Four what?
Fork fingers.
I wonder if it's the same all over the world.
You have a five-fingered fork?
I stare at it and the tip looks like a human fingernail.
I'm gonna stab something with it.
I'll scratch you with a fork
Don't do that.
Ok I won't.
I'll be gentle like this.
I've never felt this way before.
You've never felt this way before?
You just said it.
What's the first time?
Do I have to tell you?
I want you to tell me.
I'm thinking of Hiroko.
I don't care.
You and Hiroko are cousins.
I don't want to compare them, but I do.
That's enough.
How did you tell Hiroko?
I told her I was going home for a drink after the workshop because some of my college buddies were with me.
I can't stay here. I'm frustrated.
Don't miss the last ferry.
I don't wanna go home.
Mom.
I'm not a child.
But your uncle asked me to come here.
Today is Shota's 7th birthday.
Let's celebrate and give thanks to God.
Congratulations.
Let's get started.
Come to think of it, Sho is the only one who doesn't have the Omi family bloodline.
I feel sorry for you.
If Ukiko had three children, there would be no problem.
Uncle.
I'm talking about after you get married.
Just in case,right?
He is looking for you to marry into the family.
Seriously.
That's good.
Uncle, is that really true?
You don't like it?
I've been very reluctant to do so for the past year or two.
You.
Mom, you're wearing a ring today.
It's a wedding ring.
It's Shota's birthday.
Your father and mother got married and Shota was born.
So I'm wearing it.
I'll drink a lot tonight.
You are already drunk.
What's wrong?
It's about your remarriage.
That noisy father said he'd take care of you.
A woman like me can't just get married.
You were and still are a good woman
Too good to be true.
I'll help you clean up.
Serve tea for Atsumi and mom.
This tea ok?
Serve caffeine-free hot tea for Atsumi.
He can't sleep at night when he drinks tea.
When a man can't sleep, he wants to have sex.
Sleeping pills weren't enough for him.
My body is made to have sleeping pills.
You know what I mean.
Take care.
You're drunk.
Is it true you drink strong tea and can't sleep at night?
what are you talking about?
If you can't sleep, don't have sex with Hiroko.
She said that?
What's wrong?
Don't have sex with Hiroko tonight.
Good night.
Did you talk to UKI-chan today?
Not really.
You were so excited after seeing her before.
I get it.
What are you doing?
I'm trying this because I think this abalone will still be alive if I remove it from its shell.
It's impossible.
I don't think the shells have anything to do with this life.
I think I can do that if I take it slow.
see what's happened.
Oh.
I get it.
The only reason he died was because of the pain he was stripped of.
The slow, slow, slow way the pain multiplied.
If I strip him down all at once, maybe he'll live longer than I thought.
Look.
If you strip him down all at once, maybe he'll live longer?
She said like that.
Then she'd start over with another abalone.
Stop it.
I feel scary.
Why are you telling me this?
It's been on my mind.
I'm leaving today.
Drop me at Katsumoto.
I'll take the bus home.
I'm glad you back home.
What's going on the fish?
We asked people to take out this fish.
Why?
Hirono will visit us.
Why is he coming?
Where have you been?
I've been waiting for you.
Why is Hirono coming?
I asked him to come here.
Is that bad?
I hate you.
I don't care.
No matter how you hate me, Hirono is coming.
Then it's okay if I don't see him.
What?
Hirono-kun said he wanted to see you.
I think he miss you.
He really said that?
I think it means he wants to see you.
I feel sorry about the fish.
Uncle.
Don't ask me.
I'm busy.
I'll meet him.
I'll see him... pleasantly.
Hi, sorry if I bother you.
How long will you stay?
I only have 3 hours.
You'll have only 2 hours.
You have to drive to airport.
You look fine.
Are you going on a business trip to Hakata?
So Shiomi from the secretarial section over here told me about you yesterday.
Sorry if I bother you.
I thought you'd been forgotten.
He's here.
Come in.
Uncle.
You don't have time.
You don't need to greet me.
Excuse me.
Where shall we start?
We had an appointment over the phone.
It's an old story, so I'll tell you.
Please.
Ukiko is keeping her mouth shut.
And her mother is clueless.
Well, let me tell you in a nutshell.
It was my direct subordinate who got into a strange relationship with Ukiko.
That Echigo guy?
I let him come in and out of my house freely, and we have a meal together.
He was the kind of guy who would sometimes do Ukiko's chores for her.
With him..
I understand that your dog bit you on the hand.
You're right.
As a company man, it's not a good position to be in if my subordinate cuckolded my wife.
I understand about your position.
In exchange, I'll give you my wife, but you have to quit your job.
The man quit his job, went back to the country, and Ukiko and I got divorced.
I’m sorry.
I get it.
And you know the rest.
Get out.
The man didn't have the guts to take Ukiko on.
He was involved in that incident in Yuzawa.
I get it.
Hiroko, it's been a while.
Stay here.
We can eat all of this fish.
Enjoy this fish.
I kind of feel like I'm surrounded by all your relatives when I do this.
Hirono will be living abroad by the end of this year
He's looking for a wife.
Uncle.
We don't have to talk about it.
Please get Uki off this island.
It's for Uki's own good.
Please.
I have very mixed feelings about this.
I'm in trouble.
We've got a little time.
Half an hour.
Would you like him to take you around to some of the more scenic spots?
I'd like to talk.
Can you pick a place for us to go?
Driver, go to Bamboo Street, please.
Thank you so much for hanging out with me today.
Thanks for coming.
My uncle force you to come here.
I'll be brief because we don't have time.
He was right about me being stationed overseas and about wanting to get married.
What do you think?
It's so sudden.
Just tell me what you feel.
If you were to choose me, I'd say it's too good for me.
I'll ask you straight out... are you seeing a guy right now?
Why do you say that?
Hiroko looked me straight in the eye and told me to get you off this island.
I knew intuitively that something was up
Tell me.
I don't want to make a mistake, and neither do you
I see a guy.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Even if you have a boyfriend, you should say you don't.
I can tell other people, but I don't want to lie to Toru-san.
You are stupid.
You embarrassed me with your honest confession about Imaizumi before.
And now you'll do it again.
It's hard for me, too.
I can't believe it.
You might think you're a sinful woman.
I hate these words after all.
Your body wants men.
You're early.
Didn't you take him to the airport?
I thought you were going to follow him to Hakata.
We talked, and then we left.
You left?
Will you two never meet again?
No.
What's the reason?
He liked you, but why did that happen?
I can't tell you.
You broke up with him for some reason.
Did you selfishly refuse it?
I think you might be right.
Let me go.
Do as you please
You are stupid.
Why you didn't stop.
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
Which hospital is it? Where is she?
She's at Futsukaichi Central Hospital.
She's going to be okay.
Dad says I should wait here until she calls.
Where's Atsumi?
He took the first flight.
What's the hell?
I am Hiroko's father.
Why didn't she call me?
Calm down.
I'm going.
You stay with Ukiko here.
I'm going too.
Shut up!
If you receive a phone call, respond promptly.
Why?
Why did you go to Futsukaichi station?
I was going to kuno-san's house in Takamiya, but I was dawdling and suddenly my foot slipped.
What's wrong?
It was pulled by a rubber band or something and slowly settled down.
What's the hell?
I have no idea.
Why did it happened?
Where are you going?
Hold on.
No one really knows what happened.
She had an accident and is feeling very bad for us.
By any chance,Hiroko..
She's not like you.
Your divorce from Hirono was a huge shock to her.
She came out despite her bad leg.
Please understand her.
You'll be fine.
Thank you for taking time off work to look after me.
Stay strong.
We all support you.
I'll be back.
Uki.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry you had to come all the way out here.
You want some fruit?
I don't need it now.
I'd rather talk.
Have a seat.
No, don't be quiet, okay?
Do you remember?
The summer of my sophomore year in high school, when Uki came to Iki by herself.
I wonder what happened.
You got an appendectomy and were admitted to Akagi Hospital.
Hiroko accompanied me.
We chatted till midnight.
The young teacher got angry.
I forgot.
Yeah.
I remember everything about Uki.
Stay over tonight.
Stay with me.
Yuki-chan,still awake?
Does it hurt?
If it hurts, I'll get you some medicine.
Don't worry.
I like the darkness.
I'll get you some medicine.
Don't worry.
It's more about Yuzawa.
Tell me about Echigo-Yuzawa.
Why now?
Let's not do that.
We'll only make us feel worse.
Don't worry.
Tell me about Echigo-Yuzawa.
Oh my god.
I wasn't that serious.
I didn't really think about dying.
But I wanted him to respond to my feelings a little.
I was being frivolous.
You were not.
I feel sorry for you.
Hiroko!
Don't look at me.
Nurse!
Call doctor!
Atsumi?
It's me.
Hiroko just fell off the bed.
What do you mean?
She kind of rolled over like she did it on purpose.
The doctor says it's nothing.
I'll be right there.
Come here soon.
Don't come near her anymore.
Leave her alone.
There's nothing more to do for Hiroko.
Ok?
Yes.
Get the ferry?
Later is fine.
I heard you turned down Hirono-san.
You don't have to worry about that.
I know.
My uncle hasn't spoken to me since then.
Nobody is on my side anymore.
Can you be patient with me for a little while longer?
I have a lot of important things on my mind right now.
But I don't want to cause Hiroko any more pain.
There's also Shota.
Can't you wait a little longer?
I have to go.
I can't run away.
Are you going out?
Of course.
You dragged Hiroko off the bed.
Mother.
That's why Hiroko has to stay in the hospital for two more weeks.
Your uncle talks bad about you.
I should've left you at Echigo-Yuzawa.
This is a truly slanderous letter.
Thank you for letting me know.
This is really bad.
This is full of malice.
You don't need to worry about this letter.
But you always get this kind of letters.
I couldn't just ignore it, could I?
I'm so embarrassed.
What can I do for you?
Nothing.
You can leave now.
Don't worry.
I have permission from the school.
Shota... I've been asked to keep him at uncle's house.
It's easier for me too.
I don't want you to worry about me.
I'm sure everything will be fine now.
I feel sorry.
You feel sorry?
I don't want you to say that.
Hiroko?
If you're going to talk like that.
I don't want you here.
I don't want you to stay.
Come in.
I apologize for any inconvenience caused.
Have a seat.
I have something to talk to you about.
How's your wife?
Her shoulder's better now.
The cast is still in place.
She just twisted her neck a little bit, so she's got tingling in her arms and legs.
How about her face?
She got a little cut above her eye, but she'll be fine.
Will it leave a scar?
I think she'll be fine.
I'm worried about your wife.
By the way, did you just build a house over here?
Yes.
Then I guess it's hard for you to transfer.
Is that what you're telling me now?
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I've talked it over with Take.
My father?
I got this letter.
This.
It's a small island here.
There's nothing more interesting than rumors about a man and a woman.
You want to read it?
No thanks.
Your wife and Take's niece had an argument in Sakyobana.
I heard your wife was almost pushed off a cliff.
I don't think that's true.
Do you think this letter speaks for your wife?
I'm off.
Thank you for the food.
Sit there.
Hiroko will be released from the hospital soon.
I'm going to take care of her and Shota.
Even with you here, I think this is a big house.
But I think it would be difficult for you and her to live together.
Hiroko is suffering and so are you.
I don't tell the reason
I think you understand that very well.
Please apologize to him.
You brought this all on yourself.
Shut up!
I'm not emotional.
It's up to you.
Think about it, please.
I'm leaving today.
No, I don't mean today or tomorrow.
Think about it, please.
But I'm leaving today.
You can have her back anytime.
I don't have anywhere to go, but I'll be fine.
But my mother doesn't mind if she stay here, does she?
That's a given.
You don't need to worry about her.
It's not worth it for you to say that.
If I fail, I'll come back somehow.
But your heart is so polluted that I don't think you'll ever be able to recover.
Are you really leaving out today?
Because we made a promise.
It's starting to rain.
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
I'm not alright.
I feel pain.
I want you to be happy more than anyone else.
She is not good at greeting.
I will greet you on her behalf.
Thank you for all your help.
Tomoe.
Do you want to go with her?
Tell me.
To be honest, it's 50-50.
If Hiroko comes back, I won't be needed in this house.
So.
Stop it....
And if you go with them, you will perish, too.
Only she can go to hell.
Bros.
My heart is gone too.
People who are related to me thought I could change.
But I couldn't do that.
I am a really terrible teacher.
I feel bad.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I left the house.
Come in.
I just brought some personal stuff with me for now.
You have nothing.
I left it at the inn.
Inn?
I'm evil.
For you and Hiroko.
I mess up with your life.
So what?
I knew this would happen.
Hiroko called the school.
She said she wouldn't be back here for a while after she got out of the hospital.
It's time for me to do something.
Something I could do.
I need to make a decision about Hiroko, about Shota, and about my teaching career here.
Are you quitting?
I don't know if I can transfer when I move next.
If I go to Hakata, I think I'll do some cramming.
But I need time.
You can live alone in Hakata until then.
I'm going to get kicked out of here one way or another.
You doubt me?
I let my guard down.
What do you mean?
I thought I'd made it this far, that I could meditate the rest of the way and still make it to the end of my life.
I thought I'd hit something this hard.
Atsumi,Please turn back.
I know how far I can go on my own.
What are you talking about?
Why don't you just leave me alone and do that?
You can go back to being you.
To tell you the truth, I'm still scared.
I'm up to you...
Hi.
Can you take me to Byobu...Well..Sakyobana.
Now?
I'm sorry.
I want to see the sunrise.
That's the farthest east.
No problem.
Watch your step.
There's a precipice below.
I know.