Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hayauchi Inu / Quick-Draw Dog (1967)
(Inu/Dog Series #8)
Ah, Kamoi-san
Please become the manager of havor Bar.
Tsune-yan
Look, holding a child like that,
We cannot make money.
Please become the manager of havor Bar.
You are very persistent.
Did you ask him to look after me?
Oh, teacher, just a moment, this child...
How about having a female singer for our production?
Production?
Yes, yes, the president Kamoi Daisuke,
what do you think about the name Kamonegi Pro? Is that okay?
Let's leave that here
Shall we go over there?
No, wait a minute
Actually
This child is one who is not blessed with a mother's love
Your approach is outdated.
Although her father became a businessman,
He had no time to settle down at home
My only sister disappeared without a trace, seeking the love of faith
This poor Emiko-chan continues to wander in the night world,
searching for her sister's shadow, grateful for the romance of spring and southern warmth
This is a sad spring story.
Hey, that's quite a nice tune. I could be your manager if you want
Really?
However, this is a story from the first year of the Showa era,
Come on.
I can barely manage on my own, let alone take care of others
You're cold,
I have no time.
I have to go.
Kamoi-san,
Wait.
President
Hey, hey, don't worry about it. I'll figure something out
Please meet her again.
I made a promise to her.
That's something you decided on your own.
I am a manager
I am a president.
Yeah.
But...
He's the arrogant guy I was talking about.
Who gave you permission to be our territory?
Your territory?
Ah, this is the Japanese archipelago
You're right?
Hey.
Don't pretend you don't know.
Shall we resolve this outside?
Hurry up!
I need to take good care of my tools of the trade.
I’m counting on you, Tsuneyan.
You should take good care of your body.
Why am I pushing myself too hard?
Well, let's go
Beat him.
Hey.
Wait.
That pose
I am a boxer.
You're going too far with that.
What's the hell?
Let's go
But.....
If we're going to do business with them, we should greet them.
I just did it.
but now I have to clean up, which
means I can't do our work
So that's the manager's job.
You acknowledge that I am the manager's role.
I tell you then.
You have a lot of motivation!Alright, I'll go with you.
So, the Tsutsugo group is said to have disbanded
Don't provoke weird guys and stop getting involved with the police.
especially since the opponent is Daisuke Kamoi, who crushed the Kansai-based Tenchi Gamou 16 group
That guy's skills are impressive
Open
Sorry for the issue
We're sorry.
We thought it would be a good idea to greet this manager.
That doesn't matter, does it?
Boss?
The group has been disbanded.
I am currently the president of a company.
Mr. Kamoi, have a seat
Hey.
You are very kind.
Could you possibly become our store's exclusive partner?
A contract for two stages a day will be quite advantageous
What do you think?
I want to say, but unfortunately, I will decline that offer.
Why?Why?Why?
why can't you step out for a moment?
I am his manager.....
There’s a boring violent incident from the past, and there’s a trial coming up soon
Well, going to prison is tough,
but you do pay taxes, right?
It's a bit of a hassle
In the meantime,
We want to use your skills.
Come on.
I have no intention of doing that.
Is it a silent pistol?
Take this with you for self-defense.
Unfortunately, I do not accept requests from other people.
See you.
She looks nice.
If you make a contract with here, you'll be able to get closer to her
Ah, no matter where I go, women come to me
It's only you.
Wow, it's been a while since I felt this way,
but I wonder if this is how it is with Kamoi-san.
The other party is about to go to the villa!
But...
What's wrong?
It's about our Goro-chan, you know
I was thinking that maybe something happened on him.
Oh really?
Men these days are very difficult.
so I'm waiting outside for a bit
Kamoi-san,
I move by shaking my body like this.
You are stupid.
The thief was in the house.
There's nothing in our house that could be stolen.
Yes,you are right.
Your wife is having an affair.
Male or female?
Your wife is worried and looking for you.
I just had a talk with her over there
I see... I'm sorry... My family is always complaining
The crackdown on unlicensed taxis is very strict.
I worked all day and still couldn't even cover my meal expenses,
and if I go home
empty-handed, I will be beaten again.
So, can you lend it to me, Kamoi-san?
Yeah, that wife is quite strong
Yeah.
I'll lend you some money.
Tsune.
What are you doing?
Don’t do that.
Leave it to me.
Thank you for always helping me.
You are stupid.
Becoming a manger is a good way to make money, isn't it?
we earn 30,000 yen a day, which amounts to 900,000 yen a month.
that's 10 million in a year
We can earn 108 million in 10 years.
If it was 100 years....
I am a street guitarist.
Singing is my enjoyment,
I know.
but do you really think I'd accept
money collected by the yakuza?
Don't say that's a waste, we are doing it for a good reason
It seems you don't have tonsils.
What are you doing?
Which side are you on?
I won't respond to such a pointless question
Who?
Good evening, has Kamoi-san already gone home? Please sing for me
I feel very lonely without hearing your wonderful singing voice
That creepy guy's back again.
This Sagita, you know,
This represents the common people,
and for the common people, you have to sing,
but I also want to struggle with you, my lord
Just having you around is a burden
please go away
You are very heartless.
Please leave
You're going to be so heartless.
I feel sad.
Am I supposed to take this?
This is a down payment.
The remaining 50,000 yen will be returned when you come back
I hope you can stay for a week
I feel like y luck has finally turned around
There aren't many customers for a round trip drive to Kansai
Ah, Osaka brings back memories
How much can you earn?
100,000
With this, I no longer have to worry about Tamako's  childbirth expenses
Tama-chan know?
I haven't told her at all yet
Why?
I thought I'd surprise her on the morning of departure
That's not good
It's bad for her health
That's not good for her baby.
Like this?
I was born with bad luck, so I caused my parents a lot of trouble.
I was born a month late.
What kind of people are your customers?
It's a secret.
Health insurance can't be used for childbirth, but with this much support,
it seems I can give birth with peace of mind
Make sure to give birth to a good child
I wonder if I can give birth to 2,3 at once
That's tough
but You know what?
If you want a handsome child, just imagine my face.
It's ridiculous, but my partner is my partner,
You say some good things
Oh my god.
Is everything going smoothly?
I can hear the sound of our baby.
The old man's name is Goro, so it's rumbling
My stomach is making noises because I'm hungry.
Well, leave the house to me
If Kamoi-san says that, it's like We are riding in a Rolls Royce, so please.
Women possess eternal beauty, while men have infinite energy;
the vitality of men and the charm of women are all gifts from heaven
By giving thanks to heaven and understanding
God's will, one can attain a beautiful and strong body
To achieve this, it is essential to abandon all ego and rely on God
It seems you're heading to Osaka
The trial will start in 10 days
I think I should be in prison for three years.
That's quite a burden, and by the way,
Chairman, while I'm away,
I leave everything to him, so please handle it accordingly
What do you mean by that?
We will entrust all accounting and business operations of the Seirei Group to Hara.
You will go to Kansai with me.
If you don't want to go to Kansai with me, that's fine, but in that case, you won't be able to get the Roadoll
Wait
It's better for you not to get any strange ideas
The Tenjin Spirit World was created by this god
I was the one who made it profitable
If you want to live, you should come to Kansai with me.
Ugh, 10 yen per song is already outdated
It's ok.
Let's become a high-class club.
High-class clubs are troublesome to deal with Tsutsugo group, so I can't say anything about it
Will we also do business with poor people?
Poor people....
What's this?
Huh? My Sister
She disappeared on my birthday.
Just before my sister ran away from home
Is she your sister?
Did you see my sister?
When? Where?
Come here for a second,
Hara-san
Please.
so will you accept the conditions from earlier?
From now on, you're mine
So?
What can I do for you?
Kamoi brought Miyamoto Yumi with him.
He apparently wants to meet her sister.
Emi?
Emi
Will you reveal that appearance in front of your sister?
I can't.
Don’t do that.
Please.
Where is my sister?
Sister?
Miyamoto Fumiko, her sister
I don't know her
Huh?I met her here the other day in this hallway
I think that's a mistake.
Was it a case of mistaken identity?
I refused because it wasn't a body you could show to my sister
That means I've gained one more thing to be thankful for
it's a special nocturnal reflective agent cancer
Come in
Did Goro contact you after that?
I received this letter from Osaka for a while .
He is looking forward to the birth of his child.
Oh, I heard he is already thinking about name.
It seems like that.
He'll be back tomorrow night?
Well, it's true, but there's 100,000 yen at Osaka Station, it's something that's been there until now
That's right.
Osaka brings back my memoirs.
A suspect in a robbery and murder case has been arrested.
The suspects are 26-year-old Yasuhiko Tanabe and 27-year-old Kunio Komatsu, who are both homeless
What's wrong?
It's not good to let your children hear bad news like this.
Thanks.
If your stomach starts to hurt, hit that wall over there. I'll come and help you.
Thank you very much.
It hurts me.
Do you understand?
Are you experiencing labor pains?
No, I've been practicing it all at once
Well then, good night.
Good night!
It hurts me.
Tanabe.
Where did you hide the gun that fired this bullet, Machine No 32?
It's not me, you know.
There's nothing to discuss
When will you share the 32 million yen you stole?
Where did you have an appointment to meet the main culprit, Kinzo Shirai?
I don't know that man.
Don't pretend you don't know.
He is the former boss of the Tsutsugo Group.
We know he is involved.
Shirai is in Osaka; there are witnesses
How about you just come clean and confess?
I was supposed to meet in Tokyo
Where in Tokyo?
I don't know
No?
You are stupid.
but Shirai-san mentioned it to contact him by phone
So, do you have any idea who might have reported that
you guys are hiding at the Tennoji inn?
It's not one of the assistants at the inn, is it?
No, it's a man's voice.
I can't believe it.
The car's license plate number you used?
It was  a Kanagawa number, 4565
Kanagawa number, Mi 4565
Was that right?
Get off.
Here it is.
Thanks, what was the cause of the accident?
It seems there was a two-dimensional bomb planted in the engine
It exploded while driving?
Yes, the hood was blown off about 50 meters to the rear
Come here
Look closely at the face.
Are you looking properly?
There's no mistake.
It was from Shirai-san
Is that so?
I'm sorry
By the way
what was Shirai-san's purpose for the trip to Kansai?
It was a sightseeing trip
The trial for the case while on bail was supposed to start, right?
The person has secured a prison sentence
I guess he wanted to enjoy life outside
However, he is involved in a series of robbery murders in Osaka
Kamoi-san! Wait a moment, President!
Kamoi-san!
If you keep making a fool of myself as a manager,
you won't be able to call yourself a proper singer,
I'm glad to say that
Anyway, I have no intention of doing something with her
Well then, you're at a loss
You don't know my feelings, do you?
She's better than Tsune.
This girl is properly taking lessons.
and until she finds her sister, she wants to continue playing street guitar and singing.
Anyway, I've gotten an advance payment from her for the contract
What? That's corruption, isn't it?
Why?
It's a black fog,right?
I can't see your face
what are you even saying?
I lend that money to Goroyan, and the other day, you took it all away
Would you use that money to erase that problem?
What the hell is this guy!
So, are you going to pay back the debt of Goroyan?
Please return it.
Hello again
Why has the stupid police from Osaka come back to Tokyo?
Kamoi
Are you living in this Shiratori inn?
Is it not okay for me to live here?
I didn't mean it that.
but hey, are you going to come to me?
Where is Goro Yamamoto's room?
He lives next door, but Did he do something wrong?
Goro was named as a suspect in the murder
He?
He killed Shirai Kinzo from Tsutsugo group
then Who did he took on a trip to Kansai....
You don't need to say anything careless.
Kanagawa Go mi 4565...
This is Goro's car.
Yamamoto is here?
Yes
Wait a minute
What?
You cannot meet her.
She is pregnant now.
Did Goro commit murder?
You have a loud voice again, don't you?
It can't be helped.
Play street guitar with him.
Thanks.
I can't play the guitar.
Go
I can't believe it
I can't believe he would commit murder.
I absolutely can't believe that
However, even if Yamamoto....
Don't raise your voice.
It would be bad if she listened to what we have to say.
However, he is currently a wanted fugitive.
She will probably hear the news on TV or in the newspaper.
That's bad.
Hey.
Do you do this recently?
What do you mean?
Don't pretend you don't know.
Pachinko?
So, the second place for Takato is number 16 and number 48
I recommend that.
Anyway
I will meet Masae Yamamoto.
Hold on.
Hey, aren't you also a human being?
It is not good to shock pregnant women.
Kamoi.
What?
Are you going to swear?
For what?
Are you going to take responsibility?
Keep an eye on Goro Yamamoto.
Will he come back here?
Yeah.
I get it.
But instead
Can you at least listen to my request while you're at it?
What?
It smells nice, doesn't it?
Do you make egg dishes?
This looks delicious!
Stop it.
I can't?
My husband is coming home.
A man?
Is this Mr. Goro Yamamoto's room?
Yes.
I received a request from your husband.
Apparently, his car broke down in Nagoya.
Was he in a car accident?
no, it seems to be just a simple malfunction
He mentioned he would return after the repairs
I came here to tell you that.
but I am Kimura, a driver from Marutsuru Transport
Is that so?
I'm surprised
Thank you very much for your kindness
Then.
Apparently, his car has broken down.
I heard he was driving so hard that the engine burned out.
It seems that way.
What's this?
My husband has collected these from various places.
Is that so?
What is Tenshin spirit meeting?
I don't really hear about this much
What are you talking about?
There are plenty of believers in this apartment too
Is that so?
But Why would Goro, who has such love for others, commit murder?....
Huh, did you say something?
I didn't say anything
Did you say something?
I didn't say anything,
You said.
I didn't say anything
A problem occurred.
I got caught, I got caught!
What's wrong?
I need you after all.
I was attacked by the Tsutsugo group.
I was beaten up by them here.
Where's Emi?
I'm on Oyaguku Street in 2-chome.
I get it.
Please stake out this spot in my place.
But....
I'm counting on you
You guys should have already talked about this the other day.
Hey, even though you say you don't know anything,
Are you going to keep being persistent?
I have no use for someone like you, a beggar from Osaka
If you want to call me a beggar,
I will deal with all of you.
Come on,
Give him some money and let him sing.
Take it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for giving me so many things.
I'll give you a special service today.
I'll let you sing for free today as a special service
The money is right here with me.
This is the real deal of a huge service
You're stupid brat.
Don't forget our faces.
(The missing driver is wanted by the police.)
Kamoi-san
Good evening.
There are articles about the incident in every newspaper.
I know
But do you really trust this?
How can you think of it like that?
I make a guess about it
I think the person who died in the car was Goro.
I see
It's similar to the Haneda incident.
You know, because of the explosion at Haneda's Benrido,
the Metropolitan Police Department is involved
The police were in a panic.
Think seriously about things
I'm serious, how about my guess?
Thank you so much for waiting for me.
I'm so glad.
Go way.
I get hives.
I really hate this
hehehe. Both of you should go here and get your bodies modified just right
Ugh, that's disgusting.
Tenshin spirit?
I've seen that somewhere....
This is something that's posted in Goro's room.
Oh dear
I gave that to him
I hate creepy things like this.
You don't want to live long anyway?
Good night
What a strange guy
The world is really wide isn't it,
Kamoi-san
Shall we proceed with the case of a scapegoat murder for Goro?
Yeah
Are you saying that the one who was killed was the driver Yamamoto and that culprit is Shirai Kinzo?
We have already taken measures against what you have in mind
But The charred body is very suspicious.
If it turns into black rice, it will smell bad.
Wow, this is so bad.
This is completely burnt to a crisp.
This is something well-cooked, but crematorium won't make a profit
We took statements from witnesses Hara and Miyamoto.
Thank you for your hard work
that woman? Miyamoto?
Do you know of her?
Miyamoto Emi is looking for her sister
Shirai's mistress.
this is gradually getting stinks
It stinks, oh it stinks, it stinks.
You have a good nose.
I am not a dog
I am not a stray dog.
If you do something wrong, I will put a collar on you.
Please take it away
Hey! Miyamoto!
Kamoi.
Please meet your sister.
Don't shout so loudly!
Stupid Detective!
Please use your help to bring that woman and her younger sister, Emi, together.
I understand, I understand!
Promise me
How was it?
It was for the purpose of destroying evidence after
the murder that the fire was set
Looking at various data,
it seems that the fire was set after the investigation
What were the victim's height and weight?
We know.
At first glance, the height is around 1.71 meters and the weight is about 65 kilograms
The person who died had used drugs before they died.
Eh?
What kind of person is Goro Yamamoto?
He doesn't sell drugs.
Because the height and weight are different
He's much smaller
Yes, yes, he's here
Mr. Kimura
Eh? what?
Yamamoto Goro broke through the Shizuoka Prefectural Police checkpoint?
What Goro?
The victim is indeed Shirai.
Leave from here
Go home!
What's going on?
It's nothing.
This person has come again
what about our promise?
Now that we've come this far,
I can't keep it a secret anymore
Actually, I'm a detective
Isn't this person showing his bad habits?
What are you talking about?
Your husband, Goro Yamamoto, is currently wanted for murder
My husband....
Tama-chan
Kamoi.
You lied me, didn't you?
You lied, didn't you?
My husband is a murderer
How could he do something so bad?
He's not the kind of person who would kill someone.
I believe that too
Rather than killing, that person seems like a good guy
Look!
His face is like that of a murderer.
Don't say bullshit.
Bring him here
If I ask him, everything will be solved.
Look at her
She might feel unwell and have a miscarriage.
If she has a miscarriage, you can give birth to the baby instead.
Kamoi.
Have you lost your mind?
Please continue to trust your master no matter what
Everything will be revealed in the near future
I believe in your husband's innocence as well
If that's the case, don't come here causing such a commotion
If you let him escape, I'll arrest you too, you know
You can stake out this spot yourself.
I no longer help you.
Are you still here?
I was waiting for you.
but I have no business with you
Oh, is that so? You have no business with Miyamoto Fumiko?
Miyamoto Fumiko?
That's right
She said she would wait at the café at 11 PM tonight
I see!
I need to hurry up and go look for Emi
Where's Emi?
I don't know.
I want to see their parents' faces
Where's Emi?
I don't know.
I don't see her
No matter where I looked, I couldn't find her.
Please tell her to stop looking for me.
Please
Could you please help her go back to my father's place?
I'm talking to you because you're her sister
Why don't you tell her directly?
How much do you know about the truth of this incident?
For now, you're saying Goro Yamamoto is the culprit
Excuse me
Hold on.
Are you under someone's control?
There are men under your control, aren't there?
Were the siblings able to meet?
I can't find Emi.
You're a really patient man.
There's no reason not to eat udon
It is my responsibility as a professional.
Are you sure?
It seems that Miyamoto Fumiko is a drug addict
She doesn't see her sister because of that.
Are you sure?
Kimura-san
Goro Yamamoto has entered the city from Kanagawa Prefecture
The shift change is coming
For now, please return to headquarters
Kamoi , About Yamamoto, I'm counting on you
And don't let Emi get too involved
It's like I'm entering the city as a police observer, isn't it?
Goro has come in Tokyo...
She is my big sister after all
Yeah.
I wonder why she didn't want to meet me?
I don't know the reason either,
but you know the reason, right?
I won't stop singing until I meet my big sister
Is she doing something bad?
Why would you say something like that?
I have that feeling
Kamoi.
Tell me.
I don't know.
I'm worried
I won't leave Kamoi-san until I take my sister home
You're clinging to me
My father is sick because of my sister
You're not good.
Emi-chan seems like she will stop singing until you come home
It's natural for Emi to say that, Go home
Your father has also fallen ill
My father?
I can't go home.
I can understand your feelings
but what do you really know?
What do you understand about me?
Sister
Is is fine if you don't care what happens to your own body?
Anyway, please return Emi to home
I will give you my thanks
Emi says she wants to go home with you.
That's not my problem.
I just want you to meet her tonight, no matter what
I'm a bit thirsty,
Using me to talk to her is a complete waste of time.
Meet her
Please.
I'm sorry I can't.
I don't want to involve my sister in this
It's already too late even if I meet my sister
Don't say like that.
Come on.
Sister.
Hey, stay strong.
What's this?
Tenshin spirit?
Come on.
Hey, stay strong.
You should at least knock on the door.
Kamoi.
what are you doing?
It's none of your business.
When you wander around, people get killed.
You seem like a harbinger of bad luck.
Hey, you
Isn't it different from me being targeted?
You?
The Gamo group and the Tenchi-kai might target me.
Her older sister, who came to me for advice, was murdered right in front of my eyes.
She took my place.
100% it's my responsibility.
I can't rely on you guys.
Kamoi.
If you do whatever you want, I won't forgive you.
What?
I just have a few things I wanted to say
Don't be so pretentious
My ears are already covered in cobwebs
Oh, I see,
What a dirty guy
I am washing the cobwebs,
so just leave me alone
Listen.
As a result of the autopsy on Fumiko Miyamoto,
heroin was detected in her stomach
What?
And this is an unprocessed drug called 'aka neta' that comes from her handbag
This type of drug can easily turn human bones to dust
Is this all you received from Miyamoto Fumiko?
Do you know about the Tenshin spirit realm?
Investigating that is your job
I'm busy avenging that sister
Stop it....
It hurts....
My butt hurts a lot.
This is a place where we promote health based on sportsmanship
What are you doing sneaking around like a thief?
I'm not a thief or anything
I just went around to the back of the dojo
But everyone, don't get so worked up and angry
Go home, go home
I will not allow you to join.
I want to meet the chairman.
What can we do for you?
I would like to ask about the case of Fumiko Miyamoto having this medicine bottle
What is this bottle?
This is road all, which means golden water
After sufficiently training the body,
consuming this will truly refresh you
The sick person's body healed, and many miracles occurred
I see, I want to be blessed by that.
Is there anything else?
I wonder what kind of troubles Miyamoto had
Of course, her physical condition was bad,
but was there something else mentally?
I cannot say anything about that
It's a secret known only to the person involved and the chairman who heard the confession
Excuse me, but is that hood something that conveys the voice of God?
He says it's not good to show human form.
Leave Goro-san to me.
I did ask you to keep watch,
but I'll help out when I have some free time
This is my duty.
Hey, what was the Tenshin Spirit Association about?
They are a kind of religious organization, involving prayers and martial arts
I don't understand why Emi's sister became a drug addict to go there.
I don't know
Hey, come on
You tax thief
I haven't taken a single penny from you
I haven't paid it, though
That's what the people's voice says
But do you really believe  Goro is culprit?
I think Tsuneyan's expectation is more accurate,
but do you trust someone who's a bit crazy and has a messed-up head?
Club World Chain's president is Shirai.
Is that related to Emi's murder?
We won't know unless we arrest Goro Yamamoto
Should I say that everything is related to Goro?
I wonder where he went....
I'm going to buy cigarettes.
I have some cigarettes.
I don't smoke cheap cigarettes.
Tamako....
Goro?
Are you Goro?
Don't dine and dash.
Oh Goro?
Tsune.....
Are you alright?
My child....
Not yet.
How about Tamako?
She's good.
I was worried about it.
What's wrong?
I was strangled by someone involved in the match in Osaka and thrown into a river.
I drove along the Tokaido Road to get my stolen car back.
Shirai noticed it.
I was almost killed by them in Nagoya.
I had some very dangerous experiences in Nagoya and Yokohama.
Well, Who killed Shirai?
There's something I really want Kamoi to hear about that
Goro.
Kamoi,Are you here?
What's wrong?
You have a visitor.
I'll be back later.
Excuse me.
Is Kamoi there?
You have a phone call.
Hey, Yamamoto has come?
I'll make sure to tell you properly if he comes.
Yeah.
The bartender from Funfun World?
I'm going right away then.
Is it you?
Don't push yourself, come to my apartment later.
Where was that call from?
It's none of your business.
What's wrong?
Did you drop something?
It could be.
This bed?
Should I search?
You don't have to
I see.
well,
take your time
There's no charm in it
Damn it.
Why did he take my pistol?
Never mind.
Thank you for welcoming me.
Tonight, I'm going to enjoy a feast to the fullest
Thanks.
By the way,  where's Goro?
Goro?
I don't know such a man
Don't pretend you don't know.
You were waiting for me to come, weren't you?
We have to welcome our guests properly
Take his pistol out.
He does not have
Kamoi.
You've got some guts
Where's Goro?
I don't know.
Damn it.
Bring Goro.
Kamoi.
Throw him into the machine room
Kamoi is in another room.
Chairman, it's better to kill him quickly.
Kamoi has escaped?
Chairman
Let's use him for a bit, then kill him.
Kamoi-san.
She is likely to give birth.
That's bad.
We need to take her to the hospital.
Where should I go?
Where is the detective?
He's not here
He's useless.
so hang in there, hang in there!
Please be patient a little longer.
Tama, stay strong.
I've never done this before
How about bringing Sakita?
Bring him
Tama
Is she likely to have a baby?
This is very troublesome.
This is a drink from the Tenjin Spirit Society.
That's bad, wait
This is dangerous
Don't let her drink
It's laced with drugs.
Do you know that?
Your voice sounds different than usual.
I'll excuse myself
Just for today, that guy suddenly changed his personality
He suddenly became more manly,
He's probably jealous.
I wonder why that is
He's always imitating women.
He is jealous because she is about to have a baby.
He is a man, so he cannot give birth to children.
He considered giving up.
Something like that.
I believe so
My husband......
Goro....
There's a call for you,Kamoi-san
Who is it from?
He can't say the name
Hello?
Goro?
Where are you?
Hey!
Kamoi-san
I want to see you
I really want to meet you.
The location is Kenzaki.
We went fishing there before.
Goro,Where are you?
Did you really kill someone?
What time?
The detective has arrived.
I get it.
Who is calling?
That call from a heaven
Her deceased sister made the call.
Is that so?
You're going to die soon, aren't you?
It could be.
Where are you going?
I'm going fishing in the sea.
I think you'll get baited.
It could be.
What are you going to do with me?
Give me your weapon.
I threw it away a long time ago.
Hey.
Trust me.
Look.
You bastard!
Stop it.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Hey!
He's a fearless man.
Is he  planning to dig his own grave?
Who was Kamoi in contact with?
Yamamoto?
No!
I knew it, where did they say they would meet?
I thought I would ask him
Hey, do you know or not?
She doesn't know
You're quite the honest person, aren't you?
Do you think I would come here
without understanding such a setup?
There is another reason why I came here.
You can say that line in heaven.
Wait!
Stand up!
Throw away the pistol.
Because of you,
Tsutsugo group has become just me.
I don't kill people by shooting pistols.
They were just injured.
Where is Yamamoto Goro?
I don't know.
If you don't say that, I'll kill you.
He is at Port 3 in Odaiba.
Are you sure?
Goro?
I'm glad we made it in time.
What about Tamako? What about the child?
She is in the hospital now.
When will the baby be born?
Today
Today?
Everything is okay.
You guys should turn yourselves in to
the police after seeing the child's face,
Are you doubting me too?
Tenshin is already dead.
Shirai Kanzo is alive
Aren't you the culprit?
That's ridiculous
I was relieved to hear that.
Let’s go.
I know.
I will expose Shirai Kinzo's true identity.
He framed me as the culprit.
Goro?
Kamoi.
I can't move any further.
You must persevere until you can meet your child.
Yeah...
Kamoi.
You put your head down.
Let’s go.
This man is not Tenshin!
He's Shirai Kinzo!
He killed Tenshin and is now pretending to be Shirai.
This man is not Tenshin!
He's Shirai Kinzo!
Wait.
Goro.
Shirai Kinzo, I am peeling off your mask
He's Tenshin.
I see, so Shirai is actually alive.
The wreckage of the exploded car was Tenshin
Shirai used Tenshin as a substitute.
Shirai Kinzo, I'm arresting you on suspicion of robbery and murder.
You go to the hospital first, hurry up!
Wait!
Kamoi, show me yours.
This isn't it.
What are you talking about?
You know what?
Kenzaki reported that one of their comrades was shot in Odaiba.
You did it, didn't you?
I wasn't using a pistol.
Don't say bullshit.
Have you drunk too much from eating udon?
You just said 'Pistol', didn't you? No,
you said it, it's you
You are chasing me, so I can not use a pistol.
Yeah
Yes,you are right.
Whatever
Wait!
I'll take you down for drug smuggling and violating the Narcotics Control Act
Hey, hey
I'm the one enforcing drug control at the Ministry of Health
Kimura, I apologize that the Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare got the job done first.
The suspicion of illegal possession of heavy machinery, robbery, and murder falls under the police's jurisdiction
Once our enforcement is done,
I'll hand it over to you at the Ministry of Health
Ministry of Health?
You are walking the path of rehabilitation
I too am walking the path of welfare.
Do your best.
What are you saying?
I will not accept your counting.
Take this group, including its members, not as witnesses, but as drug addicts.
We are investigating the drug content
contained in this water called Roadoll
This is a drug trafficking operation disguised as a drug deal.
Oh, the car's consumption body was Kamiya Tenshin, huh?
Originally, Tenshin was my puppet
I just took him out and used him as a
substitute because he tried to walk alone
So that's why you put on the mask of Tenshin
I'm also Shirai from Tsutsugo group
I have no intention of eating stinky rice in prison for 3 or 5 years
What happened to the 30 million yen you stole?
I did turn it into drugs in Kobe.
What's wrong?
Kamoi.
Look at how much suffering there is....
This is a very difficult birth.
Where's Goro?
He's inside
Tsune.
You don't have to suffer.
I've been suffering for 4 hours.
For 4 hours?
The baby was born.
Tsune.
Hey come on.
Are you alright?
Tsune.
This baby is my child, right?
Of course.
Because he is very handsome.
Don't say stupid things.
Tamako,
I'm really happy
It's really thanks to Kamoi-san.
She looks so nice.
She's cute.
You think so?
I'm shy.
Not you.
She?
Yes,you are right.
Kamoi.
I thought you had gone back to Osaka.
I'm on the way to back in Osaka.
What can I do for you?
Goro Yamamoto wants you to name his child, huh?
Yeah, how about adding Goro to Daisuke's name to make it Daigoro?
Daigoro?
Just wait a bit, That baby is a girl, right?
I've forgotten the baby's gender.
Kamoi.
What?
Good luck.
You shouldn't keep being a broke detective forever
I hope you get promoted a little.
Yes,you are right.
Stupid detective.
THE END