Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hoodlum Soldier's Flight to Freedom (#5)
Soviet troops are currently moving south.
But We in the Kwantung Army are proud.
We will stay here and intercept the enemy.
We will fight to the bitter end until we are all dead.
I'll keep your life
You guys get it?
You guys should get ready
Attack the enemy tanks with your guns today
Attack one tank at a time.
We can destroy 100 tanks in total
Hey new comers.
Were you on boarder,right?
Yes
Have you seen Soviet tanks?
Yes I've seen it once
What kind of tanks?
3 times bigger than Japan's
Oh my god..
Don't talk!
Work hard!
We'll be die?
I don't want
I don't want to die for a tank.
We'll be alive
Come on
You get it
Hey you
Why do you laugh?
You are unlucky
I feel annoying.
You go to bed
I'll get it back for you
Try it
I took a turn
I'll bid here
I get it
All?
I like you now
Next
Once more
Wanna try again?
Sure
I'll gain next time
Ready?
Your turn
You sure?
No.3
Go ahead
Next
Keep going
Stop
I get it
Hey you, You cheating
I didn't when I played with you
You bastard
What?
Damn it!
Stop it!
Get hands off of me
I'll kill you guys!
You'll kill us?
I can't accept you anymore
Don't look down of me
Try to kill me
You bastard
Try to kill me,crook
Stop it!
Attention
What's wrong?
You guys are too noisy
Listen
Write a letter tonight
This is your will
Put your hair and nails in it.
I'll pass it over the next coming unit
OK?
That's all
What's wrong?
You don't write?
Oh you can't write words
I'll write it for you
Please
To whom?
To girls
I need to know her name
Otomaru,Sayaka,Tamako and Momoko
You should choose Only one
Only one?
Who do you prefer?
How about Momoko?
You got married with her,right?
Right
What do you wanna say?
How do you read this?
My 24yrs life was miserable
Write I loved your figure
I won't forget about you
I might go to die
I wanted to die on your stomach
Is that funny?
Not
You're free to marry with anyone now
Good luck
That's all
Write something else
You're so easygoing.
Enemies are not coming
I hear they are at Sogo now
Sogo is south of here
They passed over here
I don't think so
If it's gold and pawns in chess, I go for gold.
You're saying nice
Let's go around
Freeze!
We are Japanese
Japanese?
We are Japanese.
Help us
We missed the run and haven't eaten anything for three days.
Please Help us
Mr.private first class!
Come with me
Are you Japanese?
yes we are
She's female
Actually we are parents
I let her escape by pretending to be a man
actually she is very beautiful
Please Help us
we want to help you but we die here
We can't protect you
we would like to support you as much as possible
Ok, you can stay here
Good for you
Thank you
Hello?
What can I do for you?
Can you take care of them?
One is female
female
Don't touch her
Women should stay in separate dormitories
Let's stay in a separate dormitory with our soldiers
OK
Attention
Get ready about bath
How's it?
Please leave from here
I'll shout
I wanted to confirm if you are a woman
Enjoy your bath
You guys! Wake up!
It's urgent!
What's wrong?
Listen,
there is a woman
don't be surprised
She's young and beautiful
You're lying
Please enter the dormitory behind the headquarters and check.
I saw her for sure
It seems that there is a woman here
there is a woman
Really?
I am happy to be alive
you look really stupid
they are comfort group,have run away
Did you take them?
I know them
Is the person female?
You are quick-tempered.
Damn it
Thank you for your hard work every day
We are a comfort group, but we don't have any musical instruments.
we threw away our tools on the run
But today I borrowed a harmonica from a soldier
I blow this harmonica and my daughter sings
she sings a Japanese song
she looks like my first love
First love
Then I sing your hometown song
How dare you
Be quiet
Hi,can I have your name?
I'm Yayoi
Yayoi?
That's good name.
I'm Omiya
Omiya?
You look like my first love
Everyone says same
I really mean it
The higher the rank of the soldiers, the more liars they become.
Like manager
Omiya
do you have permission?
you didn't see this board?
I can't read
What?
you are still a boy soldier
Your face is too hard
Damn it
You bastard
Stand up
Wait
Omiya
Stop it
You should be patient.
we are patient
I want you to be patient too
I'll tell him
We'll be back
Omiya
Boss is calling you
Your daughter is called Yayoi,right?
I want her to serve us
What do you mean?
We may die so we want her to serve
You know?
I can't
It's just the three of us, not all the soldiers.
Please forgive us
I know she's not a comfort woman
So I'm asking you a favor
If you agree, we will move you to a safe place.
It seems that the last train will leave from here tomorrow.
We'll get you on it
You guys are able to go back to Japan
What can I do...
I'd rather die than ask you that
we'll get out of here tonight
I don't wanna die
But
We'll be over
we struggled to escape
I ran away to live
But
we'll get out of here
I'll sleep with them
I follow him
yayoi
It can't be helped
It's ok.
juts for living
Thank you for coming
We can take the train tomorrow,right?
Yes, no worries
You guys go outside
where are you going?
I’m going to the bathroom
bathroom?
What's that?
Are you going to eat yokan in the restroom later?
you go to the dormitory,right?
Where's yayoi?
What's wrong?
What the hell you are?
Stop it
You did terrible things.
Are you okay?
they are bad
sorry for bothering you for me
It's ok
Oh no
I helped you but...
I was going to attack you at night
Well
That's what you planed
I know how you feel
I'm falling in love with you
Just once
I made a deal with them to get on the train tomorrow.
Eat this later
Omiya
It's ok if you stay here
I can't get you on the train
you came late.
What happened?
Nothing
What's wrong?
Untie me
Boss call you
Come to see him
May I come in?
I'm here
did you have fun last night?
Tell me about it
Come here
Damn it
Shit
Leader
Omiya is getting violent
How do you feel?
Look at this,dude
Omiya
Stop it
I'll manage this
Omiya
you escort her to the station
Get two people on the last train today
Go
Yes
I will escort them
Thank you for your help
I am very grateful to you
Thank you very much
I'm sorry I didn't thank you for anything
Thank you
When I come back to Japan, I will go to your house.
do you have anything to contact?
I have no home
Let's get on this train and go home together
I have a spare set of clothes.
Please wear it
Please come
Please change your outfit
Please do it
If you get on this train, you will return to Japan.
Quickly
Please change your outfit
Omiya
If you go back to the unit, you will die
I have to go back
Please change your outfit
What are you doing?
I can't left him
your thoughts are so stupid
Let's go back to Japan together
I won't forget about you
you survive and see you again
I won't die
Let's go
Hey
Mr.private first class
Omiya
Look at that
that place has fallen
What should I do?
anyway let's walk south
Take it easy
It's long way
I'm tired
Look at that well
I'm thirty
Thanks
Look at that
this is from japan
This was a  Manchurian guerrillas base.
I heard that the number of Manchurian guerrillas is increasing.
It's dangerous to walk
We'd be safer in a unit somewhere.
do we go back to the army?
It's much safer
let's go back to the army and be officers
officers?
this dress is just right
You look good
Don't call me as Mr.private first class
Oh yeah,
Arita Lieutenant
You don't look like a private either.
my face looks better
I can make you a commander
Let's get in that truck
Stop
where are you going?
To 103 unit
We'll go there together
Good
Thanks.
Where's main office?
Over there
what is the name of the commander?
Yanagida commander
were you the only ones who survived?
Yes
Did you run away?
I fainted from the blast, but miraculously survived
This guy look fine
he was escorting refugees
you look so scary
he is an executive candidate
I'm not asking you
where did you train?
Maebashi
I'm not asking you
which university did you graduate from?
Uni...
Tokyo Uni
Oh really?
People don't care what they look like
what year are you an officer?
5 or 6 yrs
You're slow to rise to the occasion.
what did the special training teach?
Well...
Fighting
What? Fighting?
You're funny guy
I hate smart people, but you are not
By the way do you have souvenirs?
souvenirs?
You can't enter another unit unless you bring a souvenir.
You didn't know that?
If you don't have souvenirs, you can't enter this unit.
He's scam
We're doing better
But Mr.private first class
Omiya
Lieutenant
the army is a funny place.
You can't escape, you can't enter
You don't have to salute him.
You are higher
I forgot about it
May I come in?
I brought food for you
Thanks
There is a shortage of food, but it is a sumptuous meal
you are special
If there is laundry, please give it to me
It's ok
Call us if you need help
See you
Being officer is good
It is said that officers and beggars cannot stop after three days.
I never want to be a soldier again
Now is training time
We are Omiya and Arita officer
Are you active soldier ?
I'm from gakuto
Oh I see
I want to know how advanced the Soviet army is
Xingjing and Harbin was occupied by the Soviet army.
I see
After eating, please teach the soldiers about anti-tank attacks.
Oh shit
Stop
Listen
We're going to practice anti-tank attacks from now on
soviet tanks are so big they are hard to hit
you should stop fighting them
You can travel a short distance
we stop training and take a nap
Come here
Let's take turns taking a nap in case the leader finds us
wake me up in the evening
Good sleep
It's my first time working with an officer like you.
do you think I’m reliable?
Yes very
I think your face is so great
You are very dignified even when you are naked
your skin is so beautiful
Is this ok?
Yes
You look like Eigoro Ohmaeda
Eigoro Ohmaeda?
I respect him
I see
I like talking with you
do you like movies?
Yes I love
Jirocho of Seven Rings and Eigoro Omaeda
We respect them
I like Yakuza too
I see
Where did you play?
Kansai's Asakichi is famous.
Asakichi
You know of him?
No
play with me next time
Thanks in advance
I get it
You're very strong
gambling is my business
you are very senior
But it's very rare
For what?
I heard that you graduated from the University of Tokyo.
How do you know?
From leader
don't talk about college
I took this
What department did you study in?
What department?
I studied in the First Investigative Division
you are good at joking
don't talk about college
I won
I'm Yamaoka.
May I come in?
Kiyoshima officer
What?
Unit leader is calling you
Excuse me
Be careful what they say about college
you seem to be getting used to
It's easier to imitate officer
we should have been officers sooner
we seem to be wasting our time
Who are you?
You're Aoyagi
I thought there was someone who looked like you guys, so I went to check
don't be scared.
I'm no longer Kenpei
Did you get fired?
I finished work
So you got down grade to private first class
I imitate him like you
you're pretending to be a soldier
Being soldier is easy going
You guys are disguised as officers and look like idiots
Japan will lose
Either we're prisoners of the Soviet Union or we're killed by them.
You'll be killed
Aoyagi
Are you here to deal with us?
I wanna work with you
Let's run away with me
Steal a unit's truck and go to the Korean Peninsula
If you go to GENZAN on the Korean Peninsula, there are boats bound for Japan every day.
This is a only way we survive
If the three of us work together, things will go well
You are officer now
And You're good at running away
Can you?
We decline
I thought you guys were smart
I'm disappointed about you
Damn it
Omiya
It's urgent, Wake up
Wake up
Stand up
you're still like a soldier
I'm used to it
don't impress yourself
Come,officers
Communist guerrillas are expected to gather 6 km north of here.
We prepare for battle and destroy the enemy
Second Lieutenant Omiya, please go scout out the enemy's situation.
Yes
What is officer plan?
You just go
You get it?
No
What's that?
Hold on
I'm Japanese
I belong to pleasure groups.
Please help me
Please
What's wrong?
I evacuated with a woman and child to the hospital, but they were attacked by guerrillas.
I ran away to ask you, so please
I'm not unit leader.
I'm Second Lieutenant
Second Lieutenant, please
Women, children and the sick are isolated
I'm in trouble even if you ask me
You are officer
Yes I am but
I present you another Officer
Ok I get it
I'll ask our leader
Good for you
I want to help him but I can't
Eh what?
We can't afford it.
we need to leave from here
Sick man, woman and child asking for help
It's urgent
You should be polite
this is the command
But
It can't be helped
Leader
2 hours to get there by truck
I don't think there will be any obstacles to creating a withdrawal
this is not easy
There's a communist guerrilla base 6 M from here.
you don't have to be afraid of them
you are stubborn
this interferes with the operation
I don't think so.
We can leave after that
do you disagree with me?
I think the Japanese have helped the Japanese.
If you lend me a truck and five non-commissioned officers, Omiya and I will go.
I won't bother you
go if you want to go
Yes
You were unlucky to be selected for the rescue team.
I chose you guys for a reason
you have courage
I want you to complete the mission for the Japanese.
Don't give up that you're out of luck
we may be attacked by the enemy
Are you sure you follow them?
It can't be helped
do you want to die?
What should I do?
leave them and go back
We're going to Korea without going back to our unit.
To Korea?
If we go to Korea, we can go back to Japan
You may not know it, but Japan will lose the war.
If we go back to Japan now, we won't have to die.
we will either die or be taken prisoner
You people should value your own lives.
how do you get away from them?
I'll manage it
Can you?
I have a plan
I have already looked into ways to get to Korea.
What do you think?
If you want to go to the toilet, go now
What's wrong?
If you don't decide quickly, you might be attacked by guerrillas.
Hey
I won't go
Why?
I don't feel like it
Mind if you die?
I can't betray Omiya
You like him so much
Yes I do
I will tell you the truth
they are not really officers
What?
they are just soldiers and fakes
You sure?
they are notorious for being problem children.
you don't have to die for them
what are they doing?
Go to the bed of the truck
Stop here
Get off
Push
OK
do you still have fuel?
Yes
Aoyagi
Freeze!
kill them
I'll kill them
Kill me
I will blow myself up
You know who is he?
He's Kenpei
Damn it
Wait
I'll beat him
Stop it
take him with us.
It's better if soldiers are more
Listen,
We are fake officers
I'm 5 grade, Omiya is 2nd grade soldiers
we were in an army prison
I've been found and I'm throwing this away.
But I want to finish my mission to the end
The sick and children await us in Samkatan
It seems that a newborn baby is there
Suppose they are your babies
Suppose they are your wives
If we abandon them, they will be attacked by the enemy.
We can't leave them
Ok Let's go
Thanks, Takagi
I'll go too
Thanks.
Thanks guys
Get him on the truck
Stand up
Let's go!
Use this
Put on this
Watch out!
You guys all right?
This is yours
A truck is coming
soldiers are coming
Where is the sick?
soldiers are here
Get on the truck from the emergency sick
Thank you very much
Get on the truck from the sick.
There is only one truck.
Then babies and kids
Get on the truck from the sick.
Hold on
Listen, you guys
I know  you guys all wanna get on , but it's impossible for all people to get on
Kids who goes to school needs to line up as adults
Get him on
He needs to wait
He's still 6 yrs old
Don't make a lie
Get him on,please
Don't be selfish
Can you walk?
Yes I can
Let him walk
A long walk with my mother will give me good memories in the future.
Is there any sick left?
Line up, everyone
You guys line up here
We are going first.
You guard the truck
We're heading to Bashou
It takes about 50km
Enemy might attack us in half way
Follow me in the case
Go!
Everyone go
They are coming
What’s wrong?
Stop
We'll take a rest here
We'll get to sleep until sun goes down, then walk again
We'll walk in the night.
We need to take a rest now
You get it?
Yes
Kawabe,
Navigage them
Escape from here
You move ahead
Aim to their base
We made it
You guys all right?
Kawabe
Goto
Murakami
Aoyagi
Arita
I was a scoundrel
No.
You have been reborn.
I'll still be a scoundrel the next time I'm born.
Good luck
Aoyagi
We'll be there soon
Just 4km left
We can take a rest there, and you can see your family
Keep going!
You are tired?
Let's go
THE END