Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hoodlum Soldier's Escape (#4)
Omiya!
Damn it
We are about to over
we were charged with desertion
We were transported to the Kwantung Army prison in HOTEN
All inmates here are referred to by number.
Arita
You are no.30 from today
Omiya
You are no.31 from today
You must obey the guards' orders.
If you do not obey the guards' orders, you will be punished.
They are new comers
Why you are here?
Have you been thieves?
No
Run away from military?
Yes kind of
A fugitive soldier is worse than a thief.
You all ended up in hell.
Don't laugh!
Attention
Move forward
Stop
No.30 enter in no.3 room
No.31 enter in no.4 room
You will be searched when you enter the room.
Take off clothes and get pose
You don't get it?
Take off clothes
unbutton all clothes
Do it quickly!
Put your hands up
Open your legs
Open your mouth
More!
Ok go in
Go!
Don't lie down!
What the hell you are?
There are 130 rules here
you have to follow the rules
If you understand, answer me.
Yes
Mr. 26, teach him the rules
Just do what I do
do we sit all day?
Place your hands on your knees and sit straight for 30 minutes.
If you want to move your hands you need permission from the warden
What do you do when you want to mess with your nostrils?
Yeah
this is a very bad place
The warden is right, this place is hell
you seem to have run away
Yes
Which team?
Several teams
I did it many times
You are guilty of a great deal.
How about you?
I've caused a big problem.
Did you kill anyone?
I stole a lot of guns.
you are a thief
Hey!
Don't move your eyes
Keep looking at the wall
I can't move my eyes?
If you want to do that you need permission from us
No way
that's the rule here
Bed time
Go to bed now
Hey no.31.
When you go to bed, lie on your back and stretch your legs straight.
Do I have to keep my body upright while sleeping?
What the hell you are?
But it's hard
What?
Respect me
don't complain to him
Ok then I will go to bed
i have a bad sleep.
I don't know after sleeping
Good night
he's a trouble maker
Wake up!
my towel is a little small
It's same
they are stingy
There is a risk that general towels will be used for escape or suicide
Escape?
Some people have committed suicide, but no one has yet escaped using a towel.
Attention
Damn it
We're lined up
Number!
1.2.3.4.5.6.7.8
That's all
Attention
There are no abnormalities in the four people in this room.
Number!
1.2.3.4.5.6.7.8
Again
Number!
1.2.3.4.5.6.....
Again
Number!
1.2.3.4.5.6.
Shiina director
He don't follow the rules
Move forward
Go around
What are you doing?
Good
Get in the jail, No.31
Be sure to get permission before entering the room
stand up right and ask me for permission
Don't look down about me
Stay down
Stop it
Omiya
You are further charged with destruction of property for defying me and reducing my lunch for ten days from today.
Lunch time
Come, No.26
the government sent you a package
I will open this package in front of you
A photo
She's nice.
Who's she?
My wife,Hisako
Shouldn't you let your wife know you're here?
i didn't want to worry her
You're kind
She's nice
Don't pretend you are nice
i won't give you this picture
I only give you tissue paper
I'll keep rest of them
Thanks
Please use other
Ok I get them
why do you sell him flattery?
i hate your attitude
It's more profitable for me to do that
You should do same
I can't
you should follow me.
It's no use resisting them
I don't care if I can't eat
Take this
No.26,get out!
Army Private Sawamura Jiro. You have been charged with theft.
You had your indictment withdrawn on June 11.
Come back to the army tomorrow morning
Am I going to be released?
Thank you very much
Your case was decided by a court-martial.
I was in charge of it
I know
i would like to thank you
You're welcome
If you want to get out of prison too, become a feudal lord like Mr. 26.
the solicitor is waiting for you.
Let's go
How are you?
I'm fine but you do eat lunch and dinner
I want sake and women other than eating
Don't push yourself too hard
If you get along with the guards, you'll be able to leave early.
Don't say bullshit
No.26 got out
Listen.
Our case is not easy
we are fugitives
So what will happens?
we will be killed
Really?
Or life imprisonment
we have to jailbreak
Go to bed
this is broken
water pipe is rising
What should I do?
call the guard quickly
guard!
Broken water pipe.
Did you make it?
What did do do?
Stop it any way
Please close the main valve
Matsumoto,close the main valve
We can't sleep
Fuck you
you plan to escape
Keep quiet
Stop it
Don't move
Calm down, Omiya
I know
There is no problem!
Thanks for your work
Let's run and break through.
We can't
If we run and break through, they can't see us
Leave it to me
Attention
Hold on
Where are you going?
There's a sudden illness. I'm going to call a doctor.
There's a sudden illness?
Yes
Which room?
No.1 room
I don't see an armband.
It's urgent business.
The warden said he would call you later.
I see
OK
Thanks
Hold on
Come
Can you get alcohol from there?
Don't tell them I want it
I know
Hold on
Stop
You guys!
Hold on, Omiya
Ok let's go!
This is rail line
Manshu rail line?
Wait here and get on the train
We can escape if we get on the train
They don't chase us
We made it!
I got hungry now
Omiya
We'll shoot you if you run away
Stop
Everyone who escapes from prison comes here.
The jailbreak failed and we were to be gunned down.
You're Arita and Omiya
You've already known it
Give him a proper reply.
Do not interrogate him and execute him immediately.
We need the procedure.
You wait outside
Arita,It's me
You're Nagai
Yes
Long time no see
Since we graduated the college
Are you now a lieutenant in law?
I was surprised to learn that you are a fugitive from justice.
He's my classmate
Hello.
Could you please untie this too?
You stay as it is
You have caused us a great deal of trouble.
We know we are condemned to death.
I'm glad to see you
You know how I feel
I save you
I will make sure you do not get the death penalty.
Are you sure?
I'll deal with them
Is there a deal for a court-martial?
Kind of
You may be transferred to a front-line unit.
It's better than die
Don't run away and ruin my face again
I won't
Excuse me but can you help me too?
I don't know
You are the main offender, so it is not the same
what will happen to him?
I have no idea
he has to take the responsibility
i am responsible for everything
he is my subordinate
he obeyed my orders
But...
Please help him too
I know how you feel
I think you should cut ties
I can't.
If he can't be saved, I will stay here.
me and him have always acted together
Nagai
Please
We saved our life
We were transferred to the unit going to CHANGKOTSU.
But only we were sent further to the front line
I downgraded
We always have something to do with the military, don't we?
Get ready!
do we get off here too?
Get off?
Let's have fun
Don't say bullshit
no one is watching us
But I worry about Nagai
She's here
Stop it
Don't run away
Come with me
What are you saying?
i will be loud if you touch me
You are already adult
Stay down
What the hell you are
You're just woman
Stop it
Stay down
She hates it
Which teak are you belonging ?
It's none of your business
Do you know who I am?
i am an officer
i will punish you
we're on the train
Go outside if you play woman
Fuck you
Cut it out!
get out!
Damn it
he's bustard
Sit here if you like
I feel relieved
He is a guest I met at a banquet.
He's annoying
Where are you going to?
To xinkatong
We're going too
I see
We're transferred there
I work at a small restaurant there
I'm Tamako
Please visit me
i want to thank you
I'm excited.
Let's go to her shop tonight
private first class
You are just first class
I had a lot of circumstances.
Where are you from?
We were in the HOTEN Special Forces
HOTEN
I worked there as a geisha for about two and a half years.
After that, I went to XINKYO and Harbin.
we work in many places
soldiers are like you
Thanks for coming
where did you take a detour?
Train was late
don't make excuses
You guys went to the whorehouse.
Do you bet if we go or not?
What?
Look at our bodies and you'll see
you shouldn't be arrogant
The troops here are tough.
Your face is like a rock
sleep in an empty room
Mt.private first class
what?
Not you. but him
private first class?
He is just first class
He was private first class
how old are you?
I'm 3rd year
He's 5 yrs
don't take my blanket
Give me one
What?
You're no.26
You're 31
how did you get out of prison?
He's my boss
I know
Thanks for looking after him
We're related, aren't we?
Do you have drinking?
you guys go to bed early
we were redone from basic training
Omiya
Say the 5 articles of a soldier
1.soldiers should be punished
It's wrong
1.soldiers should be
1.soldiers must be loyal
should be text
This is not a song
1.soldiers behave themselves
It's courtesy
1.soldiers take their lives...I forget
You know nothing
Attention
23 people gathered
Number!
1.2.3.4.5.6.7.8.9.10.11.12.13.14.15.16.17.18.19.20.21.22.23
There's no problem
Attention
We will be dispatched to KANSHU in the near future.
our mission is very important
Was this how it worked?
We have no choice but to do it this way
Don't you remember Iroha from SONBU?
Otomaru's room were like this
Who's she?
I met her there.
Let's have a heso sake
Heso sake?
We don't have that
There is only sake or beer
Give me a beer
I'll bring some
It's killing me
Can you stay out tonight?
we will be back by dinner
We'll work at Kanshu from tomorrow
kanshu?
So I won't see you
Thanks for coming.
Let's toast
I'll please you
Really?
Where's Tamako?
She's with her customer
I see
Can you take care of me?
I think I'm the only one who went out today
Who's the customer?
It's a soldier
soldier?
Heso Sake is what you mean
My stomach hurts when I drink beer through my belly button
bring me a warm beer
i get burned
my stomach is sensitive
Team leader
Oh you
do you know where this is?
This is the store where officers come
This is not the store where you come
If you take off your clothes, you are all the same
did you know from the beginning?
i haven't had sex with them yet
They are my best friend
best friend?
Even if they're best friends, they can't be here
Get out!
What should we do?
Don't look down at me
Please go back
We'll go back
Go back
Omiya
Damn it
I hate him
It can't be helped
I can't accept
what are you going to do?
they were in prison
I don't care
Don't deal with them
Are you jealous?
They are just soldiers
Tamako?
What?
You're cold to me
Don't get angry
I'll please you
it's mouses
Attention
departs at 8am
Walk east for about 10 kilometers
It's a place that's at odds with the Soviet Union.
There are 4 monitoring stations every 300 M
We'll handle the first monitoring stations
I will use a map to explain to you
why are you laughing?
Come to my room later
did you reflect?
Tamako is my girl
i will take her back to japan
don't get involved with her
Stand up!
Do you rebel?
If I report you, your parole will be revoked.
you will go to jail again
You want me to do that?
sorry to bother you
you endured well.
i thought you would hit him
He's so nasty
he is very sneaky
Of all the superiors I've met, who I hate the most.
we will get revenge on him
Oh you
What's wrong?
Nothing
you have something
Did you see?
Money or gold?
Gold?
don't hide it, show me
Stone
Stone?
Jade
i have been saving them till now
How did you get them?
I traded this for what I stole
are you going to take it away?
No way.
I'm not that person
I am grateful to you for the meals you gave me in prison.
Can you keep a secret?
I will sell this and go back to Japan just in case
I will die after loving Hisako
I was told there were female soldiers in the Soviet Union.
This is front line
I was told that the Soviets sent all their male soldiers to Germany.
I'm guessing there are one female soldier at least
You're happy man
You think of nothing but women
It can't be helped
I think of Japan all the way
I miss Japan
We've worked for returning to Japan
We've tried to escape
But we ended up to be front line
I was told there were female soldiers who swim in the river
They are kidding
Someone go to the riverbank and get a duck.
I'll give you a gun. get closer and shoot them
Who wanna go?
Are you afraid about soldiers in the Soviet Union?
You guys are so chicken
Are you freaking out,Omiya?
You are a coward after all.
Why you afraid of being shot?
I'm going. but If I managed it, can you let me go out?
Ok I'll let you
I'm going.
Don't go.
You'll get shot
They are snipers.
You wanna go?
I'm going.
We'll shoot if they shoot
It could turn into a war.
I'll see how they work
Don't play it
You know who I am?
Don't worry about me
You are fat so easy to target
Yakuza tried to shoot me. but They couldn't shoot me.
They are snipers.
See how it goes
It was close
I got 2
We'll have duck hot pot meal tonight
I'll go out
But don't see Tamako
Answer
Yes
Mr.Private first solider
You stupid
Hey, I'm here
Welcome
Where's Tamako?
She's gone to officers' living quarters?
officers' living quarters?
There is a party
You don't go?
I feel sick
I don't care
This is Tamako's room
You wanna drink?
Sawamura is here.
May I come in?
Come in
Have a seat
I have a favor of you
Omiya went out tonight.
I told him not to see Tamako but I can't trust him
Can you check him?
It's easy
just check
it'll be after 11pm if you go now
so You can stay there tonight
Thank you very much
But be sure to come back by morning
Don't tell to other solders
I know
Go
I'm going
Hold on,Sawamura
What can I do for you?
I know you have jade
you buried them in the ground
do you think i don't know that?
How did you get them?
Did you steel?
No
you cheated and got it
Someone gave me
do you want to go to jail again?
If you don't want to go to jail again give it to me.
Follow me and I will not tell anyone else.
It's a gunshot.
enemy?
I'm going
Team leader
What?
There was a gunshot.
I shot Sawamura
Take his corpse to the observation post.
when i came here late last night
I found out Sawamura went out
When I asked him where he was going, he ran away.
He tried to escape
So I shot Sawamura
As you know, if you escape, you'll be shot.
This is the front line of the battlefield
i didn't want to kill him but i had no choice
this is a military rule
Arita
Yes
you were with him in prison
you deliver his body to the second team
I shot him dead according to military regulations.
He has wife
Treat him as a dead man, not a fugitive.
I will write a letter to the captain, so bring it with you.
Yes
Mr.private first class solider
What's wrong?
Sawamura was killed
I deliver his body to the second team
Why he killed
He tried to escape.
So leader shot Sawamura
When?
last night
i don't think he escaped
What do you think?
It's strange
I'm going too
You have to go back
He looked after me
This is really stupid.
We escaped a lot, but we weren't killed.
Only stupid things happen here
I feel sorry for him
I am so sorry he is gone.
he has jade...
he has jade...?
He'd saved them
Is it jewelry?
he put it in a small bag.
He said he would sell it and go back to Japan.
I checked his belongings and found nothing of them
he can't run away without them
The leader took them
He may have intended it from the beginning
he killed him as a fugitive
Hold on
He is not worth pursuing.
Damn it
We need the proof
Be careful
Omiya
I feel like drinking today
I treat you nice
I can't get drunk
Because of Sawamura?
No
I feel depressed when I see you
Why?
Do I look gloomy?
Seeing you makes me want to go back to Japan
he gets honest when he gets drunk
How about you?
i get merry when i get drunk
You're not
You can't get drunk too
It's his wake today, so it can't be helped.
I know you can stay here tonight
Let's have drink together
You don't miss Japan?
I don’t
You're lair
Your true heart says you want to go back to Japan
I know all people here miss Japan
No one wanna be here
There is no place where I go back
you have a hometown
Till childhood
Did you have a bobbed hair when you were a child?
Yes
You looked cute, didn't you?
You guys were cute with shaved heads too.
I'm still cute
Do you see anyone here?
Why you ask me?
You get drunk?
If so, I would like to let you get married and return to Japan.
I only love you guys
You are nice
which do you like him or me?
both
You are cheeky
But I don't wanna go to Japan
Sasaki leader told me he wanted to go back with you
No way
damn it
Sawamuwa wanted to go to Japan
So he collected Jade
jade?
You know?
Sasaki leader told me There is a soldier who collects jade.
He's Sawamura?
Sasaki leader knew about that
Hey
hey!
He's in the toilet
You help me
How's it?
keep going
I see
I'll massage you
I used to be a masseuse
Do it
I found a store where you can buy alcohol cheaply.
If you let me go out, I will buy it
I don't drink
Really?
You only like women
You are so play boy
I know
What's this?
this is a talisman
What for?
it's for the military.
Go back!
Mr.private first class solider
Good
He has the jade
I see
he has it hanging around his neck
You sure?
I'll get it tonight
tonight?
at bed time
You'll go alone?
Earlier is better.
let's take it while he sleeps
Ok Let's do it
wake you up at 3am
Let's take a turn
Thanks
Have you heard anything from me?
Nothing
Soviet soldiers are also sleeping
It's 3 am now
The enemy has attacked!
August 9, 1945 3:00 am
The Soviet Union suddenly launched an attack on Japan.
Leader has escaped!
Let's catch him
Omiya
Where he's gone?
I think he's gone for Tamako
Wake up,Tamako
I'm off today
What the hell?
The Soviet Union suddenly launched an attack
Run away!
You'll be killed
Where are we going?
Let me go
You stupid!
I beat you
Don't hit him yet
you will go to jail again
what are you saying?
I don't afraid anything
You has them as I thought
He killed Sawamura for this jade
He killed a solider?
Why he killed?
Mr.private first class solider
Even if he survived, he would end up being killed by the Soviet army.
Please calm down
The train is not coming because the tracks are destroyed
Restoration is undecided
the truck is about to leave
I'm tired
what are you saying?
i don't want to go back to japan
he wants you to go back to japan
Please show me your boarding pass
What's that?
you can't ride without it
Why?
the general public is the last
Who they are?
they are a military family
she is also from a military family
Tell my boss about it
Please let her get in the truck
Your family?
She's my wife
Solider family is the last
Why?
The officer's family is ahead
That's
Give him that
This is jade
Really?
I'll give you
Thank you very much
Let's go
Thanks,Arita
Thanks to the Jade
I still have 4
use this in case of emergency
Take this too
What's wrong?
You're so kind
Don't cry.
Stay as you are
We wanted to play with three people
i will never forget you
If you're alive, maybe we'll meet again
please survive too
Get out
What the hell?
We're officers
It is cowardly for soldiers to flee before women and children.
this is for war
Get off!
I will kill you if you don't get off
Line up
take their armbands
you guys don't pretend you're great
Everyone! Get in the truck!
driver
Omiya
Oh shit. I left him there
It's too late
Please go with me
But..
do you like him more than me?
Omiya!
Mr.private first class solider!
THE END