Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Heiten Jikan / Closing Time (1962)
Thank you for visiting us today.
Thank you very much, welcome, welcome
Good morning, everyone
Thank you for coming today
Thank you for visiting us
Thank you in advance
Please wait a moment
On the 8th floor, American, France and Italian clothing is sold.
Hey there!
Good morning!
That's not good
You're late!
I'm sorry, but I got caught up with work
You need to stick to the schedule, or it will be a problem!
Eh?
Good morning!
I want 5 croquettes
Which?
Cheaper one.
I'll have two menchi katsu.
Please. Just a moment.
Yes, two menchi katsu. I'll help you.
Sorry
I'll have 100 of kinpira, please.
Please. Just a moment.
We're open now
Are you ready?
Please do not talk.
Good morning.
The smoke button is loose
You should puff out your chest.
Good morning.
Your lips are too much, so please make them thinner
Well, it's time to open the store
Good morning, customers are coming up
Good morning
Don't forget to smile.
This is our motto, so that's great
Good morning
We are opening
What is gohachi?
It's about the customer
Gohashijuu means to come
Is that so?
You might understand it soon since you're new here
There are various Phrasing.
For example, about meal,it's hachihachi.
When you write the character for rice, it looks like 88, right?
then, about the toilet, 44, in other words, it's pee.
hey you, stop the nonsense, can't you see customers?
Welcome.
You know, I wonder if this will not lose color even if I wipe it with gasoline.
I think it should be fine.
I wanna make it sure.
Is there anyone else who understands?
It's all right
But this is plant-dyed.
it does contain a bit of chemical dye
The color stop is perfect
It definitely won't come off unless it's soap
That's reassuring, then I'll take this.
Thank you as always
Thank you for visiting us every time
Next, we have a shopping guide for 4 sets of 5 bedding
I'll go 4F
Yes, understood
Thank you for your patience
This will be the fourth floor.
I'll go 6F
Understood
Have you been kept waiting?
Children's clothes are very expensive
My child is in elementary school, but
If it feels narrow, it makes me feel inferior
It's quite tough, you know, the PTA meeting
That's right, mothers never wear the same kimono twice.
Thank you for waiting
This is 6F.
Excuse me, excuse me, how about this for my daughter?
Does anyone else want to get off?
Next is the rooftop
We have gardening supplies and a baby zoo
This is the last floor.
but I want to go to the 7th floor
This is an even-numbered floor stop.
If it's the 7th floor,
Please go down the stairs on the right
So I can go back six floor and go up the stairs, right?
Go ahead.
It seems that is a love letter
Yes.
Do you get that often?
how envious I am of you.
Maybe I should give it a try too
We are going down.
Where have you been wasting time?
What are you saying at a time like this?
I'm with the bee of the lady inside the store
What's wrong with that?
You just joined recently
Don't talk back so arrogantly
What?
Don't they teach manners at university?
I've been here four years longer than you, you know
If you're a senior, act like one
You don't even know the good and bad of dyeing, so that's why women are no good
What do you mean by saying women are no good?
You're just working hard to be prepared, kill time, and make some pocket money, right?
It means there's no harshness
Well, that's rude
I'm just killing time anyway
It's not just a side hustle
I find purpose in this job and that's why I do it
I can do the same job as you.
So, are you planning to become a section chief and then a department head, even though you're a woman?
Well, what do you mean by 'even though you're a woman'?
I'm doing this as if I'm going
to become an executive,
Come on, this is a workplace.
It's fine, it's fine
Take this and deliver it
Excuse me, but for all that enthusiasm, you lack knowledge about the business.
Ubukata
Just stop it; it's embarrassing. You're a woman, after all
If you keep it modest, there won't be any problems, okay?
Because I'm a woman
Just because I'm a woman
Why do I have to be modest?
Can I have some curry?
Is it lunchtime already?
Oh, you're busy, huh?
Can I have some milk?
Yes, curry.
Hello.
Oh Secchan.
Oh, what's wrong?
I know there's someone unpleasant in the same section
He's been with us for three months and he's a terrible man.
That's how women are, right?
Male employees become section chiefs and take office
They'll keep getting promoted, right?
Even if a female employee works for 10 years,
She's just a salesgirl
Thinking about it makes me sad and angry
but you eat a lot.
When I'm sad, I eat a lot.
I wonder if I should get some milk too
I'll give you this.
Really? Thanks.
At this rate, it's not a big deal.
Come on, listen to me a little more sincerely
Aren't you getting angry?
Women are often said to work just to kill time and earn a little pocket money
Well, that's how I am, so there's nothing I can do about it
How pathetic
Put in more effort!
I'll lose your fighting spirit
Because, you know, I'm the type of person who tends to be dependent on others
And from morning till night, I was chased around by croquettes and kinpira gobo
People are becoming more and more down-to-earth
Oh dear, but you were such a romantic during high school, weren't you?
I hear you're going to have an amazing romance with a wonderful young gentleman
What happened to your theory on love?
It's because the items being handled are special
It can't be helped
You have a 70,000 yen visiting kimono
My croquettes that cost 7 yen each
I wonder what a deluxe love is like 70,000 yen?
I'm sure we're working every day in search of love
Have you found someone you like?
I don't have that kind of time
I'm currently at this point
I really want to crush that arrogant rookie's nose when my stomach starts to feel full
I'm full,that make me to fight again.
You haven't changed at all
Strong-willed, conceptual, and combative
Your junior was quite a handful, just like back in the basketball club days.
For both me and Sayuri-chan.
I miss the old days.
Back then, we didn't yet know what the world was really like
Hey, how about inviting Sayuri-chan tonight and having a party for the first time in a while?
Yeah, that sounds nice.
your beautiful face
Your pretty feet
What a magnificent bust!
He's so pervert.
Every time I think of it, I sigh during the day and can't sleep at night
I feel like I'm going to die
Please save me from my suffering
I wonder what's going on.
Who gave this to you?
He's uncool, He has acne face.
I've received about twenty letters in the elevator
There wasn't anyone decent
The other day, I was hugged by a bald old man
Hello, this is the service department
She's here, Sayuri-chan, it's a phone call
I'm sorry
Hello? Ryo-chan.
Good afternoon.
Tonight?
Sure,I'm free.
I get it.
Well then.
Sayuri-chan
what?
How many boyfriends do you have?
Numbers and quantity
The quality drops completely
I really want an amazing guy.
You are being extravagant.
everyone, it's your turn.
Hello? Yes
Sayuri-chan
It's another call.
it's rare because it's from a woman
Hello, this is Maki. Oh, is that you, Secchan? Huh?
Three people?
Sounds good, doesn't it?
Sorry, I have plans tonight
I'm sorry.
Wait.
why am I the only one investigating this?
I had a bit of a hunch, but it's because of the rules
Excuse me,
I feel unpleasant.
Security checks are tight here.
Where are we going?
Let's go to city.
Secchan's dream of love is a passionate love
A blazing hot love burning bright red
What about your love?
Come on, it must be a blue love
A painful love
Why?
Because you are calm by nature, right?
That's why
Don't say unpleasant things
Isn't that Sayuri-chan?
Oh, I'm sorry, did you wait?
Hmm, where should we go?
Anywhere is fine
Let's have a meal.
Yeah, that person is an actor who appears on TV from time to time
Sayuri-chan's love is yellow.
We, as seniors, should give her a heads up.
Sayuri-chan has rumora; her bungee jumping is flashy
She has a lot of boyfriends, back in the day, you know
I could call and preach, but
It's no good, that person's path is also a life of its own
We are living the same life; which is better and which is worse?
No one understands, you know
That's true.
In fact, that person might be enjoying life more than we are
Look.
There're only couples.
Why are there so many couples?
Men really have no eye for things.
They leave wonderful women like us alone
Shall we go for getting a guy too?
What do you think about him?
Maybe 80 points?
75 points
How about smiling and talk him?
Doesn't he think we are crazy?
I'm sorry, but is it okay.
Let's go.
It's interesting, so why not look for more?
Hey, don't you think that person is nice?
Which one?
That guy in the Mambo style?
I don't like him at all.
Your taste is terrible.
Do you really think so?
What do you think about that?
Huh? Which one?
The person standing at the corner over there.
The guy who has rain coat?
That's a bit nice.
it's more than just a bit.
I've admired people like that since I was little
I'm into a guy like him.
That's wonderful, isn't it?
Hey, hurry up and make your move!
How?
You just need to wink in front of that person
Wink with one eye?
Well, in other words, it's a wink.
I can't.
No, this isn't the time to be saying things like that
Eh, hurry up!
No, it's okay.
I can't.
This isn't easy, right? You just have to do it like this, right?
Like this?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I can't.
Yeah, it's okay
Are you ready?
Did you wait for long?
You are late
Let's go
Hey sis, did you just wink at us?
Wow, you look nice.
If you’re that bored, I’ll play with you
It's still too early to go home
Let's dance
Or drive?
We have domestic car.
Let's go to Roppongi
Or should we go to Yokohama?
You're just bored anyway, right? Hey! Hey!
Why are you running away!
Where are you going!
Did they come after us?
It seems it's okay
My apologies.
Oh Teacher.
what happened here?
I was followed by a strange man
Did you just wink?
This person winked
That's terrible.
but you're okay now, right?
Are you alone, sir?
Yes, there was a bit of time before the broadcast
I was watching a movie and oh no, I need a taxi!
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Who is that person?
The teacher from the library I'm going.
He's a bit handsome.
Just your type, huh?
No, he has a wife
Oh, It's going t be trouble.
Oh are you coming home now?
See you then.
I wonder who that person was.
Come on.
I can't even remember.
Everyone is couple
There's nothing we can do about it
Shall we eat something before heading home?
I'm going to eat a lot
My apologies.
Good morning, good morning!
Watch out.
Oh sorry.
My name is Takei.
I deliver goods here every morning.
I believed I met you somewhere.
You stayed cool.
I was disappointed.
I helped you that morning with your menchikatsu.
Oh, did that happen?
Oh my god.
the opening is approaching, cut it out.
My apologies.
I'll make sure to remember you this time
Please.
7th floor?
Could you stop?
Today, I'm handle in an odd-numbered floor.
Are you shopping on the 7th floor?
No.
it's for work
Oh are you working here?
Yes.
You have to take the employee elevator; otherwise, it's against the rules
I work at advertising department, so it doesn't matter
Talking about anything other than explanations in the elevator is against the rules
Well then, I won't talk anymore.
I'm sure you'll have nice day.
Because I was able to ride in the elevator with Maki.
Do you know my name?
Look, you're talking again, yay!
Who are you looking for?
It's not like I'm looking for anyone specific
Well, I'm sorry I couldn't make it the other day.
Oh, it's fine
The employee book is quite messy
It's because girls are always flipping through pages looking for a good man.
Did you say someone nice?
It's quite hard.
You say you have quite a few boyfriends, don't you?
I saw you walking with some TV actor the other day
Ah, I'm getting a bit tired of him.
It seems to be gaining some popularity
So you should be careful.
it's fine.
We have to enjoy life
Take a look!
See, it's changing more and more, right?
It's like metabolism
Company always want to have a fresh, red girl at the desk and in the elevator
So they want us to quit at the right time
What does it mean to work hard for a lifetime?
I can't just say that so easily
There are many kids who say things like Sayuri-chan
Women are always looked down upon.
I wonder if that's true. But more than that, isn't it better if we can just live happily in the end?
This guy is kind of nice, huh?
Oh, you're terrible.
You think so?
Wow, this person is famous in our section.
I see this person's face even at my place
Many women come to see this man.
They have bad taste.
Who?
I just saw someone who looked fun.
Ah, if I had someone like that, I would quit the library too
Oh, are you still going to that place?
Life is dry, so
I'm going to seek some moisture
Aren't you going to start again, Sayori-chan?
Isn't there someone you like over there?
No way.
Really?
That's suspicious
Oh my god.
work work
Welcome,Next, we are at the front of the easy order section for sportswear on the 3rd floor
Well then
December 7th, 10th year of Bunsei
Kagoshima, facing the smoking Sakurajima, is warm and tropical even in winter
Under the sunlight,
it showed a lively atmosphere typical of a castle town with 720,000 koku from the Satsuma domain
In Kajimachi, by the banks of the Kamizukigawa flowing through this town,
It was on this day that Nissan raised its voice,
Responsible for the military force during the Meiji Restoration
It was Takamori Saigo from Nanshu
At that time, the Saigo family's household was made up of old book collectors
In Satsuma....
This is Mr. Sato's,right?
His voice is loud, though
He's speaking a bit fast.
That's right
I don't mean to read slowly
Take in the meaning of the words
I think that will bring out more flavor, don't you think?
I'm really sorry
You don't have to apologize
Next, let's have Wakatsuki-san come over
Please
Studio4 has been empty.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting
No, it was nice to see how the photographers have been studying after such a long time
It made me feel a bittersweet emotion
Thinking that I was like that at first too
Everyone makes progress quickly
It's impressive that this is a free newspaper for those with poor eyesight, but what is this?
Look at this.
What's this?
This is a letter of concern for you
From Fukushima Prefecture
Thank you always.
Since I came as a bride and had children
I have struggled a lot since becoming a blind person
I asked neighborhood child to write this.
I can't read Braille no matter how much I practice.
I enjoy listening radio.
My son bought me a tape recorder.
These days, listening to Matsuno-san's voice is my greatest joy
Okamoto Kanoko: Flowers are strong
The first reading will be by Kuniko Matsuno
The murky water in the glass box filled with blue mud has turned leaden,
and the two calico goldfish that had been swimming splendidly until now sink in unison, sensing the weight of the atmospheric pressure
As if deliberately aligned, the two faces
The reading directed this way is by Kuniko Matsuno
The stagnant water in the glass box filled with blue mud has become cloudy and leaden, where the two calico Matsuno-san had been swimming splendidly until now
What amazing progress!
Thanks to you.
Because you made an effort a lot.
But I feel I'm at my limit, and I would like you to make a time for me.
What can I do to make more progress from here on?
I would like you to teach me slowly
Well, I have nothing more to teach you
That's not true.
I have some recording work to do now.
It's for the dubbing of an American TV movie
If I try that too
It's quite interesting, you know
Well then.
16 yen, 88yen, 55 yen, or 87 yen
250 yen
I'll take 250 yen
Thanks.
Hey, what's up, Secchan?
Hey, Let's go for drive next day off
Wow, that's wonderful!
Who's going?
I heard that Tomiza borrowed a friend's car
It's me, right?
It's you, right?
Then, Nami-chan
and Ohara-san from the sales floor.
Aren't you all lovers?
That's right
So you should bring someone too
I can't
I don't have anyone with me
Anyone is fine, a man... hey, take a look behind you for a second
The manager is glaring at you
Be careful.
How about Kawashima at the paper sales section?
No, he's not getting married next month
Is that guy already sold?
How about him?
Who?
The person in charge at Otomoya.
Ah, Takei-san, that's good. Well then, let's discuss the details later
Ah,I'll have this kinpira.
I'll this tsukudani
Hold on please.
Oh, it's already been 20 minutes
Were there someone?
No.
Can anyone recognize who I am?
I'm glad he didn't see my face.
Excuse me earlier.
Women do their skin care when they are in love or when bored, right?
Well, I guess it's more likely when I am bored
In my case.
my next day off is my birthday
Would you like to have a meal together?
Huh?
I'll make a reservation, so don't forget. See you later!
This care is pretty good.
the driver is skilled, right?
Of course.
Don't you want to eat a donuts?
Wow, that's wonderful!
If you gain too much weight, I might reconsider my plans.
What do you mean?
I might reconsider my plans to propose to you.
Well then, I'll stop.
This one is delicious!
It smells good and looks tasty.
Is it still not ready?
Yes, it's done! Oh, thank you!
Pass me the source.
It seems the tart has baked a bit
Thank you for waiting
Yes, it's done, right?
This looks delicious.
Here you go
Here.
How about this?
Yeah, Takei-san, you should eat too
You don't have to hold back
I'll take a bite too
it's delicious.
Please help yourself if you'd like
I'll take some
I'll take some too.
it's so tasty.
Can I have some too?
Please.
I guess the only meal for Pikupiku is rice balls, huh?
We should have brought dessert after the meal.
I bought these from the Arctic corner in the basement of the store, Please take it.
I really love juice.
Oh, it's a opposite, isn't it?
You seem to be common, but you're quite considerate
Really.
Take that juice.
I heard those two are getting engaged soon
They are in love too
Is that so?
Do you see anyone?
I really don't have that much free time
Are you a workaholic?
Not really, but I was surprised too
What is it?
You really are a homely person; they say that good cooks
Homely women are no longer in fashion.
Why is that?
Because electric appliances have advanced
A man can handle small things, right?
That's why women with glamorous bodies are considered valuable
That's not true
I generally don't like tall women that much
That's disgusting
Was it a bother to invite you today?
Not at all, it was an honor to go for a drive with everyone
You must be very considerate of everyone, right?
It's a strange to  think about The relationship between department stores and wholesaler.
I'm young but my way of thinking is a bit old-fashioned.
Do my friends often tell me that.
But I have lived my life humbly in my own way
That's quite plain and realistic
But for me, it was an enjoyable holiday
I can't believe I can talk to you like this so slowly
I had fun too
I wonder what everyone is doing on this holiday.
Sorry for making you wait.
Sayuri-chan
Who are you going to meet?
I'll meet a new friend.
handsome guy?
More than you.
Excuse me.
handsome guy?
More than you.
He's a bit of a tough opponent.
It's not just a little thing, you know?
You should not definitely get married.
it's boring.
Oh, sorry to keep you waiting.
I had a meeting for the fashion show.
I was kept waiting by a boy for the first time or anything
It's not like I'm a cute boy.
I'm already 32, you know
Hahaha, you are an old man,
Sorry.
Who's he?
Me? Nice to meet you, I'm Keiichi, 22, Sayuri's friend.
I guess you can go home now
Is that so? Well then,
I'll call you again later
He's quite an unusual friend, isn't it?
Hey, Sayuri-chan, I know I'm being persistent, but...
Once a woman gets married, that's the end of it
Oh, I'm sorry,
He follow me around
Is it really fun to play with a kid like that?
Old man is more interesting.
Well, at least you have to be someone like me to be considered charming as a man
Ah, this is a celebration
It's just a small token,
I'm really touched
I received a present from Miss Department Store.
Miss Marutaka Department Store?
I've thought that for a while
Hehe, it's quite extravagant.
This is awesome.
but if you like it, then go for it
I'm happy.
it has good taste and it's cheap too
Oh, you have a bad mouth.
It comes up in conversations between my aging parents
Many names that I heard and remembered since childhood came to mind
Marriages between families of equal status held significant importance in their minds
A major event in the national society
It carried a similar level of importance
They have never seen their faces
They spoke as if they knew people very well
You did a great job!
To put it nicely
So you want to add a bit more intonation
Well then, thank you very much for today, and good job everyone
Oh, today wasn't your recording day, was it?
it's my regular day off
I came to visit a friend's house nearby, so I thought I'd visited.
I was wondering if you were free, you know?
I'm available today, though
Is something wrong?
Oh, I asked you the other day, didn't I?
I asked you to give me some advise.
It's not that I'm going to do it
Well then, let's hear your story
Let's have a meal together.
I'm so happy.
Matsuno-san, can you drink?
Yes little.
Well then, let's drink first.
Teacher.
This is a call from your home, sir
Excuse me for a moment.
Here.
Hello? Oh, it's me, huh?
Do you have a fever?
How much?
You probably caught a cold
Did you call a doctor?
Well, anyway, I'll be home soon, so just rest
Hmm, is someone unwell then?
Yes, it seems my wife has caught a cold
She says she has a fever of 38.5 degrees
I'm sorry, but...
Could you please do it next time?
Yes, please do.
I will treat you.
Excuse me.
His wife is ill?
That's what he says
What kind of person is your teacher's wife?
I hear she's a very beautiful person
That sounds about right.
But
But, what happened?
Well, there's a bit of a reason for that
I feel sorry for the teacher as well
This is a small amount
They only accept half of it
It's going to sell out,
but I don't know why
When it comes to that Nakayama
This kind of thing happens often Lately.
That's strange.
even French salad
I was pushed back halfway, you know
It's getting a bit hot and if I get pushed back, I won't have anything to throw away.
That's a problem.
It can't be helped
it suits you
Starting today, it's time
for a change of clothes.
It's clean and very nice
I'm shy.
What's going on with you?
Please go home early after handing out your work
Sorry.
Ah, you too.
Go home
I'm sorry
Hi.
Is it break time now? Want to check out the dressing room?
It's interesting, Their facial expressions are like those of other people
You have a face like a beauty of the world, but in the dressing room...
They eat a baked sweet potato
Really?
see you.
Next please.
You're much more beautiful than the model
You are good at flattery
Really.
I really do love you, I love you so much
Sorry.
Welcome.
How much?
Thank you very much.
French salad 200G
No, let's skip the French salad and go for meatballs instead
What?
What's the hell?
Do you dislike that?
Hey, what's wrong?
What's with that attitude towards the customer?
Call chief.
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, I'm here, yes, yes, hey
What's wrong?
I haven't done anything.
Your employees are very rude.
I can change the order
I am the one who pays.
I'm sorry about that
You don't educate her enough.
Say your name
Fujita, you should apologize
Come on, say something
I'm sorry..
Fujita
Is your name Fujita?
Her name is Setsuko Fujita
I've never seen such a stubborn girl
That's why the young people these days are no good
I sincerely apologize
Please ensure proper supervision going forward
I apologize
I am very sorry
Thank you very much
Why didn't you apologize?
I can't believe you managed to last until today with that
This is a issue about the entire Marutaka department store.
But, but I haven't done anything wrong
There's no such thing as bad or crap
That kind of attitude has been taken into consideration
What is it?
Basically, you're quite cheeky
Don't cry here.
Get lost.
What are you doing?
I’m sorry.
The customer started making excuses.
And then, together with Nakayama-san, they get angry at Secchan
Right in front of everyone
Apologize or whatever
He cursed her harshly.
It's no surprise that Secchan can't hold back anymore with this
I wish everyone would just boycott that supervisor
As for the supervisor,
He doesn't like Setsu-chan getting along with the store clerk at the wholesaler
You didn't know that?
So, he send back Mr. Takei's items
he treats you badly like he did earlier
It must be something unpleasant for the wholesaler and the female clerk to get along well
That's just how it is, isn't it?
In this Marutaka department store, the men here are of a lower status compared to the fishmongers
It's an outdated feeling to say it's outrageous
I see, I had no idea.
If that's the case, Setchan, you too, going forward,
It's a bit tough, isn't it? you have to pursue a love that crosses social classes,
but he's a good person
Setchan's partner
Really?
Oh no, if I do this, I'll be accused again
Gofukubu is nice, isn't it?
The food department doesn't have time to be messing around
I somehow feel a surge of fighting spirit
I'll fight against such outdated ways of thinking
That's the spirit!
But you were dreaming of a romantic love
You've become quite realistic again
You've found love close to home, haven't you?
That's why I told you I like to take care of
It's such a backlash
But once I start stepping into real life and living,
there's no room for dreaming or longing
It might be sad,
but that just means you've become an adult
What do you think about your dating.
It's not big deal.
Just for some reason
Seeing each other every day makes the wait feel so long
Looking forward to meeting again the next morning
It is a sign of the first phase of a perfect romance
You're experiencing it too, even if you try to hide it, it's not working.
with the teacher from the library.
That person has a wife, you know
I understand your feelings. if you were as smart and reliable as you are
Young men might be unreliable for you.
All the good looking men over 30 are married.
This is a dilemma.
I don't understand; I want to work equally with men without losing out, but then again...
Women really have to get married, don't they?
I feel like I don't really understand true happiness
It's true, it's really a bit of a dilemma
Is Matsuno-kun not here?
Yes
So you were here after all
There is a customer who wants to meet you.
We were all searching for you together, you know
You're actually not very enthusiastic about work
Oh, I properly got the manager's permission
There's no such thing as permission
Leaving the sales floor for more than 40 minutes due to specifications is negligence of duty
Hurry up.
I'm going soon!
He is neither the boss nor the chief.
I won't let someone like that scold me
That person always fights with you.
He's annoying.
there's nothing we can do about it if they've taken a break for more than half an hour
It's true that you're the one at fault
Oh, I came to comfort you
I will work hard and confidently fall in love with Takei-san
What about that person?
Does he do his job properly?
It's frustrating, but I can't complain about it
I won't lose to someone like that
It's that attitude that allows someone to make a claim
You need to fulfill your responsibilities completely first
Come on, cheer up!
It's like you suddenly became energetic
It's almost as if I'm the one being comforted
Let's leave.
Are you excited?
A little bit
wow that was amazing, kiss scene.
Where are we going?
Dancing? Hey, or
I don't want to, I'm going home
Hey, can you not call me from now on?
Huh? Why?
I want to end things with you today.
Are you getting married?
I have too many boyfriends
Organize everything
I want to clearly decide on one person
In other words, that might be how it turns out
Well then, goodbye.
Oh, I'm shocked.
Thank you for visiting today
Let me introduce everyone
This is Mitani-kun, who will be taking care of us as a temporary staff member starting today
Thank you for your support and I look forward to working with you
Thank you for visiting us today
Did manager say something to you?
There was a hair in foods
What?
We take hygiene very seriously
I said that couldn't be the case
I was thoroughly scolded for talking back
That's just harassment.
They say there was some harassment from the customers at first, but...
It's not like I'm going to show that Letter
Even when I ask which food, they don't say anything specific
It's terrible to make things up,
okay, I'll do it. I'm sorry
Well then
Takei-san. Please don't get discouraged
It's okay,
I'll take two of this
I'll have these two shiitake mushrooms
Please wait a moment
Since those are fresh, please take care of them
Could you take a look at this for me?
Could you please hurry up with this?
Please take care of this
Do you think this would suit me?
That's the intention
Thank you for waiting
Thank you!
Wait, wait, what do you mean this is 5,500 yen?
Last year when I bought it, it was over 10,000 yen
It seems like buying it early is a loss
Silk is a living thing
It has a lifespan, and if left alone, it will deteriorate
After one year passes,It can't be helped.
That's ridiculous.
I'm sorry.
Shall we go with that wrapping?
Let me take a look a little longer
Please
I see, I will accompany you
That's enough, I don't have any other favorites
Please just this one
Yes, that will be 4500 yen
Excuse me.
Well, there is a Dyeing around here
If you could come again tomorrow,
I can prepare a better product for the same price,
What do you think?
Then please do that, I ask you
Thank you for your continued support
I might be meddling again and get scolded
I've changed my opinion of you little
Oh, when I noticed it, I tried to catch her right away, but I was surprised
You're so great.
I've also changed my opinion of you little
She tried to shoplift
I don't want to end up in a situation where I'm pushing something on her
I am struck by your way of doing things
I've just taken one step forward
so I guess we've improved a little
So, I suppose this match ends in a draw, one-on-one
Well, I'll let you have it, ah
That's right, next we have the electrical appliances, records, and beauty salon on the 7th floor.
I'm about to switch soon
Well then, let's have some tea on the rooftop
Okay
thank you for waiting
Here's 7th floor
I'll be waiting for you
Please
Thank you for your hard work
Hey, do you want to eat ice cream?
Please eat
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Oh, Ryoko, could you come here for a moment?
Please, I'm begging you
What's wrong?
I really want a one-hour break
So, can you keep riding in my place during the next break too?
For an hour straight?
I don't want to do that
For the next hour, I'll keep riding. It's not the same, right?
I'm counting on you, okay?
It can't be helped. What's wrong?
What is it? Sayuri-chan has some casual clothes.
I took a break and asked for a change.
Well, just take a look, it's terrible.
Is she wearing nail polish?
Red is not allowed
She's so selfish,
Sayuri-chan, You can't wear red nail polish.
It's just during break time, so it's a nuisance, isn't it?
It's bad.
We received a letter of complaint from a customer.
It's generally too flashy
Please.
let's treat you to some anmitsu at the cafeteria
That's fine
You don't have to go that far
It's a world where everything is about service
Ah
I apologize for the inconvenience
I apologize for this inconvenience
Well then, go ahead
Secchan.
Sayuri-chan?
Are you off today?
I'm changing during my break and pretending to be a customer
It would be a big deal if you got caught.
There's no way they'd figure it out.
I just ran into the manager on the fourth floor
He didn't notice
More importantly, what happened to you?
You've been doing something like gymnastics since earlier
When I'm in the basement
I suddenly want to breathe the air on the rooftop
On top of that, I'm fighting right now, aren't I?
Are you fighting?
In any workplace
There are still old customs and social hierarchies, aren't there?
I refuse to be defeated by such antiquity, even if it means death
Well then, bye
She's in love right now
That's why she's so enthusiastic about it
What about you?
Me? I've broken up with all my boyfriends
for you
Poor men
Hey? Yeah?
I don't know why, but
I'm starting to not understand you a little bit
What is it?
Because most boys, after they start dating,
after a while, they ask for marriage
He will definitely say it
But you know,
ah, it's already summer, right?
It's a scorching summer
, it's a blazing love
It's a kiss of fire
Matsuno-kun! Huh?
Are you going home now?
Yes.
Hey, could you hang out with me for a bit?
Actually, I want to make up
Even though you're a woman....sorry
You really work hard, don't you?
I just got a little fired up
I'm also igniting my fighting spirit for you
In other words, even though you're a rookie, sorry...
You are a new employee but you work very hard.
I have a bit of a scheduling conflict today
Are you going on a date?
I'm busy every Wednesday.
so can we do it another time?
Let's do that, then goodbye
Goodbye
Today our worker actually brought a magazine to the sales floor
I scolded her quite a bit
But it's an amazing article, the sexual manifesto of rebellious single women
The complete denial method cannot be tolerated by her
Have you read all of that?
No, this is for educational purposes
I just looked at the table of contents
It's quite tough, isn't it?
Managing young girls
She is quite flashy, isn't it?
She's the girl known as Maki from the elevator
Is her nail red?
It's a nail polish
Huh? There's a rumor about it.
I wonder where she's going.
Well, of course it's a date
When they reach a certain age
Are they going to date every night?
When it's just one person
There's no problem, but
She went into the pharmacy, right?
I wonder what she went in to buy
I can't believe it's not a Contraceptives
I think it might not be
I have a responsibility to investigate this
How about this?
I've never used this here, but does it work?
It works really well
I wonder if it can be wiped clean right away?
Yes.
Please give me some absorbent cotton
absorbent cotton?
The matter is serious, you know.
You
Oh, manager
what are you going to buy?
Surely this isn't some inappropriate drug, right?
This and absorbent cotton, right?
What are you talking about?
This is a nail polish remover
Look, my nail polish is this dirty, isn't it?
That's why I thought I'd take it off
I'll need 200 yen
Are you feeling unwell?
I'm so tired that I can't recover anymore
Is that so?
He must be tired.
Please introduce him to some good medicine.
Well then, I'll go ahead
Fatigue is not good
Life should be enjoyed
This means maintaining good health for a long time
In other words, Health Lounge is full of energy, red and vibrant
How much?
3000 yen
Don't you have a smaller one?
We also have portable options.
For 500 yen
I'll wrap it
I bumped into a customer during the day and my clothes got stained with red nail polish.
Today, I really can't stand the red nail polish
Who is it?
I can't believe it's so serious, but thank you for waiting
At our department store, purchases are 10% off
Thank you very much
Okamoto Kanoko Hana is strong
the third.
This is Kimiko Matsuno
If I walk through the town with a red flower in hand,
There should be no fear of strength
The practice based on the four sufferings written by my friend is
Rather than including flowers,
I desperately bit into the flowers and clung to them
It's hard
It's okay, even if I'm that bad?
it's fine, it's fine. Everyone starts like that.
Can I fix my accent?
I'm serious, what I mean is the accent
It's about making it your own personality
Thank you very much
Thank you
Teacher.
I'm sorry about last day
How have you been, madam?
Yes, she got better.
I am free tonight
Shall we have a chat?
Well, please
I believe that progress is proportional
to how long the hesitation lasts
So, Matsuno-san's recent worries are probably a sign of a big leap forward
Don't rush
It would be good to take your time and confront the true nature of your worries
I have become completely confused
In such times, you try to listen to as many voices as possible
It's about listening to the radio
I have students who say the same thing as you.
could you meet him just once?
Oh, I would love to meet him
Who?
my wife
If I talked about you...
She says she really wants to meet you.
How about it?
Let's go to my apartment from here
I will come
Now, let's go
Did you drink it?
Well, I already...
What happened?
hey, what's wrong?
Give me another shot.
I apologize for the inconvenience, but
I'm home.
we currently have a guest
Come in.
Welcome.
Go ahead, please
Well then, this is wife.
Here, this is Matsuno from Marutaka Department Store, whom I always talk about
Nice to meet you
thank you for coming
Have a seat.
let me make you some tea
That was just perfect
I was doing some voice recording
Shall I let you listen?
Oh, please do let me hear it
I'm a bit embarrassed to say this, but
Your tea is over here
Lately, nothing seems to be going well for me
Me too
I've already washed the pot in the sink.
the Air India flight from Calcutta lands in Hong Kong,
due to weather conditions
The final route to Tokyo from there will not be taken
I wonder if the author is being a bit too modest
Your way of acting like you've got it all together is showing too much on the surface
You think so?
I wonder if that's true; until recently, I was being too dramatic
I'm becoming too much like a noble
And then, I should stand a little more modestly
I'm really sorry for not being able to get into the groove at all
I'll handle it.
That's fine, I'm used to it.
since the time we got married
When this person starts doing it,
I felt bad and helped out, but...
These days, I've decided not to worry about it
Oh, is that so?
Could you please let me know if you notice anything?
Oh, I can't critique people.
Because My husband tells me you are wonderful.
No way.
I really don't understand this at all, and it's quite troubling
Well, if you overdo it, it's too much; if you hold back too much.
There's only way to keep going back and forth like that
Eventually, I think you'll create something that fits your style.
I'm really sorry for the trouble.
especially since you came all this way
I'm sorry for making you listen to something so poorly done
No, not at all
Would you like a drink?
Oh, that's great!
Matsuno can drink too.
Oh,Don't worry.
Oh, then shall I add some whiskey?
Oh, that sounds good
Oh, that's right, there's some water over here.
You want some water?
Oh, I'll go get it.
Don't worry.
She's been doing that since she was a kid
But surprisingly, she is quite okay with it
I've gotten used to her too
It's been 5 years since we got married
Was she a student of you?
Yes, she showed up at the lab.
I was surprised when you said you wanted to help the people of blind.
Here it is.
I was born with these legs
Since I was small, I believed I was the most unfortunate person in the world.
Would you like some cheese?
Ah, I'll go cut it
There were times when I resented my parents and envied the world
However, in some magazine...
I realized how much more unfortunate those who are blind are compared to someone like me
I felt as if I had awakened from a long period of confusion
And then I flew to the library.
Well, it's a nice story
Is it a love marriage with the teacher?
It was not like that.
It was a romance between a couple with a disabled spouse and an unknown voice actor
I guess it's called helping each other when people have the same opinions about life
I've completely relied on this person because of this
I want to do well even just with this job
It's quite difficult, isn't it?
I'm glad I could drop by today
is that so?
I feel like I've also cooled down from my confusion
What are you hesitating about?
Both work-related doubts and
life doubts surround me All doubts
It's like you're speaking as if you were the Buddha
so let's not toast
Well, I will take this
I will take this.
I hope that Matsuno's life is filled with happiness
for the beautiful couple of you
Thank you
cheers
Hey,What's wrong?
Why are you laughing?
My nail
Section chief
Liver medicine
What do you mean?
Is that some kind of three-generation story?
She is drunk
It's the mastermind
Yes I am.
That's good.
I have something I want to say after drinking
Alright, let's listen
But first, let's make a toast
Okay
Make another one.
Are you okay?
I'm fine
Then make it
Mr. Hata
What do you think of me?
I like you, you're cute
Really?
You're getting along.
I'll get lost.
Hey, are you teasing me?
You're so drunk.
I'm fine
Not a problem
Then let's stand up.
Look
I'm sorry.
Do you really like me?
I want to eat you up
so let's get married.
Alright, then tonight is the wedding
Driver, please take us to Yokohama.
You won't regret it?
Alright, I'll go as far as I can, you know
Because I like you.
Hey, I love you
Is it okay if I tell everyone that I'm marrying you?
I don't mind
I'm happy
I'm sure everyone will laugh
Why?
I have a wife.
You were lying, weren't you? You deceived me
I didn't say I'm single.
Then marry me
I have a wife.
Break up.
we have kids too
Child?
I told my wife not to birth
My wife just stepped on it without permission
Next year, they're going to elementary school
Get out, get out!
I don't wanna see your face anymore.
If we leave now, we can make it in time
Get out.
Well then, I guess I'll take my leave
Then I'll take care of the bill
Wait for me, Hata-san
Marriage is boring.
Stay like that.
It's more fun.
Takei-san, what a fool
If you like someone, you should just say so
But there's nothing we can do about it
In the atmosphere of our sales floor.
I don't have any grand hopes.
I just want to grasp a tiny bit of happiness
But isn't that the most difficult thing of all?
I really think so just like this
How about you?
I liked him even more after learning that his wife has a bad leg
But I no longer have any ambitions
Have you given up?
Rather than saying I've given up, I want to gently cherish those feelings
It was a good experience
I feel like my life has become a bit deeper
How about the rookie?
We did reach a sort of reconciliation, though
I got caught drinking beer with Mr. Tsuruoka.
He seems to be sulking and isn't talking to me
so there's no need to make excuses.I'll just leave him be
So, he finally fell in love with you, huh?
Is that so?
Of course, it's definitely jealousy.
What's wrong?
Who is the man?
Isn't that someone from the marketing department?
That looks fun
Are you jealous?
Aren't you going to swim?
I'm no good at this
Why?
She can't swim
Then why did you come?
Is it not okay to come?
I didn't say it was not okay, how about swimming?
Huh? Well then, I'll go swim and do some reconnaissance
Don't do that.
Leave it to me.
Are you going home?
Did you mark it? Oh, what's wrong?
Oh, aren't you going to swim, section chief?
I can't swim, you know
Oh, so you're not swimming either, just like me?
You can't either?
What about you, Ubukata-kun?
He's swimming
You weren't together?
Why is that?
You see, Ubukata-kun...
He's praising you
He said that you did well for a woman
Please tell Ubukata that
I absolutely hate the phrase 'for a woman' more than anything in this world
Well, this is rude, but I should say it clearly
Well, since both of you are well-regular employees, I hope you can get along as much as possible
Or maybe Ubuakata-kun already feels like you are good friends in his heart.
This is just a feeling based on years of experience.
Are you okay?
No, it's nothing serious
Oh, it's you, Ubukata-kun
What's wrong?
He got stung by a jellyfish
Oh, could you bring me some water?
Is it really that bad?
No, it's just a little swollen
Did you get stung by a jellyfish?
Look, it's so red and swollen, does it hurt?
Water, water.
Oh no, this is terrible. Kikko, please cool it down.
Everyone, let's leave this to Kinko and go swimming.
we do that, then, Mazuro, I'll leave it to you
I'll take care of it.
No.
Come on.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry
No, it's okay.
I heard from Fujita-kun
I heard you had someone you liked
Yes.
it's the person from the other day?
I heard he has a wife
Yes
I heard you gave up, right?
No.
I've come to respect him more and like him even more
Oh, are you angry again?
No, that's quite different from what I heard.
But I've really come to like Ubukata-san a lot
Really?
Do you want to drink ?
let's get along from now on
We'll compete fiercely.
there's no way I'll lose to you.
I'm going to do my best, and I won't lose either
To make up
Don't use the word for women
I won't say that.
I acknowledge your abilities
Cheers!
By the way, what does that person do?
Oh, didn't you ask Secchan?
Well then, let's not talk about that for a while
Let me know when the time comes to talk about it
promise me
I will promise you.
How is it? Feels good, right?
if you had just let me do it from the start, it wouldn't have been a big deal
Really.
Hey, Mitani
what are you doing?
I'm making that 100-gram package
Look closely, isn't there two pieces?
That's a problem
I'm sorry
Do you know how many grams this weighs?
I have no idea.
Check it.
it's not just one piece, it's a whole set.
What's wrong?
She's wasting the slip.
How much?
It's 105 grams
How many pairs?
There are 30 pairs
You can have 30 pairs each day
If you overuse our slip,
Confirming 105 grams is not accounted for,
If you continue that for a year,
How much loss will we incur?
I'm sorry.
If you use our slip too much,
It's not a good idea to think about making a profit from it.
Director...Don't say like that
please cut it out, Nakayama
What?
That's just too much.
She just did it carelessly, that's all
Can't you tell just by looking at that much?
Isn't it okay not to raise your voice?
Does Mr. Nakayama have some grudge against our company?
If you have any complaints, please say
I have a lot to say to you
Bring Department cheif.
Mitani-san, please stop crying.
Come on, Mitani-kun, it's okay, it's okay
Cheer up, okay?
Alright, let's go, okay?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Takei-san
Aren't you coming anymore?
Maybe even if I wanted to come, I can't
Thank you all for your support for a long time.
Well then, let's go
Alright, that's fine
Setchan, boss is watching you
Setchan
So, did that person get fired?
The next day, the executive of Ootomiya
He brought another staff member
He bowed to Chief Nakayama and introduced him.
So, are you planning to give up on that person?
That's not it!
So what should I do?
That's why I'm consulting you, who has rich experience, right?
Just take action and do it
In what way?
Make a phone call
From the woman?
That's right, anyway, you should find out what the other person thinks of you
If he doesn't think much of it
You should organize it
Now, hurry up and make that call
Wait, now?
Yeah.
I'm still eating soba.
It's not important.
Come on, hurry up!
It's the time when your life will be decided, you know
Yeah.
Oh, is it already done?
not yet
That spot is free
I see.
Um? Sorry, hello there!
Here.
You look so happy, don't you?
You have a familiar face
Is that so? I'm hungry, though
Did you see this?
What?
It's the brochure for the Conference,
Already talking about autumn?
Well, I'm already 22 this autumn.
They are a whole new design and layout
They have a good reputation.
So what?
This was designed by Hata, right? From the advertising department.
Is that so?
Yeah, it looks good. You have a great sense of style.
When are you getting married?
With Hata
does that mean I have to get married?
For sure
If I can enjoy my youth
That's enough for me now
What's wrong?
Did you talk?
He wasn't there.
Oh no.
Well, it's now 6 o'clock, time to close
We look forward to your visit again tomorrow
Thank you, thank you.
By the way,
Yes, we do. I'm sorry about that
I’m sorry.
How much?
It's a 10% discount off 700 yen
The register is already closed.
so I'll just leave the money with you
Is that so?
Oh, that's fine
Thank you very much
You're welcome.
hey you?
Where did you take this?
I bought this book at the bookstore
Let me see it
Why isn't it wrapped?
I said it's fine as it is because I'm in a hurry
Where is the purchase receipt?
The register was closed
I just left the money
Let's ask them.
Come.
OK
the book department
It's not like stealing this book is a big deal
I can't help it, why can't people be trusted like that?
I wonder if everyone has gone home
Anyway
I'll take care of this book
it's a bit troublesome
I am doing tape recordings for blind people.
Starting today, I will be reading Tanizaki's Genji
Is it part-time work
It's social conservatism.
It's free
To use the recording studio, there is a schedule
I have to go by 7 PM tonight
for any reason
Rules are rules, you know
I can't give you this book
What's your name?
Please tell me your name
Matsuno Kimiko
thank you for your hard work
Matsuno-kun, what's wrong?
You were quite late, weren't you?
I got caught by the security staff.
By the security staff?
I bought a book and didn't wrap it, so I was suspicious.
He's making fun of me
If that happens, there's nothing we can do about it
That's their job, after all
Shall we grab a meal?
Will you treat me?
Well, sorry, but please pay on a taxi with that money
Could you take me to Shinjuku?
To the library?
Huh? How do you know that?
I heard it from Fujita-kun
Come on, let's hurry up
We made a promise that doesn't hold anything back.
If there's even one thing I don't understand about you,
It can no longer be left as it is
I'm impressed
I knew it was you after all
And the sense of competition has become even stronger
Ah, driver, please turn at the next corner
Oh, teacher
Good evening.
He?
Yeah, I've said it many times, but
I really love him.
But more than that, I've come to like your wife
I feel embarrassed.
I guess it's like how female students admire their high school teachers.
It's not like that.
But it's true that I've become somewhat immune to love and stronger in life, so well then
Thank you very much
Ubukata,
I've been feeling great lately Life is really enjoyable because I'm thinking of working with you as equals
I have a strong sense of competition
Could you give me that?
please wait a moment
Please wait a moment.
Setchan, phone call.
I'm sorry
From who?
Are you getting married next month?
Yes, congratulations.
Hello, this is Fujita
Huh? Takei?
Is that you, Takei-san?
Yes, next, next, next, this is okay, right?
Yes, next, yes, next, yes, this is okay, yes, next
I will deliver it right away once it's ready
Please
Thank you very much
I was scolded a lot
As you said, I was wrong too.
The reason companies don't trust their female employees is because there are problems with them.
Why?
Women tend to quit work as soon as they get married and are not enthusiastic about their work.
You are making fun of women again.
Of course you are the exception.
I forgive you
What's going on with you?
Ah! While being too unfriendly is a problem, being too friendly is also not good
Huh?
But you know, times have changed
Actually, I also fell in love and got married to my wife at this department store
I was looked at with disdain by everyone
Well, if it's a healthy relationship now,
no one will blame you for it, right?
So please make sure to do it properly
Manager think of us like a lover.
I think so too
It's still early
I'm sorry for being late
It's really crowded, you know
I went back here from Ikebukuro in just one day
Ikebukuro?
I'm currently being sent to a department store in Ikebukuro
So, it's a demotion, isn't it?
I messed up at Marutaka Department Store
That's just too much, I'm really sorry
I also have some responsibility in this matter
No, that's not it. More importantly, I actually have something important to talk about
What?
Anyway, let's eat something
Please eat what you like
I withdrew some savings today, so
I'm fine, really.
I don't like luxury
Then let's take advantage of this kind offer and go somewhere that suits us
A modest place
Here it is.
I remember the picnic from some time ago
Ina-san will marry next month, right?
I heard she's quitting today only
What about Obara-san and Nami-san?
Getting hotter and hotter
It feels like they are on fire.
Do you miss them?
Well, this isn't something to talk about while stuffing my face with rice balls
I had something to say too
But I'll wait until I hear your story.
I'm curious, please tell me, Fujita-san
It's not something to talk about while eating rice balls, but
But I'll talk.
It's good because it's realistic
I liked you, Takei-san
I liked you so much that I couldn't help it
Well then, I'll talk too
I like you too, but I can't get enough of it
This is yummy.
Please eat more
I couldn't help but want to see you, so I came out
Really?
It's true
like at Marutaka Department Store
It's actually a boring place
I mean, it's really enviable how they keep saying to increase sales all year round
Please take a seat
Sales don't just increase recklessly, you know
I was quite energetic back in my twenties, you see
I keep thinking of various new methods
I gave a lot of ideas to my boss.
They're really conservative
everything was Canceled.
It's so ridiculous that I won't do anything
That's the safest option
Shall we leave?
Check please.
I'll be in the underground sales area for life
No, that's not the case
If I had a wife from a president or an executive lineage,
Then surely I could have risen to the top
If I marry someone from the sock department, it will be the end for me, and I will regret it
just give me some alcohol
Isn't it enough already?
I'm just waiting to die quietly, whether it's through retirement or my last wishes
I'm only 38, really.
It's a quiet place, isn't it?
Just a little further after crossing that bridge,
Mr. Nakayama is a pitiful person, isn't he?
That's true
The reason he is being mean to us and lashing out is essentially due to his suppressed frustrations.
It's understandable for a salaryman to be weak against the strong, but it's wrong to be strong against the weak
I believe Mr. Takei will surely become great
Even after becoming a section chief, you take good care of the people below you
Since you're a section chief, I'm sure you'll be a very understanding section chief
Fujita.
I don't mind if you just call me by my first name.
then, Setsuko
I have something to talk about
Oh, we didn't just talk to each other a moment ago, did we?
There's another story.
This is exactly what it means to not be able to speak while munching on rice balls
What?
Tell me.
Come on.
Please marry me
I haven't even gone to university
my father dies soon so I took care of my younger brother and sister
As the eldest son, I had to work
Including my salary and everything else,
So far, my savings are about 18,000 yen
To be honest, my current life is tough
But I really want you to become my wife
It's too sudden.
I want to work really hard
When I think of Setsuko-san
I feel restless
So I need to stabilize my feelings quickly
I want to work more and more
Could you please think about it?
And please respond as soon as possible
Takei-san, I'm the same. I want to feel calm too
It's fine if it's just small happiness
I want to drown in that
That's quite a quick reply, but...
I accept your propose.
Setsuko
Huh? Are they still doing it?
Heh, they're really going crazy
Well, I've walked the equivalent of 130 yen in a small taxi
What should we do?
I still want to walk
I'm tired
Well then, let's go
Where to?
We can go a place
Sorry
I'm going to head home now
My child is almost there, but I'm still a parent, you know
I'm worried
I'll go home on foot.
Well then,I'll go ahead. See you!
Matsuno-kun, did you see this month's display?
No.
That must be Hata's.
It's bold, innovative, and overwhelming. I think it would be great to incorporate that kind of sensibility into kimonos.
I feel that kimonos are somewhat different from decorations
There's a longing for the old world behind the desire to wear something as inconvenient and troublesome as traditional Japanese clothing
As civilization develops,
Emotions and atmosphere will disappear, won't they?
You know, I've really felt this after reading the current situation
There are no air conditioning, cars, or jets, nothing at all
Wasn't life more human back in the old days?
Since I'm a woman, I think classic kimono is better after all
I can't express it well, but...
What are you grinning about?
Well, our principles are different, but
Women who speak their minds clearly are wonderful
You made me talk.
Welcome.
Please show me that outfit
welcome
About how many days will it take to finish this cloth?
It will be completed in 5 days
Really? Then please go ahead
Thank you very much.
I will take your measurements
Please come this way.
They'll be dating soon.
What does this mean?
Well, it's nothing
lately it's been getting really extravagant, hasn't it?
Yeah, it's true. We're really in trouble
That's right, it's really something, isn't it?
Have you heard that rumor?
What?
Is that true? That would be annoying, right?
Be quiet.
I don't care if she hears us.
What?
Is that a story that concerns me?
Why don't you just say it clearly If so?
Don't gossip behind someone's back
So, let me say it clearly then
When someone like you is in the elevator,
everyone gets annoyed
Oh, why?
With our salary, there's no way we can afford luxurious clothes like yours
There's no way we can wear that
I heard there's someone working as a call girl among the elevator attendants
Don't you know?
Are you saying that I'm a call girl?
I can't believe you would do something like that
But you know, if you wear heavy makeup like that,
It's only natural to be suspected if you get calls from boys for no reason
That's none of your business
I'm saying this because the problem is no longer just yours
Do you all think I'm just a call girl?
Do you think my presence here is a nuisance?
What do you think?
Ryoko, What do you think?
Well, I understand
but I just wanted to say that
I'm not a call girl or anything like that
But you know, whatever I do,
it's my freedom
I do what I want
This is the publicity department.
Is Hata-chan there?
Hata Hideya?
Did he quit?
When did he quit?
Sayuri?
Oh, are you off today?
No, I'm going home
Oh, leaving early?
No, can Mr. Hata see the store ?
No, not at all lately
Oh, yeah
I heard that the display he set up here this month has been well-received and that a big PR company has recruited him.
Oh, you didn't know that?
Hey, could you please let me work at your shop, Mom?
Am I quitting here too?
Because it's boring, you know
Hello? Is that you, Takei-san?
I'm Setsuko
It's tough
Mr. Nakayama, the supervisor, was hit by a car
I heard he got seriously injured
Aren't you going to visit tonight?
I'll buy some flowers
Then let's meet at the usual place at 6:30
There's no need to go visit someone in the hospital
He's annyoing.
Isn't it just pitiful?
I'll take this
Kimiko
Why are you making such a strange face?
Well, it's because Sayuri-chan is wearing a kimono
Because I saw it for the first time
Surprisingly, it suits you, right?
I heard you started working at a bar?
Yes.
Isn't it interesting?
Well, yeah
It's definitely more thrilling than working part-time as an elevator girl
But how should I put it
It's quite an amazing world, isn't it?
It must be tough, huh?
It's not as easy as everyone thinks
If I want to, I can get money, but...
It seems like the heart is gradually becoming corrupted
I couldn't manage even a day
That's right, it's not suitable for a girl like you
Hehe, but it's a respectable profession for women
Do it properly, okay?
However,
What does 'doing it properly' mean in that world?
I still can't quite grasp it
But anyway, I'll do it. Show me the kimono for business
I'm already a customer, you know
Ah, I see.
Please look around.
Well, I prefer a white background, though
Oh dear, it's a bit dirty
It's dim, so it's fine. I like something extravagant and unnecessary for the store.
What's the budget?
Don't worry, I'll do my best.
Sayuri.
Secchan.
How are you?
Oh yeah.
I have to thank you, right?
I decided to marry Takei-san
Just go for it more and more
Sayuri-chan told you, right?
So it's about one-fifth thanks to you
I'm glad to hear that.
It's time to close.
Be happy.
You too.
Thank you for visiting us today
We sincerely appreciate your various purchases
Thank you very much
It is now 6 o'clock, and it's time to close
We look forward to your visit again tomorrow
Thank you very much
Additionally, the nearby grocery store is open until 6:30 PM, so
please feel free to make use of it
Thank you very much
Thank you
Thank you for your hard work
Yes, thank you for your hard work ahead of me
Yes, thank you for your efforts
Thank you for your hard work
I have a request, Manager
Tell me.
I would like you to officiate the marriage between Matsuno-kun and me
Ubukata-san, aren't you forgetting something important?
What do you mean?
You haven't proposed to me even once yet
Ah, I see.
Then would you marry me?
It's fine, it's fine
Please don't provoke the elderly
Well, I was prepared for it to come around this time
How did you know?
No, it's just a intuition.
After many years of intuition
we don't have high hopes for you as a couple
I believe that a new couple in a new era will surely emerge
Anyway, congratulations
thank you!
Good luck.
Let's create a new couple.
Yes, I absolutely won't lose to you.
I'll continue working even after we get married
The department store, the library, and you all help with housework
I don't want you to be jealous
Please respect my opinion as well
Everything is equal
Everything is a collaboration, okay?
Got it?
I got it, I got it, I got it, I understand
At least let me have the engagement kiss
Well, here? How unsanitary.
How unsanitary?
What’s unsanitary about it?
That kind of thinking is outdated.
That's right?
Is anyone here?
I don't care if anyone here.
THE END