Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
August 15, 1945
the war is over
Manchuria was occupied by the Soviet army and Japanese soldiers were taken prisoner.
The survivors walked south
At this time, the Manchurian people began to rob
Hoodlum Soldier Looting and Pillaging (#8)
Heitai Yakuza Godatsu
Omiya and I kept walking to get back to Japan as soon as possible.
Mr.private first class solider, is it far to Shoukatong?
It takes 20km from here
do we go camping again?
i want to sleep with a woman
Omiya.Japan was lost
Japan was lost but I didn't
They're unlucky even though the war is over
we might get killed
I won't die
I will go back to Japan and enjoy my life
What are you doing?
All pistols stolen
they all robbed
guerrillas did this
He's alive
guerrillas did this?
Omiya!  give him food
they are our food
give him food
he is our mate
Hold on
Hey guys.
Help yourself
1.2.3.4.5
6.7.8.9.10
Damn it.
he took this alone
Shit
they are Japanese
What are they doing?
Who are you guys?
Come here
Hold on
What are you doing?
Come here
Don't order us
We'll shoot unless you listen to me
Attention
We are no longer solider
You dude
the war is over
You're lair
Hold on, Omiya!
We were disarmed.
you have no right to hit us
Mind your mouth
don't you know the information that the war is over?
You are stupid.
it's a conspiracy done by someone
We, the Kwantung Army, will never surrender.
I will fight here until everyone dies
Do it on your own
You bastard!
Omiya!
lock him up
Get in!
Soldiers are active
everything is as you think
let's investigate her
Look at us
Come here
Give me fire
how many Japanese did you kill?
Take off your clothes
Omiya!
Omiya! You awake?
Mr.private first class solider!
It's dirty
We are here
What will happen to us?
They will kill us?
It might be so
how many men have you slept with?
tell me how strong your unit is
tell me
You don't feel hurt?
You have a nice figure
Take off your clothes
she is stubborn
She is strong
What should we do?
Well
I'm starving
Bring me meal
i have no food to give you
you will be killed by a gun
they don't feed us
Hey come in
What?
Oh you guys
Who are you guys?
It's me, you know?
you helped us the other day
Oh you. you look good
Thanks to you
Bring them out
We have canned food.
Really?
Oh yeah
There are many
Sake is also here
We can't hold all
Hey, why you don't help us
Damn it
They have no humanity.
Omiya!
What's wrong?
Stop
Omiya!
I will shoot you if you shoot her
Don't shoot
Omiya!
Let's take a rest here
Be careful
Drink water
She's nice
She got hurt
Does it hurt?
Let her take a rest
Lie down
I found out. She wanna go to toilet
wanna go to toilet?
Let's go
Omiya!
I wanna go too
Here bring me back my memory
It smells good
I will go to watch
She's run away
I helped her, but she didn't thank to me
Mr.private first class solider!
Where's her?
She's gone
She's left this
What should I do about this baby
Leave him here
But
Leave him here.
We can't take care of him
But I can't leave
We don't know he is Japanese or Manganese
He's human
Listen, he will be in danger if he is with us
Do whatever you want.
Mr.private first class solider
She left him. It's none of our business
He's going to die if we leave him
Omiya!
Bring him
We'll take you
Mr.private first class solider!
He looks happy
You're lucky
Don't be shy
you are good at taking care of baby
Don't worry
Leave it to me
You like him now
Hey baby
Omiya!
we must go back to japan
we have to survive
For him too
Let's go back to Japan and live together
good
I'm excited
I will give you a ride on the Sumida River boat in Tokyo.
Omiya!
Come here
What's wrong?
Listen,don't get excited yet.
From now on we will have a hard time
If we deviate on the way, let's meet at SOUKATONG
You don't have to worry
don't talk cold like that
He's crying
What happen?
He needs boob
You are stupid
He needs to piss?
Shit
Good boy
What's this?
Fukagawago?
He is Japanese, not Manchu.
i don't care about his nationality.
He is our baby
yes that's right
Omiya!
What's wrong?
Are you alone?
Where is Mr.private first class solider?
Mr.private first class solider
we are the national liberation army
What is your name?
Arita
Why you are here?
I was on the way to Sokatong
It's a different direction
I lost my way
don't lie
I'm not lying
Don't trick me
where did you hide your luggage?
My luggage??
Yes
What luggage?
Don't pretend you don't know
if you don't tell me i will kill you
Tell me
The Japanese around here must be our enemies.
where did you hide your luggage?
That...
Definitely you know, tell me
Tell me
I can't tell
That $100,000 is our precious war fund.
Tell me
$100,000
Hold on
If you kill me, you don't know where the $100,000 is
Let him go
I wish I could have Omiya here
Hello
What?
You want dollar?
Yes $100,000
I'll give you
Really?
I only tell you the place
$100,000
Let me go
Come
Here
To the right
I am your mate
He is Kato UNIT who abandoned us
he is the man in charge of weapons
So Matsukawa should be here
I found him
Damn it
kato leader is here
It's strange that Matsukawa isn't here
the unit is destroyed.
But he is not here
I'm tired
Drink this
You bastard!
Come here
i hate you guys
You bastard!
Oh my god
Keep him quiet
They will kill us if they find us
No problem
Let's go
Is he dead?
You guys
He's dead
Hold on
I'll beat you
Fuck you
You guys should go to hell
You are alive
baby
Wait
I'll kill you
Don't shoot us
i will give you gold coins
gold coins?
I'll give you half of the $100,000 gold coin
Don't shoot us
What's the gold coins?
We found it. We were going to bring it back to Japan.
But Matsukawa found it
Matsukawa?
we used to work in his unit
He used the Kato Unit to imprison us in the mountains.
you don't have that money right now
we're sure to get them back
We'll find him
I can't count on you
Give me what you have now
Give me
Thank you
See you
Damn it
Take care
Oh my god
Where's Milk?
The Milk is missing
Omiya!
Where are you?
Japanese?
Shoot him
I'm not your enemy.
Throw out your pistol
You're very strong.
I have something to ask you,
Can you come with me?
To where?
There are Sake and women
There is very nice place
There is milk too
You should take off your Japanese soldier's clothes.
you should change your clothes
please wait here for a while
Come
Don't cry
Wait
I have something to ask you, so please come right away.
He's my boss
What can I do for you?
Can you kill him?
i will give you everything you want
I can't help you
My boss can do what he wants
Really?
He can't lie
There is a Japanese named Arita
he is captured by the liberation army.
Can you help him out?
It's easy
He's associated with the Straight Army and the Liberation Army
So can you?
I'll give you this
I don't need it
Damn it
Bet it
You bastard!
you were cheating
If it's Japanese rules you are being killed
Get out!
Good baby
What? Was he kidnapped?
You sure you don't know about the $100,000?
I don't know
Don't pretend you don't know
I don't know at all
If you don't know that, why are you his bodyguard?
I got information that the money is at your club
We were about to fight the boss.
But You sabotaged us.
So you were cheating
We'll give you a chance
I'll count 10
I don't know at all
I see
You wanna say something before you die?
Yes
Tell me
Can you take care the babe if I die?
Ok. He is innocent.
What else?
Arita private first class solider!
See you, baby
Ready?
Ah..You?
I've met you!
I am RAN JJIURAN, a squad leader of the Liberation Army.
Liberation Army
It's been a age
That $100,000 was stolen by the Japanese army
That money is our most precious war fund.
by the Japanese army?
You speak Japanese good
I graduated from school in Japan.
I like Japanese people
But the war changed them
Many Japanese people has been in trouble going back to Japan
We can't get them back to Japan.
This is National policy.
Because That $100,000 was stolen by the Japanese army
You are Japanese.
What do you think about this?
They are just shame of Japanese
You are his bodyguard
What?
Is he?
He's the Matsukawa
You want the money too?
Shut up
I'm not the person
Trust me
Ok wait
I'll get the $100,000 back for you
Wait
I don't lie.
I am Japanese man!
Boss. car is ready
Are you sure going back to Japan?
Yes
It is far. Will you take me too?
I will make you go farther.
You knew I was what kind of man.
I destroyed Kato units
You gonna kill me too?
No one knows about me if I kill you
I'll help you
$100,000 is heavy,isn't it?
You know about it
How much you want?
I want all of them
Matsukawa
Since you are Japanese, use Japanese.
You knew who I was
Yes I knew
I'll take this
You bastard!
You are stupid
Want to fight with me more?
What are you doing?
This is the $100,000 I promised
i don't lie
I'm Japanese man
Get on the truck soon
Mr.private first class solider!
I'll give this back to you
See you
don't have bad dreams
Get on the truck soon
You can't go back to Japan without this truck
Mr.private first class solider!
Omiya!
Mr.private first class solider
He's safe?
Let's go back to Japan together and take a boat on the Sumida River
THE END