Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hoodlum Soldier on the Attack (#7)
Heitai Yakuza Nagurikomi
Move forward! Stop!
We're back!
Attention!
What are you doing,Omiya?
What can I do for you?
I'm asking what are you doing
I had my gun maintenanced in case of an emergency.
You stupid
Omiya! Isogagi!
You guys go to main office to pick up mails
And Kuroiso solider
You go to Ryomatsu with Kamata and Ishino
Transport trucks have arrived after two months.
Something might happen
Leader, I wanna go with them too
You have to listen to me
Bow!
Omiya
Bring something for me
Leave it to me.
Let's go
To Kisaburo Omiya
Hey! Damn it
Can you read for me?
Mikagero Yoshihara.
There is a weird drawing
This is a picture of plum blossoms..
oh from Umeka!
Umeka?
She knows I can't read so she draw
Can you read for me?
Now?
Yeah
Dear sir, it's been a age
I am fine too
Stand up
Look at that
Here is Military office
You should respect the military.
You all read your own letters first. you are too selfish.
Our warriors are waiting for this letter.
I'm sorry
Anyway I need to give you a punishment
Stay and bite
You dude
Leader! I asked him to read the letter.
Hit me only
What's your name?
Kisaburo Omiya
I gonna remember
Omiya
Remember to protect your warriors.
I will
He is very humane.
Next
Here
Go home first
First?
Don't care
Next
I will beat the sergeant
I get it
Inukai sergeant got sick!
Help him
Are you OK?
sergeant!
I will call doctor
Sergeant! Are you OK?
what are the ingredients for tempura?
leave it to me
Come here
Let's go
Let's get them
smells so good
Hey!
what are you guys doing?
Well...
bring it to me later
You get it?
You caught a fish with a grenade, didn't you?
It's against rule
You get it?
Hey!
We'll bring this to you later
Good
I really hate him
It tastes good
do you hate fried fish?
I like it..bit it's smelly
this smells like oil
i will eat this for you
Attention!
Pull your chin, Mizumaki
Number!
1.2.3.4.5.6.7.8.9
Damn it
Number!
1.2.3.4.5.6.7.8.9
What's wrong,Omiya!
What are you doing?
My stomach
i have a stomach ache
Omiya!
You have diarrhea and you are gutless
It can't be helped
I think that fried fish was bad
What do you mean?
nothing
Number again!
1.2.3.4.5
Again
What are you doing?
i have a stomach ache
What's wrong?
I'm back
roll call please
You stupid
Wait, I'll go to bathroom too
I'll go to bathroom too
The oil for fried fish was castor oil.
castor oil?
you should have told me that sooner
i just noticed it
Again?
I'll go to bathroom
I'm waiting!
I'll get out now
Soritani,This is the leader's exclusive restroom.
I'm sorry, I couldn't stand
You dude!
I'll get out now
You're just solider
What are you doing?
I want to check if the colors of the soldiers and the poop are different
Hey!
Omiya!
You are just a solider
Can't you read this?
I can't read
Stop it
Who's the hell you are!
Today is a competition to test military discipline.
our team is very old.
We have achieved a lot.
Our achievements are very prestigious.
We are a great team that follows military discipline very well.
The Emperor praised our team as a great team with very good teamwork.
Keep in mind what I said
You guys, get ready!
Ready go!
I understand our future war situation
our future?
Why?
we don't have the fabric to make the flag
Your turn!
last one!
I'll do my best
Go for it!
Hey
Women!
Solders!
He's winner
wait
you made a misjudge
What?
You watched the women and didn't see them fight
I saw Omiya win
Omiya!
This is your reward
Hold on
I know how you feel
i want to drink this with someone
Let's drink,Takumi
I heard that you were complained by Colonel Kazuki in the ring.
I hate bowing to people younger than me
It can't be helped
Personal connections are very important in the military.
He looks very elegant unlike us
How do you mean?
His father is a famous military leader in Aomori Prefecture.
I hate him but I'm really disguised about Omiya
How can we control him?
He's too strong
His friend Arita is very schemer.
That's  the point
I think it's better to separate them
I'll come in
What's wrong,Omiya?
i want to drink with you
With me?
Yes
Thai is the reward you won
You should drink with your teammates
I'm here to drink with you
Thank you
I'll have it
Have a seat
why don't you go to the leader's meetinghouse?
I don't wanna go
You don't like women?
Not
Why do you always read a book in a small room?
There are many things more important to me than women
I am amazed that there is anything more important than women here.
very interesting
You think so?
Have you slept women before?
No?
No
Are you sure?
I didn't know that.
I was a virgin until I was 17
You lost your virgin when you were 17?
I was seduced
What's wrong?
I'm leaving from now
Where are you going?
You can guess
I'm different from you.
See you
Good
Mr.private first class solider
What?
I'll take Midori today
I won't give her to you
Shit. I cut the way
Hey
What's wrong?
I was stuck in the quagmire
Come in
I tied to cut the way
Two people
Wait 5 min more
Who's here today?
Satsuki and Yuko
You take Satsuki, You take Yuko, wait here
What a nice name
You are smelly
You are smelly too.
I can't stand
You are stupid
wait here until I call you
Hey
He is here to pinch a large amount of money
Although he is a superior officer, he does nothing but bad things.
Hold on
Don't be rush
I refreshed
What's this?
Watch the sunrise from the top of the mountain in summer
Watch the sunset from the beach in winter
This is nice poem,right?
Enjoy your meal
I don't need it.
Come here
what university did you graduate from?
I graduated from many universities
I need you to tell me one thing.
Tell me
Do you know Akiko Yosano?
I know
Watch the sunrise from the top of the mountain in summer
Watch the sunset from the beach in winter
do you know the meaning of this poem? Kimii means Tekkan?
It could be Tekkan
you are very sarcastic
Come here
i want to know your favorite poem
You learned poems when you were a student, didn't you?
I have but I don't know if you like it
I tell you
That woman fell in love with a customer
Customer say he's coming to the store again
clash of lies and lies
Who's the poemist?
Takao Konya
I don't know about him
What else?
I'll tell you later
i want to know
Ok I tell you
hell is right there
i don't want to go there
The wind with affection was blowing there
I didn't know it was a farewell to brothers
the fog is very thick
I can't see any enemies
Look at that?
Omiya!
Get up,Omiya!
Dinner?
don't fall asleep.
It's time for work
How's it?
I'll report to leader
It's time for work,right?
you are still half asleep
You guys tricked me.
Did you sleep?
How do you know?
You are stupid
Keep watching
Last night, the 3rd team was attacked by the enemy and wiped out.
Our team was ordered to scout the vicinity of the water station.
meet there at 1:10 in 5 minutes.
That's all
Hold on,Arita
You go to Takeshima leader's room
He's calling you
I'm here
You graduated from university. Why do you want being a soldier
i like being a soldier
You're strange
You'll have you enter the command center from today.
For what?
Those who graduated from university were to receive training in cryptanalysis
For 3 months
For 3 months?
This is the transfer order
I have a favor of you
I wanna stay here
you have to follow orders
I believe that even in the military I have the right to express your opinion.
right to express your opinion.?
You're cheeky
you can't decide for yourself.
You are stupid!
Who's the hell you are?
pack your bags and get in the car
Move forward
Run!
I'm going without talking to you.
Don't push yourself too hard
I'm tired
Hey
Where's Mr.private first class solider?
Where's he?
He escaped from here?
He doesn't escape without me
I'm kidding
Stop it
What's this?
There's a letter for you
From Mr.private first class solider
Attention!
Listen,Arita was transferred as a factor of cryptanalysis from today.
Where he's gone?
It's none of your busyness
It is
No
It is!
where did you let him go without telling me?
Tell me
What's the hell?
I'm your boss
Omiya!
Stop it
Damn it
Mr.private first class solider
You are stupid
Kanemura, Yoko is new worker but she can't earn much
she has a breast problem
you should be strict with her
This is our business
I know
you should be stricter
Satsuki does not sell at all
Did you talk with her?
she always makes excuses
You too
Call her, I gonna teach her
you are not a writer.
You just need to serve your customers
I get it.
i fall like you
What's the hell?
You are not learnt yet
Make some money and then act like a big shot.
You are not higher class solider.
You are just like rubbish too
You should be improve yourself
You have no right to hit me.
You are just scam
This is our business.
But we are at end of line. We are unhappy
You are educated, why you work as this?
We promised to ask about that
I'm sorry
It can't be helped
I am of the opinion that if I sell your body, but don't sell my heart, someday I will have a chance.
But it was just my imagination
You should go back in Japan soon
I have no home
Does it hurt?
He kicked me
I'll bring some medicine
Thank you
Who?
What's wrong?
It's too late
You don't feel good?
Just little
I can't serve you tonight
I'm in trouble
What?That's not so you
Tell me
Can you read this?
Read?
I can't read
Omiya
I'll write briefly
Akaike has something to do with my transfer
Akaike?
Where you wrote?
not finished yet
But If I become a cryptanalyst, I think I can figure out when the war will end.
So I decided to go the office
I worry about you
While I am not here,don't escape or fight. otherwise that will be what Akaike aim
Stay calm for 3 months until I will be back
I'll tell you again. Do not escape. Arita
It's too late. I escaped...
You should go back until they find you
I'm surprised
What's wrong?
She's injured. come to my room
What are you doing?
You are here for sex
Am I not good enough?
I don't mean that
That's not so you
Are you sick?
You should rest when you are sick.
I want to comfort solders
Do you like solders?
Some solders are so bad
Akaike hit Satsuki so she feels bad
Akaike?
Akaike is here?
don't go?
Who are you?
Where is Akaike?
Who is it?
It's me
Omiya!
You've escaped
Call Kenpeitai
Call them
What are you going to do to me?
You'll be in trouble if Kenpei come
You are stupid
What are you doing?
i do nothing wrong
You are stupid
Stop him!
Clam down
It would have been better to hand him over to the military police at once.
No way, the military police is suspecting us
If I get arrested, you will get arrested too.
I know
It's not good to keep him in jail like this.
he is used to being in jail
I really wanna beat him
It is most effective to reduce the amount of food he eats
Meal time
I'm starving
What's this?
Reduce the amount of food you eat
They reduced the amount of food
What's this?
I'm starving
You're smelly.
Go first
Omiya, eat it
This is for you
You bastard
You are solider
You guys watch us
Omiya!
What are you doing?
Mr.private first class solider
I'm about to die
You bastard!
Work hard
Get up
Hold on
You are the same Japanese soldiers.
calm down and talk
Actually I trust you the most
I have a favor to ask from you
So?
I want to talk about my MATE
Who?
Omiya solder
What's wrong about him?
Wanna drink?
is it whiskey?
This is my first time drinking this since I came to the field.
you live a life of luxury
Why you take care of me so much?
you saw me the other day
Are you into me?
i feel like I’m dreaming
It's true
are you always here?
I am always in Shoutoku
I come here only twice a week
you don't work for five days?
Yeah
It's waste time
You seem to be Tokyo person
I was born in Sumida in Tokyo
It bring me back my memory
I lived Mukojima before coming here
Mukojima?
Do you know Mukojima?
I lived near by Mukojima
Can I play?
Sure
But If the boss finds it, it's a problem
Don't worry
He went to headquarters and won't be back until evening.
I'm horny
I'm horny too
Please use this opportunity to meet with me from time to time
Please
you should go home soon
What? I really love you
It's good for you
I won't leave you no matter who comes
What are you doing?
You are stupid
You bastard!
I'm starving
Akemi was nice woman
Where's Mr.private first class solider
i have a stomach ache
Insulting the boss is a felony.
Inhumane acts like that should not be tolerated.
it's my job to decide it
it's not your job
I'm asking you
you think bad things will happen to you if you get involved with him
Shut up
Please consider about it
It's pointless
We should make an example out of him.
I’m not going to reconsider
We shouldn't make an example out of him.
Shut up
are you going to defy me?
Get out!
I'm leaving, Katsuki leader
I finished my cryptanalysis education on July 7th
Starting today, I'm going back here to work in the encryption room.
I report this to you
Relax
Your grades were excellent, so the three-and-a-half-month plan turned into one-and-a-half months.
Good luck with your work
Arita first class solider
Welcome back
Mizumaki
You guys ok?
How's Omiya?
He's in a jail
What? He's in a jail
Hey,What are you doing?
I'm doing nothing
What's ur name?
I'm Arita first class solider who is Omiya's friend
i wanted to tell him i was back
You are stupid
Mr.private first class solider!
Arita first class solider!
Did you back today?
Yes
Why you know of me?
I wanna talk about Omiya. come with me
Wanna smoke
No thanks
Be relax
He wasn't being treated well, so I discussed it with my leadership.
But it didn't work well
I heard about you and Ogami from Mizumaki.
I asked my father's friend to bring you back here ahead of schedule.
I see.
thank you for everything
That's all I could
I'll leave it to you for the rest.
You know?
Sure
Please
What's wrong?
do you have any problem?
Nothing
you seem to be in trouble lately
I'm going out.
Take care of this work
Who?
I'm Arita
What are you doing here?
you are very bad as usual
You teamed up with a friend to create a double bookkeeping system.
you were fraudulently taking military bonds
You...ok..come with me
will you take me to court?
I will shoot you
Shoot me if you like
I put the proof and a note about you in my room.
What if military know about this?
Kagenuma and Takejima will be killed too
Ok. let's deal
Listen to me.
Get Omiya out the jail
And Hire him as a security guard in the cryptanalysis room
Thank you
did you read the letter i wrote?
I wasn't here at the time
Never mind
i am happy to see you after a long time
How was your training?
It was difficult
For the training?
I mean, war situation.
i learned a lot of information
Japan is going to lose
is the situation so bad?
We want it to be clear that if we lose, we lose, if we win, we win.
What should we do
I know
I give it to you
Thank you very much
You look tired
Don't push yourself too hard
I like being tired
You
Thank you for the other day
I hear you've been punished
It was piece of cake.
I present this to you
I came too late
What's wrong?
You don't know?
Japanese here will return to CHOUKAKKOU on today's truck.
So they are busy today
So...
We are
It's a clean break.
Kind of
Ouch
Does it hurt?
get on the truck quickly
We have to leave on time
Everyone get on the truck?
Let's go
Satsuki and Yuko has not come yet
Take them
Yuko is in trouble
I'll go there
What's wrong Yuko?
She is dead
Yuko?
let's leave her
Where are you going?
But She is dead
I can't look after her
do you say that in front of buddha?
you took a lot of money from her
You get on the truck and go first,Satsuki
See you Yuko
They depart soon
You are stupid
You should make a memorial service for her.
I can't.
Do you want money?
See you Omiya
Let's meet again if there is a connection
Good luck
Omiya!
What's wrong?
this is an emergency order
This seems to be a very important command
Get up and get together!
this is an emergency order
The enemy is massing 40 kilometers east of RYOMEN.
It'll be hard to defeat them
We have to get over this
Katsuki
You must form a convoy immediately.
Move military flags to Amano in Saiching
Let's get prepared
Move forward
Hey, Hase!
Damn it
Leader!
Call headquarter
This is guard team. can you hear me?
This is head quarter
We are under attack by the enemy and we are struggling.
I get it.
Let me know the location
Hello?
Onita!
Kazuki team.
Let me know the location
Sorry.. our flags....
second lieutenant, where are you now?
1 km south of Ryugen
Near Okabio
I get it
I'll help you,Kazuki second lieutenant
Omiya!
Kazuki second lieutenant
second lieutenant
I'm risking my life.
For Kazuki second lieutenant
Put your head down
Damn it
What's wrong with the woman?
She got out and shot
Stop it!
Are you OK?
Stay strong
Good boy
Be a strong boy
Salute for him!
get back in shape
We're going to look for the military flag now.
don't come back until you find it
Stop
that's our military flag
Attention
Salute for the flag
get back in shape
I got back Kazuki's military flag back
We're glad
You did good job
Nagai! take the flag
I wanna take care this flag
Ok, you bring the flag and lead our team
I will lead with this flag
Omiya!
Mr.private first class solider!
I'm glad you are safe
I'm glad
What's wrong?
Omiya, the war was over
the war was over
Really?
japan was lost
So we can go home
are you cleaning up?
Yes we are
I have to clean up one thing
Share this with you
Thank you
i give you this
It is enough to live in Japan
Who are you?
don't enter the room without permission
What's the hell?
japan was lost
There is no longer military
You are no longer my boss
What can I do for you?
What?
i will pay you back
I'll give you this
Omiya!
Stop
Forgive us
Sir
What's the hell?
Sorry
Omiya!
You made it
Greet him
Japan lost because of you guys
You get it?
I get it
you guys don't do bad things in japan
Put your head down
You bastard!
If you have the chance, let's meet in Japan
You look down
japan lost but we didn't lose
Right?
That's right
Omiya!
you are my boss from now on
THE END