Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hoodlum Soldiers 6 (#6)
Heitai Yakuza Ore Ni Makasero
Anyone here?
We are here to help you
Total loss.
He's alive
Get them in to the truck, and go back
Come on everyone!
I'm here
Where?
Mr.private first-class
You're die
You're die, too early
Good. You made it
Everyone come!
Don't play
You guys attack tanks with suicide bombs.
You don't have to worry about being alive
We'll train until you guys all succeed.
OK?
Hey
Get out
Wait
You don't know about us, but We are a unit honorably commissioned by the military.
Don't look down on me
What the hell?
You wanna hit me?
I'll teach you later
Notice.
Team 102  Kizaki
You have done a great job in battle.
You have done your duty.
You did it because you acted in solidarity.
We send you a honorable certificate of thanks for that.
General of the Army, Kanto,Shiro Saijo
We received three certificates of appreciation in two months thanks to Chief of Staff Tanaka.
We really appreciate him
Please continue the suicide precept in this honor.
Tanaka tell you about next mission
We will change our mission today
In short, We will target to South
We will leave from China main land
So We will go along with this new mission
how is the war situation?
I have no idea
The situation is certainly not good
There's no winning in this gamble
You know what?
we have bad luck
we have overcome many difficulties
We're causing all sorts of problems in the military
we move around like yakuza
we are with the traveling birds
Hey
What's that?
Today was the day of the party, and I received various gifts from Mr. Tanuma
That's good to know
You told me Tanuma
Yes
Tanuma what?
Tanuma Seiichi
Tanuma Seiichi?
Converting current Teams in this region to other Teams is a very difficult task.
On top of the terrain, the passing point is likely to be MOUKATONG
MOUKATONG place is so dangerous
I think it's very dangerous to go through there
I'll come in
Come in
Cho has come back
Attention,ready?
Once again
Thank you for your hard work.
What is the state of recent guerrilla activities?
It's been very quiet lately as a result of the mopping up operation the other day
How about around the MOUKATONG?
It's quiet..well at the moment..
The guerrillas are now down to this line
I see.
Collect accurate information there
Hi,Chou
Let's have a drink
No thanks
do you refuse?
This is the liquor I received from the boss
Why do you refuse?
I can't drink
You're the boss' brother, aren't you?
Drink it
I have nothing to do with this
What the hell,
I'll force you to drink
Get out
He hates it
What the hell?
I don't know who you are
I'm boss's driver, Heijo Takiguchi
You're his driver
What?
I'm not just the driver
My name is popular among Kanto Kizaki team
I don't know about Kizaki team
I belong to various units
I have a higher status than you.
I was boxing in Nagoya
i can knock you out
I never heard about you
Damn it, come here
You guys fight
Ok we are ready
they start fighting
What's wrong, Omiya?
Stop it
You bastard
Get up
You don't drink,Takeuchi?
I prefer watch repairs to drinking alcohol
are you a watchmaker?
Do you always carry this repair tool with you?
I have loved repairing watches since I was a child.
That's why I carry this tool with me
do you have a watch?
I broke my watch long ago
Hey, Kisaburo Omiya is here?
I'm asking you
there is no such person
don't lie
I know he's here
You're too noisy
I know about him
You're the Omiya?
So what?
I need to talk with you
he is drunk.
please come back tomorrow
What the hell?
Ok just bring it
Omiya
I'm so busy today
he is the Kisaburo Omiya
I hear you exaggerated yourself greatly
So what?
I'm Tetsu from Tokyo Asakusa
i have pride in myself.
I was in Kanto unit for 3 years
Don't look down on me
Why do you laugh?
I'm Sentaro from Osaka
i am a cook.
I've been waking at Kizaki unit for 5 years
i cook you like sashimi
I'm Tesugoro from Wakamatsu, Kyushu
I love fights so I won't be promoted
I will beat you today
Are you Yakiza?
Do you wanna fight with me?
I'll fight first
Damn it
I beat you
You damn it
Once again
I'll beat you next
That's enough
I beat you
You made it
Are you feeling good now?
A guerrilla force broke into MOUKATONG at 8 o'clock today.
We suffered two casualties, but sank the guerrilla force.
It seems to be different from Cho's information.
That's bad
The strategy for attacking TENJING has been decided.
We will prepare together at 12:00 on the 15th.
We decided to converge from MOUKATONG to SHUUANKO as soon as possible.
4 days later, right?
This strategy is hard
Mr.private first class solider
It's very bad of you to hold back on him.
more alcohol please
They need more alcohol
why do you bring each bottle of alcohol?
you are stingy.
bring a lot of alcohol at once
Bring more food
i want to eat fresh food
i want to eat fresh food too
make fresh food for us
They wanna eat fresh foods
1.2.3.4.5.6.7
one is missing
I'm full
You treated me well.
thank you for this gift
We had a lot of fun
I drink this liquor at night
thank you for this gift
I'll take this too
That's the liquor I ordered for the boss
You're stingy.
I'll take this
The bottle will break if dropped like this
Let's go
Thanks for the foods
Thanks,Omiya
Attention!
Line up
unbutton
Sazawa sergeant
It's not good to search the soldiers without my permission.
i got the consent
What?
my property was stolen
Is the culprit one of my subordinates?
Yes.
Surveillance soldiers reported to me that he escaped here.
Are you sure?
Yes
is there a culprit in this?
why don't you reply?
That's enough
I was going to do it secretly.
However, as you requested, I will also investigate together.
I will report it to my boss and have him formally investigate.
That's better
Leader
you stole first
What?
do you have any evidence?
Ask him
he has been timid since a while ago
What I said was right?
we are a draw
who are you talking to?
I don't care.
I stoked it
What happened if I stole?
You bastard
Stop it.
I'll take care of this issue
Omiya.
You said you don't care who is he
don't you know military rules?
I'm teaching you how tough this unit is.
Come
Leader
i stole it
you have nothing to do with this issue
Omiya.
What is the spirit of the Kizaki team?
I'll go
Don't go
Seven years after I joined the military, I became the commander-in-chief.
I have confidence in my mental strength
In the military you have to follow the rules
But today forget the military rules and I want to fight you
I'll teach you
Were you sure what you said?
You wanna stop?
What are you guys doing?
why are you fighting the leader?
Stop it,boss
i have to settle the issue with him
This act is against military rule
It is forbidden to fight with the leader
I follow what you say about military rules
Please leave it to us
are you really the leader?
it's your responsibility
I'll teach you first
Stay
Stop it,Omiya
Get your hands off
You stupid
is it time to eat?
there is no food for you today
can't you forgive him?
Of course
the army operates by military rules
he broke the military rule
Moreover, he had a fight with the leader
He will be court-martialed for destroying the verification given by His Majesty the Emperor.
please forgive him
Arita
It was 20 years ago that you and I were classmates.
You and I went our separate ways after graduating from elementary school.
The result is my current position.
You and I are in completely different positions.
i can't treat him special
This is my wish as a human being
I put my personal feelings aside and am in the position I am in now.
i have my own ideas
You made Nomoto Kinuko unhappy with your own beliefs
You were in a relationship with her, but when she was asked to marry Ms. Nakamura's daughter, MASAE, you married her.
Kinuko committed suicide soon after
Her suicide has nothing to do with my marriage.
i know you want more career
I can go public about her suicide
do you threaten me?
No.
This is deal
Get Omiya out from jail
I want your reply
I decline
I don't get involved in my private life
Get out
Omiya
I'm here
Mr.private first class solider
Thanks
i have canned too
Take them
What are you doing?
I'll come in
come in
I received an emergency call from MOUKATONG
Gather all members of the team.
And Chou too
I'm sorry to have troubled you
Tomorrow is the day of the mission to Tianjin, but the transit point, MOUKATONG, has been attacked.
Fortunately, security fought them off, but they could strike again.
They could have come to investigate.
They are waiting around the Moukatong for sure
We have a hard time executing an operation in a short amount of time.
We must pass through MOUKATONG withstanding attacks from the enemy.
We'll call for reinforcements.
How many?
2 teams
Too less.
We need more
This is what we can do most
Who wanna be the leader?
Who want to be?
I'll be
He was just deployed on a recent sweep.
We don't have to think about it.
He is the right man for this mission.
Can you?
Iwagane is left here
Operation Tianjin will go ahead as scheduled at 12:00 p.m. on the 15th.
Iwagane team help us
You should explore the enemy's movements in advance.
I get it
You shouldn't talk to him about military secrets.
He was educated in Japan and swore an oath to the military.
But
You don't trust me?
You have to focus on your work
I'll manage this
Yes
Attention
Listen.
Tidy up your belongings
You might not come back here again
Write a letter and bring it later
All letters are censored.
OK
Yes
Moukatong is hard place?
That's a dangerous place
What's wrong?
A photo
A photo?
Your mom's?
I guess I put it here
Look at there
Here it is
She's beautiful
We don't wanna die
Omiya and Arita are so lucky
Get out
Get out now!
You are so unlucky
Attention
I was told you would be willing to do this work.
I will show you the results of my training.
Wait
This is weapon
You dude
You all right? Yokoi!
Let's go
We can't.
We all die
We have no time.
Let's go
Where's my mom?
Yokoi!
We offer my death to God.
Stay
We'll take a rest
You and I have been through a lot.
we never got out of the army
we can get out of the army
It's very cloudy around here
You can't see it, but the surroundings are full of enemies
TANUMA is using this strategy to try to kill me, who hinders his career advancement.
Really?
I was a fool for believing my classmate
I'll take you and die with you.
Sorry
this is my own business
Let's get easy going
Army is coming
there is a comfort station
Omiya
It's me
MOUKATONG has dangerous places, so be careful
This place may disappear once the operation begins.
we will meet next time in heaven
Here it is
I'm glad to see you again
We're leaving tomorrow, but it's nice to see you
We have a connection, don't we?
I really wanted to see Otomaru
You’re so mean
But I am happy to meet you, her sister.
Really?
I'm glad
I've also heard a lot about you from Otomaru
I really wanted to see
Let's have a drink together after a long time
I'll go later
I'll go first
Have fun
Please enjoy yourself
What's wrong?
You look down
Let's drink
Today is the last time I see a Japanese woman
today is the last day i see the sun.
I feel sad
Oh yeah.
All drinks and meals are now free
Please enjoy yourself
today is the last day
I feel sorry for Otomaru
we will die tomorrow so let's have fun
Is she doing well?
Otomaru?
I think she's enjoying her life down south.
are you suicidal?
Yeah
But I don't know well
please don't die
I won't die
Get off!
Target the house ahead
you go forward to the right
lure the enemy
we go to the left with three
and rush in
Move!
Let's go
Move forward
Soyoki
Shit
Omiya!
Stop
she is hurt
Who's she?
she can't speak Japanese
it's so weird that she's alone
she doesn't look like a spy at all
Send her to TEAM to find out
How?
By truck
It's okay to have an extra person on the truck
But Driver Sawaki got hurt
Anyone can drive?
Omiya can
Omiya?
Mr.private first class solider
It's nice to be with a young woman even if you don't speak the language.
That's so you
I'm excited
But she's still young
The road is bad here
She looks strange
She does not look feeling good
Stop here
A pistol bullet is in her body
We have to be in hurry
Wait, It takes time because the road is bad
What should we do?
I'll give it a shot.
get the gas out
have you ever done this?
No
hold her hands and feet
Lie on your back
Don't move
please do it quickly
I don't know where the pistol bullets are
cut it properly
Leave the rest to me
Here it is
I found it
She got better
I won't attack her
Mr.private first class solider
i will break through here.
Protect her
Shit
Omiya
Mr.private first class solider
That watch is useless
I can fix this
If you fix these parts, this watch will definitely be fixed.
It's too quite
Is it radar?
Truck found, bullet holes in tyres.
They could have surrendered.
Omiya
I was tricked by you.
You use your cute face
You're laughing
Stupid.
You don't get it
You're Chou!
Be quiet.
This area is an anti-Japanese zone.
She's my sister
She?
Are you his sister?
I found out
You were an ambush.
You targeted my car.
All was you
I found out
Are you gonna kill me?
You gonna kill Mr.private first class solider too?
Thanks
I'll eat
It tastes good
I was told they would give him a treat before sentencing him to death.
I gonna die?
Never mind
You look nice
You treated me nicely
You ate all as you told me
He is such a man
When you depart?
1 hour later.
We will gather at Moukatong by daybreak
Did you forget about that day?
Our parents was killed in front of me by them
When I gonna be killed?
You don't get it?
I'm freaking out
Why I gonna be killed?
Shall I attack you?
I know it's bad
I wanna meet Mr.private first-class solider
You are here to call me
Do whatever you want
Can you speak Japanese?
I can't help but tricking you
Shuran
have a seat
You speak Japanese
Does it hurt?
Please eat a lot of feasts again.
Don't go to Moukatong
What she writes?
Mr.private first class solider!
Omiya
Where have you been?
I was too busy
Stay strong
I wanna lie down
Give you cigaret
What's this?
What she writes?
Don't go to Moukatong
This is a warning of incoming attacks from the enemy
Really?
She wanted to return the favor to us.
What will happen?
The army will be wiped out.
So Are they going to die?
I want to see how that leader dies
Let's go
Everyone get together!
Aim and shoot them
At 11:50 the enemy started attacking
We have the upper hand in terms of military strength, and the current situation is advantageous.
the enemy can't come here yet
Are you ok?
our helping soldiers haven't come yet?
It's too quiet
What's wrong
It fixed
I didn't think this would fixed
Noguchi!
Yes Sir
At 12:20, please inform them that many of our casualties occurred.
our helping soldiers haven't come yet
Damn it
headquarters responded
Will the operation change?
Keep the status quo.
What?
Keep the status quo?
Is that all?
we don't know what to do
What time is it?
It's 12:32
It's almost time for the operation to end
Report the current gathering situation to OKA UNIT
To Oka unit?
Do it!
Yes
The operation was successful
Was it a lie to make MOUKATONG your base in Tianjin?
The policy of the Imperial General Headquarters has been the same since the beginning.
Why was the WAKANA UNIT dispatched to MOUKATONG?
in order to concentrate the enemy's attacks there.
do you mind if they all die?
Sure
I think losing 20 people is a good strategy.
let's go save them now
We can't
I'm in charge of mission
I order you
Iwagami is glad that he died in battle.
There are many bad people in that unit
Kizaki unit is happy to clean them
they are all my precious subordinates
You can't get ahead unless you stop thinking
From head quoter?
I am intercepting reports to the OKA UNIT
From Oka unit emergency report?
All Units are gathering in the south of KEITOKU
What? they moved?
This is an order from Officer Tanuma at Headquarters to the OKA UNIT.
Mission is completed.
Thanks to Oka unit
I'll go to Keitokuching soon
Leader
what will happen to us from now on
We gonna die here
we'll crush
They tricked us
Tanuma used us as a decoy.
Damn it
Sawaki!
Don't get away from here
Leader!
You came here
Omiya.
Tanuma was going to kill us as I thought
Damn it
i am a soldier
I am prepared to die in battle
But it's frustrating to be deceived by an ally and die
Leader!
Get back
You must not die until Tanuma takes responsibility.
You should be alive
Damn it
I can't forgive them
You had a good result in the operation in the Moukatong's mission
I want to thank KIZAKI UNIT very much
what you have done is so amazing
Omiya
the officer is driving this car
Get out
Tanuma
You have nothing to do with this.
Get out
Get up
i hate you
Shall I punish him more?
That's enough
where are we going from now on?
I'll leave it to you
THE END