Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hitotsubu no Mugi / A Grain of Wheat (1958)
Everyone, please take good care of yourselves and work hard
After a long winter, everyone is now ready to
take a step forward in the work they have done
You have taken a step forward in your new life.
Please be careful
Don't forget your stuff.
Take care of your health.
Take care.
Teacher.
Only Yuko Koizumi hasn't come yet
What's wrong?
With this I conclude my greetings.
Thank you very much.
A special train bound for Sendai from Ueno will arrive at platform 1
Everyone, please step back behind the line
The students are lined up here in a single row,
everyone is lined up?
Ok get on the train.
Take care.
Mom.
Take care of your health.
You too.
I'm counting on you
Please send me some letters.
Do your best
yet, it's still cold.
Don't catch a cold
Please stay strong
Don't worry about us.
Do your best
Make sure to listen carefully to what the people over there are saying
Excuse me, excuse me, I'm sorry
Come on, hurry up
what's wrong?
Teacher
I'm sorry to worry you, but I can go with everyone.
It was good that we went together
I'm glad we made it.
Get on the train.
Thanks.
Here it is.
I made a bento, please serve it.
Thank you
Inoue-sensei, and please take care not to catch a cold
Thank you in advance
Ah, then we will be off.
Get back your seat.
Put your luggage
everyone remember the number, right?
Hurry up and sit down.
Everyone okay
From here on, these seats are for the people who will get on later
Make sure you don't go this way, okay?
starting today,
You have to take responsibility for your own actions,
We will arrive at Ueno Station at 6 o'clock
Everyone, make sure to sleep well. It's not good to be drowsy, right?
and then follow the instructions from Mr. Arishima from Public Employment Security Office
As the teacher just mentioned, please make sure to get a good night's sleep
And if you have any questions about anything,
I will be with you all the time, so don't hold back.
So please feel free to ask questions, okay?
Thank you in advance
How about you, Ryuko?
I'm fine
Sleep well
It feels like we're on a school trip for some reason
Yes.
Well, just try to relax and take it easy
Open the window.
What's wrong?
The villagers are sending us off
What's going on?
Come on.
Get your seat.
Oh my god.
Hey, is it true that Ichiko-sensei made that?
Yes.
Are you still awake?
Wanna eat?
I want to eat, but I'm too full
What a shame, I'm going to sleep
Mr. Yamada
We meet again.
I'm Onoda
I’m sorry.
Oh, I heard that you are here.
Wanna drink?
I can't drink.
Hey come on
We are having party there.
How many students?
Ours are 60
Our entire province ,1,300 people.
That's a lot.
Next year there will be more people.
I'm not a teacher, I'm more like a job referral agency.
I find myself spending more time on physical activities than standing at class room.
It seems that our roles are tough for both of us
The kids in Tohoku will be welcome because they work hard.
How about coming over there and doing it together?
I'm fine.
Don't say that,
Ok then see you in Tokyo.
I'll stop over there.
However, there is quite a bit of time before the next job
so please listen calmly
Thank you all for coming.
Please try to look towards the front as much as possible
Yes, everyone, please gather at the flag that has the same number as your chest number
Yes, the person at 12, please come over here, the person at 12 is this way
Go to number 12, number 12, okay?
Alright everyone, please come forward and squat down
Thank you all for your hard work
My name is Mutou from job referral agency.
If you have any worries or need to talk,
feel free to come anytime
Now, I will take attendance
Minoru Obara and Tsugio Endo
You will soon board the train, so wait here, okay?
Yuko, are you okay?
Tetsuo Yoshizawa
Yutaka Suzuki
please line up here
Nobutaka Saito
Takuma Tsutomu, Koji Iwanaga, and Umeo Watanabe from Hirata Junior High
over here, over here, over here,
He's your master
I am Umeo Watanabe
Welcome
He is our teacher
Thank you in advance
Are you the teacher?
Thank you for your hard work
I've been waiting for you
I'll take care of it
Please wait a moment
I'll go first.
Take care.
Teacher.
This is Inoue.
Thanks for your hard work.
Please rest assured about her.
Please
Kayo.
Work hard.
then, goodbye
Look at that huge chimney!
There are four of them.
that's the famous ghost chimney.
What is a ghost chimney anyway?
Well, just take a look at that
Well, it's been 2 now
Here it is.
welcome
Mom.
Come here quickly, this is the child
welcome
Take it easy.
Have you just graduated from junior high school?
We are small
This is your senior, Macchan.
Thanks in advance.
What's your name?
Watanabe Muneo,right?
Yes.
You wrote it here yesterday,
I know that.
Come in.
Have a meal here.
You are still guest today
That's right,come over here
Bring some tea
Come over here
Macchan and Umechan
My husband is Mr. Take, so The best of the best
That's right
This is so great.
Absolutely, everyone is so great.
Welcome home.
What is this? you haven't cleaned it yet?
Hurry up and clean up
this is so annoying
Come here.
I'm back now
Please greet him.
You call him 'teacher'
Here's your room.
I'm off to school.
She's new worker.
Call them Obocchama.
Yes.
Hello
Ah, I'm home, dear.
Thank you for your hard work
He's your master.
I'm Tsuyoshi Nishiyama
Nice to meet you
Oh, you're quite solid, aren't you?
Everyone come here
this is Nishiyama-kun, who has come
to join us a trainee starting today
Please get along with him.
Nice to meet you
Make sure to listen carefully to what everyone says and learn the job quickly
Take him to his room
Wife
He's new trainee
I'm Tsuyoshi Nishiyama
there's nothing we can do about
the increasing number of heads
Don't worry about it
She's nice
This is your place
You come in here
and you can use this desk
Well, you probably won't need to use it anyway
Which ship's factory?
What do you mean?
No way
We're in the auto repair business
Is everyone here?
Then let's introduce ourselves one by one
so that he can remember our names
You go first.
I'm Minoru Obara
Be polite
Next.
I am Endo Tsugio
I am Yoshioka Gonzo
I lived near you
Thanks for coming.
Let's eat first
You guys must be starving
so just eat it.
Thank you very much
Oh, It's red rice.
You like it.
it's the factory manager's heartfelt effort
This is the feudal aspect of this company.
It might be like that
Hey close the door. It's cold, isn't it?
I'm also busy and can't go out to greet you every time
But it's the first day,
and the children will feel lonely
It's not like I came to Tokyo just for sightseeing
They are at an age where they can feel lonely
Speaking of age16, that was the year when they went to the military as a young aviation soldier back in the day
Now we are also making glass here, you know
Even so, during the war, this place was bustling as a military supply factory
Well done.
I'm off.
please, don't say that anymore.
Hey please serve us too
Are you jealous?
We are human too
Can I borrow this for a moment?
please
thank you for your hard work, teachers
Well, I would like to ask for a good child again next year
Same here.
I would also like to ask for a boy next year
in the Tohoku region have plenty of children, you see
There are a lot of kids out of work., so there's no need to worry
I can bring anyone along
If they work at our factory for three years, you will be able to properly get married and return home,
so it would be helpful if you could also help arrange the marriage destination
Mr. Ogata
Stop it....
What's the hell?
Mind your mouth
you have no right to tell me
What's the hell?
Stop it....
Bring some cakes?
How about some fruits?
It would be nice.
Are you off?
Hold on.
Get your hands off of me!
Don't pretend you're cool
We are working hard every day
Minoru is a trainee
Tsugio is skilled with his hands
and is learning about tabletops
I am being taught electric welding
I heard that this senior is someone who hasn't even graduate junior high school.
I wear a mask to protect my eyes
from the welding
Please rest assured that we will work hard to become skilled craftsmen. Best regards, Gonzō Yoshioka
This is a letter from Yoshioka who went to the ironworks
Next is a letter from Shiro and Makoto who went to the glass factory.
I'll read them.
Both of them are working hard and doing well.
There are many glass factories in Tokyo, similar to the one we are working at
The inside of the factory is really hot,
but as you get used to the work,
I start to find it interesting
I want to get out quickly.
I see, next is Watanabe who went to a soba shop.
our lunch is at 3 o'clock
I sometimes eat what customers leave behind
So we eat anything, whether it's tempura rice bowl, oyakodon, or tamagodon
It's really delicious
But sometimes I get fed up with just going to the eat same foods, morning, noon, and night
Hey ready?
It's tough to deliver food.
My senior, Macchan, can carry about 20 dishes.
Of course, it took more than three years to get to learn this.
Hey ready?
Take care.
Hey.
Watch out.
It was close.
hey, this isn't a laughing matter
Sorry.
Hurry up.
Take care.
Ouch
hey, this isn't a laughing matter
Yeah, I'm sure I'll become a great soba shop owner
Please say hello to everyone, and also to Teacher Ichiko Numata...
You and Ichiko.....well, the rest doesn't really matter...
Um, Tsuyoshi Nishiyama, who went to the auto repair shop.
how is everyone doing?
I have gotten used to both my work and the environment
The mechanic has to learn how to drive the Ohto three-wheeler first
Turn right.
keep cutting
More.
Stop.
Try going backwards.
Hey.
Stop.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry
Hey, you idiot!
Inoue-sensei?
Did you talk to that kid?
Oh, I'll try talking to him today
Inoue-kun,come
What's wrong?
Have a seat.
this snack is really good, you know
Actually, we need to start preparing for
next year's employment system, you know?
Am I going to be the one doing it again?
I was thinking of asking you for help
You've gotten used to it.
but if you say I'm used
to it, I can't deny that.
I really don't want to get used to something like this
Don't say like that.
I think it's important for graduating students to find employment here
I understand that
Few students graduate from high school and go to college.
But how many students can't do that.
They will be the ones who lay the groundwork for society in the future
In reality, they are the ones who will stand and support the foundation of the world
I think they are the most important person
Principal, I became a teacher
because I want to be an educator
I want to study more about myself while I still can
I need some time
Well, I can understand that
You were a farmer's son, weren't you?
Yes but so what?
Living in the countryside is a big challenge.
In any case, In the future, they will definitely have to go abroad to work.
I won't force you to do this, but please think about it carefully.
It's convenient for me that you, who understand the situation, will continue
So, you didn't say a word about marriage?
It's okay if I talk to the principal!
Don't worry.
I'm not going to take the principal's daughter
I'm going to take you
We should just submit a marriage
notification to the principal
and say that if he wants to come to the wedding
What's wrong?
It seems like they can't take a break because of the work
But today is the third day.
Tsugio is currently negotiating., but I wonder if it will go well
I've got urgent work piling up today
I've decided to cancel my day off
Our situation is different from your thriving factory
Hey, what are you looking at?
You didn't come to Tokyo just to have fun.
You're here to work
Excuse me, President
What?
I would like to go to night school
night school?
That was the promise we made at the start.
Workers don't need education
It's just a waste of time
You should say that when you can do the job properly.
What should we do?
Lets go home
what should we send as a wedding gift for the teacher?
Look for it in the department store
Let's also cover Shiro and Makoto's share.
let's go to Asakusa today
It's boring, I went there the other day
Hey, how about going somewhere to take a boat.
Sounds good, I'm in!
I thought that Mr. Inoue and Ms. Ichiko had a dating
Don't say bullshit.
Let's buy some gifts soon
Which department shall we go to?
There are as many department stores in Tokyo as there are tobacco shops.
They are here
it looks like a lovely bride
Don't push me.
Oh.
Where have you been?
I went to buy this
You don't have to be drunk.
Now it's time to show off our skills
We just finished
It was tough.
please
Wow, this is The principal's wife
Thank you very much for everything.
Everything ended safely.
Congratulations!
Come here
Well then, I'll be waiting for you later
What do you want to do?
Everyone has been looking for you,
I bought a new one.
There are many customers who don't drink alcohol.
Look, that person hates alcohol
Unfortunately
Call Ishiya.
Come.
Osono
It seems that Ichiro has returned,
but what's going on?
He seems to have some urgent business.
He doesn't go to a job
It's all over.
Well, it seems like everything is just about done
Yeah.
Where is my sewing machine?
I placed an order so I'll deliver it when it arrives.
That was very expensive.
Hey, I only got a sewing machine from my brother
Thank you very much
Thank you for your hard work
Well, let's have dinner then
Okay, I'll go this way
I used all my savings for everything else,
even bought Shelf stuff.
It's too late for you to complain to me
now; until now.
I was putting all my salary into everyone
else's needs without even buying what I wanted
You have no right to complain to me
What? Then I'll say it to you.
Who do you think
helped me earn until today?
Thanks to whom was I able to go to school?
It's been six years since our dad fell ill, and it's like a different world
If I keep sending tuition every month,
who would forget?
Brother, you don't like that I didn't go to Yamazaki's place, do you?
I don't like Inoue.
What's the hell?
He is a really bad guy
So I even held
the wedding at my house, didn't I?
Now, let's go to the tatami room
Come on, brother
You will probably regret it later
you really say some awful things
If I marry to that agricultural cooperative person,
Sure, it might be convenient for you,
but I won't always go along with your convenience
You did try to use me.
I understand it properly, you know
You're making a face like you oppose this marriage, aren't you?
What? Don't say like that.
That's true.
Come here
What are you talking about!
Stop it.
Today is her celebration day.
Damn it.
Everything is over.
please take this
Hey you too.
My legs hurt so I want to stretch them
Let's take it easy.
Where is the bride?
Ah, I see, I see
She's coming.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
what's going on here?
What's wrong?
Inoue-san, let's have a drink together.
A man should get married and have a family
After that it gradually calms down
I don't want to do any more job placements.
Don't say bullshit.
Someone from the school is here
I wonder if something's wrong?
What's wrong?
A telegram arrived from Tokyo.
There seems to have been some problem with the student who got the job.
Thank you for your work.
What's wrong?
A telegram arrived from Tokyo.
Two people from the glass factory have dropped out
Please contact us immediately.
They must be Shiro and Makoto.
They come back here?
I think they will contact you if they are back.
I will go to Tokyo
Are you really going?
your bride must be feeling sad, right?
Don't worry.
Let's go
I want to go too.
That's better. It's good
to go together, isn't it?
Sorry about that
You should prepare
Thank you everyone.
You have had a tough time.
It's my responsibility when it comes to those kids
I'm really sorry to you
Just think of it as a honeymoon trip
A honeymoon trip, huh,
I received a call from the Ueno police station late
They were apparently taken into custody as part of a crackdown on delinquent youth.
I went ahead and contacted the glass factory just in case
The police are over there
teacher?
What happened to you guys?
They said you left the factory two days ago
We were looking for another job
We were in a pachinko parlor.
So, you guys
Did you leave because you hated that factory?
If you didn't like it, you should have told Muto.
I thought it was useless to do that
sit down.
There were many things that were different from the initial promise.
What do you mean?
There are many people in the world without jobs,
you can't say that in those situations
Teacher, we don't have holiday either
When they said they would give me a salary of 2500 yen, it turned out to be 1500 yen
When they said they would let us go to night school, but it was a lie
In between work, we take care of the dog,
fill the bath with water, and work
every night
I'm too tired to write the letter
That's terrible, isn't it?
I'm really sorry to keep you waiting
Oh, please go over there. It's your father's pick-up, so come out
Please go there.
Your dad is here, come on
What is this situation? Where were we going to get involved?
I'm worried
Dad, please don't say that right now
Wakabayashi
Explain the situation well
Yes, let's head over there.
You all come this way too
We were cracking down on juvenile delinquents.
I realized it was a mistake right away,
I stopped because it was too late,
Thank you
Well, as you know,
Today is May day, so we are busy
Look like that.
Section chief, someone like this is visiting you.
Get him throgh here
Come in
Oh, I'm sorry for being late
Why you are at the police?
This is Mr. Inoue from Hirata Junior High School, who has come to Tokyo
I'm Ogata
The children are in your care
Please have a seat
Yes, let's get started
It seems that you are forcing overwork
I hear that you are forcing night work.
Because they are all healthy
I would like to ask about the salary and night shift pay
It seems different from what was promised,
even if you mention the salary
I took the child unconditionally
In the first six months or even the first year,
it's actually more like I want to receive something from you.
How difficult of a situation our small company is being pushed into
Yes, I understand that it's tough
Basically, the government is to blame
This is a story about a small factory
that should just collapse
If a big disruptor appears in the neighborhood,
factories like ours will just fall apart in no time
What are you guys going to do?
there's no need to hold back;
just say what you're thinking
Speak clearly
I don't want to go factory anymore
I wanna work somewhere else
Is that Chinzō group still ongoing?
They are doing city tour, right?
I was impressed by those people's persistence
this is an important time
I asked for it on the phone earlier
We are from Hirata junior high school.
I know
It's on the second floor
Guide them.
There are a lot of people who use the Prefectural Association's dormitory, too.
since they are inexpensive
Oh yeah.
Those guys over there
I was on the train with the director today,
and I escaped to the national teacher
Aren't those two boys just a bit too much?
If you can find another job,
you can come here and tell me about it
You showed me that newspaper.
Well, of course, they are from our prefecture, right?
Of course, it's Shiratamura in your electoral district.
Um, it's over there
Um, well.
this, this.
I see This is terrible, poor children
Phone.
Eat this.
How about teachers?
We bought them for you guys
Eat up.
I brought some tea
There's no tea or anything
It's tough if your throat gets tired
Come on, eat up.
Thank you very much.
Why were you guys hanging out in Ueno?
No matter how much we search,we can't find a good job
I thought we should go back to the countryside
Even if you go back to the countryside, it won't change anything, and even if I go to Tokyo, it won't help either
We can't do anything here.
What if we joined the Self-Defense Forces?
It's too early
whatever it is
that's not good. Not everything can be okay.
Oh, it's already done,
I'm sorry
It was very delicious.
Please show me the timetable
Yeah, why?
Please show me
I'm going to Hamamatsu for a bit
Apparently there's a store that wants to hire a man.
Maybe you guys
can work too
Sorry, but everyone
please stay here together
I'll be back soon
but you can't go home tonight, right?
Hmm,
I'm taking this train.
I'm from Hirata Junior High
What do you need?
I would like to meet with our student
Is something wrong?
The factory has been closed for about a week now
And what about the girls?
They were selected from our prefecture for today's encouragement meeting
Member of Parliament Yoshirō Tsukamoto has
kindly provided us with his busy schedule
He came to encourage you.
I would like to ask him for greetings
Please.
Well then, welcome back
Oh, I'm sorry
I was worried. I thought there might have been an accident or something
and the factory is on the verge of collapsing, so they are taking a break
Well, it's not about asking for a job; it's about being a role model to encourage everyone
Yuko and the others were feeling anxious,
so I stayed with the conductor at the factory
Shiro-chan found a job
Really?
The professional is here now.
It's someone named Tsukamoto
Zengorou Tsukamoto
It's said that the he is an advisor for Maruishi Bicycles.
That's great!
Well,he took a look at the newspaper
Last night, he went out of his way to contact us
We are from Fukushima Commercial Broadcasting.
Let's all help each other if we're interested
Although we are not related by blood, we must take good care of these children.
We are the newspaper
Please strike a pose
Oh, this is a bit strange
How about this?
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Everyone, I think some of you may already know from the newspaper history
Mr. Tsukamoto will help two children who have escaped from the factory.
bringing them the sun of hope
Don't say like that.
The newspapers found out about it.
I wonder where Sakata-kun and Saito-kun are. Sakata-kun, right?
Saito-kun, where are you?
Hey, He is calling you
Please raise your hands.
We are right here
Alright,Please come here.
let's go, let's go
Yes, yes, yes, please come up
Excuse me, could you come here ?
Take a photo from there
please give a round of applause to these boys
Is this okay?
Thank you anyway
It doesn't matter what Tsukamoto Zengo's purpose is
Anyway, as long as they can work
It's hard to take care of them.
Their dreams and reality are too different, you know?
Starting next year,You shouldn't work this role
You can't study on your own
But Someone has to work this role
I think someone can do it
That's not going to work
You said you were going to quit, didn't you?
Nobody wants to willingly do something like this
this has turned into a rather strange wedding
But maybe something like this is actually fitting for our wedding
Ichiko-sensei
Stop calling me 'sensei'! It sounds weird,
so what should I be called instead?
Ichiko or you
what happened?
This
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Ah, it's going to be hot again today
Oh, Sensei
Principal and also Inoue-sensei
She's Nishiyama's mom
It's been quite hot lately, hasn't it?
How's Shinzo doing?
He's fine, thank you.
Where are you going?
That's why I'm concerned about next year's job situation
We are going to the Tokyo Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare
I'd appreciate it if you could take care of her.
I was thinking of meeting him up if I have some time
Did you get a letter from him?
He wrote me a letter the other day.
He said he never had a day off from work.
Please tell him we are fine
Ah, bus has arrived
Take care.
Good morning!
Well, this is quite troublesome. Please refrain from doing such things.
Don't say like that.
I apologize for bringing this up so soon
What do you think about the outlook for next
year's junior high school graduates?
even if we say outlook, it's pretty much the same as before
It probably won't change much from this year
I think our school will see a significant increase compared to this year
That's right, everywhere is on the rise
As for me, I am putting a lot of effort into developing new workplaces
director,Someone came to pick you up
Oh you.
Call Muto.
This is for takeout
Once the job application form is ready,
I will distribute it to each school
Um, Can you let me know about them in advance?
I have other things to do today.
so I will take my leave now
Hey, welcome,
Thank you for the other day.
I'm just heading out for a bit
I often receive your messages
I see, thank you for your patience
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Please.
See you.
He is Mr. Onoda from Kitayama Middle School.
Is there some kind of meeting?
He's Principal Aizawa.
Nice to meet you,
thank you for all your help
Thank you for your hard work
Please, come in
Please bring me something cold
Welcome back.
Welcome back
Want dinner?
No.
It must have been hot, right?
Why don't you have it in the bath
It's too late.
I am already preparing for that.
Is there any beer available?
I'll borrow some from next door.
that's fine.
I talked to principle.
I think it's better for you to stay until the end of this month after all
It's still fine, right? I can still be here for three or four months.
Are you okay with working at a sewing machine?
Isn't this the most important time
for your body?
I know that getting married means having kids,
but maybe it was a bit too early
What does that mean?
Well....
I don't want to end up as a middle school teacher
I don't want to work in employment agencies anymore.
That's all about your mindset.
Didn't you say before that you wanted to quit this kind of role?
Yes, but now it's different
How is it different?
I really want you to become a true educator
I've started thinking this way
since I had baby.
Is someone who runs around in the employment
department a true educator?
Teaching in class room isn't the only form of education
Don't be cheeky
Is that so?
When women get married and have children,
they all tend to have such passive thoughts
It's not that I'm being negative
Your feet aren't on the ground
What? Say that again
Good evening
Ah, were you back? Thank you for your hard work
Are you Tsuyoshi's mother?
I wonder if he is doing well
I called, but I couldn't meet him because he was busy
He seems to be doing well.
Is that so? I just wanted to give this
little bit to you, teacher, for you to eat
Oh, thank you.
This is a nice color
You used to like this too
If that's the case, I just chilled it a bit
You guys get along well.
Just because your friend got license
why do you have to be the one to get a ride?
You are in a privileged position, after all
You really need to understand that part well
Well, there's nothing
we can do about it today,
Thank you very much.
Oh
what did you come here for?
I came to see you
The women's association in the village decided to inspect the stadium,
and I was chosen as the representative to come
and help with the construction of the stadium
I'm glad it's a big factory
Mr. Tsukamoto is such a kind person
Everyone just dispersed a little while ago
I'm going home on the train this evening
They said you can't come because we're busy during the day
You're going to the night school, right?
We are not going to night school
This is our pamphlet
Thank you for your reference
Hey, you all, I'm going to give you a break from now on
why don't you try talking her somewhere?
it would be nice if you could make a great sightseeing in Tokyo  with the kids
If I can see their cheerful faces,
then I can talk to everyone
Change your clothes.
Thank you very much.
Let's get ready.
Please wait a moment
4 cold noodles.
Oh, you came!
Auntie, you came here well,
You've grown up
Since you are here, They let me have a break
I want to eat quickly.
What, you haven't ordered yet?
We've been waiting until you got back
Alright, I'll have whatever you want to order
Thanks for treating us
In exchange, say everyone
You had something delicious at my place
What do you want?
It's already decided that we're having tempura rice bowl
Alright, three tempura rice bowls.
Yes, three tempura rice bowls
It'll be ready soon,
Hey look.
Isn't that Tsuyoshi?
That's amazing,
He passed the exam in one go!
Oh, you got your driver's license?
That's great!
I'm going to practice today
Are you going for date?
That's great!
What's up with Minoru?
He has been sleeping for about a week because of his bronchitis
That's a chest ailment.
but it's not serious case.
That guy isn't strong.
so should we visit him?
No, no, don't do that
Why not?
It would be a problem if everyone know
Oh it's time to work.
I see
well then, see you next time.
See you again, goodbye.
I’m sorry.
This is the smell of grass.
This is the smell of sea.
kayo-chan?
I'm a fine mechanic
A fine mechanic must know everything about cars
I feel like I want to dive into the engine and become gasoline for a moment
Don't rush it
You have to graduate one step at a time,
but you've completed an important stage
You got your driver's license, right?
You're going to be a nurse?
I still have a long way to go.
whenever I think about studying, I get sleepy
I'm going to become independent and take charge around 30.
You're a hard worker,
so I'm sure you will make it.
You have to get a bride first, right?
A bride?
I'm home.
What have you been doing until now?
You have a customer, right?
Yuko.
What happened to you,
The factory went bankrupt.
Oh, is that so? What about Aki chan and others.
Akichan and Masachan are going to work in Hamamatsu
They went to a coffee shop,
Kacchan ended up becoming a service girl at a hotel in Osaka
I thought there might be something in Tokyo, so I came out here
Until I find a job
Can you let me stay as maid here?
It's fine to be free of charge
Try asking the wife.
See you
Buy a medicine and come back
What's wrong?
The truck we repaired yesterday got stuck in the river with the steel materials still loaded
It got stuck in the river with
the steel materials still on board
They say it's our repair fault, you know
Three people died,
Sorry to keep you waiting.
There's nothing wrong.
You should drive us there
Please, go ahead and get in
Don't worry about it
Today's work is finished
Shall we head home?
Tsuyoshi.
Do you want to drink tea?
Just wait a moment.
there's no point in worrying about it now,
so let's have a drink of shochu to lighten the mood
This is quite nice, isn't it?
Come on, let's not do that
But, isn't there anything we can do while we still have time?
It's nothing serious, really
This place isn't going to collapse, right?
Don't say such bad luck things
But we might have to pay damages, right?
We haven't had an accident like this until today
However, working two nights straight
like this is such an unreasonable task
If we did the same as other factories, they would take our jobs.
Well, that's true, but...
So, Tsuyoshi, do you want a drink?
I'm fine.
I'm really sorry about this, you know
Hurry up.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry for making everyone take a break
Thank you for your work.
I will let everyone know about your achievements.
so take care and stay healthy
Make sure to work hard!
and studying hard.
Thank you very much.
Sorry.
She thought we'd been to night school.
I really thought I should tell the truth
but it's better to stay quiet
I feel hot.
You don't go to the night school but
Why you wear high school uniform?
Is this it?
You're pushing yourself,
I like to wear this.
I've always wanted to wear this.
Don't dress up so extravagantly.
You guys shouldn't be whining either.
I'm not going to cry or whine
even if I can't study
I'm going to become a respectable person
If such a big newspaper comes out,
trust will take a hit
It’s written as if we dropped the truck ourselves
You know, I’ve been thinking about it
If it's the boss's responsibility, the commotion will get bigger
Well, what if this guy runs to the police?
What do you mean?
If we say it's just a rookie's mistake,
the penalty will be lighter
On that day, I was removing rust from another car
I know that already
Do you hate to save this factory?
Can you go to the police?
that might be a good idea
This is the time
It's time to repay the favor to boss.
Wife.
What's going on?
I've been asking on them until now
It seems that we will have to cover half of the expenses
That's terrible.
when is boss coming back?
I heard he might be back tonight.
It seems that the compensation for the three deceased will be covered by Yamashita Construction,
but we will have to cover the truck's compensation
It's really troubling
it's not a small amount of money.
So, I have a favor to ask you
It's about your month's salary
Wife, I actually have a good idea
It was decided that we would sacrifice one victim
What does that mean?
Do you need something?
Ah, I'm from the Tsuyama Auto Repair Shop
Tsuyama? Oh, the repair shop for the truck that got stuck in the river?
The issue was just finished
The master is eating at the eel shop behind with the truck right now
Don't worry, he'll be heading back around here
What are the factory saying about?
They say to cut the salary in half for the time being
Since the accident, we haven't had any work at all
I'm in trouble with half my salary.
I've been sending half of it to my family every month
Starting next year, my younger brother will be going to school,
why quit and look for something else?
But I still want to do car repairs.
aren't there any other repair shops?
There's no job opening.
See you later
How are you?
Have you seen a doctor?
Yeah, go buy some eggs with this
Don't worry.
You're in trouble
I'm just physically strong
Even if things get a little tough, it'll work out somehow
Well, thank you
it's all good
We're in this together
Ah, it's raining
Oh my god.
Take my umbrella.
It's unavoidable for now,
but please look for other good places eventually
Well, as long as the person is reliable, it doesn't matter where she works.
Thank you for everything.
Alright, let's go.
It's a nice place you live in
What a lovely kitchen!
If anything comes up, just give me a call, okay?
Kae?
You forgot something again
Sorry.
See you.
So you're going again, huh?
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
Take care.
Yuko
Here it is.
I'll take the first
month's salary as a thank you, okay?
Yes.
Excuse me, may I come in?
Come in.
Hey Tsuyoshi.
You come over here, okay?
Yes.
Well, you have to stop
Is this factory going to shut down?
There's nothing we can do about this
We suddenly lost my job.
I had to compensate a huge amount of money for the truck
So what are we supposed to do from now on?
If you say that, I can't really say....
but you guys too...
It's no use just sticking
around here forever.
what are you going to do, boss?
I think we could buy at least one new
souvenir truck instead of this rundown factory
With that, I think we could do some work for a transport
company and get back to a point where we can own a factory again
So, will you come back again
Boss?
Isn't there any way to keep this factory running?
Even if you say that...
Aren't you the one saying this?
I have nowhere to go anyway
I'll work for free a little,
so please give me a job
Don't say anything to me anymore
I've run out of my evening drink
It's quite a mystery that such a small factory has managed to survive until now,
But.
come on, there's no helping it
It can't be helped.
Oh, someone is coming
For you, right?
What's wrong? Do you need something?
Are you in Nagoya?
you're really far away, huh?
I thought there wouldn't be any jobs in Tokyo,
so I looked around, but all I found were jobs as hostesses at cabarets or maids at hot springs
I don't really want to do that, but since I quit the hospital and decided to move, I thought I'd go along with it
The person they call their late brother from Nagoya
So he really was a doctor
I heard it's a big hospital
It seems that our teacher will take over from there
When are you going?
it's soon.
then I guess I won't be able to see you
I can't even take a break to come back once a month.
It's hard.
What will happen
to your factory?
I have no idea
I sometimes write letters, so give me some too, okay?
Yeah, I promise,
Definitely.
Teacher.
Inoue teacher.
Please be quiet, I can't study
What?
Everyone, calm down!
What's going on?
It's so noisy that I can't study
for our entrance exams
Could you please be a little quieter?
Who said that?
Miura teacher.
Please value students who are working as well as students who are going on to higher education.
There are many people here who work after graduating from junior high school.
In the future, when you enter society, it's all good
Now, everyone, please begin.
Welcome back.
It must have been cold.
It's snowing
I'm cooking now.
What's wrong?
Children who got jobs must be having a hard time like this
I received a letter from Arai who work at hospital
She's going to Nagoya with her master.
Really?
It seems Yuko has also
become an assistant at the inn
Tsuyoshi's repair shop is something wrong.
it feels like just yesterday
when everyone left with their hopes high.
The places where junior high school graduates get jobs are all just barely making ends meet
They say that when a department store opens in Fukushima,
it causes a lot of retail businesses to collapse
What will Tsuyoshi do?
Are you going out?
I'll go to Tsuyoshi's place.
I heard that mom is sick, so I think I'll go visit her
Make sure to eat your meal first
I come back right
Aren't you going to eat anymore? The doctor said you should eat more.
Good evening, teacher
Good evening
I wonder how she is.
Her sickness haven't recovered for a long time
I wonder if Tsuyoshi-kun
will send a letter.
he hasn't said anything lately
Come in.
Tsuyoshi's teacher is here.
Ah, you have to sleep,
you can't be awake
That guy, Go-sensei
It's been nothing from Tsuyoshi lately
He can't really say anything about it
I wonder if something happened
He must be busy.
I think he's fine.
Don't worry.
Bring the tea.
It's fine, it's fine, I'm sorry
Excuse me.
How was it?
The director had been saying for a while that I should go breathe some fresh country air
The director said like that.
Speaking of Minoru Obara,
The doctor says it's quite serious
We are thinking of sending him back to the countryside
Will you fire him?
I'll use him again once he's better
But I don't think he will be better for a while
It's not about the retirement bonus
If he lose his job,
he will be discouraging.
So, I thought I would use one of them
since they had been asking me for a while
Oh, what was your friend's name again?
Is it Nishiyama-kun?
Hmm, is he still over there?
The auto repair shop
hello, what is it?
Is this the Tsuyama repair shop?
Hello, is Tsuyoshi Nishiyama there?
Eh, Tsuyoshi?
You know, He's just out for work right now
He's going to get the vehicle inspection for the Auto mobile.
I'm glad I made it in time,
thank you
Our Factory...
What's wrong?
Kayo,come.
send me a letter
Inoue-teacher.
What's wrong?
Mom,Teacher is here.
She came on foot from the union.
Teacher,please take care of Tsuyoshi.
Ah, I see, I understand
hmm, the eldest son, huh?
So, how many family members are there?
Five
Well then, come right away starting today
Thank you in advance
Do a great job.
This.
Well then, I'm going home now
Yes, that's right
Oh, you're Ishiyama-kun, aren't you?
Phone call from the previous factory
Yes, I'm sorry
Hello, it's me
Huh, I just got a telegram now
I'm sorry.
Your mom has passed away, I'll read it again
Can you hear me?
Our mom is dead,Machie.
Yes
I'll hang up.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing
Then hurry up and bring your luggage
Yeah
Tsuyoshi is coming from today?
He's worried
Well, I suppose it's okay
They are practicing singing.
Is it already March?
It's been a year for us too.
Hey hurry up.
Reach.
How about this?
Come on.
There's still a lot of chess left
I'm off to bed.
Hey, tomorrow you're the one who will boil the tea.
Hey Tsuyoshi
it would be nice if you went to bed too
Here it is.
oh, thank you
oh, is that you, Sensei?
Welcome.
I'm sorry for coming suddenly
Make a tea for him.
it's fine, it's fine
Tsuyoshi.
You saw the telegram, right?
Yes.
Why aren't you coming back?
Your mother died saying your name.
Forgive me....
I got a job here today.
I couldn't tell the factory manager about it.
I feel sorry for Mom.
I was afraid of losing my job.
What is it? Did you have something?
I was able to talk to the factory manager.
Bus has arrived
Thank you very much for coming.
Thanks for your hard work.
Welcome back.
It's cold, isn't it?
Tokyo is already fully in spring
Hmm, I guess so.
how was Kiyoshi?
The telegram has arrived there.
It was just about to get a job at Gonzo's factory
He thought that he shouldn't bring it up because it might ruin his job.
Oh, I see
They are doing their best in their own way
Principal, Let me be your employment officer again this year.
Please
Can you?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Temporary employment train for Line 1 will depart
Please give my regard to the kids in Tokyo.
I'm counting on you again.
Have a safe trip.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'll be off.
THE END