Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Honjitsu Kyushin / Doctor's Day Off (1952)
I started business here 18 years ago
Of course, my hospital was burned down.
But after the war,
I welcomed the elderly Gosuke as director and restarted my hospital
It has been exactly one year since then.
Tomorrow is our first anniversary, and we will be holding a pre-celebration event.
We will be putting up a sign saying that we are closed.
I want to take a nice long nap and relax.
Baya,Kyo too.
I will be taking a nap today too
Nurse Taki says I want to go somewhere, maybe Hakone or Atami
Same here.
I'd also like to take a relaxing bath in the hot springs
but Director Gosuke is against it
If you go to Hakone Atami, It's too far.
Doctor.
I took their vote.
You should enjoy lots of entertainment.
Go to hot spring.
The next morning the group set out while it was still dark
Gosuke ended up to agree to trip to a hot spring
I'm here to order you.
Our soldiers do their best to be polite.
Our soldiers do their best to fight.
Doctor.
What happened?
Yusaku has another seizure.
Again?
Our soldiers...
Hey, which group are you belonging?
Come here
What's the hell?
You against me?
Stop it.
don't be violent.
Hey, hit this solider.
Give me a break
Whoever it is, he's a lunatic
Leader, it's a general enemy operation
Sorry he's my son.
He became like that after his head was damaged in the war
Be careful.
The 22nd mission,the boobs is something...
OK OK.
Hey, you can lie down under this tree
Leader,The operation failed.
Shut up!
You always lie down under this tree
and your right heel resting on it, taking a comfortable nap
Try doing that in front of me
Yes,
Stay like that.
doctor..
Doctor, Can you cure him?
That disease is impossible to cure.
He's the only child.
You're even happy.
He's back from war. He came back alive,
I lost my only son.
Shut up
It's a holiday today,
so who's there? The clinic is closed today
I'm Matsuki.
I'm the Matsuki Police.
Any care happened?
Sorry,
but please exam for a moment
This girl?
Yes.
She was attacked by someone.
came in
Come in.
When was it happened?
Last night.
this girl came from Osaka
Osaka?
Apparently she came to visit a friend who lives
in an apartment.
No matter how hard she looked, she couldn’t find the apartment.
She asked a passerby, and
Oh that is...
There.
that's exactly wrong direction.
Is it heavy?
Shall I help you?
Don't worry.
Don't be hesitate.
She's gone?
You have no choice
Come with me.
Don't speak up.
I'll give you this.
Watch?
That's all what you told me?
This woman is quite tight-lipped and wouldn't even tell
me the name of the apartment.
She said that she had a terrible experience
and that she can no longer see that person
That person is your lover?
Is that so?
Let me examine her. Thank you
What a terrible.
Let me examine
No.
If you don't examine , there won't be any evidence when the culprit is caught
I don't need.
No.
That's troubling. You're worrying so much.
Stand up.
Let's do dissolution.
Matsuki.
You look nice.
Did you practice at the police station while you were asleep?
Sorry.
Have you done the exam yet?
I told her how to care
Is that ok?
I worry if she kill herself.
She's crying.
I feel sorry.
I'll make a tea for her.
I'm afraid this is going to be a long battle
Sorry for making this on your holiday.
Again.
Excuse me.
Who?
I'd like to see that doctor,
but he's closed
But I need.
I need.
He's closed today.
Wow, it's been a while, Doctor
Who is it?
You forgot?
I am Yukawa.
Michiyo Yukawa?
I just returned from the site
She was the first patient to come in on the day I opened my practice here 18 years ago.
Please come in.
Have a seat.
Thanks for the other day.
That was a lot of work for you, so please have a seat.
It was a long time ago, but I still remember it clearly. It was around noon
You were on a board
Did she get hurt?
It's called a Caesarean section
Of course it's important.
She was a first-time patient. I want to help
her. I took up meditation with all my heart
I held the fetus in my hand.
Grab that leg and pull it up. It's no longer a fetus,  it's a baby
The baby cried
It's ok now
Two lives were saved, a mother and her child. I was moved to tears
The child is now 19
That's awesome.
Actually, the Doctor's son told me
I have brought the bill that was left untouched at that time
You've brought the bill for a patient from 18 years ago?
I brought it.
So I'm embarrassed
How much was it?
Yes, it was 240 yen.
Do you work now?
I'm collecting light items.
My son works as a waiter for the company
Don't worry.
I have to pay.
My son earn this money and told me to bring here.
You saved our life and I will pay you, he said.
I see.
I think his named me Shunzo.
You named it.
Thank you so much for  taking the time to give it to me
And doctor, there is a letter inside from him?
Letter?
He like to write letters.
Whenever he as free time, he write letters and send them.
Oh, that's what they call letter mania
Is it an illness?
It's a hobby, a pastime
We went around together again today
He thinks a letter would be better than meeting you
He's in front of here.
I see, it's a mania
This is the roman alphabet
Yes, when he has free time at work, he types on the typewriter
I think my mother had the surgery done by you...
and was born in a mysterious way like Momotaro.
I'm glad I was born or
it would have been better if I had never been born...
I would say it's good that I was born. Thank you.
Is it already done? There's nothing wrong
What happened last night wasn't your fault
I was bitten by a crazy person
I'm leaving.
Cheer up
What happened?
Some young people were playing a prank on her
See you.
This is tough business.
Hey
Hey, this ship called KiteMaru?
Is this the ship with the sick person?
Thank you for your hard work. I was waiting to see
I don't even know what it's like?
She often gets dizzy
Because of postpartum
Okay, look, I'll take a look
Be careful.
Thanks.
It's narrow?
How're you?
Do you get a headache?
It's especially bad on cloudy days
Is it necessary to keep the ceiling closed during the day?
I have a strange thing to ask
Hey, this ship is sometimes used for gambling, so that's why the ceiling is set
I'm not part of it 'cause I've got the baby out the whole time
The ceiling is closed so it's stuffy.
when you give birth,you will go to the village, it's too cramped on the ship
Doctor, if I'm not here, it's worrying
She thinks I go play often.
Take care.
See you tomorrow night.
Hold on.
This is something small.
but it's a souvenir
Thanks.
I'm keeping quiet about the gambling
Oh my, what a waste!
Who was that?
The doctor is here, right?
He's not here.
He'll probably be back soon. I'll have to wait
Today is a holiday
I know,
Omachi.
let's go home, don't cut your finger.
You go home.
Please let's go home
Please stop it
No.
then do as you please
Do whatever you like.
So you're mad? Don't be mad
Doctor, I want you to give
me an anesthetic injection.
anesthetic injection?
Please stop it.
It's none of your business.
there was some kind of happening?
So you cut off your fingers.
It's obligation.
It's painful
Yakuza world is hard, come in.
Doctor.
ladies, stay away
Have a seat.
You are with Sai?
No, just a woman.
She's a mistress?
Your name is?
Kakichi
How old?
I'm 24 years old,
Kakichi-kun. My son was also 24 when his finger gets cut
So he was a playboy after all?
in battle field.
He died in battle
In the Burma.
A comrade who survived cut off his little finger, put it
in a bonfire, turned it into bones, put it in a container, and brought it back to me
If I shake the container like this, it makes a rattling noise
The sound of bones is a lonely sound.
How's Your parents?
They live in the countryside
If you cut your finger, I recommend putting a container
of Mentholatum in it and sending it off to them.
I'm sure your mother will do like this
I am not here to listen about it.
I need the injection.
Oh I’m sorry.
Doctor.
What?
Look at this.
75000...sorry We are closed today.
Can you please think about it again?
Which is more important, your fingers or your obligations?
I don't wanna make a mistake.
so if you don't like it, that's fine
There's more than one doctor here
Are you going to another clinic?
I can't stand the obligation
But I'll think about it again
Let's go home.
Dinner is ready
Let's have a drink and go to bed.
Then I got a call from the police
from the police?
Apparently someone suddenly fell ill at the police jail.
I can't have a drink...
I got eggs. Look!
This is broken.
Is it stylish? This is nice
Can I have my hair cut too?
Please…
It won't take times?
Sure
Thank you for your hard work.
Apparently someone is sick
I think she was faking it.
Today is a holiday, What's the hell?
Even if you know it's a fake, you need to examine.
This is the woman who was with the criminal last night
Did you catch the culprit?
I caught it by myself, but it was so hard.
The main culprits and accomplices are the tough guys.
It was hard.
A hat was a clue.
According to the victim's testimony, the criminal was wearing a hat with the top flattened.
It was around noon and I saw the man and
the woman with it in front of the market
The moment we passed each other, I felt something.
I doubted them.
I'm hungry
I followed them for a while and noticed that they had gotten away
Stop!
There is something I want to ask you.
Thief!
Wait, somebody catch that woman!
Help me.
Damn it.
I wonder if...
They are the criminals?
It hurts.
She's always like that.
When she entered the detention, she suddenly
complained of stomach pain and I had to let her rest
She shouted that it was a violation of human rights
It's democracy
Anyway, please check her out.
Let me see what's wrong
It hurts so much?
That's strange, your pulse is
normal and you don't have a fever,
but doctor, it hurts
It hurts.
Stick out your tongue.
it's a nice color.
You have a nice tongue.
It hurts.
I've already done
Hold on.
there's no need to embarrass a woman.
Is this a temptation? Stripping is not uncommon for doctors
Are you going home now?
I can't cure your fake illness
What's about the faking?
You won't know if you like the sound unless you try hitting  the drums.
It's a violation of human rights to pretend to
be ill without even a proper medical examination
You are idiot doctor.
Have you done it?
She?
She's  called in as a witness.
Is she going back to Osaka?
She's saying she can't go back to Osaka anymore
So she's staying with Yukawa for a while.
Yukawa?
She went to your clinic  this morning, right?
She really felt sorry for that girl
She said she'd stop her if she had nowhere to go.
Where is Yukawa house?
It's the tenement house behind the police box.
It's near Baya's house
That's right. It's on the outskirts of that tenement house
It's that guy. That guy is the culprit.
Hey, there are scars on your forehead
I'll take care of you
Look, here is a wound, here is one too
Here too.
I'll take care of you
Hey, why did you that?
Poor thing
The dreams of young girls have not been cruelly crushed by you.
People like you, it's best to go to the jail.
Please go to the hospital and fix that posture
I would hit you.
Idiot.
I just got a call from home
It seems that a Patients with appendicitis was carried out again
We are closed today.
Baya also refused, but someone was curried.
What?
That's breaking and entering.
Anyway, Doctor is not staying home
There's a clinic ahead called Yokota, so please go that way
But they said.
They looked at my appearance.
The room was full
Is here too?
I'll wait.
Stay strong, I guess I'll make you easier
I don't want to get you too comfortable though
What's wrong?
Doctor
I thought I'd ask you to do (surgical) operation.
Wait please
Wait, today is a holiday and there are no nurses
It's none of my business.
I was a medic in the military
So I can assist you.
This looks like a lot of pain
When did she become ill?
She often get caecum.
But this time it happened again and it's been so serious.
Did you leave it alone?
She tried to heal herself.
She was drinking a lot.
What did she drink?
It's a burdock and carrot drink.
According to her
Chickweed waters the rotten appendix
The burdock turned that water into gas
I don't know it works.
Yeah.
Come on.
Be careful.
Turn to the right
Call Yokota clinic and borrowed a nurse.
It must be hard for you.
It can't be helped, it's a business that takes responsibility for people's lives
I'll get another half
Doctor, You drunk a lot tonight
I was unlucky today.
She's home.
where did you go? You're late
What? Momotaro ? Shunzo is here
Good evening,
what do you want to do, Shunzo?
SOS
SOS?
Mr. Kozuka will be a birth.
The midwife came but
The baby hasn't been born, so I was asked for help
The baby is too big.
She has left now.
SOS.
Where it is?
It's in the neighborhood.
You are drunk now.
It's SOS.
Doctor.
Baya.
Something might have happened
I got sick of it, seriously
Then, Doctor, Yoko said hello
I hear she's already causing trouble for you
I respect her.
What?
Yuko is a typist who types 100 words per minute
It's so fast!
Writing letters with typewriter is your hobby
So I'm going to have Yuko bring to my company
We need a typewriter.
SOS.
Sorry, Please guide me.
I rent a car.
Can you drive?
That's good.
You're drunk so much.
there's no need to worry
before the war, no matter how I drunk.
I drove himself to the site
Doctor.
I had a surgery after drinking a lot,
but the next morning
I couldn't even remember how I had the surgery
I thought this was bad, so I woke up and rushed over to the hospital,
but the patient was given proper treatment
Occupation is consciousness, that's what I came here for
Here it is.
Yuko-san? What's wrong?
It's not Yuko-san
It's Kozukai-san.
Watch out.
Over here.
A Mitaka Station express train leaves from platform 2
Please hurry up
Here it is.
I guess we'll take the train after all.
No, it's this way
Good evening, Keep sleeping.
It's getting so late.
Sorry I'm late,How's her?
You must be hungry.Have a meal.
I've made your nightgown.
Sorry, this part is still bad
Have a meal.
Sorry to worry you too much.
Don't be sad.
I heard from Matsuki about the details.
It's like a procession of disasters
If you think too much about it, it'll just come back to haunt you
I walked in the dark, stepped in the mud, and got my best kimono a little dirty
I have to be back in Osaka?
Don't worry, Yuko?
I can't go back to Osaka either. I have no where to go.
Why you come to Tokyo...
All personnel, please report to your assigned stations.
According to information from the emergency headquarters,
about 300 people are aiming for official documents
Stop it.
Enemy's current location is Muffin-san
Southern medicine, each state, you
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
I’m sorry.
Your attitude is bad.
It's military music.
Break up.
Come in.
Good night aunty.
I'm home.
Keirin,again?
Omachi.
It is so profitable.
That's why you're asking me to lend you some capital.
You are Take-san from Tadonya
why you don't make Tadon?
tadon shops make tadon..
I know.
You're in bad mood.
I decided to write a letter tonight.
Who is this for?
For Kakichi.
It's over now
It's all over
There's no need to deal with someone like that, he is idiot
It's okay to go to bed now
I don't need.
OK OK.
It's your fault because you are sloppy.
What's the big deal?
When our dad died, you didn't have any money
so you couldn't give him a funeral
That's terrible.
There's nothing more embarrassing than this
So I close my eyes, close my eyes
Omachi, are you ok?
That's why I get dizzy sometimes.
Dizziness? Pull yourself together
If you're not feeling well, you need to see a doctor
Who earn the money?
So I'll lend you money.
You're good bros.
Good evening, thank you for the rear cart
Are you fighting?
You're just a kid and you
say unnecessary things.
Shun-chan?
There is soba noodles there. Eat it
Shun is back.
Good night.
The next day, the Mikumo Hospital will be busy as usual.
Excuse me.
I'm in hurry.
Are you here for a examine?
I need a (surgical) operation
(surgical) operation?
What's wrong?
I'm fine
So what kind of surgery is this?
I want you to remove this tattoo.
That's woman's name.
She's older than I.
I was threatened and got a tattoo. I have to go home, but I can't go home because of this tattoo
My father scolds me. My father is strict
I was threatened and got a tattoo
Wait a minute
Doctor, There's a patient.
An emergency?
He's a student.
He need to have his tattoo removed.
He's idiot.
He's still student.
Apparently, he was threatened by an older woman.
He's becoming more and more stupid
Would you decline?
I'll remove it out. Maybe he's trying to get out of this stupid life
Good morning.
Good morning
I'll be doing the tattoo surgery,
so please take it easy today
You'll make up for the last night?, yesterday I was so tired
as soon as you left, I visited there.
Sorry to hear that.
I went to the site late at night, but what was that all about?
The baby was too big, right?
Yes but...
but I wonder what kind of treatment I did..
Damn it.
Hey.
Taki?
Hurry up.
Baby is big. please prepare the stuff.
You are here.
Kaozukai?
Hello.
I was just thinking of picking you up from here
Is the sick person serious?
I'm talking about the (surgical) operation fee
our salary is due at the very end of the month
Don't worry about the fee.
How's the sick person?
I really don't know..
Where is the woman of childbirth?
I'm glad
Oh, Kozukai-san, Give me water.
Sorry about the fee.
I need water.
On the way back, I took a detour and went out to the bank
I thought I'd visit him.
Stupid.
It's not good to move the ship for her.
The boatman was probably worried about the bills and gambling.
The Doctor!
How's Yuko?
Is she feeling better?
she came to the office with Shunzo this morning
But Doctor, I feel sorry about her.
You know a lot of women.
If you have a good woman, please introduce us.
Ok I get it
Please…
Are you going home?
I'm going to see another one.
Up ahead is a mansion called Minoshima
and they refer to this visit as sankin-kotai (alternate attendance)
That was for the housewife of this mansion, who is over forty years old
This is because once a month, doctors are forced to imitate historical events that are almost meaningless for the sake of maintaining beauty.
why did you listen to Minoshima ?
He has nothing, don't deal with him.
Omachi, I'm heading to Minoshima now.
I can't stop feeling sick from the river
For what?
I'm upset.
I'll hit him.
Don't do that.
It's none of your business.
Omachi.
isn't it Miyajima's fault?
You are sick these days.
Leave it to me.
Madam, Madam, do you know a man called Kakichi?
I don't know a man like that
He came here to see Minojima.
He is out too,
He says his wife is okay with it
but she's sick
When I told him, he got angry.
he'd gone home?
No.
You're an idiot.
I'm busy today. See?
ma'am, Dr. Mikumo has come
Oh, Dr. Mikumo, I've been waiting for you.
Please come in.
Have a seat.
You are absolutely great.
I always look younger than Yamada-san's wife
But She's older than 4 years.
Yamada's wife is the same age as me
I mean, Yamada's wife is about 6..
Yamada's wife lied about her age by 4 years?
That means I've lost one cutting
What a shame.
What's wrong?
That man is here.
You are noisy. I know, I'm going
Please wait a moment, sir.
It's okay
I'm the wife of Minoshima.
I came to get compensation.
Why?
What do you mean?
settlement for Omachi.
Your must know what Minoshima did to Omachi.
I know.
At that time, I scold him.
Even though he had a wife.
But he played around.
It doesn't matter .
I mean settlement for Omachi.
What's your name?
I'm  Kakichi.
I don't know what kind of person you are, but
What do you mean by settlement?
I didn't think Minoshima did something bad to her.
He paid her.
Shut up!
Don't say ridiculous things
He cheated her for very little money
He used her weakness.
Kakichi.
please don't speak too loudly
calm down.
Be quiet.
Ok?
You don't have to join us.
Eh, don't be violent
Ok?
Oh.
Don't violent.
Is it dangerous to bring up such a knife?
Please be quiet
I won't accept it if you suddenly jump out.
You're noisy.
What are you guys doing?
Feel free to tell me how much you want?
50,000 to 100,000?
150000?
Hey.
poor thing, it's all gone
Are you leaving?
that's smarter. It's still boring if you get hurt.
The customer is leaving.
Get back.
Say hello to Omachi-san
Doctor.
He's an idiot.
He's  fool but Miyajima did something bad.
He's so bad.
Good luck.
thank you very much.
Omachi-san, are you just overworked?
She collapsed at the store?
When I came home from work,
She felt dizzy and had to run to the side of the road
I was so surprised that I immediately called my Doctor
Is it better for sick people to cool their heads with ice?
Listen.
She needs to have surgery right away.
What surgery?
The baby in her belly is dead
She has baby.
So the rumors about Minojima were true.
The sooner the surgery the better
Patient is worried about surgery and hospital fees
Please tell him and take her to the hospital right away
They can pay me later.
Thanks very much.
I told him to bring her over right away
Please.
Thanks very much.
You will be hospitalized and undergo surgery
You don't have to worry about money
The Doctor said so too
All you have to do is get stronger, earn some money, and pay him.
I don't mean to sound arrogant
He's been waiting me  for 18 years.
But.
I'm the one who's worse off than poor
You should listen to me.
What are you doing?
Where did you go?
Now I've made some money myself,
so you went to play pachinko again
Omachi is going to be hospitalized
She'a going to have surgery
Surgery?
Yes.
You are lazy and always makes her a pain.
You have a work but
but it looks like a festival lantern
You always hang around.
You are scam of men.
I thinks so too
What? are you even going to let me have you fool me?
Get out.
Give it back to me.
Visit her.
Yes.
Are you alright?
She's sick.
Get well.
Stop it, Yusaku-san
It has been rainy days since Omachi was hospitalized
Do you visit her?
How's her?
She's going well. I got the stitches out last night
Thanks.
By the way, about the (surgical) operation fee..
There's something happened.
the kid has the mumps
So please wait.
Don't worry.
It it big bag.
Look, these are her clothes.
See you.
Sorry to disturb you.
Doctor,he is annoying.
He's crazy.
What?
every time he see a woman's face, he always talks dirty.
People with same room are also having trouble.
That's bad.
He's crazy.
I want to hear some old love stories to kill time
I wanna hear.
That's rubbish.
You look like You'd done something like that
That's not true, that's ridiculous,
it's not enough
how old is you?
What are you asking my age?
You look nice
it would be a waste
It's none of your business.
No, that's not true
I like women who have experience like yours.
What are you doing?
It's great that you're doing well, but this is a hospital
And be mindful of your roommates.
I get it.
I'll definitely pay for the surgery
Of course you'd have to pay
This is not a charity hospital
I get it.
Anytime is fine.
Lieutenant General Okazaki is here.
Again?
military doctor
Lieutenant General Okazaki is here.
Thanks for your hard work.
We have wounded soldiers.
You have wounded soldiers?
Is someone injured?
It's an airman
It's an airman?
Please come right away.
He's in pain.
Hurry up.
Where are you going?
Where is he?
He's at my base.
This is it.
Is he injured?
He's back.
I see, He is airman, a child, a boy airman.
He was shot with a gun.
He's got injured.
Is he going to get better?
It won't serious much
Stay down.
you're an Imperial soldier, aren't you?
What are you doing, Doctor?
It's duck?
This is an eagle.
You've had a hard time
Take good care of him.
Did you finish your work?
I'm off today.
I heard that Yuko were able to get a job.
Doctor, Yuko really is a talented person.
She was immediate employed.
So you go together every day
Yuko is making our lunch now
She'll deliver it to her mother in the hospital
Then, on the way back, you two should go to see a movie.
But Yuko said she does not want to go see a movie. She wants to take some commemorative photos
What's that?
It's a commemorative photo of a new start.
But Doctor, that's so realistic and serious
That's weird.
I was a romantic when I was young like you
I wanted to be in the photo with some girl.
So, Yuko is a romantic and masculine?
She's feminine and classic.
Get ready to cook.
Is he your patient?
What are you doing?
What did he eat?
Go to buy it.
Is your lunch ready?
I asked Shunzo to go out and run an errand,
so I'll deliver it
Are you feeling better now?
Isn't your job hard?
Shunzo-san is very kind to me.
so that's fine
Some people become pessimistic and angry when disaster happened.
but they are the ones lacking courage
They are so timid,
Doctor. How's Omachi?
Don't worry
She'll be able to leave the hospital in about a week,
so I'll get it when you can
Where's doctor?
can you reply me at least ?
He's having a bath.
A bath?
Baya?
It's not hot enough.
Really?
Hurry up.
It looks delicious.
I looked it earlier.
Its sesame sprinkles are very tasty!
It is so well seasoned and delicious!
Have some.
Yuko is very good cook.
But there are a few things that I worry.
What?
Yuko is just an ordinary girl
Women who are good at cooking are troublesome.
That's the first time I've heard of such a word.
But is there anything like that happening to Yuko?
No way.
Since Yuko-san came to my house, My son has stopped writing letters to people.
I am worried that He may start to heat up.
In fact, that's a good thing, isn't it?
It's not so bad to have an older wife
Do you mean that they have to get married?
In fact, that's a good thing, isn't it?
But Yuko is....
What's wrong?
I'll go make some tea
Are you trying to claim her what happened the other day?
It's not her fault.
That kind of thing won't change Yuko's worth.
But ..
you don't want her to be the wife of your son?
Didn't you feel sorry for her?
You told me to find a wife for your son.
That is certainly true, but...
What's wrong?
I don't care
But.... Yuko Apparently his father lives in Osaka
Maybe her dad is against it
Not at all. I'm sure her dad would be happy to hear about it
You think so?
This is really a problem,
Have some.
Are you not going to eat anymore?
Well then
I'm sorry
Omachi.
Doctor,Omachi is here.
What's wrong?
Patient with appendicitis is missing.
Don't move.
Oh my god.
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
Gosuke!
Are you alright?
Stay strong.
what happened?
An appendectomy patient escaped.
Run away?
I thought she was strange.
So she brought something like this
Apparently she ran away with rear car.
I was careless.
No.
It's my fault.
I was the same room.
Don't think too much.
It's Shunzo's fault.
It was no good leaving it there.
Even so,
She suddenly disappear...
No,  I'll have to pay for it at the hospital.
I'm in trouble.
I can't even pay for hospital or surgery fees.
If you did that, I wouldn't be able to stay here.
That's not good
Then we'll both be responsible for the rear car and have the
hospitalization fee deducted from the rest of the money,
so you can stay in the hospital without worry
But I'm not being that selfish.
Please prepared a injection.
You'll just have to be patient for another week, so you are going to bed quietly
Promise me.
I'm sorry,
I'm glad
22 and 23...
What happened?
Was the thief caught?
It's no good, as expected he was missing.
The address is unknown.
You see someone who is poor and you immediately have sympathy for them.
However, while the wealthy can go to any hospital on their own,
the poor cannot do that
It may seem simple, but It can't be helped.
Have a drink?
Come on.
it's boring to be doctor.
You think so?
Doctors are so busy worrying about the hospital from morning to night
that they don't have time to think about themselves
Their life and  happiness,
I thought about that there was a better business.
I thought there was a better life.
So what happened?
I won't do anything about it then. I got a wife. It's a dream that everyone has in their youth
when you get a wife and forget about it.
You think so?
Why don't you get a wife?
I agree.
Who are you talking about?
Don't hide it, I know, Taki.
Yes.
Uncle.
Are you calling me?
Are you asleep already?
Yes,
what happened to the patient in second floor?
Her body temperature was 38.5.
It's still high.
Rest her for a while, so be careful.
You go to bed too.
It's ringing again. Please answer.
It's Mikumo Hospital, a grocery store in front of the station? Are you giving birth?
That Doctor is now sleeping.
tomorrow morning ok?
Yes, I understand. take care.
She gives birth a lot.
This will be 8th baby.
There's many case like that these days.
People don't have the ability to properly raise babies.
That's bad.
Rather than giving birth, they should think about whether they can raise a child happily
That is true parental love
Let's go to sleep.
Anyway, since they were born, everyone should be happy
Even their parent, a child, a man, or anything like that.
I can't make my baby happy.
That's not true
No matter what happens, as long as you have a good feeling, you are entitled to happiness.
That's right, that wasn't the case, Women are miserable
Stay strong.
Let's get stronger, be happy, and give the nuts back.
We had the same disaster
Let's be happy.
Who?
I thought I should have come sooner.
I just couldn't come up with the money
You need money for the hospital.
Leave it to me
I made mistake at Minoshima's house.
I have other ideas. Please wait.
Don't worry.
Hospital charges were secured by a rear car.
rear car?
So you don't need to worry about that anymore
My illness was Minojima fault, as you say
I'm glad about what you say.
Omachi.
Let's go to the countryside when you get better.
I'm thinking of getting out of the Yakuza business
My Yakuza boss really wants me to cut off my finger.
I don't mind if I lose one finger.
But the doctor told me.
My mother's wrinkled face flashes before my eyes
I wanted to go back to the country
My mom is doing business by herself, so I'll help her
Please take me.
I don't do gambling and the blackmail anymore.
Today is my day off.
Yusaku was allowed to participate as a carrier.
Hurry up.
Let's fish here.
Take care of it gently.
My tegusu is missing.
Where's my tegusu?
I forgot to bring Tegusu.
Where did you leave it?
I have no idea.
If you know, I'll get it.
I left it next to the phone.
next to the phone?
There was call this morning.
I was on the phone and left it there
It is at the phone definitely.
Are you alright?
I think it's best to think of it as a hike.
Yes, that seems more romantic to you guys
Let's go.
No.
Doctor, Yuko is romantic and nice.
Women are very moody.
She's feminine and classic.
Yuzo!
Here we go
They make fun of me.
Lieutenant Okazaki
We took a rest.
Tegus?
Where is it?
On your head.
These are my white hairs.
This is Tegus.
This is not your white hair.
It hurts.
This?
Don't make fun of me.
Wait!
Where's Yuko?
I won't let you run away. Hey, wait
Stop it.
That is my white hair.
Give me.
Cut it out.
It hurts.
This is Tegusu.
I'm sick of him.
I should have brought him.
How about this?
I'm pretty sure I left this under the phone
I was once again invited to a strange party.
Yes, yes, the chief of the police station?
Hisao? Ok I get it.
Is there a reason for this?
No at all
As a police officer, I would like to ask you a favor.
So have a drink.
Thanks.
President
Well then, excuse me for a moment,
Ready?
Come on, wanna play?
Make your bid.
I liked it.
What's wrong?
Keep going.
Excuse me for a moment
Let's prepare for a party.
Let's have fun.
Sake is more important than words
Music start!
What's the hell?
Bid it!
Ok come on!
Hold on.
Hey.
What's wrong?
it's a fight again.
I'm tired.
Forgive me.
The police officer is trying to make the idiot let his guard down
You are a cart thief. Your actions are cowardly.
Stop!
I returned it.
Hey! Get down!
Wait!
It's cold
You are the boatman of that ship.
I told you not to play gambling.
Your wife is sick so where have you been?
Sorry,
Oh you are Kakichi?
What's this situation?
Didn't you get over your Yakuza business?
Weren't we supposed to go back to the country with Omachi?
I just wanted the hospital fee.
hospital fee?
I feel sorry for him having to be hospitalized because he can't afford the hospitalization fees
So you made the gambling?
Stupid!
He's stupid.
You too should really think about what you say about.
You guys need to reflect on this.
Something has happened!
What happened?
Omachi has came back home
Why you make her do that?
sickness won't get better.
director of the hospital went to doctor's visit
Nurse is laundry ,Baya is sleeping.
In the meantime it happened.
It's your fault.
You're the one who stole the rear car.
I gave it back.
You don't have to do unnecessary things like that
Omachi might not be able to stay in the hospital.
The rear car is back?
Omachi was relieved that the amount was deducted from her hospitalization fee and the rear car.
She'll have to pay the hospital fees when the rear car get back.
He did something unnecessary and ruined her idea.
Excuse me, please
Please help her
Let's go.
Let's go
military doctor
The airmen have left.
I'm busy.
Watch out.
Please come in.
What's wrong?
She has acute pneumonia.
I've given her penicillin and a coagent.
Her Fever is 40.
Why you are not in the hospital
You were about to cure.
I'm going back to my trip, but I can't stop the gold color
But when I think about how Omachi-san is feeling,
tears come to my eyes
Omachi don't wanna die.
She's poor now so...
Please help her life.
I am always giving her trouble and I'm so stupid man.
but I still love her.
Doctor, look, Take-san is crying
Doctor, Omachi won't get better?
I'm sorry, Doctor
I'm sorry.
I promised you.
but it's okay, I know
I just wanted you to spoil me a little more like a daughter
I've wanted that...
I felt sorry.
Omachi, you have to be strong.
You promised me.
You have to be happier.
Doctor, She won't get better?
What do you think, Gosuke?
I think she'll be fine.
If she'll never do something stupid like tonight again
So Doctor, She will be okay?
My sister will be saved?
Because Kakichi has asked me...
I can't let her die.
Thank you very much.
I see.
military doctor
The airman is finally missing
It's probably because his wounds have healed and he has returned
He's a boy airman, so I guess he went back to his parents
He returned...
Go back to your dorms quickly and have a good night's sleep.
She's sick.
Please be quiet
Stop!
What's going on?
Everyone gather round. Do
you understand? Hurry up.
It can't be helped.
It's superior's orders.
Please take care of the rest.
Yuko-san.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
What's the hell?
Baya.
I'll tell you guys.
Today, I have wisely requested this.
I really appreciate of that.
Please have it with your all heart.
I'm giving you.
Open your mouth.
lieutenant colonel
He's an airman.
They ended up going back to their home.
Look,
there's a father, a mother,
and siblings - what a happy airman.
So now we are going to see off the airmen.
You're music solider.
Yusaku!
THE END