Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hyoheki / The Precipice (1958)
Welcome.
Were you going to the mountain again?
I went up to the top of the Gofuku mountain.
Not many people there anymore?
There were only two groups.
I came straight from the mountains.
I want to eat something tasty.
How about salmon egg?
That's good.
Welcome.
Were you going to the mountain again?
Mr. Kosaka was here a while ago.
Yes, unusually, he didn't drink, but ate dinner and left.
I see.
I wanted to see him.
He said he was meeting someone on the second floor of TOKIWA Kaikan.
I guess he is still there.
May be.
Hey.
Oh you.
Is there such a greeting?
I'm waiting for someone here.
Where'd you go?
Mt.Godaka.
Alone?
Who are you waiting for?
You look like you've been waiting a long time.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is Mr. Uozu, my friend from the mountains.
I'm Yashiro.
Have a seat.
I'm so sorry I called you here.
No, it's fine.
What's so urgent?
I have something for you.
What is it?
I'll give it to you later.
He's my mountain buddy from school.
Don't worry about him.
Look at this.
What's this?
You'll be home, and then you'll open it.
I have to go.
Why don't you have a cup of tea?
I'm tired.
I have to go.
Sit down.
You can stay here for five or ten minutes.
I just came by to take a look at your face.
See you.
Uozu.
I finally caught up with you.
Where are you headed back to?
Omori.
I am in Denenchofu.
We're going in the same direction, and if it's not too much trouble, I'd be happy to walk you home with you.
Where's Kosaka?
I just left him there.
Actually, there's something I'd like to discuss with you.
I didn't have any intention of doing so before I saw you.
I suddenly had that feeling.
Taxi.
Go to Denenchofu.
Thanks.
Please.
Did you hear something about me and Mr. Kosaka?
No.
I just returned a letter to Mr. Kosaka.
It was given to me by Mr. Kosaka over the past two years.
I appreciate his kindness, but I'm in trouble.
I'm married.
How long have you known Kosaka?
About four years now.
This was before I married into the Yashiro family.
We didn't see each other for a while after I got married.
We met by chance at Christmas the year before last.
Then we met again.
How do you say Kosaka?
He asked me to divorce and be with him.
And you?
I'm in trouble.
I have a favor to ask.
I was wondering if you could tell Mr. Kosaka.
Yes, I will.
If you're right, Kosaka's attitude is insane.
Isn't that right?
Is there anything about your relationship that you haven't told me?
For example, you really like Kosaka or something.
No.
But.
But?
I think Kosaka may have misunderstood me.
Like I said I have affection for him.
Why?
Haven't you clearly stated your feelings?
I have told him many times.
Then he knows exactly how you feel.
I don't know what it is about you two.
It's not love, of course.
I had sexual relations with Kosaka once.
It was foolish of me, and I made a terrible mistake.
That's why I can't say no strongly enough.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
When did you get home? This morning?
No, last night.
Why do I climb mountains?
Because the mountains are there.
Climbing the mountain
Step by step we climb higher and higher. You carry heavy things on our backs.
That's a lot of work.
It's not a lot of money from this tiny company.
You spend most of your monthly salary on the mountains.
That's great.
In his hometown, his aging parents want to get a wife for their college-educated son.
But their son is too lazy to get a wife
He climbs mountains in his spare time
He spends all his time in the mountains
Unlike you, we like to climb down from high places step by step
On the other hand, every time I move my feet, I lower myself that much lower.
The stable part comes down from the unstable part.
This is at least more natural.
it's because of your age.
My age?
Don't joke about that, boy.
You mean, When you're young you want to climb high.
When you're old, you want to climb down?
That's not the point.
It's whether you like it or not.
I don't understand how you can avoid step by step from human beings and climb up to the heights.
Osaka headquarters is on the phone, sir.
Why you told me earlier?
You mentioned it with too much enthusiasm.
Yamada.
Put this and this in tomorrow's ad.
I appreciate the order from headquarters, but from the standpoint of the Tokyo office...
We can't just accept an order from an executive without questioning it.
Hello,
ToKo publisher?
Is Kosaka there?
Uozu?
What's wrong?
I need to see you for a minute right now.
I'll take my side.
I'll be out in half an hour.
Wait for me out front.
What do you want to talk about?
I ran into Mrs. Yashiro after I left you last night.
I took a cab to her house.
Thanks.
That's when she asked me to do something for you.
I thought it would be something like that.
At that time, she was in a hurry to get home, so I thought maybe she was chasing you.
What she said?
I'll tell you exactly what I heard.
In short, she wants to break things off with you.
No I can't.
Why?
I think just having some sort of connection with that lady is what keeps me alive.
I can't imagine myself no longer having any relationship with that person.
I wonder if I won't be able to survive?
Don't scare me.
No, it's true
But she is someone's wife
I think your way of thinking doesn't make sense.
I've been out of line from the beginning.
It's a mess.
It's true.
I don't like that you agree with me so honestly.
But is that what love is all about?
She only cares about the world.
She's letting her feelings show.
She didn't say that.
She said you misunderstood her.
Misunderstood?
Well, the way I see it, she doesn't....
she doesn't....love me?
No.
I knew it.
But it's a lie.
How do you know it's a lie?
Whose side are you on, anyway?
I'm not taking sides.
You're just trying to keep me away from Mrs. Yashiro.
I would if I could.
You love her too?
Sorry.
That was a gaffe.
I'm excited.
She once told me outright with her mouth that she loved me.
On Christmas Eve.
What kind of a woman says she loves me if she doesn't love me?
How is it possible that love can so easily disappear without a trace in the heart of a single person?
But she has no intention of leaving her husband at the moment.
I don't think so.
She's married to an old man thirty years older than she.
They live a loveless life in the name of matrimony.
I got it.
From her?
Good morning.
I'll leave the tea here for you.
I wanted tomato juice.
Oh, you don't like tea?
It's ok.
Okay, I'll bring you some tomato juice.
Tea's fine.
You're making meal, right?
It will still take 10 minutes.
This tea smells a little like leeks.
Does it smell?
Well, I'll go change it.
It's ok.
You probably have the smell of leeks on your fingers.
Did you see it?
For what?
No, it's okay.
I'll be home late tonight.
What's up?
I have a nuclear work study meeting.
See you.
From your house.
It's me.
What's wrong?
Stop working.
OK.
What's wrong?
I was getting worried.
About what?
You knew I pinched a tea pole with my finger this morning, didn't you?
If you saw me, you should have reprimanded me.
I don't like the way you say that.
It smells a little like leeks.
That's fine.
You didn't mean to be bad.
You were trying to get the tea pole.
That's why your fingertip touched it a little.
Well, it can't be helped, can it?
You think so?
I don't see any malice in it.
I don't think there's anything to be blamed for.
I'll hang up.
There's nothing else that you don't like.
About what?
Besides the tea pole.
Besides the tea pole?
What do you mean?
I'll hang up.
This is Yashiro.
Hello, this is Uozu.
Thank you for the other day.
May I visit you with Kosaka now?
You two?
Kosaka wants to see you one last time.
We've discussed many things.
I'm sure he won't do anything to offend you.
If it's convenient for you, why don't you come down to the station?
It would be better at my house.
Welcome.
Come in.
I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused you, but I've made up my mind.
I came here today because I didn't want to leave without seeing you.
I’m sorry.
You're not the only one who's sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Don't say sorry.
We will be miserable.
I just need you to do one thing for me.
You promised not to say anything.
Don't worry.
Are your feelings really as you described them to Uozu?
I wonder if you have a little bit of love for me.
I hate to say this, but...
I think I was affectionate that night.
But at other times...
You say you don't have it?
But if that's the case, then we can't trust the human heart too much, can we?
You said yourself... that you loved me.
Stop it....
I honestly believed it!
We talked so much last night, and you agreed with me.
I mean, you're not even related to me as a person.
I just know that you want to be a person who passes by me on the road.
Uozu, I'm going home first.
No, I'm leaving too.
I want to go home alone.
Kosaka
Regardless of Kosaka's attitude
What he said sounds reasonable.
As he says, there is a lie on your part.
I have told you my shame.
I will tell you anything you want to know.
I have not lied to him.
I made a mistake... at night... but I think I was in love with him.
My husband was in Kansai for a month.
We ate at a restaurant in Ginza and walked around the city on Christmas Eve.
I was the one who told him I wanted to have a drink.
When he asked me out at the hotel, I didn't refuse.
But on the way home, I was so miserable I wanted to cry.
I had only loved him for a short time.
I knew I would regret it later.
I knew I would be accused of being a married woman.
But I wanted him.
Ma'am...
Let's put this matter to rest.
Kosaka may suffer for the time being.
But time will tell.
Besides, we're going to the mountains at the end of this year to climb the Mt.Hodaka
Climbing that wall for the first time in years will calm Kosaka's mind.
I'll make you some tea.
Excuse me.
I think Kosaka's walking without taking the train.
I feel sorry for him if he's drinking tea here.
On foot?
Yes.
He'll walk home.
We don't mind walking for two or three hours.
We walked in the mountains when We were a student.
I think he's walking more and more now.
Where's he gone?
December 29
Left Sawando 8:00 a.m. departure
Sakamaki lunch 1 pm
Pass through the Kama Tunnel at 2:30 p.m.
Passed with ease
Kaisho Pond at 15:45
Arrive at the hotel hut at 5:00 p.m.
Feeling somewhat fatigued
Snow temperature -5 degrees Celsius
Uozu.
December 30
Departure from hotel hut
1 foot of snow
9:30 a.m.
Arrive at Myojin
Tokusawa at 11:00 a.m.
Take a break and equipment
Organize food
1:30 p.m. Sat. down of Matsue
Cloudy, sometimes snowy, temperature -6C
Departure at 7:00 a.m. on December 31
Avoiding avalanche danger
Take the Nakahata New Road from the lower part of Maskollunsee
Deep snow,The slope is steep
3:00 p.m.
Arrive at Okumata no Chihan
Pitch the tent at the base of a tree.
It starts to snow.
Temperature minus 18 degrees.
Wind's picking up.
It will stop tomorrow.
If it stops snowing, we'll get up at 3:30 and leave at 5:00.
Hey, wake up.
The stars are out.
That's a lot of stars.
I make zoni every year.
I don't know how it happened, but I've been eating only your zoni for five years.
It's New Year's.
Happy New Year!
I think it's 8:00 a.m. for the north wall.
The north wall.
I wish Minako Yashiro could've seen that wall.
Kosaka.
Don't worry... my feelings are under control.
Tea in the thermos.
Crackers, cheese, chocolate, dried grapes
Pack yokan jelly and other food in each of our sacks
Check and pack the rope, harten, carabiners, hammers, and a stubby rucksack.
This is the first time to use nylon rope.
Departure at 5:30am.
Climbing this 150-meter rock wall
The snow-covered rock wall is challenging us from the other side.
8:00 a.m., drink a cup of tea from the mouth of a thermos and put on the rope
Here we go.
It was the first time to use a 30-meter-long nylon rope.
3:00 After climbing up the North wall, we finally reach the second terrace.
It took 7 hours.
3:30 a.m.: Climbing the A face.
The wind picked up and it was blizzarding.
Climbing is impossible.
We decided to rebark.
Blowing from the front of the blizzard
It's cold and blustery.
We were so tired.
We're in trouble.
It's only 30 meters.
Don't sleep.
I'm not sleeping.
I've been thinking...
For what?
Why do we climb mountains?
Because we like it.
But I don't.
Because I want to escape from the human world.
I risk my life to climb the walls because I want to forget the pain of reality.
I'm a weak man after all.
I guess I'm weak-minded.
2am.
I think the climbers feel the same way I do.
Sometimes you come to the mountains to forget something, don't you?
It could be.
It's 7:30.
Let's do it.
Three hours of fighting, and we'll be on top of the mountain.
I'll take the lead this time.
Let's go!
Let's have a rest.
Kosaka!
What is your relationship with Kosaka?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
Something happened?
Do you have any cream puffs?
Sorry we don't have.
I ate all last night.
How about fruits?
Apple?
I'll have it.
You look unhappy.
I'll do it.
Are you Mr. Kosaka's sister?
Yes.
I am Yashiro.
Oh Yashiro.
Please come in.
Are you going to the mountains?
Yes, I have a colleague who is going to the site, and I'm going with him.
What time will you leave?
The 12:25 train.
Then you don't have much time left.
But please, have some tea.
This is my brother's room.
I don't know how he got into trouble.
I am sure he thought of you in his last moments.
This is one of his favorite pictures.
I'd be happy to take it home with you.
But.
Don't worry.
I'll take this.
This is not good.
Why?
Because Mr. Uozu is here.
Uozu,
You have to sleep.
Kosaka,
You loved this fire.
One day or another, if I die in the mountains.
I will leave this note for you, my old mountain friend
Please see my mother.
Then tell her.
I died happy.
Tell my dad I didn't suffer a bit because I was there for my mom.
Tell my brother I was a man.
Now pass the baton to you.
I couldn't find him.
It was too snow.
It's probably stuck in the snow.
If we search any further, we risk an avalanche.
I'll stay here until spring.
So don't worry.
You'd better get off the mountain and comfort Mr. Kosaka's bereaved family members.
Did you find Kosaka's body?
We are co-worker of his from Tokyo.
Kosaka.
I'll be back soon.
This is the last stop
Forgive me.
He changed the top to cover for me when I was tired.
We were only 10 meters from the finish line.
Let me cry just now.
I will never cry again.
The rope was cut.
I know that.
Are you Uozu?
The rope was cut?
Did the nylon rope break?
That's a lifeline.
Did something go wrong for you?
Tell us about the detail.
Let's hear what veterans of the mountaineering community have to say about nylon ropes
First, Mr. Ichiro Jukuyama, a lineage sports equipment dealer, says
Nylon rope is stronger than ordinary Asa rope and will never break.
It is used by climbers all over the world today.
Also, Mr. Yoshihiko Takekoshi, editor-in-chief of Asahi Shobo says.
The nylon rope is supposed to be unbreakable.
I think there must have been a technical failure somewhere.
Good morning.
You must be terribly tired.
I left my friend up in the mountains.
That's what's killing me.
Winter in the mountains can be scary.
But you went out there knowing you'd be scared, so there's nothing you can do about it.
I'm sorry about your friend.
It just so happens that your friend got the bad end of the stick, not you.
Or maybe both of you would have been died together.
It would be nice you're happy to be home alone.
The rope was broken?
Yes.
Was there any particular sharp rock that you hung it on?
No rope would break because of the sharpness of the rock.
The rope was weak.
I need four or five days off.
I have to go to my friend's hometown and report everything to his mother.
Where?
Sakata in Yamagata.
Let's go.
I'll go soon.
Ok go ahead.
You need money?
Ask our account department..
The guy who just left with the branch manager is Executive Director Tokimatsu from Osaka Headquarters.
He says he's here about nylon rope.
A call from the newspaper.
Oh Uozu?
I ask this not as a reporter, but as a senior member of the mountaineering club.
Kosaka crashed when the rope that bound his body came undone.
As a mountaineer, that's quite a disgrace.
So you defend your friend and say something about the rope breaking or something.
I don't know if that's true or not.
Tell me.
The rope broke.
That guy was Uozu?
He's convinced that the rope was cut, but that's not good.
Sakura Steel, the company that makes the nylon rope, is a major shareholder in our company.
Yeah, I know, they're brother company.
They're very angry.
It can't be helped.
Anyway, Sakura Steel says nylon ropes never break.
But it did break.
I don't know if it's really off or not.
What do you mean?
Maybe there was a malfunction in the handling.
Maybe he stepped on it the night before and scratched it.
Uozu's not a cheap climber.
The rope broke.
Uozu is the only one who knows that.
No one knows.
You can trust him.
Uozu is not the kind of man who lies.
If he says the rope is broken, believe it is broken.
I know his character.
I can't talk with you anymore.
I believe him.
This is going to be a tricky problem.
If the rope breaks, Sakura Steel's credibility will be ruined.
It will be problem.
Uozu
I called your apartment, but I was told you were leaving on this train.
I'm going to Kosaka's hometown.
Top row on the left.
I'd really like to ask you something.
What is it?
I think I may have killed Kosaka-san.
That's not true.
You must not talk about Kosaka to anyone but me.
For Mr. Kosaka's sister too?
Yes.
She may misunderstand I loved Kosaka.
Kosaka is freezing alone in the snow in the mountains right now.
Leave him alone.
See you.
He's Uozu.
Welcome.
This was my brother's playground.
Tomorrow, when the sun shines, I'll take you somewhere else.
I have to go home tomorrow.
I have a duty to perform.
But just for one night?
I'm sure Mother and I will both miss you so much we'll start crying.
I'll go to be first.
Your eyes are getting tired.
Oh,I'm a little tired tonight.
They asked me to test that nylon rope to see if it would break.
It's from Daisaku Tokiwa, the branch manager of Uozu's company.
Why did he ask to you?
Because the nylon in that rope is a product of my company.
Do you think the rope will break in the experiment?
We don't know that, that's why we decided to test it.
What do you think?
We're gonna have to test the rope a bunch of times before we make it.
Well, it won't break.
What happens if it doesn't break?
It's nothing.
It's just a matter of restoring confidence in nylon rope.
What about Uozu's position?
It's going to be difficult.
You told the newspapers that the nylon rope had been cut, and that has irritated headquarters and Sakura Steel quite a bit.
They want you fired.
The rope really was cut.
I know that.
So, for my part, I'd love to do the rope experiment and prove to the world that you're right.
But just to be clear.
You're not going to get yourself in trouble by doing this experiment, are you?
No.
Were there any flaws during your climb?
Or Kosaka-kun can cut it himself.
What do you mean?
Suicide.
Did you see Minako Yashiro?
Yes.
I came to visit while you were at Sakata.
Minako said Kosaka cut the rope to kill himself?
Yes.
So if you do the experiment, the rope probably won't break.
And that's gonna make your position even more difficult.
She insists that us stop the experiment.
What's her relationship with Kosaka?
She was his friend.
I see.
Kosaka would never kill himself in the mountains.
Only the mountain and I know the truth about what really happened.
Hello,Yashiro.
This experimental facility is excellent.
I'm sure you'll feel right.
He's Uozu.
He's Yashiro.
I'm Uozu.
I'm Yashiro.
You are very young.
My wife told me your name.
Now everything will be clear.
The truth will come out.
And your position will be saved.
I'm not certain the rope is cut, though.
Who's going to be there?
There will be two from headquarters and six from Sakura Steel.
And me and you.
You shouldn't be here.
If you show up, the guys at headquarters won't be happy.
Were you asleep?
Yes.
Carefree bastard.
Let's go home.
How was the experiment?
Kyonosuke Yashiro is a good man.
I believe him.
You have to believe in him, too.
Can you believe in him?
Of course I believe him.
The rope didn't break.
The rope was super strong.
Get in the car.
I can't believe it.
I thought the rope break.
But It couldn't.
But....
Don't complain.
Get in the car.
No one trusts your word anymore.
You stand on colder ground than a wall of ice from this day forward.
Mr. Uozu.
You have a visitor.
She's waiting for you in your room.
I'm sorry I went up there without asking.
It's ok.
You look tired.
I'm fine.
I've had too much beer.
The rope?
It didn't break.
It doesn't matter.
You said the rope was cut.
I believe you.
I'm going to the mountains next week with a senior.
To find your brother's body.
If we find your brother's body, it'll settle a lot of silly suspicions.
He would have had a rope tied neatly around his body.
There would have no suicide note.
suicide note?
You think he killed himself?
Some people say that.
Yashiro?
right?
I imagined that my brother and that woman were lovers.
I'm sure that's not true.
Yashiro must be in love with someone else.
He is....
Kaoru.
It doesn't matter.
It's none of my business.
When you come up the mountain next week, can I come with you?
Welcome.
I'm here to see your husband.
He's not here?
He often has meetings on Sundays.
Please come in.
I would have liked to ask him more about the experiment.
Perhaps it would have been better if I had not met him.
I'll see you off.
If Kosaka committed suicide over me, I am not afraid of it.
I am sorry for what happened to Ms. Kosaka, but I had no choice but to do what I did.
No matter how nicely I put it, my relationship with Kosaka is a scandal.
I am the one who should be blamed.
If you are denying Kosaka's suicide in order to protect me...
I don't care if everyone knows about me.
I don't want to cause trouble for you alone.
We may find a red lighter on Kosaka's body, but we will never find his suicide note.
Did you see the lighter?
I'm going back up the mountain tomorrow.
To look for Kosaka's body.
Alone?
With his sister this time.
With her.
I was expecting you yesterday.
She's Kosaka's sister.
Thanks for your work.
I'm sorry.
Yoshikawa,
Uozu is here.
Thanks,senior.
I went to the second terrace yesterday to look for you in earnest, but I couldn't find anything.
We are going to do another search tomorrow from point B.
You're Kosaka-san's sister, right?
You look a lot like her brother.
Isn't that a rope?
Don't touch the rope.
We found his body.
We got his body in the upper middle field.
We'll take it tomorrow.
How about the rope?
It was neatly tied to the body.
Watch out!
They're back.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please burn incense.
I made coffee.
And this is my brother's notebook.
I knew he didn't kill himself.
I'm telling you.
That's what I was thinking tonight as I watched the fire burn my brother.
I am really serious about it.
I'll never be able to say it again if I forget the color of that fire.
For the first time in my life, I'm thinking about marriage.
Don't laugh.
I don't.
I'm telling you.
I wanted to ask you to marry me.
I am really serious about it.
Kaoru,
You're excited, too.
Let's go inside.
Leave me alone.
I don't think I'll be able to sleep tonight.
And?
There was no will, no note, nothing.
Nothing in the diary either.
There was also a rope tied neatly around his body.
I brought it with me because I thought it might lead to some kind of scientific conclusion.
All right.
I'll take this to Mr. Yashiro.
I'll go with you.
I don't think you should go.
I brought the rope that was attached to the body of the person in distress.
You want me to look at it?
Welcome.
This is a layman's idea.
I was wondering if you could take a look at the rope cuts, see if you can find anything new.
I don't think so.
You stay here.
This is it.
Shall I open it?
Leave it as it is.
It's the same when I look at it.
I'm sorry.
Amateurs are funny.
If I looked at this under a microscope, I would immediately discover something very important.
Of course, there are ways to examine rope cuts from various angles.
We may be able to figure out the meaning of the cut to some extent if we look into it.
But even so...
I don't think it will be of much use in solving the rope experiment.
Like the last experiment, it's just to provide the material for judgment.
If that's the way experiments are supposed to be, then maybe you shouldn't have taken on the last one.
I think the idea that the rope was deliberately cut by human hands for the sake of that experiment has been generally accepted.
I was just experimenting.
I don't know anyone who draws conclusions on their own.
That's just human nature.
Someone has been hurt, someone has suffered because of your experiment.
Do you ever think about that?
You don't know the human heart.
Do you believe what Uozu say?
I brought it , and I forced to take it.
I'll leave now.
Excuse me. Hello. Is Mr. Uozu there?
Even if the investigation shows that this cut was worn out by a rocky corner...
We can't write about it in the paper.
It's too old and has no news value.
If you'd like, I can put it in a sports article in one of the corners.
No, thank you.
Tokiwa came to see you today.
I just heard the results from the branch manager.
I think your husband has a point.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it anymore.
How did the rope break?
Only the mountain knows that.
That's all right.
As long as it proves Kosaka didn't kill himself, that's all that matters.
Madam.
The red lighter was burned in the mountains with Kosaka.
I'm not going to see you again.
Why?
It shouldn't be.
I thought to myself, I have to stop what's wrong.
For the sake of two people.
For the sake of two people?
One is a living person and one is a dead one.
Of course, one is Yashiro and one is Kosaka.
Kosaka wanted you to see the cliffs of winter mountain.
If there's someone who wants to show the icy cliffs of Winter Mountain...
I think it's you.
Excuse me.
Welcome back.
I'm sorry to have disturbed you while you were away again.
It's only been five minutes.
I brought my brother's bones to Sakata.
I see...
What's wrong?
You look tired.
No.
You have a blue streak on your forehead.
blue streak?
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
It's a red streak.
I'm sorry, it's not red, it's a yellow streak.
What's wrong with it... red or yellow?
You looked so cold.
If I were Mrs. Yashiro, you wouldn't look like that.
Right?
You're probably right.
Are you leaving?
I came here tonight to ask your answer to my marriage proposal.
But I don't want to.
I'm crying.
It's not because it's hard for you to give up.
I'm sad that I can't give up my life like my brother.
Let's get married.
You don't have to force yourself to get married.
I'm not forcing myself to get married.
I'm getting married because I want to.
But Mr. Uozu, you love Mrs. Yashiro, don't you?
I would hate to have the slightest hint of Yashiro in your mind.
Let's go to the mountains
Let's climb a winter mountain together and wash it all away
I'll climb from the Takase River.
You, as I told you the other day, climb from Kamikochi.
When we meet in the mountains, we'll see a different landscape.
I will be a completely different person from the one I am now.
Then I'll go back to Tokyo and we'll get married.
I'd like to take five days off.
The mountains?
I need a vacation.
Rest your head
You won't get a vacation for the next year.
I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused you this time.
Don't say a word.
Thank you very much.
I'll be waiting for you in Tokugawa on the 13th.
Take care.
This is my brother's camera.
Take it.
see you 13th.
Hello.
I'm Kosaka.
I remember you.
Are you alone?
I'm meeting Mr. Uozu here.
He's coming here from Kitakama.
I see.
He will be here tomorrow.
Please let him stay here.
Sure.
Mr. Uozu is coming.
Come in.
Injured in an avalanche at about 15:30
Unable to move at all due to femur fracture
Intermittent drowsiness of consciousness
I did not pay attention to the abnormality of the new snowball.
In short, it is reckless
I've been in a disaster, and I don't think I'm going to make it.
I'm in this mess again.
No gas at all
The weather is wonderful.
2:15 PM.
No pain at all, no chills
It's quiet, infinitely quiet.
As you all know from the newspapers, our good friend Uozu was lost in Kitakama and was found dead this morning.
Please say a silent prayer for Uozu.
Silent Prayer
If you ask me if Mr. Uozu was a good employee, I hesitate to answer that he was a good employee unconditionally.
He was not an ideal good subordinate, at least not for me.
He took a vacation and climbed a mountain.
He lied and climbed a mountain.
Was the mountain that important to him?
Was the mountain more important to him than the company or me?
If the mountain was so important to him, why didn't he just say so?
That's the one thing he's not good at...
It's all right.
I'll forgive him.
He was a good climber.
You can see it in his notebooks, where he wrote it down exactly.
How did Uozu die?
Well, it's pretty clear. He was a brave climber.
He takes the fight to the places where nature has rejected man, armed with technology and will.
It's a man's fight, to be sure.
But...
Uozu doesn't have to die.
He's idiot!
Uozu's remains are leaving for his hometown in Hamamatsu on the 6 a.m. train tomorrow morning.
Will you go?
I wanted to see Uozu again, but now I can't.
I am sure Uozu is very happy that you did everything for him.
Uozu did it for me when my brother died, so I did it for him this time.
Why don't we have dinner alone sometime?
I'll set the table.
I'll take you home.
No, I'm going to Uozu's apartment now.
I'll go to Uozu's apartment to arrange his stuff.
How about you?
I'm going to town.
Excuse me.
THE END