With.
TAMBA Tetsuro - Lawyer Kikuchi
MATSUZAKA Keiko - SAKAI Hatsuko.
ÔTAKE Shinobu - SAKAI Yoshiko
NAGASHIMA Toshiyuki - UEDA Hiroshi.
Directed by NOMURA Yoshitaro.
THE INCIDENT
My sister was dead in that forest.
While you and I were living in Yokohama!
Forgive me!
I don't know what to say!
But I've come here to see you.
Haven't I?
Will you forgive me?
It's not a question of forgiveness!
Even mother said that I shouldn't come here!
Is our baby inside you alright?
"SNACK BAR OWNER SLAIN BY YOUTH"
"KILLING ONE SISTER.
LIVING WITH THE OTHER ONE"
"YOKOHAMA DISTRICT COURT"
"COURT OF JUSTICE"
"SCHEDULE OF HEARINGS"
Please.
Thank you.
- Good morning.
"JUDGE'S OFFICE"
Good morning.
Do you know the counsel for the defense.
Kikuchi?
We graduated from the same school.
I've met him at gatherings.
How is he like?
He has handled many criminal cases.
Prosecutor Okabe is likely to have
a hard time.
"The two lived together in
a small apartment."
"A brief period of happiness..."
Everything's ready.
Rise!
The trial of defendant Ueda Hiroshi
can now begin.
The charges are: Murder and
abandoning the corpse.
Defendant.
State your name.
Ueda Hiroshi.
Date of birth?
September 10, 1956.
Domicile?
Kanagawa Prefecture.
Tsuchida Town.
No. 28.
What is your correspondence address?
Yokohama.
33 Hara-machi. Isogo Ward.
What is your occupation?
Shipyard worker.
Arraignment.
"The defendant is a worker
at the Shipyard..."
"...located in Yokohama."
"Living in an apartment house..."
"...with his wife Sakai Yoshiko."
"Aged 19.
Second daughter of Mrs Sumie."
"Yoshiko's sister. Hatsuko.
Aged 23."
"Found out Yoshiko was pregnant
and wanted to inform..."
"... Yoshiko's mother and
the defendant's father."
"The defendant started planning..."
"... to kill Hatsuko."
"On March 28th 1976, at 2pm".
"He secretly went to the town of Chogo."
"From the Kikuichi Hardware Store
in that town..."
"... he bought a knife with a 8.5 cm blade."
"At 3:00am The same day..."
"... he stopped at Chogo Motor Co."
"The rental of a light truck for moving
was negotiated."
"Just then Hatsuko passed by."
"He decided to carry out his murder plan."
"He took Hatsuko on his bicycle
and rode with her..."
...up to a dessert spot. Located...
...50 meters south of the
Sarashizawa Crossroad. And then."
"Suddenly. He pulled out his knife..."
"...and plunged it into Hatsuko."
"Inflicting a wound that reached the heart."
"Death resulted from excessive bleeding."
"Then. In order to conceal the crime."
"He dragged the body for about five miles."
"The body was finally dumped in a forest."
The charges are: 1. Murder,
Article 199 of the criminal code,
2. Abandonment of a corpse, Article 190.
Has the defendant anything to say
about the arraignment?
An answer is not mandatory.
Whatever you say. Favorable or unfavorable.
Will be recorded as evidence.
I killed Hatsuko-san.
But that's not why I had bought
the knife for.
I really never planned to kill her.
But...
...Hatsuko was going to tell everything
to Yoshiko's mother.
I wanted to stop that.
I took out the knife.
But I can't understand how it happened.
I must have killed her.
I am ready for the death sentence.
The evidence will now be presented.
The prosecution. Please.
Murder. Abandonment of a corpse.
In presenting the case against
the defendant...
...the facts to be proven by evidence
are the following:
First - the defendant's background.
The defendant was born on
September 10th, 1956.
His father is a farmer.
He graduated from Junior high school
in March 1972.
While studying further at a night school...
...he worked at a factory in
Chigasaki in the daytime.
As an apprentice. A temporary worker.
Diligent and with a genial disposition.
He never quarreled with others.
From about September 23rd, 1975.
He became intimate...
...with Yoshiko.
The second daughter of Sakai Sumie.
They used to meet at an inn.
And in other places.
Yoshiko became pregnant
in December that year.
There was talk about their relationship.
The two became afraid...
...of Yoshiko's pregnancy becoming
known to their parents.
The two planned to run away
and live together.
For that purpose...
...he decided to move to Yokohama.
And went to the Kinoshita Shipyard there.
He applied there and was hired to start
work on April 1st.
Next:
The preparations for the murder.
Sakai Hatsuko...
...had worked as a hostess in Tokyo
since 1972.
In various restaurants and cabarets.
She returned to her father's house in 1975.
She then opened a snack bar.
The defendant went there
with Yoshiko very often.
Hatsuko became aware of Yoshiko's pregnancy.
She strongly urged them for an abortion.
On March 20,
Hatsuko insisted again for an abortion.
Both the defendant and Yoshiko refused.
Hatsuko said that she'd
inform their parents.
In order to prevent that from happening...
...the defendant decided to kill Hatsuko.
On March 28th...
...the defendant finalized his plan
to murder Hatsuko.
At 2:00pm he cycled to the town of Chogo.
Hatsuko had come in town by bus.
He went to the Hardware Store.
There he brought a 8.5 cm bladed knife,
Planning to kill Hatsuko at the
first opportunity.
At 3:30pm
...he went to the Chogo Motor Co.
Where he had talked...
...on an earlier date about renting a truck.
He negotiated for renting a truck overnight.
As he was talking in front of the store.
Hatsuko happened to pass by.
Next.
The facts concerning the murder.
On this day the victim was collecting...
...the drinking debts made
to her snack bar...
...situated in front of Atsugi Station.
She boarded a bus...
...heading for Yokohama at about 2:16pm.
She collected 2.050 from Mr Sakakibara.
After chatting there for a while...
...she visited Miyachi Tatsuzo
at his apartment...
...above the snack bar "Ah Li".
And she left there at 3:30pm.
She walked along the bus road
to the Chogo Motor Company.
The defendant was negotiating there.
He was startled to see Hatsuko.
Hatsuko asked him for a ride
back home on his bicycle.
Suspecting she was on her way
to tell her mother and father...
...about Yoshiko's pregnancy,
the defendant felt the time
for the murder had come.
At 3:50pm he let the victim ride...
...on the back of the bicycle.
While on the way home.
At about 4:10pm.
While passing by a flower shop.
They quarreled.
They kept quarreling all the way
to the top of a hill.
East of the forest.
Knowing that this was a very lonely spot,
the defendant was ready to kill.
He intended to conceal the body in a forest.
In the countryside.
Suddenly turning to the left.
He made the victim get off
and walk to the scene of the crime.
He took out the knife.
Hatsuko laughed. At first.
But she was soon overcome by fear.
She said that she
admitted she had done wrong,
and that she would not tell anyone.
"Don't kill me, I beg you!"
Despite her plea, the defendant struck.
He grasped Hatsuko with his left hand.
Taking care not to have blood
spurting on him.
He plunged the knife into her.
Inflicting a wound that reached the heart.
Death resulted from excessive bleeding.
A few drops of blood on his trousers...
...remained unnoticed by the defendant.
Don't you feel well?
No. I'm all right.
Just acting.
Young and clever.
You may proceed.
On the way back home...
...he washed the knife.
...then threw it into a field.
As he pushed his bicycle
along a hilly road...
...he met with Omura Goichi.
The defendant said he had been
in Chogo on an errand.
Next.
The abandonment of the corpse.
The defendant.
Upon ascertaining that Hatsuko was dead.
Attempted to conceal the crime.
Careful not to dirty his shirt.
He dragged the corpse for 5 meters.
Then dumped the body in the forest
about 10 meters below.
When he noticed Hatsuko's
handbag and sandal.
Which were lying there.
He also threw them in the forest.
He intended to take a shovel, and,
late at night,
bury the body.
But he became afraid and didn't.
Defendant.
Go there.
This was at the defendant's place.
Is this the same bicycle on
which Hatsuko rode?
It is.
Is this the knife the defendant used?
Yes.
On March 28th...
...Hatsuko was wearing this.
Was it torn here when the knife
was thrust in?
I... I think so.
Counsel. Your procedure at the next hearing?
I would like to call witnesses...
...to substantiate the intent to kill.
Is April 25th satisfactory?
Quite all right.
The defense?
The date is acceptable.
Defendant.
The next hearing will be on April 25th.
Court adjourned.
I hope it goes smoothly.
It might get entangled.
Was it premeditated murder?
Intent to kill is difficult to prove.
The prosecutor appears to be confident.
Voluntary confession is evidence.
But. The defendant will turn 20
in September.
That means attaining adulthood.
It will affect the sentence.
Speedy handling is necessary.
How does this look?
It's difficult to say!
Death penalty?
No burglary or rape involved.
Legally he's still a juvenile.
Even if judged guilty...
...12 years at the most.
The prosecutor spoke as if
he had been there:
"Careful not to have blood spurt on him".
"The knife between the ribs".
It shocked me.
Maybe the Prosecutor was shocked too.
He may not have written it himself?
The other investigating prosecutor
probably did.
Based on the investigation
and the confession.
- Two prosecutors?
- You didn't know that?
One investigates.
The other one is the trial prosecutor.
Yamazaki? Okabe speaking.
Ueda Hiroshi's first hearing has ended.
I read the arraignment. But.
When I said: "Careful not
to have blood spurt on him".
The defense stared at me.
I wonder...
Did Ueda Hiroshi really say that?
I'm sure you wrote it accurately.
But that part seems unnatural...
when read aloud.
I have some doubts about
Hiroshi's confession.
Otherwise I'd have never
accepted his defense.
I think this case is complicated.
There's the wide decline in morality;
Ueda Hiroshi was a good boy.
The environment spoiled him.
Those villages around Atsugi...
...are still under the influence
of the U.S. Military base.
Though it may seem a story of the past.
There's still poison underneath.
And it slowly seeps to the surface.
Hiroshi's folks were once farmers...
Now. They're just waiting for the price
of land to go up...
After his wife died. Hiroshi's father...
...took a geisha as his mistress.
That kind of environment spoils people!
Especially young people...
A teacher's responsibility...
As a teacher...
- I feel...
- That's enough lecturing for today!
Will you help me?
- Help you? In what way?
- Ever been to that bar?
No... I never go to such places.
Really?
Two customers are to be witnesses...
...on Hiroshi's intent to kill.
I want to check them up.
- But I...
- You can do it!
You brought me into this.
I have plenty of other cases to handle.
I'll do my best!
One of them is an yakuza.
Miyauchi Tatsuzo lives in Chogo.
Hatsuko met him before she was killed.
The other one is Tada Saburo.
See what you can find out.
The family environment of Hiroshi.
Hatsuko and Yoshiko too.
Come on. Pep up!
Mister Hanai!
Just a moment. Please!
You went to Ueda Hiroshi's trial today.
Didn't you?
Yes.
A former student of yours?
Always quick to blame the environment!
They're physically big.
But mentally immature.
Besides. They are still young.
They know the Juvenile Law protects them.
They feel free to rebel!
Take this Ueda Hiroshi case.
Classic example of a youth...
...who thinks he can do just anything!
- Isn't that so?
- Yes.
Wait a moment!
The parents must also be kept in mind.
Be careful!
Everyone seems to be criticizing
my son only.
The Sakai family also has
its share of the guilt.
That mother has got herself
a reputation as a flighty woman...
Shortly after her husband died...
...she got married to a real scoundrel!
He pawned her belongings.
And secretly sold part of the fields.
In the end.
He ran away with a cabaret hostess.
Please.
Hatsuko was working then at the US base.
One night. She came home all muddied.
She had been attacked by 3 GI's.
Her stepfather tried to rape her. Too.
What a shame!
Hiroshi and Yoshiko...
I think Yoshiko seduced him.
The pregnancy. I've accepted it.
Sir...
The baby is absolutely innocent.
I just hope Hiroshi's sentence
will be a very light one.
I'm glad to hear you say that!
I want to help him.
Was your sister's bar sold quickly?
Did she have any money saved up?
Sis' didn't have any savings. Only debts!
You always speak ill of her!
Your sister wanted to pay for the abortion!
If we had wanted an abortion...
...Hiroshi would have paid!
Hatsuko went into debt to open that bar.
She used all the money she
had earned in Tokyo.
Later. A signed loan agreement for
500.000 showed up!
Miyauchi brought it.
Miyauchi?
The bar was sold for 2.000.000.
But the money was also used
to settle other debts.
All she had...
was the 15.000 that were in her handbag
when she was killed.
Nothing more.
Is Miyauchi the man from whom
Hatsuko was collecting money?
The yakuza? Miyauchi Tatsuzo?
Yes... I can't believe sis' collected
money from him.
Something must be wrong...
Why?
Their relationship...
Lovers.
What!
He was Hatsuko's man for a while.
I think sis' was forced to seal
a deed as severance pay.
Excuse me.
Does Miyauchi Tatsuzo live around here?
Miyauchi? Upstairs.
You see...
Went out.
Where?
Don't know.
It's about the trial.
Who are you?
Is Miyauchi absent?
I'm a teacher at Tsuchida High School.
A teacher?
What can a teacher want from Miyauchi?
Know where he is? I'll go there.
What's that important?
Are you a relative?
A relative?
That's funny...
Yes. Something like that.
Living together?
Shut up!
Detectives. Investigators.
One after the other!
Miyauchi drifted in from Shinjuku.
He was always hanging out at that bar.
Eventually. "Cattleya" got known as a drag
place and lost customers because of him.
I liked Hatsuko.
Always open-hearted and generous!
The police questioned me as
if I were a criminal.
They wanted to know about the night before.
Tell me about it!
I'll do that at the witness stand.
I get all mixed up as well.
I have to be careful!
What was Hatsuko doing before
getting killed?
Well...
She was writing in a notebook.
At the counter...
...debit and credit items.
A small red notebook.
The notebook I asked
you about on the phone...
Sure.
Are you looking for something?
Just want to take a look.
Do you want to surprise me with
some new facts?
Not at all!
Can I borrow this?
Of course.
I asked him where he had been.
"In Chogo. On an errand". He said.
That's all.
You may cross-examine the witness.
The witness said that the defendant
wasn't looking well.
Had you ever met him before?
Yes... Many times.
He used to run around there
when he was a kid.
When had you last met him
before the incident?
When?
I wonder when that was...
You can't remember when that was?
I must have met him often in town...
Then. Again. Perhaps not?
Well...
In fact. You didn't know how he
usually looked.
You have no basis for your judgment,
that the defendant wasn't looking well!
I object!
The witness is being asked for an opinion.
It's irrelevant.
It's related to the witness's credibility.
It may be related to the incident.
Objection overruled.
The counsel for the defense will avoid
disturbing questions.
Very well. Sir.
Did the defendant actually say
he had been in Chogo?
That's no mistake about that.
- Wasn't he lying?
- That road is a shortcut to Chogo!
Thank you. So. The defendant
told the truth about his actions?
Except for having killed Hatsuko.
How wide is that road?
About 3 meters.
He was pushing the bicycle.
Not riding on it?
Wasn't it strange?
A criminal would want to get away quickly.
He' ride on the bicycle.
His knees must have been shaking.
The witness is warned to answer
only what is asked from him.
When the witness found the body...
...did he recognize it as being Hatsuko's?
No. I didn't.
I reported to the police at once!
Did you know Hatsuko well?
Since she was a child.
Had you ever gone to the snack bar?
Had you go or hadn't you?
I had gone 2-3 times.
Be more specific!
Maybe 5 times in all.
Objection!
Time is being wasted with
immaterial questions.
What is the counsel for the defense
trying to prove?
This witness has been called
in order to establish...
...that the defendant was present
at the time of the murder.
The witness doesn't admit to being
a regular customer.
The defense proposes itself to prove that...
...Hatsuko had intended to meet
with the witness on that day.
Does the prosecution accept this?
If that is the line of questioning...
...the defense may proceed.
Your last visit to the bar?
I don't remember exactly.
End of January?
Why didn't you go after that?
No special reason.
I guess I just didn't want rumors
spreading...
...that I was chasing after Hatsuko.
My old woman'd have pounced on me!
Quiet!
Did you pay in cash?
Sometimes it was on credit.
You owed 4.520 at the time of her death.
Was Hatsuko pressing you to pay?
Objection!
He's leading the witness!
The defense is making a supposition only.
The witness is refusing to testify on...
...his relationship with the victim Hatsuko.
A entry in the notebook in
Hatsuko's handbag...
...shows that Omura Goichi owed her 4.520.
We intend to use this entry in
the notebook as evidence.
I am offering a copy of it
to the prosecution.
Does the witness know Miyauchi?
The fellow that was always
hanging out at the bar?
Did he know about your debt?
Objection!
The question is irrelevant.
What is the counsel for the defense
trying to prove?
That the witness is being
intimidated by Miyauchi.
Your Honor. This is a mere supposition!
I ask that the statement be
stricken from the record...
...and that no further questioning of this
witness should be permitted.
The objection appears well founded.
But why not listen to the testimony
a little further?
The defense should not stray too far away.
Did the witness ever drink
with Miyauchi at the bar?
He picked a quarrel with me there. Once.
But we had a drink and
parted on friendly terms.
The 5.420 bill was for that one time.
Very expensive for 3 bottles
of sake and ham!
But you promised to pay it!
It's written in the notebook!
- Yes. I promised to pay.
- Did you contact her?
In what way?
- Telephone.
- When did you promise to pay?
- On the 28th.
- Where?
- At the station.
- What time?
- At 5pm.
- At 5pm!?
The time when Hatsuko was killed.
Did you go to the station at the
appointed time?
Didn't you meet her there?
- You saw her being killed!
- Of course not!
It was 4 days later that...
...I found the body!
That's all.
What's that lawyer got against me?
On March the 28th, at about 4pm.
I worked at the store as usually.
A young man had a girl on the
back of his bicycle.
They were quarreling as they passed by.
Does the witness remember
what he looked like?
- Of course.
- Is he here. In this courtroom?
It was Ueda Hiroshi.
Do you also remember Hatsuko?
I recognized her from the photo in the news.
- That's all.
- Cross-examination.
How is your eyesight without glasses?
I can read the newspaper without it.
- Did you read about this murder?
- I did. It was published in detail.
Without eyeglasses.
I put them on.
You just said you didn't need them!
Without glasses.
I can only read the headlines.
I don't understand difficult things.
The headlines are enough for me.
The witness should only reply
to questions. Please.
They say she has a lover.
Quiet. Please!
This newspaper is from the morning
after the body was found.
That's the photo of Hatsuko that you saw?
Yes. I saw it! I can read that kind of
photograph even from 1 Ken!
Was this the girl who passed by you?
I didn't recognize her at first.
But I noticed a likeness.
The girl on the bicycle...
...which way was she facing?
She was seated facing towards the right.
- The right. In the travel direction?
- Yes.
Your store is on the left side of the road.
So Hatsuko must have had
her back towards you.
A face can be seen from any side!
Wasn't it after you read the newspaper
account about the two people...
...that you thought you had seen them?
That's not the case!
The police brought pictures...
...and asked if the two had passed by.
I remembered them at once!
So. It was after the police asked you...
I thought you had reported to the police.
Why should I had done that?
I am very busy...
Being called here and treated like a fool...
How long did it take the bicycle
to pass by you?
I wasn't keeping track.
The witness should answer plainly.
2 seconds at most?
Were they having a fight?
- Certainly seemed to.
- Seemed?!
You didn't hear their voices?
A quarrel means a verbal dispute.
You heard what they were
saying in just 2 seconds?
Objection!
The defense's questioning implies...
...unjust criticism of
the police investigation.
It is inappropriate.
Is the counsel for the defense implying
the witness didn't see the defendant?
Not quite that far.
Then this is a bit tedious.
The witness may have seen them.
What I want to clarify is if they're
really quarreling.
They were quarreling!
That is speculation. It lacks credibility.
The prosecution will not insist
that the two were quarreling.
They may have been chatting pleasantly.
It may have been with sweet words...
...that Hatsuko was taken there!
The facts of the crime...
...that the prosecution intends
to prove remain unchanged.
Please. Put your seal on this.
Right here.
I know all about it.
Everyone's acting so arrogantly!
Tied up the entire day...
A pittance of 1.750...
You got Omura flustered!
It was no big deal.
How did you know Miyauchi
was leaning on him?
I didn't.
Just a random guess.
It struck home.
Miyauchi's that type.
I thought he might have.
It is strange to drink alone for so long.
The defense seemed overeager
in questioning that woman.
Adverse result for Hiroshi.
What makes Kikuchi hustle so much?
Not the money.
No money in it.
But the case attracts the media.
That's Rule No. 1 for a lawyer.
You'd better keep that in mind.
Preparing for the future.
The witness's name?
Miyauchi Tatsuzo.
Age?
33.
Occupation?
Unemployed.
What was your relationship
with Sakai Hatsuko?
We were very intimate.
Since when? State it simply.
I came to know her in a Shinjuku cabaret,
in August, 1974.
Later she returned to Tsuchida
and opened the snack bar in Atsugi.
I moved in later with a friend of mine
living in Atsugi.
So we came together again.
She asked for my advice about the bar.
I acted as a caretaker. Too.
At times I was asked to collect debts.
But never used threats.
Did you ever threaten Omura Goichi
to pay his debt?
Wouldn't dream of such a thing.
Liar!
No outbursts here!
On the night of March 20th.
8 days before the killing.
Were you at the bar?
Yes. I was drinking there.
Hatsuko's sister, Yoshiko, came in.
Hatsuko had told me that
Yoshiko was pregnant.
She had called the two to urge them
for an abortion.
They had refused.
She wanted to convince them.
Their mother and Hiroshi's father
hadn't found out yet.
Hatsuko said she was going
to inform the parents.
An abortion was necessary.
Couldn't let her sister marry
a youth like that.
I object!
The testimony is nothing but hearsay.
The witness is only telling us
what happened.
Some parts of it.
Such as the two having refused abortion.
Is nothing but hearsay.
And most detrimental for the defendant.
Even if it were as the defense claims.
It helps to explain what occurred
on the night of March 20th.
Why not hear a little more?
Objection overruled.
The testimony can continue.
Where were the defendant and Yoshiko
seated in the bar?
They were sitting at the counter.
About that far away. I'd say.
At first they talked in low voices.
Then Hiroshi shouted:
"Why don't you trust me?"
Hatsuko signaled to me with her eyes,
as if to say: "See the trouble I'm having?"
I knew right away what was it
that she wanted!
And what was that?
That Hiroshi's father should
be told the whole thing.
What did she say after:
"Trouble I'm having"?
Hatsuko?
"Don't be stupid. Just do as I say!"
"Go to the hospital tomorrow!"
"No. I'm going to have the baby!"
Hiroshi wanted to leave.
"Wait!"
"What if I tell our parents?"
"Stop meddling!"
"What will you do?"
That's how the conversation went.
I felt the situation was dangerous.
What do you mean by dangerous?
Punks often have fights around Atsugi.
When Hiroshi said:
"Stop meddling!".
He looked just like one of them.
Did it sound like he meant:
"I'll kill you!"?
I object!
That really is leading the witness!
Objection sustained.
The people should reformulate the question.
Did Hatsuko and the defendant
quarrel vehemently...
...while you were there?
Yes. They did.
That's all.
The defense may cross-examine.
The witness first met Hatsuko in a
Shinjuku cabaret. In what way?
I was a customer and we became intimate.
- I moved in with Hatsuko.
- Since when?
October 1974.
- After meeting her in August?
- It was Hatsuko's idea!
Were you working back then?
- Unemployed.
- Same as now. Isn't it?
It means you were living off
Hatsuko's earnings?
I don't need a woman Tu support me!
I can earn my own money!
By squeezing people to pay their debts.
Like with Omura?
Objection!
Defense counsel's question is irrelevant.
It defames the witness's character.
Objection sustained!
The counsel for the defense is asked
to re-frame his question.
Hatsuko returned to Tsuchido in June 1976.
- She opened a snack bar in August.
- That is so.
- Were you living with her?
- Yes.
Throughout?
You must answer frankly!
We were separated for a while.
For how long?
A year or so.
Where were you during this time?
I object!
This question is immaterial!
In prison.
I'm only asking where he was
during that period!
A waste of time!
Objection sustained.
The counsel for the defense will
re frame that question.
Did the witness move with
Hatsuko to Tsuchida?
I didn't.
- Did you follow her there afterwards?
- I went to my friend's house.
Did you meet with Hatsuko?
- Of course I did.
- Why?
She was my woman.
But. In January of this year.
You moved away to Chogo.
Why?
There was some trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Trouble with Hatsuko.
Objection!
I have objected several times.
And Your Honor has sustained me.
- But the counsel for the defense insists.
- No!
The relationship between the witness
and Hatsuko...
...has a vital bearing on the
background of this crime!
The court wishes to hear it. Too.
The prosecution must agree...
It is natural for the defense to delve
into the background...
I respect the Court's search for truth.
But there are way too many
immaterial questions.
And questions that defame
the witness's character.
That may be so.
But the court desires to know more
about this relationship.
The judge is all right.
We have learnt that...
...Hatsuko was in your room on March 28th.
From 2:30 to 3:30pm.
What was she doing there?
Drinking beer.
You were drinking together?
- Yes.
- A lot?
Just two bottles. Or maybe there were three.
A whole hour to drink three bottles...
Maybe four.
Which was it. Three or four?
Probably 4.
Do you always have beer in your room?
- Hatsuko brought it from her bar.
- Don't lie!
She got off the bus with only her handbag!
Who brought the beer?
There was someone else there.
Why didn't you say so?
I wasn't asked!
Was it a woman?
Answer, please!
On Mar 28th, at 2:30pm.
A woman was in your room
when Hatsuko was killed?
That's right.
Has she been living with you
since Hatsuko's death?
So what!
The witness is asked to be more careful
how he speaks.
Describe what happened between
that woman. Hatsuko and you.
Kyoko.
Her name is Sakurai Kyoko.
Kyoko ordered the beer.
While we were drinking. Hatsuko came.
Were you expecting her?
- I wasn't.
- Why?
She was going to meet Omura Goichi.
She came just to say she was going
to collect from Omura?
That's right.
In your deposition to the prosecution...
you've stated that Hatsuko came
to collect and you paid her 3.350.
- Well?
- I remember now!
She came for the money.
I paid her.
Which was it?
Be explicit. Please!
To collect money.
You were lovers. Why did you have to pay?
Hatsuko was always strict about money.
A debt was a debt. No matter what.
When her family sold the bar.
After her death.
You showed a 500.000 loan agreement.
You demanded repayment.
If so. You were a creditor.
Why did you pay her?
That 500.000 was to be repaid
when the bar was sold.
500.000 is a large sum of money.
How did she get it?
I lent it to her. So that she could...
open up that bar.
But...
...you were away for 18 months
and couldn't return.
How was the loan made?
This is the document that the family had.
You made Hatsuko write it two days
before you moved to Chogo.
- For repayment if she had sold the bar...
- You're lying!
Your severance pay. Wasn't it?
I'd never never do such a thing to a woman!
Couldn't the counsel for the defense
speak more moderately?
You were drinking with Kyoko at that time.
What did Hatsuko have to say?
She asked me to pay the 3.350 debt.
I paid her and said:
"Let's have a drink".
She thanked me. Saying she was not thirsty.
Then left for her meeting with the old man.
Your relationship with Kyoko...
...Hatsuko must have known.
She knew. But she didn't make a fuss.
She wasn't that stupid.
One hour to drink a beer?
No. Only about 15 minutes.
You told the prosecutor she came at 2:30
and left at 3:30.
Which story is correct?
Upon thinking deeply. 15 minutes.
Hatsuko arrived at Chogo Motor Co.
At a little after 3:30pm.
Less than 50 meters from your place.
If she stayed for only 15 minutes.
Did it take her 45 minutes
to walk 50 meters?
How could I know if she walked or ran?
I'll end my cross-examination here.
I would like to recall the witness later.
As a defense witness.
Just a moment!
An interview!
Who are you?
I'm not on exhibit!
Of course but...
Be careful about what you write. Or else...
A few words will do...
What more does Kikuchi expect
to draw out from Miyauchi?
The prosecution's choice
of the witness was bad...
Using threats to collect debts...
Very little credibility.
Waiter! Over here!
What are you doing?
This is ridiculous!
You're disagreeable!
This is where I'm living.
Here.
You don't fool me!
I'm surprised!
You were lying to me. Weren't you?
What about you?
Why try to hide it?
You're being very strange about this!
You've spilled the beer!
Come again. Hiro-cha.
When...
I came to know Ueda Hiroshi at the factory.
I quit the factory last year.
I'm helping my father.
Hiroshi said he wanted to borrow
a truck on March 28th.
I told him he could.
He came in the afternoon to talk it over.
Did you ask what he was going to use it at?
I didn't ask.
When Hatsuko passed by.
At about 3:30.
Were you at your place with Hiroshi?
Yes.
What did Hiroshi say when he saw her?
Well...
He asked me not to mention about the truck.
He didn't want her to know about it?
- It seemed so...
- And then?
Hatsuko asked for a lift on
Hiroshi's bicycle.
He said the bus would be faster,
but she wanted to go back home.
When Hatsuko made her request...
- was Hiroshi troubled?
- No!
They were getting along fine.
Getting along fine. Were they?
Yes... That's how they appeared.
Do you know the snack bar "Ai"?
Yes. It's about 50 meters from my place.
Did she come from that direction?
Yes. She did.
On the way to your place...
...Hiroshi bought a knife at the store.
- Did you see it?
- No. I didn't!
He had something in his shirt pocket...
What was it?
Clothespins.
Clothespins?!
Yes.
Are you sure? Clothespins?
Yes. I am... Aluminum clothespins.
When he came into the store.
I knew at once...
...he didn't live in Chogo.
Did the defendant pick up a
number of knives?
He did.
Is it customary for customers
to test the blade?
The defendant was
particularly... enthusiastic.
He'd pick up a knife and test the blade
time and time again.
He chose a mountaineering knife.
Didn't he? A multipurpose one?
That's correct.
Is yours a cutlery store?
Not only a cutlery store!
- Isn't it?
- No. No! A hardware store. Too!
There isn't enough business in Chogo
for a cutlery store alone.
I also sell pots. Kettles. Buckets...
Stand face front when answering, please.
Then you sell clothespins. Too?
I sell them.
On the 28th. At about 2:30.
Did you sell to the defendant...
...the knife and clothespins?
I sold him clothespins.
Before. Or after the knife?
He handed the knife to me
and said that he wanted it,
then, seeing the clothespins,
he said: "These, too."
Let me ask your opinion.
A multipurpose knife. Wasn't it?
Couldn't the defendant have bought the
knife and clothespins for a new home?
It is possible.
I have no more question.
Does the prosecution have other questions?
Yes.
So... After handing you the knife he wanted.
He saw the clothespins hanging there...
and he said: "These. Too?"
Correct.
Doesn't the witness think he might have
done that on purpose?
He wanted a knife to kill Hatsuko.
But. In order to camouflage his intentions.
To give the impression that it wasn't just
for that that he had bought the knife.
He bought the clothespins. Don't you think?
Objection!
We must be close to adjournment.
And it is not my intention to waste
the court's time.
But this "camouflage" is nothing but
the prosecution's inference.
The prosecution can sum it up later;
Seeking an opinion now.
Confusing the witness.
May harm the witness' credibility.
It was the defense that first asked
for an opinion.
I just asked for an opinion in the same way!
Wait a moment. Please.
This is not a prosecution-defense
battleground.
The court wishes to hear everything.
Including the opinion of this witness.
Objection overruled!
Don't you think that buying the
clothespins was intended...
...to camouflage the knife
as a murder weapon?
His purchase of clothespins
didn't appear to be...
a move to camouflage the knife.
A knife to kill someone.
That's a very positive assertion...
You've hesitated earlier.
And were unable to answer.
It became clear while
I was thinking it over.
Is it so?
But. In your deposition...
you said you couldn't tell...
...what every customer was thinking about...
Quite inconsistent!
Your previous deposition stated...
...that the undue attention the defendant
had given the blade had troubled you.
That wasn't the only thing!
He seemed so fascinated by the knife...
...that I had begun to wonder...
...if he hadn't... planned to steal it...
The clothespins also made me think.
I can say this from my own experience...
and it probably happened to you to...
...when newly married.
Household trifles often catch one's eyes.
A wash basin...
Did your impression change...
...after reading in the newspapers...
...that the defendant had been living
with Yoshiko?
Of course not!
Not at all!
I'm speaking from my own experience:
He was really very happy
when buying that knife!
He didn't strike me at all as
buying a knife to kill someone!
Then why didn't you say all that
from the beginning?
Have you been lying in the
Prosecutor's office?
Lying? No!
What would I gain from lying?
Then. The deposition you gave to the
prosecution was incomplete.
Isn't it strange you're remembering it now?
Don't know about that!
- Has the defense anymore questions?
- Yes. We have.
Did the prosecutor ask you about
the clothespins?
No.
- You didn't tell the prosecutor?
- No.
The prosecutor questioned you.
But there never was such a question?
Never!
So you didn't answer that?
That's right!
How could I answer. If I wasn't asked?
When the defendant bought the knife.
He didn't just look at the blade.
He bought clothespins. Too.
Didn't he?
Yes.
Then. What the prosecution has surmised.
About camouflage. Didn't really exist.
He acted naturally?
Yes. That's how it was.
He was shopping in a pleasant manner.
I see...
That's all.
The witness may return home.
The case was brilliant!
Prosecutor Okabe may find it difficult
to prove...
...an intent to kill.
We won't know that until the hearing ends.
Is there a prospect for Hiroshi to get
a lighter sentence?
The defense counsel said so.
I'm depending on you. From now on.
I want Hiroshi-san and you to be happy.
Hatsuko was unfortunate.
But. It wasn't her fault.
I'm the one to blame.
That man was a scoundrel!
I shouldn't have remarried!
The relatives urged me to...
but it was all my fault!
Mommy.
Let's stop talking about the past!
Good evening!
It's so late...
There was a phone call for Yoshiko-san
from Prosecutor Okabe.
He wants to see you tomorrow. At 10am.
I wonder why...
It must be something important...
I don't like this prosecutor!
You' better go see him anyway.
"Yokohama Prosecutor's Office."
Is the baby coming along fine?
Yes.
A high school teacher named Hanai
helped a lot.
Was Hanai your teacher?
- Yes.
- And your sister's?
Yes.
How much older was your sister?
4 years older.
What was the relationship between
your sister and Ueda Hiroshi?
We lived close to each other...
They often played together. When children.
They were childhood friends...
Yes.
Your sister quit school...
...and worked in a restaurant.
Isn't it so?
That is correct.
Then she quit.
And became a hostess in Shinjuku...
Why?
The restaurant made some cutbacks...
No other reason.
What are you doing?
Please, Hatsuko!
Don't go away!
What will you do in Tokyo?
Please. Stay with me!
I don't know anything about
her life in Shinjuku.
But... she returned completely changed.
In what way?
As if she was a stranger.
Even her voice had changed.
So it seemed.
What did you think about your sister...
...and Miyauchi?
I hate him.
He was like a parasite.
Clinging to my sister.
But my sister stayed in contact with him...
...I don't understand!
I may call you as a witness
at the next hearing...
Please. Be there.
I'm home!
This was so heavy!
Hatsuko!
Welcome home!
Yoshiko and I were just having lunch.
Won't you eat with us?
No place like home!
Yoshiko. I brought you a present!
Why are you staring? Open it!
Hiroshi!
Yoshiko!
Hiroshi drinks here because he wants to!
It's none of my business!
It's because you seduced him!
I seduced him?! Don't be silly!
What are you saying?!
Yoshiko... you. In love with Hiroshi?
You're just a child!
Don't take him away from me!
If you love him. Take him by force!
The night before the incident...
...did you go to drink at the bar?
Yes.
Tell us what happened. Please.
When I entered.
Hatsuko was looking in her notebook.
The one in which she kept her accounts.
I hadn't been there for a while.
It had changed...
It seemed rather desolate...
I asked about Miyauchi;
"He's left", she said.
"Let's drink till late tonight".
Then, that young man came in.
She introduced him to me
as her younger brother.
They immediately went out.
I went on drinking the beer in front of me.
Hat-cha didn't return.
What did you do?
I looked out of a small window.
How did the two appear to you?
Lovers?
Or, were they quarreling?
Well...
It was dark, I couldn't see too well...
I didn't know about Hiroshi going
there that night.
Didn't the defendant tell you?
No.
But. I'm sure there was nothing special.
You met Hiroshi on the road that
night at 6:30pm, didn't you?
Yes... I did.
Was it to talk about when
to run away together?
Yes.
Did the defendant later go
to your sister's place?
Please. Tell us what happened
on the night of the 28th.
Just as you told the prosecutor.
On the night of March 28th.
In front of the house. At about 7:30.
Hiroshi seemed rather excited.
I thought it natural.
Since we were going to run away.
I'll come at 10 o'clock.
I'll bring the car here.
Hiroshi-san!
What were you doing?
Is the hen-house closed?
It's warm tonight!
I wonder if it's goin' to rain...
Looks like raining...
Your sister hardly ever comes home...
Did you go to see her?
No.
I wonder how she is...
That night Hiroshi-san came for me
at 10 o'clock.
I went with him to the apartment
in Yokohama.
I'll ask about Yokohama.
On April 4th. In the morning.
The newspapers reported the finding
of your sister's body.
What was the defendant's reaction?
Go back to Tsuchida right away.
But. They'll find out we've lived here.
We'll worry about it when it happens.
Good morning.
You didn't notice any particular change
in the defendant's attitude?
Even the workers at the shipyard...
...noticed it.
I asked when I went to see him...
He said he hadn't had a single day of peace.
You mean he had a guilty conscience?
That was only natural
I don't think he's inhuman!
Yet. He lived brazenly with you.
The younger sister...
In order to have the child.
We had to live together!
Is that all there is?
Wasn't it in order to enjoy a free
and wayward life?
I was 3 months pregnant at that time!
We had to be very careful!
Hiroshi said I mustn't stumble!
He did all the household work.
However, you two were enjoying life...
I don't know if that was the case...
After the baby was conceived. We stopped...
Stopped what?
Objection!
Having sex!
About Hatsuko's relationship
with Miyauchi...
Did you know about the two?
He's vulgar! A parasite...
...who tore my sister to shreds!
The witness should watch her language.
That's my answer.
Did your sister think the baby would stop
you two from separating?
I don't know.
I understand how you feel.
But answer truthfully.
Could it have been that your
sister was jealous?
She may have been somewhat envious...
...I was the only one who got
the happiness...
...and she was so unhappy...
She may have been sad...
Did Miyauchi ever flirt with you?
Sis'?
Not here!
What do you want?
Yo-cha...
You've quite grown up all of a
sudden recently...
Having fun with Hiroshi?
Won't you come to Tokyo with me?
Don't you know Hiroshi's in love
with Hatsuko?
They go together to Spas...
You didn't know?
I guess ignorance is bliss...
The people in town had spread rumors
about Hiroshi and Hatsuko...
They were simply talking nonsense.
I don't believe it at all!
Nothing like that happened!
But... isn't it possible that your sister
loved Hiroshi?
You can think what you like.
I believe they never were that intimate!
I'm certain of it from Hiroshi's attitude!
I would have known!
Still... the defendant met your sister
at the bar on the night of the 27th.
He never told you.
No.
I heard that from you.
I've said that already!
I understand.
I won't ask you about that any more.
I've only been trying to discover the truth.
Don't forget that.
That's all.
You said you were drinking beer with
Kyoko when Hatsuko came.
And that Hatsuko had left in 15 minutes.
Was that true?
Was it?
I'm not sure about the time.
There was a fight...
Last time you said everything
had been pleasant.
- Did you lie?
- I didn't lie!
She was in good spirits when she left.
Describe what happened. Please.
Finding me drinking with Kyoko must have...
...made Hatsuko angry.
She all of a sudden demanded
payment of the bill.
You owe me 3.350. Pay it!
I should pay you?
Don't have that much dough now.
Have a drink.
You start drinking in the afternoon
but you have no money!
Take this and leave!
You only wanted to see Miyauchi. Didn't you?
Don't be silly!
I pay 500.000 to get rid of him!
Hiroshi switched over to your sister!
Stop it!
Go fight outside!
You're going to be dumped soon. Too!
Stop it!
I said. Stop it!
- Did you hit Hatsuko often?
- No. It was because I was sore.
Hatsuko must have understood.
Seeing you there with Kyoko.
. Guess so.
She said: "You left on your own.
This is separation money."
So it was separation money...
I wouldn't have taken it if she hadn't died!
I meant to return it!
Return the note?
You made her write it!
No! Hatsuko wrote it herself!
She was deeply in love with Hiroshi.
This is a new twist!
At the last hearing. You said...
...Hiroshi was in love with Yoshiko.
Which is true?
Both. Maybe.
Anyway. Hatsuko loved Hiroshi.
A woman in love looks different!
Weren't you Hatsuko's lover?
I could tell most things about her.
She was always fickle.
So she didn't understand much about me!
Let's return to the 28th.
How did the fight end?
We're all like relatives.
Not much sense in quarreling.
Did it last over 15 minutes?
More like an hour.
Why did you follow Hatsuko afterwards?
You did. Didn't you?
Why should I have followed her?
There was a reason.
You knew that she was going
to meet Omura Goichi.
You didn't want to be left out in any way!
You thought of intimidating Omura later?
Objection!
This question is based on
suppositions alone.
It is unreasonable!
The prosecution's objection is well taken.
But the Court would like to hear the
witness's answer to this question.
The witness will answer. Please.
Did you follow her. Or didn't you?
I followed her.
Farther ahead!
Farther!
Where it turns to the right!
Around there!
I was watching from here.
Approximately 70 meters.
Could you hear their voices?
Couldn't hear a thing!
- Were they quarreling?
- It seemed so.
Hatsuko was pressing for an answer.
Am I wrong?
Was it possible to tell?
Did Hatsuko start walking?
Which way?
This is the place!
I was watching like this.
Go and stand over there.
Did they look like sweethearts?
Yes. But like having some kind of a dispute.
Kind of a lovers' quarrel?
I was surprised to see the knife coming out.
Hiroshi's knife...
...it was like this.
You saw the knife?
You couldn't have seen the knife then!
Hatsuko was in the way.
The knife?
I couldn't see it 'cause it was behind
her body! That's why I didn't stop her!
What did Hatsuko do?
She suddenly embraced Hiroshi.
How? Show us!
Like this.
What's the matter?
Are you sure Hatsuko moved first?
Yes.
All of a sudden...
I had no chance to do anything.
You say you don't recall the moment
when the knife thrust in.
But you told the investigating prosecutor...
...you held Hatsuko and were careful
about the spurting blood.
How were you able to describe
such minute details?
There was practically no blood on my jumper.
While explaining why.
It came out that way.
I couldn't remember well.
But no one believed me.
You made sure Hatsuko was dead.
Do you remember that?
When I came back to my senses.
Hatsuko-san was lying on the ground.
You conveniently remember only
beginning from there...
You say the investigating prosecutor's
questions led you on.
Please. Tell us exactly what did the
investigating prosecutor ask you?
I don't remember all the questions.
That can't be true!
This is a very critical moment for you.
Don't try to be evasive!
But it's the truth!
I was confused. Very tired. Too.
When the investigating prosecutor asked
me those questions.
I felt completely terrified.
I can't recall what I said.
You became aware of the
gravity of your crime?
But. For 6 days after having killed Hatsuko.
You went on living brazenly with her sister.
Why didn't you try to help Hatsuko
as she lay fallen there?
I thought she was dead.
You didn't think she could have been saved?
No.
That's all.
The defense may cross-examine.
Miyauchi has testified that Hatsuko
had embraced you.
Were you surprised when she did so?
Her expression changed as she drew near.
Her expression?
She had been scolding me until then.
Suddenly. Her expression altered.
How did she look?
For instance...
...as if she was loving you...
...or hating you?
What did you talk about?
Hatsuko-san asked me to say
clearly if I loved her.
Because she didn't intend to run after
a man who didn't want her.
And then?
I told her I didn't love her.
"Love me or not,
I won't let you two go to Yokohama."
"Do you think I can endure a wretched
life here, alone?"
That's what she said.
Then her expression changed...
You told the prosecuting investigator you
took out the knife to scare her.
That doesn't seem to have been necessary.
I felt afraid of Hatsuko. Then.
I didn't know what she might have done.
Why would she have done anything?
She seems to have been fond of you.
Did you have sexual intercourse
with Hatsuko?
Answer clearly, please!
I didn't!
Don't hide anything!
It'll come out.
No. I didn't!
Not even once?
Never!
That's all.
Your honor...
...the defense would like to call
Miyauchi again.
I accept.
When I first went to the bar.
Hatsuko and Hiroshi were the
only ones there.
Hatsuko said he was only a child.
But even after we took up living together...
...she still went on seeing Hiroshi.
That's when you told Yoshiko that
Hiroshi loved Hatsuko?
I thought of spilling the goods so I put
some pressure on them.
I kept watch outside a hotel; I took
Yoshiko to show her what was goin' on.
I was the one who went there
with Hiroshi-san!
Miyauchi mistook me for my sister.
Miyauchi said the two of you saw
the defendant and your sister...
...coming out of a hotel!
That's a lie!
Everything he says is a lie!
Either you or Miyauchi are committing
perjury!
Your Honor... Please!
No comments from the gallery!
Your Honor.
I'd like to recall the defendant.
There's no need for that.
That's all.
Does the prosecution have any questions?
No more.
The witness may withdraw.
Defendant.
The next hearing will be on June 3rd.
The prosecutor's summation
will be made then.
Court adjourned.
This is my summation.
Murder and abandonment of a corpse.
The prosecution's views on this case
consist of the following.
Juvenile crimes are on the increase;
Especially crimes against the basic
right of others to live...
...are being committed with
alarming frequency.
From the standpoint of crime prevention,
this case cannot be regarded lightly.
The "Getting rid of those in the way"
idea has been displayed.
The defendant is legally not an adult.
But this does not mean a reduction
of the gravity of the crime.
Prosecutor's summation has just ended.
A sentence of from 8 to 10 years
has demanded for the accused.
The defense's summation is next.
The defendant in this case may have...
...meant to threaten.
But there was no intent to kill.
The cause was the victim's
unforeseen action.
The defendant was not responsible...
...for murder. Injury causing death.
Or accidental manslaughter.
It was purely an accident!
I affirm that he was only guilty
of abandonment of a corpse.
Why. It's you. Hiroshi!
You've come back?
Why're you staring at me?
I've changed. Haven't?
The countryside is so nice!
How was Shinjuku?
I grew tired of it.
That house has been rebuilt. Hasn't it?
They must have made a lot of money!
Thanks!
I'll be opening a bar soon. Be sure to come!
Goodbye for now!
Are you all right?
I'm going.
- Stay a little longer!
- I'm leaving!
You'd better not move around!
Just sit here.
D'you want some water?
What is it?
Hiroshi... I love you.
Don't be stupid. Yoshiko!
Just do as I say!
I'll take you to the hospital.
No!
- I'm going to have the baby.
- No way!
You're just a child yourself!
We don't need your help!
Let's go!
Wait!
Our mother and your father
don't know about this.
Stop interfering or...
Or what? What'll you do?
I'm tired of everything!
This bar is hopeless. Too!
I'd like to sell the bar and go with you
somewhere far away!
Don't lose your hope.
Help me!
Won't you help me. Please!
You've become so cold!
I know why Yoshiko won't have an abortion.
She became pregnant to take you
away from me.
Please. Don't talk about that!
I've heard enough!
Listen. Hiroshi...
Aren't you and Yoshiko planning
to run away somewhere?
What'll become of me?
Why don't you take me away from Miyauchi?
It's too late!
There's nothing that can be done now.
Tell me once and for all if you love me!
I won't run after a man who doesn't want me!
I don't love you!
What ever happened between us it's over!
I'm going away with Yoshiko.
To live in Yokohama.
I'll tell her about us!
No! You can't do this!
You mustn't!
You'll regret it!
What's that?
You mustn't!
All right. But love me or not.
I won't let you two go to Yokohama!
Do you think I can endure a wretched
life here. Alone?
Stop it!
I believe it is murder.
No matter how.
Hatsuko's action alone couldn't have
led to her death.
The defendant had his knife out.
She may have tried to grab the knife.
The body was dragged cruelly.
It reveals Hiroshi's character.
He hid the body and the weapon.
Then lived brazenly with the sister.
It is an act of murder.
I wonder about that...
There isn't a strong enough motive
for murder.
Dragging the body may. Off hand. Seem cruel.
But there was no other way to move it.
Even if the victim moved towards him first.
Hiroshi didn't pull back the knife.
The victim's action at the crime scene
is the crucial point.
I agree with your opinion on that.
But the fact that Miyauchi was
watching became known...
...after the trial started.
Doubt also arose about Hatsuko
and Hiroshi's relationship.
The investigation was incomplete.
Miyauchi's testimony may not have
been entirely reliable.
But. If certain facts had been known.
The defendant might have been
examined differently.
If. As Miyauchi said.
Hatsuko and Hiroshi
had a special relationship.
Then it was a love triangle.
That psychology is complex.
This case might have been
handled differently.
Of course.
Yoshiko pretends she doesn't believe...
...there was anything between the two.
But... Hatsuko is dead;
It has become difficult to find out
the truth.
Finding the truth is of interest.
But a judge is unable to probe
deeper into this.
The court's confirmation of the truth
must be based...
...on the actual evidence throughout!
The confession is not ignored.
But you know how it is obtained.
About the depositions presented
by the prosecution...
the judge must decide for himself.
No matter what!
The motive is insufficient.
Intent to kill is hard to recognize.
No attempt to help.
Abandonment of the corpse.
Whatever the circumstances.
This is a serious crime.
Then. Living with the deceased's
younger sister for six days...
...this must surely be morally condemnable.
What do you think?
Not involuntary manslaughter.
But bodily injury resulting in death.
In the case of the defendant Ueda
Hiroshi charged with...
...murder and abandonment of a corpse.
The Court will give its decision.
- Defendant.
- Yes.
The defendant is sentenced to a prison
term of 2-4 years.
Forgive me!
I failed to raise my boy the right way!
Hatsuko was to blame!
After she returned here.
She inveigled all the men around!
Hiroshi became a victim. Too!
I'm going to sell this house!
Abortion might have been better.
As Hatsuko said.
Why?
Why do you say that now?
We endured hardship in order
to have this child!
Mom has started to say that.
Hatsuko was partly to blame
for what happened.
I'm not fit to be the child's father!
That's not so!
Atonement will restore you
to your former self!
Can this crime be erased in 2 or 3 years?
Maybe I really thought
about killing Hatsuko-san!
Everything would've gone smoothly
with her out of the way!
I spend nights thinking about it.
You're wrong. It wasn't like that at all!
You didn't carry it out!
Anyone can daydream!
You always had a strong sense
of responsibility.
Hence this delusion.
It's not at all a delusion.
I've always been bad.
Outwardly I appeared docile
and fooled everyone.
Yoshiko's pregnancy was really bothersome.
My relations with her were
becoming a burden.
There's no use...
...thinking in such a way now!
Sir!
These hands are bloodied. One human life...
...has been lost forever.
Even if by mistake.
I killed a human being!
When Hatsuko-san advanced.
I should have pulled back the knife!
I killed her with this hand!
Hatsuko will never come back now!
Why don't they kill me. Once and for all!?
I'm surprised.
It might be a reaction to the
rather lenient sentence.
At heart. He must be glad it was so light.
It embarrasses him
and he exaggerates the crime.
That often happens.
But. Hiroshi says he daydreamed
about killing her.
A daydream is nothing.
Different from an actual deed.
There's nothing we can say
to one suffering from guilt.
He must solve it by himself.
I must leave now for an arraignment.
Goodbye.
It's been a long time!
Where are you going?
To see Hiroshi.
Bringing him supplies?
Just a few things.
How's he doing?
Are you going to move?
He's in the prison at Kawagoe.
I will move there.
Looks like he's on the way.
A cute face. But some woman you are!
I'm not a liar like you.
Look who's talking about lying!
Anyway. Take care.
Have a healthy baby.
Thank you.