Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Judai no Yuwaku (1953)
It's still a mess though
I will leave it to you.
Take care.
There will be a lot of executives here today.
You've said it many times
I clean my house,
and you clean the office.
Sorry for making you do the work for me.
You should go to the office early.
You must not cause trouble for your sister.
Got it.
Take care.
Hey, hey, big sis!
What are you doing? Your buttons are still fastened
Hey, big sis!
Where's my lunch box?
It's under the table.
There're just a few side dishes
You shouldn't be extravagant
I made it.
She's becoming more and more professional
She is just a part-time student
If you go to university, you will also have to work part-time.
I'd rather work at a soba restaurant than at a lottery shop.
I can eat as much shumai and fried rice as I want.
What are you talking about?
My sister has gotten really fat lately.
You idiot
It's currently in the phase of gaining weight
Come on, you two have to hurry up
You're going to be late for school.
I'm going now.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and go
Can you bring me some shumai as a souvenir tonight?
I want a manju.
I'll bring back lots of them
Don't say anything arrogant
You just take home the leftovers
Hey!
Tsukimura-san
oh sorry
Good morning, good morning
It's late.
Wait a minute.
Mitsuko-san
Good morning
I felt relieved
Let's hurry up
You are weird person
If I come, you'll have to hurry up
Because there's no time left
It's okay
I've been up all night
I'm currently writing a 50 page novel
and I'm so sleepy
If you don't hurry, you'll be late
Ah, let's go
Ah, wait
Well, see you later
Hello, Aoki-san? It will be tonight at 6pm, right?
it it called "Rose-Colored Youth."
It will be the first piece
It's okay
I just need to draw about 10 more pictures
I'll draw it quickly today and finish it
Good morning
You're always late
Go quickly
You got scolded.
That teacher is always angry
You're always late, so I'm going to tell your sister,
I don't want to, teacher, say that, no,
You have to enter from here.
Oh no
The origin of the word culture is the verb
to Cultivate, right?
In other words, it is created by human will and power
This has a lot of meaning in spiritual culture, whereas simulation has the meaning of material civilization.
Ah, this reminds me
Look, the last one has begun.
My senior novelist....
You're late.
I was actually thinking of taking a day off today
I forced myself to come out because of the teacher's actions
You should tell that to a young teacher who just graduated from school.
Oh Setsuko.
Sorry, I'm busy today.
See you!
I'm sorry about that.
I was shocked
What happened?
He's blushing.
Did something happen with her?
Idiots ,We don't do anything
She... she...
Are you studying?
uncle, be quiet for a second?
Are you writing another novel?
Don't do that and study for school
You don't understand literature, uncle
Don't say something stupid
I'm your surrogate parent
Ain't I an adult now?
I don't need a parent substitute
What are you talking about?
A woman isn't a real woman until she's married, right?
Your sister's situation is fine, but
You're still five years away, or at worst,
ten years away
I'm having a hard time too
Is it delivery now?
I'll go
That's fine
I'm a little busy today
He's tired afterwards
But I can't force you...
No worries.
Are you okay with that? Be careful,
it's dangerous!
Be careful.
Tsukimura-san!
Where's the manju, big sister?
that's right, I forgot, sorry,
I'm disappointed,
it's you, Nobu-chan?
You  played a prank on you this morning!
Don't do that anymore!
but you'll be selling soon
What are you talking about?
What's wrong?
He played a prank this morning.
I was embarrassed.
Don't do that to your sis.
Sorry.
so sorry about the school trip money...
Don't worry.
I had no intention of going from
the beginning
But I feel sorry...
Let's make a coat for Nobu-chan
I feel sorry for him when it gets cold
Thanks.
You are an idiot
Sorry
I've caused you so much trouble
it's nothing.
Come on, let's have dinner
What's wrong? Are you done?
Are you feeling unwell?
Dad,we need to live in a world where poverty
is eliminated
What's wrong?
You have never questioned the fact that you are rich, right?
Haruhiko-san, aren't you a little obsessed with that kind of thing?
That's not the case
I'm sure you think it's natural
that you can eat such a delicious meal
Hey hey, what's that?
Dad, there is a girl in our class who is studying
while working part-time as a maid at a soba restaurant
You like that student, no?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not like that.
Are you at the age where you're interested in girls?
Dad, you make fun of me like that
Don't get me wrong.
I am happy to see that
you have become so reliable
Please don't make any stupid comments
Haruhiko has completely changed
Haruhiko is 18 now
Some girls will be attracted by him
Your thought is not pure.
Haruhiko
it's fine, just leave him alone
Oh I see
It's bad to keep Kawahara waiting.
Setsuko
Wait just a little longer
Just leave her alone.
Have a tea
Let's wait a little longer
It's done!
Is it finished?
it's a masterpiece
Shall I read it?
Leave that for later
Well, that's fine
Setchan is also a candidate for the Akutagawa Prize this time around
Not so much though
But aren't female writers these days sloppy?
You're right
Keep going
Please don't flatter her.
She is easy to get carry away
It's like a balloon, blowing up at each other, right?
it's rude to call it a balloon
Kawahara-san, I'm a writer in the future
I'm scared
Ah, I'm sorry
Oh, it's already 7 o'clock
I have to go.
Where are you going?
I have a group meeting tonight.
Well, we feel bad for Kawahara-san for making him wait until now
But wouldn't it be better if I wasn't there?
You're such an idiot.
Kawahara-san and my sister He's the kind of person who doesn't really care if it's his lover's hand or a broom.
Sometimes, I want you to lead her so hard that it makes my sister's heart bleed backwards
Don't say like that.
Even if I just do this,
it's heavenly love, earthly love
I'll go with the flow, eternal love at will.
I'm off.
I'm sorry I have time until the last train
I'm sorry she being selfish
No, it's fine to be innocent
But my hands are better that a broom.
Well, that's true
Come on.
Welcome.
Yes, hello
He's here?
Yes.
Sorry I am late.
Give me a second.
I got chilling out when I came here
My school friends, the guys are studying hard for exams,
but the girls are so young
That's not worth talking about
How old are you?
17.
What are you so impressed with?
I thought you were about 13.
Don't make fun of me.
I'm a little confident, please listen.
Are you going to yawn now?
Everyone, start yawning
I'll read it then because I'll get distracted if I'm in the middle of it
The cosmos flowers have also fallen
Soon, when the chrysanthemums bloom in profusion,
how about a fading art? I absolutely loved it from the start
Hmm, I see, I think so too
Is she here?
I wonder if there's anything interesting to talk about
Sorry no.
The snowflakes that began to fall soon disappeared into the pavement
Finally, the light from the window in Room 7 fades into darkness
Wow, this time it looks interesting
Please be quiet
Aoki-san!
It's great!
Go for it! It's a masterpiece
Wonderful.
How nice it is!
Well, what do you think, Murata-san?
I guess so
What do you think? Murata-san,
well...
I mean....
So It's like mix whiskey with soy sauce
What does that mean?
Listen
Thinking about your experience and age
Do you really think you can write a love story between a middle-aged man and a widow?
Because girls' novels are so weird
I'm talking about how you can mix
whiskey with soy sauce
First of all, it's impossible to write a
novel without any experience in relationships.
That's exactly it!
Okay, I get it
Teacher
What's wrong with you?
Can I come up a little now?
Yes, please, please
Good evening.
That's rare
You want me to read your novel again?
No.
So what is it?
Teacher!
Kiss me!
It's a kiss!
You've really changed your mind again.
It's more brilliant than the fake robbery the other day
Because I can't write a novel without experiencing relationships
Idiot, I don't know who accused you of something bad, but basically,
It's important for humans not to
overstretch themselves on this bungee
If we follow your logic, then surely more and more great female writers should emerge from the local women and women of that class
So am I a bad person?
You are a good person.
But little...
What?
Sometime you act weird
But if it's a fake, then a bad is better than a good.
That's what they call the Chewing gum philosophy
Oh yeah.
Yes, you should read this book
Is this helping me?
I don't know if this will be helpful or not
If you have any other books you'd like to read, feel free to bring them with you
Really?
You took that much?
You won't read all at once
It's okay.
Well, I'll just borrow these, see you.
Sorry
Sorry about yesterday
I was the one who was spacing out
But you are amazing, I could never imitate you.
There's no need to imitate me
I was surprised
From now on, I'll follow your example and become even stronger
Sorry sorry
I've wanted to talk to you for a long time
Me too.
because when our eyes meet
you immediately turn away, right?
I thought you didn't like me at all
Me either.
I wish I'd told you that earlier
You can start now
We're going on a trip to Kansai soon,
right? I've been there and I know it well
So I'll guide you.
I'm sorry, sorry
Are you Mitsuko Tsukimura?
Yes.
Professor Fujimoto is calling you
Hello, Tsukimura-san, Setsuko-san's sister has something she'd like to tell you
It's about my sister...
She's too much
I'm worried if she goes on the school trip
So I just recommended you to be Setsuko's contributor
Unfortunately, I can't go
Because you're exaggerating like that
It would be fine if you just go out
with her when they are free to go out
If I left her alone, I don't know what she would do.
I'm not going on that
upcoming trip
Huh?
Excuse me.
Professor Arikawa,come in
It's been a while.
Tsukimura-kun,let's take it.
Tsuji-kun's sister has kindly offered the travel fee.
Of course, I'll keep this a secret from Setsuko,
so don't worry about anyone
Since the two teachers were so kind as to say so, you should grateful to take it.
I'm so glad. Now I feel good for Itsuko and it was worth it to have the teachers come
She is a really outrageous teacher.
She only think of me as a bodyguard or secretary
She's like that.
Teacher, There is another person
who can't go on the trip.
Who is it?
The one in the hospital Hiroko-san
I feel bad because it seems like I'm
the only one doing something good.
I'm going to visit her tomorrow
She's in the hospital in Kurihama?
Okay, I'll go with you
I'm so jealous. Everyone is healthy and on vacation
I wonder when I'll get better?
It's a young person's disease.
You'll be okay.
It will heal quickly.
That reminds me.
You always go off the rails with the teacher, right?
No... that's not true
Actually, during the war
I was on the Okinawa front
You guys probably know that too
The Himeyuri Student Unit
With those girls I was wandering through a hail of bombs and shells
That was the first time I saw a first menstruationa girl
menstruationa?
I don't want to hear that kind of story anymore.
Listen to me.
I actually cried then
Oh, that person?
No, it was me
I was the one who cried.
Now I can laugh
I were really touched at that time
The power of an individual to grow despite the great violence of war
I felt this
The power of human growth is strong.
Miyashita-kun, you are at an age
where you are growing rapidly,
You must have this power too
Come on, cheer up and do your best
Teacher, I have confidence
That's right, that's true.
Take care, Mitsuko
I'll be waiting for you to come home
I'll buy you some souvenirs
Please.
This looks great
Everyone's tastes are surprisingly old-fashioned
I'm not interested in that kind of thing
Don't you want to eat?
Anyway,this is how it is
but it's true
This looks delicious.
Tsukimura-kun, there's space over there
Yes, I'm fine here
I see.
Let's go out for a drink tonight, okay?
Hey,
you want to come too, right?
I can't.
Why?
Taraki is so noisy
Hey come on
Shall we go?
which school do you guys go to?
Jonan High School in Tokyo
Is Jonan High School in Asakusa?
No, it's in Komaba
Who the heck is he?
You guys are from Jonan High School in Tokyo?
Tokyo brings back memories.
Oh, you're in Tokyo too?
Yes,
I studied at Keio for a while too
My specialty is ancient Japanese art.
It's quite inconvenient in Tokyo
I changed to a university in Kyoto
Oh, so you know a lot about Kyoto?
That's true for most things
but a school trip is just an extension of school,
so we can only see certain places
Then I'll guide you
Please.
Definitely
I have to report my findings to the professor today,
so how about we meet at Yasaka Shrine at 8 o'clock tonight?
That's fine.
Setsuko
What?
Kyoto at night is so romantic
Yes, it's wonderful.
Everybody be quiet, everybody be quiet
Be quiet
and listen to me for a moment
Well, you're free to go out now
However, please be sure to return by 10:00.
Anyone who is late will be severely punished
Hold on.
Let's go.
It's only 3 hours, so let's go
Hey, hurry up,
Aren't you going?
I'll go later.
What about Risuko?
I'll go later too.
Let's go quickly
Wait a minute!
Let's go quickly!
Hurry up!
Kyoto isn't uncommon!
Do whatever you want! Idiot!
Setsuko.
Are you sure to go?
I'll go! But isn't it a little early?
Maybe it's better not to go.
It's okay!
Then I'll go with you too!
You're acting childish.
But
I've been thinking about a lot of things about tonight!
It seems like it's going to be really romantic,
but three people would ruin it
Tsukimura-san.
Ooi-san is there.
You were waiting for me
Let's go
But Setsuko...
You promised me so much
Since the beginning of this trip, you've only been walking with Tsuji-kun.
I'm sorry, but...
Do you think you can't trust me that much?
No, that's not the case
I get it.
You've been making fun of me from the beginning
Oishi-san
Setsuko!
Grandma, one noodle.
Wait a minute.
No.
We can't.
OOi-san.
I'm in trouble. Setsuko went to see a college student
A college student?
You know, the person he was with on the train from Nara
Ah, he's face student.
What do you think?
I got drunk
Is this your first time drinking alcohol?
No, I've been there many times, even to cabarets and bars
Oh, then let's go to Cabaret
In my imagination?
Sometimes I can't tell if it's a dream, fantasy or reality
Setsuko-san and Tsuji-kun
Let's go there.
How's that?
Reality is better than dreams, right?
There.
Aren't you cold?
What are you doing?
Let go! No! Let me go!
No! Let me go!
Be quiet.
Get your hands off of me!
Setsuko.
Ooi-san.
What's wrong?
why are you getting in our way?
Let's go
What's with that guy?
No, let's go home now
But what about Tsuji-kun?
it's okay, it's getting late
Let's go back early
Hurry up.
You're so noisy.
Oh, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Door is locked.
Please open up
You're late
Has anyone returned yet?
Everyone has returned
I'm glad.
Come in.
The teacher might get angry at you.
Young people these days are like this.
They're really smart
Where have you been up until now? Huh?
Where have you been up with Ooi until now?
Were you with Ooi-san?
Whatever it is, just leave it alone
Hey come on.
Jonan High School Haruhiko
Ooya is currently with a woman
Don't tell anyone what happened tonight.
Please be quiet, please. Both players have arrived
If you can't name famous male-female pairings from all
over the world, past and present, within 5 seconds,
Well then, ladies first, see?
Romeo and Juliet
Come on.
Sicily
Onase.
Ukarukanpei
Kanichi Omiya
Takeoka Namiko
Next.
Denge Ishihara
2 second
Harujiko Oyam Tsukimura Mitsuko
That's right!
You shouldn't say such realistic things.
What's wrong?
A romantic love story forged in a Kyoto night
It's like a novel Alto
What's that?
Don't you know what Alto is?
It's a one-off love story about a young prince who falls in love with a beautiful girl while studying abroad
That's totally fine
Oh Kitty, I promise
Don’t do that.
Don't get mad.
We are rooting for you
You bastard!
Do you think they will get married?
We will support them.
Leave them alone
Does the teacher know about them?
If the teacher found out, he would be angry.
Teachers have neither imagination nor aesthetic sense.
Teachers are like scrubbing brushes
I've heard rumors about them too
Teacher, that's nonsense
That's probably true
But it's only natural that suspicion would be raised about the two of us sneaking out in the middle of the night, and I want to know why too
There must be some reason you can't tell me
You don't have to reply right away, but instead, can you be confident enough to not succumb to rumors?
Or have the courage to explain everything
to protect yourself?
I hope it's one of those two.
Got it?
Well, go home
You're treating your students a little too leniently.
I choose to trust my students
I see, that sounds good
I think sometimes that word means as an educator
Well, I've already contacted their current families before things get out of hand,
Please wait
Have you contacted them yet?
Your attitude is a bit confusing
But before we even knew the situation
I am in trouble
Excuse me.
Yes, please come in
Thank you very much for everything
No, it's my pleasure.
Has Setsuko come back?
Setsuko hasn't come back yet
Please come up and wait, okay?
Excuse me.
Welcome.
I am her uncle
Setsuko always takes care of me
Have a seat.
I was just talking about this now
It seems that Setsuko has been doing all sorts of things
If she makes a mistake and it becomes a newspaper article, then there will be problems with the marriage.
so I was worried
Mitsuko-san, I guess nothing really happened to that girl on her trip.
Is that true?
She didn't listen to anything we said
I really hope you will continue to do more in the future
I also ask
Excuse me
Oh Mitsuko-san?
Please keep staying.
Excuse me
Mitsuko?
How was it?
No, I can't do anything that would make Setsuko's family unhappy
Why is Tsuji's family unhappy? Hey,
tell me the truth
We've created a huge misunderstanding
But wouldn't that be blown away in an instant if the facts were clearly proven?
Ooi-san, please forgive me
There's something I just can't say right now
Well, she's precious children
I'm not saying who is at fault
Well, there's nothing we can do about what happened,
but we need to be careful about what happens next
My daughter doesn't do that.
So my Haruhiko was the one who seduced her?
that's not what I meant
Unfortunately, I couldn't make it to school today,
so this was the first time I heard your story
When she returns home,
I will listen carefully
However, it ended up reaching the ears of the teachers
Of course, I'm not saying that Haruhiko is not responsible,
I'm home.
This young lady...?
Ah, I've already spoken to your mother about.
Let's make sure you don't have any further contact with our Haruhiko
You're both still students
Now you just need to study
Well then, I'll excuse myself now
So please excuse me
I got a letter from the school
That's a lie, we're nothing wrong
Everyone is just making up rumors
Okay.
No matter what anyone says
Mom knows you're not that stupid
But the reason the rumors started
was because you were vulnerable
Since when have you been saying that?
Don't ask me anything
Believe me
Then I won't ask you anything
I believe in you.
Don't cry anymore
Don't let things like this
discourage you and make you hate school
If you have nothing to hide in your heart, then you should be honest about it
Right now, studying is the most important thing for you
Stop it.
you. We are being bothered by strange
rumors being spread about us because of you
If it's just a rumor, leave it alone
I'm actually celebrating your brave actions
Don’t do that.
Right now, I'm writing this about my travels
Of course, I model myself  and you guys
Idiot
I'll listen to your experiences
someday.
I’m sorry.
I heard my mom went to your place yesterday. Sorry
No, it's nothing
Look!
Those two, you said something stupid
Everyone teases them.
Because at that time...
poor thing
Please help them both atone for our sins
What should I do?
Oh, hey! Please! Thank you!
Come on! You idiot!
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
What can I do for you?
Why, you said it yourself
But you...
Someone must have played a prank on us.
If we remain silent, we will be misunderstood even more.
We have to tell them the truth.
But Setsuko.....
She is the kind of person who doesn't mind things like that
She's laughing out loud
But....
why are you protecting such a person?
I'm sorry
But we haven't done anything shameful
I'm sure the misunderstanding will be cleared up soon.
That's good, that's good
Don't show it off too much
Dear Haruhiko
Ah, I'm troubled
Stop making fun of her.
Don't be so arrogant.
What on earth do you think this place is?
Making love with a girl in a sacred school
We don't
If you don't,Why are you two secretly meeting in a place like this?
Because I had business to attend to
Are students not allowed to discuss things with each other?
Don't be so arrogant.
There
Hey there! Don't bully them too much, you guys.
Shut up.
What's the hell?
Are you complaining?
Sorry for complaining
What's wrong?
You guys are slacking off,
You're just students and you're always running after girls
Hey Come Grand, I will train you
What's wrong?
What did you do?
What's wrong with
you guys?
Why are you silent?
Why don't you say it?
Tetsuko was spoiled
I can't stand it anymore
I'll tell the teacher everything
Wait, Tetsuko
Please kept that a secret
If they find out about that, I have to quit school
Please! Please
You idiot!
Wait.
I'm in trouble
What should I do?
What did you guys do to
avoid this?
That's right
Mitsuko!
I'm sorry about earlier
I did too much
I couldn't forgive their pranks.
Mitsuko!
Where are you going?
Hiroko.
Did you come?
Ooi too?
How is your health?
I'm sorry to wake you up while you're sleeping
I just had a very strange dream
There were hundreds and thousands of candles lit
Then suddenly the wind started to blow and they were wiped out one by one, and
I felt sad
But one thing didn't disappear
It didn't disappear until the very end
Yes, I'm sure Hiroko has hope to live.
Yes, that's right.
I'm starting to feel relieved
But somehow Mitsuko-san, you don't seem to be in good spirits today
What happened?
Something unpleasant happened
I thought maybe I would find the courage
to meet Hiroko
But I'm an idiot
On the other hand, I tried to rely on you
Yes, it's mutual
When I'm alone and just sleeping,
I start to think that it's really beautiful
that people are alive
I wonder if that's true
Hiroko is sick, but your mind is healthier than anyone else's.
But I still want to be healthy
Please enjoy true health for me
That's right, Jogashima is right there
Have a nice trip together
Have fun for me.
This is the Bronze statue in the daylight
What a great song
Did you know?
Yes, it was quite popular back in the day
Shall we walk there?
Yeah, let's go that far
Wow
that's amazing!
It's dangerous so be careful
I love the ocean because it's so wide.
I love it too
I want to be a diplomat
If I become, I think I'll be able to see the oceans of the world
Ah, now I understand
I understand why you are so passionate about English.
But the exam is difficult.
Don't worry.
Oi-san will make a great ambassador.
Don't be arrogant
I really mean it.
But I need something very important to become a diplomat
What?
That's embarrassing
Come on
Tell me.
I tell you.
I need my own wife.
This is cold.
I feel very good...
Let me do it.
It's not cold at all
Your cheeks have warmed it up
Give it back.
Did it hurt?
It's okay.
Look, today's high school students are so in love.
That's true.
We can't be any closer
Good evening
Welcome.
Aoki-san is here?
No
I completed the work
What did you write?
It's a true story
about a high school trip
It's about first love.
Shall we read a story?
Later is fine.
Excuse me., but can you show me?
I'm Komori of the literary world
I'm going to do a feature on new teenage talent soon, so I'd like to recommend you
Hey, really?
Please
You are stupid.
Did you really believe what that guy said?
Have I ever heard of The names of such magazines?
No kidding
So why did he take my manuscript?
I'm guessing he's trying to blackmail someone?
Well, he's not that kind of person
What evidence are you basing this nonsense on?
Nonsense?
Aren't those two students actually
becoming a problem at school?
Well, I have solid evidence for all of this
What if the school's disgrace
didn't end up in the newspapers...
Well, 50,000 yen is cheap
That's like a threat
Even if you say that
if proper procedures are followed,
you will be the one who is punished
I  have the evidence.
What evidence do you have?
Here's the proof
You guys tell the truth
Why did you sneak out of Inn
and do anything?
Teacher.
Why didn't you tell us?
Nowadays, rumors aren't just a school issue
Your actions have been featured in the newspaper.
Tsukimura-kun, I told you the other day
The courage to defend yourself?
please wait just one more day
We haven't done anything
Please.
I just can't understand what you think.
Why do you defend Tsuji?
I'm sorry
I actually received money from Setsuko's sister for our junior high school trip
If that's the kind of money
I have,
I think you should give it back to her.
I can't do that
Why?
Her sister asked me to make sure
Setsuko didn't make any mistakes
But I'm sorry
I've caused you so much trouble
I don't care about that
Ooi-san, can you please transfer to another school?
Unlike me,
you have to go to university soon,
You can't stay the way you are now
But If you do like this,
you'll end up all alone
It's okay, I have Hiroko
But.
You have a much bigger and more important future ahead of you
Please, forget about the rumors about useless people and study for me
Please
I'll do as you say
But I have just one request
I want to invite you to my house tomorrow as a final farewell
so I hope you'll come.
But your mother...
Don't worry.
My parents will be out tomorrow
so I'm sure you'll come
Yes.
Welcome.
I'll give this back to you
Really? Then that's fine
But even if it appears in the newspaper, I don't think anyone will complain later
Stop doing stupid things. If you stop doing such childish things, it will be a big mistake
Before that, I'll sue you for blackmail
You got carried away thinking you were going to settle things quietly,
What are you going to do with me?
You bastard!
Go home now! If you ever show up with something like this again,
you'll die!
You'll regret it
I'm sorry,
He's a nasty guy
I was in a good mood
I made this coffee
Ah, I wish I had let you in
Oh well, let's do that from the second drink onwards.
Don't be shy.
What's wrong?
Why are you silent?
Say something
You look like you did when I first met you
But....
Well, that's right, won't you listen to my piano?
Eh? are you good, right?
I'm not that good,
but please listen to me
Don't come over here
Go over there and close your eyes and listen
Tsukimura-san, have you seen this newspaper?
If something like this comes out,
Haruhiko won't be able to go to school
He's become a laughing stock of the world
and his future is ruined
He should have firmly refused to associate with you
Please go home
Where's Mitsuko?
Haruhiko,please take a look at this.
Aren't you embarrassed to be written such a thing?
And yet you still dated that person
It's a lie, it's nonsense
Even if you say that
It's too late.
Something like this was
written in the newspaper
Who else can you trust?
My mother can't face the world either
Mom, why do you say that?
You don't understand my feelings at all
What's this newspaper?!
I'll go to school and tell them straight out.
Don’t do that.
You should quit school and transfer.
His transfer alone will not restore the school's reputation.
This newspaper wrote an article like this
Of course, Arikawa-kun will be held responsible!
I ask the principal to definitely attend today's meeting.
Where are you going, Haruhiko?
You don't have to deal with me anymore
Haruhiko.
Ooi.
Why are you so panicked?
You must have had a fight with her.
Mitsuko left on the previous train.
Huh? I wonder where she went?
I'm sure she's going to see Hiroko.
She just bought a ticket to Kurihama.
Where's Hiroko Miyashita?
That person passed away.
When?
Yesterday evening.
So She had it delivered to her house.
Hiroko..
She was trying to live as much as she should....
Mitsiko-san!
Let go! Let go!
Mitsiko-san!, you're an idiot!
An idiot! An idiot! An idiot!
An idiot!
You're here after all,Setsuko.
I've been looking around for a long time.
Welcome.
Did something happen?
Aoki-san,you guys are so greedy
Setsuko did something incredible
Setsuko, look at this.
You wrote this.
You did a terrible things.
You helped with this newspaper article.
You did something really terrible
You're a big problem at school
You have to quit school
It's not enough to just drop out
What should we say to Ooi-san and Tsukimura-san to apologize?
You are idiot! You have to go to school and say it's your fault
You.
I don't see Haruhiko
What should we do?
Fall down
This is the time to trust Haruhiko
But maybe you...
that's not the case..
If that's your intention, it's too late now
If not, he'll be living a good life
But...
We don't need to panic.
That makes me anxious too
I'm so anxious I can't stay still
But please think of this as a test for parents, and wait
Sorry, how was it?
He's not coming to school
What on earth happened?
When I told Arikawa teacher that he left home this morning and didn't go back, he was surprised
He's in a meeting right now
He'll come over as soon as the meeting is over
If school is a place to teach social justice,
I believe that those of us who work there need the strength
and courage to not give in to anyone for what is right
I will definitely take legal action at this point
Shouldn't we impose strict sanctions on fake newspapers?
Hold on.
You immediately talk about the law
The key is to quickly restore the school's reputation.
With graduation looming, it's not the kind
of thing we can take your time with in court
The problem is how much trouble
some bad students cause to other students
But this is fake.
So what evidence do you have to prove that those two are innocent?
I trust those two
Stop messing around
Arikawa-kun, what are you going to do about this?
Calm down.
We have to stay without getting too emotional
It's about how to best protect the school's reputation
Principal, you say that the honor of the school is the honor of the school
Which is more important: school or the life of young students?
I agree with Arikawa Sensei's theory
Why didn't those two tell the truth?
I think there must be something to this
If that was the case, why didn't you make it clear?
It's your responsibility as the person in charge
That's right
I too would not feel comfortable leaving my
child in the care of a teacher like Arikawa-san
But I.....
Anyway,Please have the principal respond
Teacher, Principal...
We are currently in meeting.
Leave from here.
Teacher, Principal, that newspaper article is all nonsense
It's my imagination
I was the reason those two were late returning to the inn
Teacher, please forgive me, I was stupid
Setsuko,Thank you for saying that
It's cold isn't it?.
I'm fine.
Sorry
I'm hungry
Yeah.
Eat this.
What? You didn't eat lunch?
then, it's fine for me, you just eat
Don't worry.
You're hungry, right?
Let's eat half each
Yes.
Here it is.
Just a little would be fine.
Don't worry.
Here it is.
Right now, Our family are probably making a big fuss at home
We're both staying in places like this.
This is a very good case for hoax imagination.
I'm fine
I don't care what they say anymore.
It's much more important to live righteously.
That's right, It's absurd to defeat oneself.
Why did I care about dying?
The Grim Reaper got so surprised when I slapped him that he ran away
Did it hurt?
No
It was a good test for us.
From now on, I won't lose to anything
That's right, let's both do our best
Yes.
Are you okay?
Ah, dawn has broken
Ah, the storm has completely died down
Hurry up.
I feel so good.
Isn't it Setsuko?
Come on.
Ooi.
I found them.
Hurry up.
Ooi.
He's Arikawa teacher.
My dad and mom are here too
Oh, my mom too!
It was just as I said.
Both of them are strong and not at all discouraged by this
Sorry, I really did worry you
Madam.
That was good for us.
I'm sorry
That's enough, that's enough
Rather than that, they must be hungry.
Ah, Sendou-san, will you have a bonfire somewhere?
Come on, Call them both quickly
We are going to have a party.
Oh no, what should we do?
I feel so embarrassed.
but there's nothing we can do about it
Let's be bold and apologize together
That's right, we ran away from home
Oh, Setsuko has come
Mitsuko.
Oishi-san.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
My apologies.
It's all my fault
Can you please forgive me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Setsuko,come on, stand up.
We are not angry anymore.
Never mind.
I'm glad.
You're stupid.
Hold on.
Hold on, Setsuko and Ooi.
THE END