Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
The Sexual Code of the Teenager
That's all, As I explained
Women have a major role in human birth, from conception to birth.
You are growing every day to become a mother
So don't be afraid of this mission as a woman.
You have to be solemn
Because you must carefully protect your virginity until marriage.
You both need to understand this female physiology correctly in marriage and love.
You girls need to learn this important period of your life well.
Start!
Please turn your arm from the front
Takanashi-san!
Hey, Fukuoka,
Another cheat day, huh?
What the hell you talk about?
It's a man's common sense
Stretch your arms forward
Start!
(A school song)
Nishikawa-san.
If you feel sick, you can leave early.
I'm OK
Excise start!
Hey! I saw it
Don't look so serious.
I won't tell it to anyone
Hey,Let me kiss you instead
No...
Why you afraid?
Let me do it for once.
What are you doing?
This is yours,right?
Yes
Do you know this?
No
This was in this wallet
Eiko-san, I can't control my heart when I think of you
You're on a high horse.
In short, this is a love letter
Who wrote this?
There is no name of the person who wrote this
Hey, you wrote this?
No I haven't written the crap
See?
Writing a love letter is crap
You confess directly
But I am...
You stupid!
What are you doing?
What's wrong, Eiko?
Eiko is in great trouble,sister.
There is a man who put a love letter in her wallet
Teacher,
I am a thief
It ’s not good to blame yourself.
Anyway,You get head and stomach aches during your period.
When your period is terrible, you unknowingly do strange things.
I also get frustrated during my period
Hey, you girls go home today
If you blame yourself forever, you will get sick.
I worry about it
I'm sorry
So cheer up, and go home
If you feel sick, please take a break from school tomorrow
She is coming!
Eiko-san
What?
Ms Nishikawa seems to have stolen your purse
She didn't
She didn't?
She just picked up my purse and put it in her pocket
I see.
Is that so?
Okawa-san didn't say that
Are you covering for her?
What do you think if that is true?
Of course that's a problem
See?
What are you doing looking for someone else's mistakes?
Do you think you should let bad things go?
God will not forgive you if she does something really bad
Oh...you said God?
I don't want to talk to you girls
Let's go
They are lesbians
God, acknowledge our justice.
Amen!
Hey
I feel sorry for Fusae
I think so
You are graduating soon,sister
I feel sad
I will always see you after graduation.
But....
You will get married someday, right?
I have a grudge against a man who marries you
Don't say stupid things
Please eat this,sister
Thanks
It doesn't matter if it's a little time, so please come visit us
Sorry,I have a plan
Ok, you are good girl
No...
Let's say good bye here
See you
Bye
Sister
I sweated my hands
You've been waiting for me?
I've been working on this painting.
Let's go
I told my mother that I would go to a concert with my friends
I told my dad that last night too
Let's go
That line is funny.
You're on a high horse,Eiko-san
Don't say bullshit
It's not your business
Oh, she is coming
Hey, Princess
Get out of the way
You are scary
Hey, Princess
You're on a high horse
Hey
Stop doing it
What the hell?
That's bad
It's not good to make fun of girls
it's cool
I get it
You are the one who wrote the love letter
I'm not
You are lair
I'm not that for sure
Oh
Come on
You go home
Fuck you
Damn it
Stop it
Let me go
My body is defiled.
I am a woman without shame.
Awwww!
Did you get angry with me?
Stop it
Let's go home
Hi, Nitta
Hi
You're still drawing, aren't you?
I will introduce you someone
This is Ms. Nakatsugawa who is in an art school
This is my art friend Nitta
Nice to meet you
You can introduce her too
Ah..this is Kaoru Mitani
Nice to meet you
We're going to have a party at home from now on, so why don't you come?
Sorry, I need to go
How about you?
I'll see her off, sorry
You stupid!
Oh you, don't play the bell
Who play the bell?
Oh
It was not me
You stupid!
Don't quarrel
You are terrible,sister
What's wrong, Eiko?
I'm fine
I brought some sweets
I don't want
It's very delicious
Leave it there
You are strange
Welcome back
Do not eat sweets before meals
Give this to Eiko
I brought some sweets for her but
She locked the door
She is strange
You shouldn't go
What?
It's pointless
Why?
She's frustrated
I don't like you!
I want to hit that guy's friend
And I'll kick his ass
What is she doing?
She's frustrated
I see
She is becoming an adult
She's a woman of her age.
I see, I get it
No
Which do you like better, me or him?
Tell me
Are you still upset?
No
Don't do that again
OK
I'm leaving here
Thanks
Kaoru-san
God, why can't I shake hands obediently?
I'm scared of my body once polluted
I'm scared if he knows my secret
I'm so scared to live
But I really love him
What should I do?
Please tell me
Fusae,
Are you sick?
I'm fine
I have an English exam today so I'm short of sleep
Oh I see
Good morning
Are you going out?
I have an English exam today
I see
Letter for you
From who
There is no sender's name
I'm going
Eiko-san,
I repeatedly wrote your name on a piece of paper and then tore it up.
But I wrote you this second letter
The last letter I wrote was laughed at by my male friends.
I apologize for the inconvenience to you
I was sorry
I'm waiting for you in front of the workshop room for today's lunch break
Please be sure to come
Oh my god
What the hell?
Watch out!
Hey
Kudo
You sent this to Takanashi?
You wrote this love letter?
Why can't the person who writes this answer reply?
Sorry I wrote it
I wrote it
Don't you think it's bad?
No
I thought I would meet her and apologize
You sure?
Yes
If true, this is forbidden.
Kudo-san
Ah!
Hey,Nishikawa
You didn't come to school today
Where did you take a break from school and play?
Sorry for the last time
I apologize for the inconvenience to you.
Forgive me
Right?
Don't touch me
What the hell, Thief woman
Stop it!
Nishikawa-san
Stop it
What's wrong with you?
It's not nice to bully a girl.
I didn't
Please wait until tomorrow
I'm back
Welcome back
Right now, it's exam time at my daughter's school.
If the electricity is cut off, my daughter won't be able to study.
So please
I'm in trouble
If you have the money to send your daughter to school, you will pay the electricity bill, right?
So please pay it today
I told you I'll pay tomorrow
I'm not saying I won't pay
So please
I'm in trouble
Please
Dad
What happened to this money?
I've saved money
Oh
So I'll borrow this
Take it
She's a good daughter,right?
She is studying in high school
I see
She is currently in the exam
Please do your best to study
He changed his attitude when he took the money
Right?
I'm sorry to worry you
I'll get the money back to you as soon as I can.
My business is not doing so well these days.
I have shamed you
Never mind
You should study hard and graduate.
I'm proud of you
Then I'm leaving here,
Say hi to your parents
Thanks
Sorry to keep you waiting
Depart
Hi,Nitta
How are you?
Good
Do you have time today?
Will you come?
She has left
We are not lover
That ’s okay, right?
Let's go
I'll go to our factory
You can go to sleep
You will be late?
Huh?
Well....
Anyway, our factory is no longer good
My father says he'll shut down the factory and see how things go for a while.
But I have to work
You will be unemployed
Um
Don't worry about us
I'll still talk to him.
So don't worry about it, just study.
Refill
Cut it out.
It's already the 7th cup
Refill
Scold him
Your stomach will explode
A visitor has come
Hi
Is Eiko in?
Yes
A visitor has come for you,Eiko sis
Sorry for the last time
6,7,8,
I won 10,000yen
Tome-san is here?
He just went to their factory
Oh I see
Woman arrested for running away with 700,000 yen
I get it.
You only drink gin, so it's called bar-gin.
Yes
It's a pretty fashionable name
It ’s a really honest sign.
You are a business person
Anyway
You think a virgin woman is attractive?
I don't know
How about you?
It's strange
How about you,Nitta?
What if you marry a virgin female
Well...
You don't care?
Of course I care
You like virgins
Is Virginity Important for Men?
Of course
You think so?
I don't care about that
I care
So I can get married in a matchmaking
The virginity is the most important thing for you?
Not
But
I have to be a virgin to be your wife?
Thank you very much
I want another Gin
Sure
You don't have to go to Bank?
I asked my sister
I want another Gin too
me too
How about you,Nitta?
I can't drink Gin, that's too strong
So beer OK?
Kind of
Can we have beers?
There are only Gins here
No beers?
Then put a lot of ice on JIN
Oh yeah,
Why don't you go skating during spring break?
That man had a lot of 1000 yen bills
But the man was very stingy
Excuse me
Can I ask you something?
Can I work with you?
You can do something different than sell the flowers
You can do something different
Anything ok
Good luck
Oh sorry
What the hell?
Do you have any complaints?
Don't be so upset
I'm not bar girl.
I'm a fish shop
If you want to touch woman's boobs, why don't you go to that shop?
please calm down.
Forgive him
I'm so upset.
If you do next time, I will hit you
So you should be careful
I was sorry
This is not a spectacle.
Go home everyone
Oh Fusae
Long time no see
Oh Makiko-san
You look fine as usual
Did you see?
I did it little
This is not a spectacle.
I don't have parents, so I have to be strong
You are great
I'm not
I was jealous of you girls going to high school when you graduated from junior high school
But I'm not jealous of you
Working is fun even at fish shop
Do I look good?
I'm cute,right?
What? She stole a purse?
I don't mean that
But...
I see...
It's something that women have when they're not feeling well, a seizure.
Teacher...I thought about it
I think I know what it is.
Eh?
Last night she had 1000 yen for some reason
Oh....
She said she saved money but it's strange
Women have a lot of problems.
No way
As you can see, We are so poor
She doesn't have that money for sure
Teacher...
It ’s the will of a dead my wife.
She want her to graduate from high school even if we are poor
And yet, this is what happened.
Don't think too much
Really she is shameless
She might be skipping school to hang out.
Anyway, she's a sensitive time
That is especially true during menstruation.
No..whatever you say
She is a thief
Really she is shameless
Don't say that
I'll kick her out when she comes back
I'm about to catch a cold
Please finish early
Only 20 minutes have passed
Not yet
It's your turn, today
Give me a break!
Not yet
Are you studying?
When did you come back?
Just now
Welcome back
But I'm only in Tokyo today and tomorrow
That's bad
Please wait for a whole
My work will be done soon.
I can't wait
But it can't be helped.
You have your life
Oh, you are good girl,today
Yes
You want reward, right?
Here is your reward
I want more
I'll transfer some money to your bank account.
so Don't waste money
Sure!
Then see you guys
Enjoy your work
Hey Oda!
That's not fair
I don't want to be naked in front of visitor
Don't make excuses.
Be naked!
Give me a break
No
Please share me the money you got from him
What kind of pose you like?
Nude
Yes nude!
nude!
Ok decided!
I'll try it!
Then just draw my face.
OK
Are you excited,Nitta?
Kind of
Get ready for drawing
Turn around, everyone
Close your eyes
1,2,3 then open your eyes
Okay?
1,2,3
Will you still play with me when you go to college?
Sure,Eiko
Please do your best for another year
Why?
I'll go to college with you.
I see.
I'm glad
But sorry I have a plan tonight
I'm sorry
My friend is celebrating my graduation
Your friends are adults, right?
Yes
There are also men,right?
I'm sorry
I thought it was rude to refuse
I'm jealous
Congratulations on your graduation,Kaoru-san
I can't drink
It's Ok,
Right, Nitta
She can't drink
Shall we leave now?
Are you going home?
Yes, See you
See you tomorrow in Shinjuku
Thanks for today
Thanks
good night
See you
God, I'm a dirty girl.
I am not qualified to be loved
Even so
I forgot myself and God
I've made another sin.
Oh....you are here
Dad...I'm a bad girl
What's wrong?
I can't accept people's feelings obediently
I sometimes quarrel with my wife
It ’s not that easy.
I thought you had a quarrel with Nitta
I'm not in a quarrel with him
Don't worry
People who grow up without being loved will eventually love people
Listen,
You are already growing
Did something strange happen?
That's fine
The body is weak
You have to value purity
We can't hire someone without a guarantor
So her guarantor is me
Am I good enough?
I'm working properly
I have a lot of friends
So Please hire her
I'll sell you fish cheaply
Please
OK?
You are good man
So please
It can't be helped
Ok I'll hire her
So you should work here for a while
Work is hard
I respect you
That's good for you
By the way, I don't have a little money, so please lend me 1000 yen.
What?
What the hell you talk about?
You are good man.
I'll sell you fish cheaply
It can't be helped
Thank you
You should repay with this money
Ok we have done
Oh yeah
It's not a thank you, but I'm giving this to you.
Eh?
Ah!
You're going to play tennis?
Yes
I want to play too
No,
I'll play with sister
That's Ok.
You play at school?
Um,
You go ahead and get ready.
Okay
The more I love that person, the more scared I am.
I'd rather not to go for skate
Would you like to play tennis together?
Please
I'm sorry
What's wrong with you?
Actually I had a plan today
Did you intend to go somewhere?
I was going to skate on the lake
With Nitta-san too?
Yes
I feel lonely
Ok, you can go
But you have to come home soon.
Please also buy souvenirs for me
What's wrong with Kaoru?
Did you do anything wrong with her?
Give me a break
I guess so
She is not like you
What do you mean?
Please stop talking bad about her.
She's probably a virgin
She is not like me
Kaoru has already graduated
It's more fun for her to play with him than to play with you
Love is delicate
I hate people who pretend to be adults.
We are already adults
I'm not an adult yet
You don't know?
I'll show you this
You are dirty
Why did I come?
I'm starting to go against my own mind.
I don't even know
They are skating good
Ouch!
Ah! Kaoru-san!
Thank you for coming
Yes
Oh She has come
Let's skating
OK
Ah..I'm tired
Let's go home
We practice a little more and go home
I see
Bye
Skate alone this time.
I'll try
Go
Oh, it's bloody
We can't
No....
I love you but
No..stop it
I love you so much
No...
Stop it
kaoru-san
I saw it
Get out of here
No
No way
I'll tell everyone when you make a noise
It ’s also bad for Kaoru-san.
Don't worry
It's cold outside.
She can't stay outside for a long time
I wonder if she love you for sure
Nitta-san
I like you
I've loved you since the first time I met you
I love you
I'm going to be abandoned by God.
Hello?
Let's go there
Let's go over there
You caught a cold
I'm sorry.
Because you were outside in the middle of the night
The lake is so large that it's hard to find
Right?
Sister
I'm sorry
I don't know how to apologize
It's all my fault.
No..
If only you could play with me
This never happened
It's all your fault.
You're wrong.
Never mind,Eiko
Let's pray to God instead of Kaoru
I don't know how people feel like dying
Her life was about to begin
Kaoru was a little weird
After all We like women like Asako
Oh you
What's wrong?
Are you feeling sick?
After all it is not good to catch a cold at night
But the common cold is not part of the disease.
Cheer up,
It's not so you
What's wrong?
Are you worried about Kaoru-san?
She tried to commit suicide on her own.
So you never mind
Go home!
Go home guys!
You don't get excited.
They came to visit her
I don't want to see their faces either
Calm down
You should get some rest as doctor said
Dad...I...
I will never be involved with them again
What's wrong with them?
Nothing
But When I see them, I feel like I'm looking at me
I was so stupid
I see.
I'm sorry I didn't care of you
I believed in you
I knew you'd reflect on yourself at some point.
Thank you for your reflection.
That's what I believed in you
I'm not..Dad...
I'm not..
Let's go
When you're sick, your nerves can get on edge.
Never mind
Do you believe in a daughter like me?
Why not?
You stupid
You know nothing
You're a foolish parent.
I...I....
Asako...
Please leave me alone
I'm not asking you to be sorry, just you.
I also reflect on myself in various ways
Please talk to me anytime if anything happens
Ok? Please rest
Thank you for telling me
Repenting is more courageous than sinning
As her father, as a religious man, I thank you.
But You're not the only one who sent her to her death.
In fact
This is her diary
I didn't know until I read this
She seems to have been raped by a man before
She was very suffering
I didn't know her suffering
I think I'm also responsible
I feel sorry for her
But she had a beautiful heart
I thought I'd burn this diary as her secret
But I'll give you this,Eiko-san
Take your time reading this.
She tried to live beautifully while suffering
She made a lot of effort
Nitta-kun
She committed suicide against the heart of God
But I'm sure God will forgive her
You two must have the courage to live strong for Kaoru.
Then Let's pray for her
I pray for mercy, God.
I lost my beloved daughter
I pray to you now
Forgive me for all your sins.
Please forgive her sin
Amen
You must carefully protect your virginity until you are married.
You can love your husband, raise your children, and love your home.
This is the greatest happiness as a woman
So as a woman.....
Finish