Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kaei / Shadow of a Flower (1961)
One Saturday in late April
Here?
You'd be happy.
Thank you very much
Hello!
Welcome.
You look happy.
I will also be on holiday from tomorrow
Toku-san, is the madam still in the hospital?
You look great.
Oh, you're wearing an overcoat
Kan-san
Are you planning to go hunting in Hokkaido?
Hey come on!
I'm going to do Fishing
What can I get you?
The usual one is fine.
Whiskey with water
What about you guys?
I'll have a beer
I'll have a beer too.
Where are you taking it?
The east coast of Izu.
By car?
Right, I'll get there then
I'll set out by boat while it's still.
Take me there too
Me too, me too
Look, there's a lot of wind outside.
You shouldn't go
What will happen if the wind blows out?
We might be on newspaper
Two Jokyu of you were dead in the water
No way!
We are not Jokyu
Why?
That's so old-fashioned
What's the point?
They don't say "hostess" anymore
So what do they say?
It's a hostess
That's right, a hostess
Hostess? Looks like a self-propelled drug
There are no more Jokyu people anymore in Ginza
But there's no one like Yo-chan here in Ginza
She's the last Jokyu
Hey come on.
If I don't catch any fish, I'll head back right away.
Welcome.
Don't make weird noises.
Madam
Don't call me like that.
Welcome.
Don't worry
Thanks
The sign outside is broken.
Ginza has great hostesses.
Please be considerate about Toku-san when I'm not around.
I'm sorry
You sneaked out of the hospital
Who is this?
Aya-chan introduced me to this customer
Because of him
Be careful not to steal our customers
You and Yo-chan have to be really strong
By the way, where's Yo-chan?
where's Yo-chan?
She went to drug store
Drug store?
Oh, Jun-chan
Another escape from the hospital?
What? What happened?
You look so beautiful tonight?
Right?
If only you could get motivated
I'm no good, I don't have the talent to be madam
Toku-san, give me a highball.
It's okay, I'll pay in cash
You're a little drunk
I can tell right away because you lick your lower lip
Scotch
What's wrong with your health
I was going to buy some sleeping pills.
Eh?
I can't sleep these days
I see
When I think about this store, I can't sleep either
What if I close here?
I wonder if I should really sell here.
Oh, you owe this much to Takashima-sensei again
It can't be helped
I feel sorry for him, I can't refuse
You have absolutely no talent to be Madam.
Hello, this is Tombo
Please wait a moment
From hospital
Don't be loud
Please tell him I'll be back soon
Hello, She's back soon
Well then, I'm counting on you
Toku-san, please do your best to collect money
I'll send her.
Okay,Don't force yourself
Take care of here
Be careful
Ah, She is here!
It's been ages
Welcome
Let's have a toast for the last Jokyu, okay?
What?
Oh well, let's have a toast for Yo-chan.
I'll have it.
Let's have a toast
I'll go too
This is for car fee
Please share this
But...
Don't worry.
Because it's a hassle
Take it
Sorry
Well, I'll give it back tomorrow
Oh no, tomorrow is Sunday
Oh, I see
Driver
Please have a safe drive.
Trust me
Hey come on
Good night, good night
Good night
The letter was a suicide note addressed to his mother-in-law who lives in Mishima
From this moment on, the timetable for this woman's life was set
Once dawn broke, she tidied up the things she had left behind,
sent this with the key by mail by evening,
and then all she had to do was take the medicine
However, speaking of a timetable for life, Yoko may have thought about it a long time ago
About two years ago in an Autumn
My child said that Tsuyuko said
she would die with my wife
Once you hear it, I understand.
My wife and even my kids say the same thing
But thinking about dying and actually dying are different things
But Tsuyuko is 11
She found out about  that her
mother was suffering so much that she wanted to die
She doesn't talk when she sees my face
She was the one who chased after me so much,
Close the window
Are you suffering?
No, I'm prepared
Even if the young lady dies?
she won't die
She thought she would become disabled in her legs due to polio.
She won't die
because she know it was misdiagnosis
As long as she doesn’t die,
that's fine for you?
Anyway, I don't think I can stay here for a while.
I received my manuscript fee.
Here are 100,000 yen,
but I don't need money
Let's break up instead
It's better,right?
No, I didn't mean to show it like that
Even if you talk about love and romance
The ending of all relationships is the same
I really was going to get married with you.
Even if I quit college, I could get by on my current income. That was my intention
But
it's okay,
you don't have to make excuses
But the word marriage
Today is the first time I've heard it from your mouth,
we were together for 3 years though.
I wish I'd heard those words at least sooner
Even if it's a lie
No
and even when we break up, you
don't even say a word about breaking up
No, I'm not lying, I still have no intention of breaking up
I want to be with you.
That's enough
I don't need a lot of money anymore
I've had enough of this
enclosed life
But we've been together up until now,
so don't make fun of me
Don't even try to make fun of other people's feelings
Just go home. Whose house is this?
If that's your house
then please go home.
Yoko,
Leave
I don't want to break up with you.
Let's think about each other again
Yoko.
that's all
Your precious things
But how do you plan to get on with your life from now on?
Mishima's mother won't be worried about you
I'll be fine.
Ever since I was forced to quit girls' school at 15,
I've been living off the emptiness of Ginza
I'll consult with Takashima
Takashima-san ?
He is a genius when it comes to Antiques
His character is bad.
Please take good care of your daughter
Yap
I won't see you off
Jun-chan is at the store yet?
Not yet.
I'll stop by later
Takashima-sensei is at the grave behind
Oh, Yoko
It's been a while.
Oh, I heard you broke up with Matsuzaki
He brought it up?
No.
I told him
I've been told by you to break up with him
That's true, but that's ridiculously sudden
Come on up
Yoko there?
Jun-chan
I was going to stop by later though
But I'm going out
About Matsuzaki-san?
Well, yap
That turned out to be a good thing.
Even though he's a university professor,
he's a person with no money
You've been following him up until now
So how much did you get?
I can't get it
That person is poor
Plus the kid is sick
You are stupid.
You've wasted three years of your prime
You should send him 30,000 yen every month.
I'm disgusted with you
You're too kind
It's good
Because she says she doesn't need it
But....
what are you going to do from now on?
I'm here to consult about it
The woman who worked in Ginza have no choice but to go back to Ginza.
I'll have to find some place
Why not just have her come to Tombo?
Tombo?
Did you open another bar besides Clara?
Yap
that's why I wanted the money
That's how much preparation you need to do to work in Ginza
Professor Takashima,There is calling
You don't want to owe it out yourself,
Even if he says something arrogant
Unlike before, his wallet is empty
Even the antiques in this room is gone every time he come s here
But they are belong to him
But he has a brother
and is currently in court
Say big things like 30 million yen,
but you won't know until you actually hold the money
He hasn't paid his rent for a while.
But I wonder if that has anything to do with the value of him?
You are always on Takashima side
Your ex boyfriend Matsuzaki said that too
He told Takashima didn't work
Work is not the only measure of a person's worth.
Isn't it more admirable to be respected
without doing anything?
That's a strange logic
Oh, I've known Matsuzaki for three years
I've just started to work with Takashima
You've been friends with the teacher for almost 20 years
Isn't  the only one who respects Takashima is you
But, you know,
All the customers at the bar try to hit on you when they get drunk.
If they give you a ride home, you won't even bother to say it
But Professor Takashima...
I understand that
You say he'll treat you like an ordinary amateur wife or daughter,right?
You are impressed he's
never had your hand held before
He gets involved with other girls
It's different for me.
I've acted a little selfish
but the teacher's attitude hasn't changed
For me, it's enough that he's alive.
I guess that's what happens when you're born a
beautiful woman like you and pampered by a man
I get it
Well, I'll talk to him
Rich people are stingy
There's a lot of fuss about buying a 2.3 million's pipe
Oyo, what happened?
I've decided to help out at Jun-chan's store after all
I've left it to a girl named Ayako
Let's have some madam for Io-chan too
That doesn't matter
If I can work comfortably,
it's no good
It's a battle to be won in the first month of opening
How much do you pay her?
We can talk about it later
Oh It's time
I have to go to the store early today to see the new girl
Can you get me some money?
5000 yen is fine
5000 yen?
Well, I wouldn't say that's impossible
He paid on credit a lot.
Teacher?
I have a little bit,
but I can't borrow it from you.
It's okay.
Instead, Treat me tonight
I'm surprised you're motivated to work again
You hate bars
but I can't help it
I have to believe I can die whenever I want
I can't go out to Ginza when I'm like this
You are still beautiful
It's been my childhood dream
to die before I get old
I don't mind dying anytime now
I want to die too
Why you have to die?
It's good to teach good antiques to people
What's the point of teaching them?
People don't do what I tell them to do,
so who cares?
I'll be satisfied
if I can die doing what I want
Humans can never be satisfied with their own lives
So it's okay to die anytime
Ah, if you are going to die, I don't mind dying too
Yes, then let's die together
I'll work hard for you, teacher
Take care.
Madam, there is a call
Thank you
Kulara's Madam
Isn't she  being greedy again?
Yes, it's Ayako
It's been less than a month
since we opened, right?
Should I ask Yoko?
From Jun-chan?
Yes, I understand that very well
Thank you very much.
Yap
Wow, you're so strong
She's always been unable to talk
in front of customers unless she drink
I sometimes forget that I'm an old lady
and I'm performing in front of customers
Don't be humble
When you are at the store,
I told you to be considerate of Kimono in this pattern color, right?
Sorry
Shimizu-san, welcome back.
You were too late
Give me the bag
Are you going home already?
I have a script meeting with Daita
The video shoot is coming up
I'm totally busy
Well then, goodbye,Yo-chan.
Thank you very much
You acted like you were Madam
She has a husband in Osaka,
but she's cheating on him with Shimizu
That's good
Oh Yoko-san, what's that nice Kimono
You think so?
Oh Toku-san, make Yoko-san another highball
Don't worry.
Kulara's madam won't know anyway
Oh, Hata-san, are you going home already?
Well....
Toku-san here, Prepare any wet towels ready
Yoko
Hata-san again....
Again?
He really wants to get married now
Anyway, seriously
If only you were okay
so please go to the table
Yes, please,
Thank you.
Ayako, weren't you treating me like a fish?
No way
Would you like something to drink?
Yes, I'll have some
You go and order something.
I wanted to have a long talk with you
The highball that Yoko drank
Put it on Hata-san's bill
I get it.
Now I am a lawyer and works as a legal advisor for a large company
I was originally born into a fisherman's family in Chiba
My dad sold his last fishing boat to send me to college
You're with your daughter?
Who told you that?
But that child isn't mine
She's the stepchild of the deceased dorm member
Oh really?
That's hard, isn't it?
What's the problem?
Raising a child on your own as a man?
I've got to ask
my grandmother to come over
I think your child feels lonely when you come home late every night.
Do you want me to come home early?
That's not true
I'll go home if you're with me,
No, I'm at work
No, I told Ayako
Should I tell Junko?
Okay, let's call Kulara
Don’t do that.
Better yet, go home earlier today
Oh, what's wrong?
You're just saying nice things and nothing is getting through
I'm serious
Give me my bag.
I'm leaving
Please wait for me
Hata.
I'm glad you came
Come on in, come on in.
It's a big house,
but we're only renting the second floor
But it was really nice of you to come
Come in.
it's not you, I came to see your daughter
Oh my god.
But It's enough that you came
It's true, I was adopted too
That's why I wanted to meet your daughter
Oh, I see
Is she out?
She's here.
The weather is nice today but I'm not taking her anywhere so she's very upset.
Matsuko
Yes
She's Yoko
Say hello
Welcome
You are called Matsuko-san, right?
Yes.
That's a nice name.
Is Matsu a pine tree?
Yes
Really? I'm Yoko the Leaf Yoko
I work at a place where you and your dad drink.
I know
Oh, Dad says anything to Matsuko-chan
That's because there's only one parent
and one child, so I know everything
You guys looks alike
You think so?
It's not like we're related by blood, though
What an idiot.
What's wrong?
You shouldn't say something like that
in front of a child
Matsuko-chan, why don't
you go out and play somewhere with me?
You wanted to go somewhere today, right?
An amusement park? Or a movie?
Let's leave Dad alone
and go just the two of us, right?
Let's do that
What's wrong? Do you not want to?
You came to see my mother, didn't you?
Yo-chan
Wait up
You left something behind
You don't have to follow me.
I know the way
Don't be mad
Matsuko is like that sometimes.
I'll scold her
She has no reason to be scold
It's not your fault at all. All that talk about blood ties
Yo-chan
If you care about Matsuko that much,
will you marry me?
That's very old fashioned
Don't take advantage of children
Yo-chan
That's how you cheat women.
but Yoko-san is a little clever, so don't underestimate me,marriage fraud.
What?
So it's OK without marriage?
Look,the truth is out
You are about to let the hostess into your home.
and gave it to you for cheap
Let's go home,
Wait a minute
That was a joke
please marry me. My kid is grown up and you can work at bar
I'm in love with you
I am a country bumpkin and not very manly
But I'm really in love with you
Someone has come along.
Please marry me
Please
It's an overstatement.
Don’t do that.
No matter how much you rub your head against the tatami mat
or shed tears, in the end
Only men benefit
Only women get hurt
I'm not a woman worth that much
You don't have to decide
if it's worth it or not
Please reply me.
No way,it's too soon.
Please reply tomorrow at the store.
Well, I can't accept
Anyway, I'm going tomorrow
As you say like that, I guess she didn't feel too bad about it?
Why?
What did he look like?
I can roughly guess
He won't make her a woman
But I don't think it's a bad thing
Reach
Oh lucky again
I agree too. Even in mahjong, if you miss your chance,
it's hard to make up for it
Plus, that person has connections in big companies
and is important to the store
It would be helpful if you could marry him
Because he has a cheeky daughter
There's no ideal marriage arrangement like that.
Don't care the daughter.
What do you think, teacher?
What do I think?
It's not like I'm going to get married
That was it
I'm up.
Stop it, it's dirty way.
Sorry
I'm unlucky today.
Today I got drunk and talked a lot
I feel like drinking whiskey
No Half-drunk whiskey
If you met Hata-san,
you should have brought back some bills
I'll buy them for you
Give this to me
No, it's 5000 yen at the department store
Please pay the cost price
Please
Don't worry.
Because I'm going to drink too
Yoko, it's fine to drink, but if you do it while drinking, it's bad.
That's dangerous, let me take you home in my car
I'm going to the studio for rehearsals anyway
Thank you
it feels good to be treated so
kindly by another girl's boyfriend
Are you talking about Aya-chan?
She is aiming for something bigger
I know this is unnecessary,
but be careful of Hata-san.
Come on, Yo-chan,
I'm sorry
It's okay now, I'm used to coming home drunk
Maybe we should have some tea?
I did, but then the rehearsal started again
Hata-san
You're probably thinking
I'm being too persistent
I just couldn't stay still like that
I won't get a response until tomorrow night
I don't like this place,
take me somewhere else,
You were sleeping comfortably
Go to take another bath
What's wrong?
What time is it now?
It's a little after 11 o'clock
There don't seem to be many customers tonight,
so I think you can sleep in
I'm going home,
what's the matter?
Let me do that
I'll give you my marriage proposal tomorrow.
Who is it? Hata-san?
Oyo, it's me
What's wrong, teacher? Teacher,
you're not even wearing a scarf.
It's gotten cold
Oh, let me have one
I got robbed at mahjong yesterday
I barely made it this far
Did you lose that much?
5,000 yen
I even left a debt
Are you hungry?
your stomach is fine,
but please give me back some delicious pickles
Didn't you go to work today?
No, I went to Mishima to relax
Didn't your mom say something
terrible again?
Talking about marriage
You were pretty serious yesterday,
She's not my confidant.
I regret not telling you it was yesterday
But in the end,
don't you want to get married?
Does that seem like how I see it?
Oh, I'm sorry
Oyo, don't deceive yourself
Well, I don't want to marry you, but
Hata-san doesn't seem like as bad a person as people say,
but I just can't make up my mind
You are confused
To be honest
Well then, I have something to say
What?
I think marriage is bad for you.
Not just Hata
In other words, how should I put it? In short,
I don't think you'll be happy if you get married.
It seems that's the case
Marriage is a kind of deal.
Whether it's money or love, you only get along if you have each other's long asses
You have no experience doing that
Many men have fallen in love with you
but no matter what, you always give it back twice or three times as much
That's why it doesn't matter
Yes, thank you
This is very delicious.
oh, you're right
I'm stupid
no, you're too good for a woman
Matsuzaki once told me that too
In the end, I'm a villain
But there is such a thing
Well, if he loves you, then I don't care what happens
I just wish you'd stopped getting married
It's sad though
Well, there's no rule that every woman has
to have a husband.
It's more comfortable being alone
It could be.
Yeah, I was also muttering after breaking up with Matsuzaki.
You shouldn't act tough anymore
It will snap completely
It's safer if you stay low and creeps along the ground
So you're saying to keep a low profile
Oh, you're smart
But it's strange
When I was talking to the teacher,
I felt a lot of things building up inside me
It always feels like the lump is gone all at once
Oh, I see.
I've already eaten.
Eat some ochazuke
I'm going home now.
Oh, you just got here
That's all I have left of my life.
Why don't you stay? The wind is blowing.
Thank you for the meal
I'll come again
Oh, right? You don't have any money,do you? Yes,
I have 3,000 yen
Take it with you
So, shall I borrow it?
Junko gets mad when I get into debt
Ah, teacher
Be careful.
Is it okay here? It's cold,
so please pick it up quickly
Please give me some extra film too.
Don't show this to Hata
Another one
Squat there
I can't see you much these days,
but maybe you're not letting me in?
Do you not want your boyfriend to spend money?
Don't be cheeky.
Boy?
Stand up.
Your dad pays the bill for this bar.
You are still child
Oh my god.
When you say that, what's so funny about men coming to bars?
Probably no one will come for fun
I don't think there are any girls who enjoy working there
It's a strange place,
Definitely
In other words....
Give it to me
Be careful.
In other words, the anxiety.....someone with no talent like me can't do a job like directing a TV show
And I am constantly being chased by time
It becomes like a kind of neurosis
Confidence is gone and anxiety is building
That's when I need to come to the bar
By your Dad's money
You say it again.
Hey you, let's take a photo
Oh yeah, your dad was a TV executive
Stop it about saying my dad.
Hey, Professor Takashima
please put him on an educational TV show or something?
If that's the case,
I don't have to tell my dad, I'll talk to the programming director myself.
Come in.
Excuse me.
but can you go ahead for a bit?
Yo-chan.
Can't you see Hata-san?
No
oh, that's right.
I just came downstairs with a customer so I stopped by
About his bill?
sorry, I haven't forgotten, but how much was it?
Sorry.
Well, it's not right to ask you to do that
Anyway, his bill has already accumulated
Come inside and wait for a bit
Oh, I see.
Toku-san
I'm short on 2000 yen. Can you lend me
some?
Yo-chan, it's time to stop messing around
There's no need to pay Mr. Hata's bill.
Because I got him to buy Christmas tickets
It looks you are giving me 10,000 yen in change for a 1,000 yen bill
Sorry.
Good evening.
Aya-chan is off?
Hey Yo-chan. I need to talk with you.
What's wrong? You've got a scary look on your face.
I'm so angry.
Can't you be the only one who's okay?
I'm so frustrated,
so what's wrong?
Look,
it's Clara on 7th Street
There was a place that was trying to replace that.
In the basement of a building in Higashi Ginza
That spot got stolen away from me.
Guess who it was? It was Ayako.
She used me to get that spot.
And moreover
It was Hata who gave the push
and brought the matter together
Hata?
Didn't you know? I thought Ayako had a lot of days off recently, and it turns out they went to Osaka together,
to prepare the money for that.
Ayako is Ayako,
and Hata is Hata, right?
He pretended to marry you.
You were trying to pay his bills,right?
I'm totally shocked
and don't like it
Yoko, Hata is here
Kumi-chan
what's wrong with you?
You know what?
What's wrong?
It's been ages.
How are you?
Yes, thanks to you,
that's good
It's so cold
You are prone to catching colds
Oh, by the way, Matsuko wants to meet you
Look, that big doll
you gave her for Christmas
She still sleep with it by her pillow.
I've also been in a bit of trouble lately with the Kanto Electric Railway's land acquisition
After all, it's a government job
I'm very busy
Oh yeah, I thought you were busy buying up bars in Higashi Ginza again
What?
How did you like Osaka?
You felt like a newlywed couple?
Yes, I guess you're serious this time
The other person is a young person
What are you talking about?
Because you're a great person too
It's about time to pretend to slam your head on the tatami mat.
What's wrong with this girl?
You should stop trying to get a hold of the hostess' money.
Stop it
Stay strong.
Are you alright?
You're a crybaby
I'm not going to cry
I've been in Hostess of Ginza for over ten years
I have had many experiences like this.
It's mostly because Yo-chan was spoiled too much
I warned her
but I an really that stupid
Remember that
Yes, yes, I want to be stupid too,
but it seems like my turn never comes
You're cheeky.
I don't care if anyone knows.
Even Takashima-sensei?
It can't be helped.
Come on, you idiot, it's already noon and you have a book reading at 1 o'clock,right?
Oh wait a minute?
I'm so happy
they finally changed it
This is the first time someone has asked me to change my hair style
Yeah, it's absolutely wonderful
I think you should put out a bit more here
You're too noisy
Even in actresses' hair
I often claim
Now I'm ready,
You are sleeping again.
You see, the smell of you still lingers
You idiot.
Are you there?
It's Takashima Sensei
Excuse me.
Don't worry.
I was thinking of going to visit Junko
I came to invite you
Excuse me.
You're welcome
You changed your hair
I wonder if that's Shimizu's hobby
What about dinner, Sensei?
It's lunchtime.
Please try the eel bowl.
I've only made enough for two people
This is the real "thank you for the meal" thing.
I'll call then
Please have some tea.
Is this yours? Oh,
Yo-chan's
but do you have about 5,000 yen with you? Oh,
if you have that much
there's a shop called Nihon
Hobby Store at the Yaesu exit that caters to tourists
I can pay you back right away once I've decided a deal about the Muromachi pottery
Anytime is fine.
Don't tell Oyo about it
Surely you were single
Yes.
Oyo still has the heart of a child
That's how I like her
There's something so sweet
about her little expressions and gestures
Are you going to marry her?
No, no, I haven't decided yet
She seems to have given up on marriage.
But it seems like she wants a little
Please think about that for a moment.
Ah, it's cold.
Are you surprised?
I've been dyeing it secretly up until now
I'm scared to look in the mirror every day
It's not that bad
If you just stay still, you'll get better soon
No...
I knew this would happen someday
If it wasn't lung disease, I'd be cancer
But you're not worried about money
That's good
That's not true
It's okay though, because I sold Clara on 7th Street
As for Tombo, you and Toku are the only ones I can rely on,
so please do your best
You're getting greedy again
money, money, this is your punishment for making so much money
What would happen if I became like this?
So, you should save money or get married
I'm saying you have to choose one or the other
It's about time for you too
If Shimizu-san could marry you
As for Hata
If you had felt that way, you would have gotten together
Hey, hey, you may know a lot about money,
but what about getting marriage?
Stop complaining
That's right, I have something to talk to Yo-chan about
Can you please leave your seat for a moment?
What's going on?
I can't tell this to a man
Oh, I am waiting in the hallway
What,Jun-chan?
Takashima-sensei is broken in the end
I heard it from someone who came to visit me just now
You know, the story about the 30 million yen mansion?
Apparently the bank took it away from him
to pay off his debt,
and nowadays, He seems to be selling fakes.
The person lamented that the antiques world's
records have also fallen to the ground
The world has become a difficult place for people like him to live in
It's not the world's fault
In these harsh times, there's no way he can make a living with such a cheap business
Should I ask the teacher to come to my house?
Don't say stupid things
Even his old friends don't pay him
any attention anymore
Even those people
When teachers used to have money
Everyone was praising the teacher
They were saying he's a genius
That's right.
I wonder why people with such hobbies don't want to give money to the teacher
I don't know much about art or anything,
but the teacher needs money
If I had it, I would give it all to him.
Thank you for the meal!
Good morning.
Yo-chan!
Welcome!
I've brought a rare person with me today
So who is it?
He's liked you for a long time
I wonder what he's doing.
Welcome. Welcome
It's been ages.
Maybe you forgot about me for a while?
that's understandable
It's been 15,6 years.
Wow, Non-chan
I'm sorry
but it was good
I'm glad you remembered me.
Welcome
You look so nice.
I look like grandmother, right?
You are much more attractive than before.
I explained that to you.
He didn't want to ruin the old image,
Hey come on.
Treat me.
Make me drink that most expensive Napoleon whiskey
Welcome
It's fine
Welcome,
this guy was in the same class as me
Unlike us department store managers,
He's bourgeois
Ah, I'm sure it's something like in Kofu
Yes, that's right
He succeeded his father as president of a wine company.
Hey, hey, stop it already.
Anyway, he's having trouble figuring out what to do with the money
Today too
I happened to meet him at the Momoyama
art exhibition in our department store
Well, that's fine
Everyone, please drink as much as you like
Can I have some?
Please, please.
You can drink whatever you like.
Thank you
I'll have brandy cup
Same here.
I'll have juice
I'll have gin.
Thanks.
Back then, all I saw was Non-chan in his school uniform
You should have kept an eye on him then.
Really.
I'm sure I would have become the president's wife
Sorry, I got carried away with the story
What would you like to eat?
This is Napoleon whiskey.
Thanks.
Let's all have a toast.
I'll have.
Cheers!
This, this
You suddenly disappeared back then.
I was dragged into the war,
so if only it hadn't happened....
Stop it....
What?
This guy wanted to marry Yo-chan
Sasagara, You confessed that to us earlier.
I was not lying
But back then, I was still a student living off my parents
You were too popular back then
No way
Yo-chan's customers were amazing back then
Mr. Kikuchi, Biography, Rintaro Takemoto and Shoichi Yokokawa
Also, all the musicians and painters like Soutaro were fans of Yo-chan
and they were wrecking that bar
And look, did you know the art critic Kenzo Takashima?
You knew him?
Yeah
He often scolded me
I don't get lectured often
Was it?
Well, why don't you meet him next time?
I'm sure he'll miss you
Is he still coming here? Of course I want to see him
I'm starting to get interested in antiques
There's something I'd really like him to see
Maybe he'll come by tonight
Tonight? That's a shame
I can't relax much tonight
Oh no, that's no good
I have to go soon
I have to catch a 7 o'clock flight to Kansai
No rush
I don't want to postpone it next time
I'll come back when I've had enough
I'm sure I'll come
Hey Sahara, take your time.
Bill please
If you give us it, I'll lose contact
I will definitely come
I don't trust you
Keep going.
Oh my god.
Oh, that's right. Then I'll leave this here until then
It's a rare watch
My late father's
This was the watch that he gave to his first girl friend
Why do you have that?
I always stay there whenever I'm in Tokyo
Thank you.
Are you dating with her?
Come on
She run an inn in Yugawara
I stayed there yesterday too,
but I asked her to give it to me
It seems to be a survivor where my father went to France a long time ago
That's nice
If he doesn't come, I'll take it
That would be a great way to celebrate
Okay, then I'll lend it to you
If you like it, use it
But this is a memento of your father
Don't worry.
Just take it
Wow, I'm so happy.
Has the customer from Seibi arrived?
That's right, I have something I'm taking care of
How about the three of us go to Yugawara together?
That's great
shall we go?
If the teacher goes, I should thank the person who brought this watch.
That's right.
Wakanourazu, isn't this unusual for Takihara?
It's quite good, it's from Edo period, isn't it?
Is this yours?
No, I was asked by the publisher
Is it for sale?
Yes, there is silver in the gold
Well, 7 or 80000 yen would be a good deal
7 or 80000 yen...
If it was at least 50,000 yen, I'd be ok with it
Like a child, when I see it, I want it right away
Yeah, that's good
Because I was told to leave it to me
Is that so?
I'm sorry about that
Let's take this to Yugawara.
Thank you very much.
How about going to an old place tonight?
Most of the Madam there have changed
But Lupin and Cytheria
Just the name sounds nostalgic, doesn't it?
Okay, come on,
Why don't you join us,Oyo?
I'll call them
Oyo, isn't it about time to break up with Shimizu?
That's not going to happen
You always fall in love with men who don't have money.
Good morning
I heard you were drinking wine with a guy from your company.
but you couldn't give this back?
He gave it to me.
Wow, that's generous.
So...
Are you leaving already?
Yes,the director is calling me at 11 o'clock
The ratings for my show have been dropping lately
I might got scolded
Then see you on Saturday
Oh, what was it?
Oh....
I told you we were going to Kinugawa for an overnight stay
I forgot it
I was in trouble
Why?
I promised to go to Yugawara on Sunday.
With whom?
Nogata-san and Takashima-sensei
Can't I do it next time?
No,I told you yesterday.I won't be off work for a while
Have you forgotten that?
I was so drunk yesterday.
I don't remember anything
Even if you remember his promises , but you forget my promises
You shouldn't say it like that,
Refuse their promise
That's not the case
They are my customers
so just say you received a watch.
I don't even know what you did yesterday
Are you serious?
It's rude to say something like that.
You are a hostess anyway.
I've done this kind of drama before
What do you mean?
I didn't expect to be humiliated.
You switched to the president of the wine company.
I am bar woman
Isn't it natural to cherish the rich?
If you don't like it, just go home
I'll go home without being told
That's right, I owe Takashima-sensei 5,000 yen
I have 5000 yen in my handbag
This was the car fee  Nogata-san gave me last night,
I tell you
but if you open a girl's handbag without saying anything like that, she'll hate you.
I've been cheated by you till now.
So please take your time
Please.
Do you know there's a guest in the Five-Person Autumn-Leaf Room?
Yes, I understand
Oh, Master
please check this
How do you like it?
He's a very nice guy, isn't he?
I understand why you do watch business
I see, that's good
but I don't agree
She's so beautiful as a woman
What do you mean?
Any man would fall in love with her
I wonder if such a person is not suited to be the master of the inn
If men come from Tokyo all the time,
it will be a shame for the inn
She has no men
Don't get mad
Well, she's has no men right now
But what I'm saying is, you never know when she'll find a man
You never know what's going to happen in the future
So you don't like if she takes over?
I've been making it since your father's time
so I'm not thinking about my own selfish gain
A woman can understand a woman when she sees her
You just met her today
Young master
When I spoke to you the other day, I asked the Private Investigation Agency to look into it
Of course, I don't take these things at face value
She's met a lot of different people, like
novelists and painters
She's a bar girl
Well, there must have been a lot in the past
But I'm aware of that too
I got it
If so, there's no need to rush.
Let's take a closer look
I guess you haven't talked about taking her here yet
Not yet.
And the antiques teacher who is also there
I'm a bit curious about that person too
I get so drunk today
It's rare.
You aren't drunk at all yet
It would be a problem if Oyone disliked me for drinking
Oyo
You're a girl who can't stand the lifestyle,
but this time you'll have to be patient
If you feel like you're dead, there's nothing I can't do
I'm going to work hard and not make you suffer financially this time
Don't care about me
Hey, Oyone is kind of nice
I want to be like her when I get older
I think I'd get along well with that person.
I'm drunk
Are you alright?
I apologize for having to step away.
Oh you are here!
Tell Oyone
Oyo has no men besides me
I am her man
Hey, where is my room?
I'll show you
Teacher
Good night
Is it really that unusual for someone like
Takashima to drink alcohol in a hot spring?
The teacher was very happy with this story
What did Oyone say?
she said you should try helping her out until you get used to it
Will I be able to work?
That's why she thinks of me
as his real son
She cares about you a lot too.
What a wonderful garden
How nice it would be to live
a relaxed life in such a fresh air
I'm tired of going back to cramped bars and apartments
When I think about it like this,
it seems like I've been dead until now
I won't let you feel that way.
Come on, let's go.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Mr. President of Kofu is here.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Thank you for your hard work
How is it? Have you gotten used to it?
I think so.
That's a good thing
By the way.
I was just talking to Oyone-san,
but can you please break up with Takashima-san?
What do you mean by break up?
if the way I say things like this is wrong,
I'd rather you just not have him to come here anymore
Apparently he stayed for two nights while I was away
Non-chan
Also, I didn't want to say this, but I'm causing financial trouble to Takashima-san
Well, it's not a huge amount
Even so, If it is made public
He is a fraudster
If you want to bring it up,
Can I settle the matter?
What do you think?
You just keep quiet.
Hello? yes
He's here.
From the Tokyo branch
I will pass it on to you.
Please
Yes?
I know
What?
Of course I've paid
We were just talking about that now
I guess I should have told you first so as not to make things too complicated
I'm going there tomorrow morning at 10 o'clock.
Yo-chan.
Well, you remember this, right?
Apparently Takashima did it again
Apparently, the only things that haven't been given to the other party are the 200,000 yen that I paid for this and the Kiseto cup I bought later
My company has just received an inquiry
It turned out I hadn't paid
It's sad that people only think about what happens if they worry about it
Isn't this the right time?
Yoko.
Thank you.
Oh I see.
Yo-chan has gone to Yugawara for a week
Mom is  in the hospital
No customers will come if we keep doing this.
Welcome.
It's been a while, teacher
It's been a while
What would you like?
You like whiskey,right?
Yes
How about Takashima?
He hasn’t seen me in a while
That's a good place to be
In the end
Is Madame suffering from breast sick?
She collapsed after New Year's
That's a big problem
Sometimes when I come here
I feel a bit strange.
Welcome
Haven't you lost some weight?
You think so?
You look better
You've calmed down too
Yeah, it seems
You were always frustrated back then
but there were good things too
We met around here at Yugawara Station
I really wanted to call out to you
Same here.
Let's go to Box
Welcome
I heard you met a good husband and going to stay at Yugarwara Inn
Takashima-sensei tells me to be patient,
It's his habit to tell you to be patient
When it was my turn, he told me to break up
Did you feel resentful?
Or did you not listen to what he said?
You've always disliked Takashima-sensei
For me,
I hate the way women treat each other
He's actually in love with you but he's scared to sleep with you
That's why he despises people who are with you
He's trying to win your heart by selling the fact that he won't hold your hand
I don't want to hand you over to that guy
But I'll follow him.
You've been in dealing with various
men for a long time in the Ginza bar world
When you're in this business,
you start to get tired of being connected only to guys
At times like that
A man like Takashima looks so beautiful and impressive for you
I think that's the kind of relationship you have
It's dangerous to follow a man like him
It's like blind person is pulling blind person's hand
Aren't you blind person?
I don't care about such troublesome things anymore
When I think about it now, it all seems like a long time ago
One day I tagged along on your trip to the park to see the cherry blossoms in Yoshino
Oh it was beautiful
I didn't even notice the flowers blooming this year
Has it already scattered?
That's right, the evening paper was out
I'd like to see the cherry blossoms in front of the British Embassy, Benkei Bridge, Aoyama Cemetery, or somewhere else
I'd like to see
Shall we take there now?
It's so pretty
I feel like eating it.
I'm not going home tonight
You're the one who went back to your wife and daughter
You're going to Yugawara,right?
For Takashima-san's sake
I won't be going home tonight
OK
In return, I'll play with you just for today
Yoko...
Because the cherry blossoms are blooming
I'm pretty sure Oyo was born around here too
My grandmother, who loved me, often took me
to the Juban night market when I was a child
How is Mishima's mother?
I'm planning to send her a letter tonight
Tonight?
Teacher
I’m sorry.
I couldn't hold back in Yugawara
after all
I tried my best, but I'm really sorry,
You are such an idiot
You didn't care if
it was for me
Did the other party bring it up?
No, didn't
He tell you to break up with me?
I was the one who said I wanted to break up with you
In return...I never want to see that person's face again
I didn't mean to ruin your conversation,
but I've been pressed for money for the mansion's lawsuit
It's not the teacher's fault
Of course, I had planned to cover the expenses.
Well, this is also going to happen
Speaking of things happening,
things are strange between you and me
I'd only ever been jealous of once
It was when I was in Yugawara for the first time
You were really drunk that time
but maybe it was because the other person was a rich guy
Teacher?
I'm going to die
That's already decided
Don't be stupid
You are beautiful
The flowers still bloom
I want to die while I'm still beautiful
No human being is worth committing suicide for
Thank you very much.
You left your underwear
The letter was a suicide note addressed to his mother-in-law in Mishima
I'll send you the apartment keys
Although we are not related by blood,
thank you for raising me since I was little
This is the last time,
so please clean up after yourself
I'm like a found child,
so don't put me in the grave
I would be happier if they turned it into an abandoned grave
and put it in a temple somewhere in Tokyo
The apartment deposit should be enough money
I think you're just saying selfish things and not expressing your true feelings
Maybe that's what leaving a note is all about
I don't want anyone to know that I'm dead
I am dying with such a good feeling,
so please don't cry or feel sorry for me.
Goodbye
She thought she was cleaning up quickly,
but Yoko might have actually been moving
around slowly
Suddenly she became worried that something had gone wrong
and she would fail
She was extremely angry
that such anxiety had arisen
Once she started to get angry, there was no stopping it
She got angry about everything and everything
To Matsuzaki, Junko, and Ayako...
She found the room very small and stuffy.
She was very angry at herself for living in such a small room.
She was upset about something she had spent so much time preparing.
However, when she finished taking the medicine,
something welled up in her chest,
and she thought she could finally cry
It didn't turn to tears.
And darkness came.
THE END