Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kagero Ezu /  Stop the Old Fox (1959)
In the 11th year of the Tenpo era,
the 11th shogun of the Tokugawa family has retired and become the elder statesman,
and it has already been three years
The actual control of the shogunate has passed to the current shogun Hideyoshi and remains firmly under the influence of the elder statesman.
This is a story of the people writhing in that absurdity
It was a heavy rain.
This kind of rain is making everyone nervous.
Taro Mukojima's lord is indeed a person of fortune
He returned home at the right time.
I am known as Okumura Daizen for the Maeda family
Is there something to change into?
Please wait a moment
What a rain.
Rokubei.
Yes.
It seems the rain has stopped, but We can't be able to go to the roof anymore.
First of all, that's not good
Do you also repair leaks?
We have also handle of it.
Ochiai.
Myosenji's Godaisan is calling you.
Oh no.
here we go again.
I can't keep this vague forever.
Just let my intentions leak even a little
to the main keep, and see what happens
Today, I must absolutely report to the lord.
Mukojima's lord said
He's going to have a bath.
Bath?
Well, it takes time again.
In the meantime, I will see Omiyo.
I'll call him.
I'll go.
Recently,I hear there is a maid who has been transferred.
What is her name?
She's called Tomi.
Ask her to bring a tea for me.
Nakano is passing by Okuno room
Nakano is passing by.
How are you?
You look so nice.
Mr. Grand Master seems to be in a good mood these days.
My dad?
Yes that's right.
Actually, I went to my hometown yesterday
and met Inuchiyo.
Inuchiyo?
Has she been in good spirits?
She was very rambunctious.
I wanna see her once.
They say that grandchildren are cuter than their own children
At that young age, I already have a grandchild,
To my father, she is his great-grandson.
I want her to be in control and take
Will she be living in the general's house?
Very soon.
But it will take times.
Inuchiyo is beloved grandchild.
No wonder she is taking over as General.
I can't say it's just that
In Main house, it is to properly fulfill the duties of a shogun
Who?
I'm Tomi
I didn't call you.
I asked her to bring a tea.
It doesn't matter,come in.
Tomi.
Since when are you working at the castle?
since around the end of February
It's unusual to have risen to such a position in just four months in the third circle
You owe them a debt of gratitude.
Please leave.
Is there something troubling her?
That woman is at the cherry blossom viewing contest in Ota
She offered a stepping chair, didn't she?
As a result, the Otaki suffered a miscarriage and came to an end
The Ogosho favor returned to Omiyo once again
That's fine, but she's so clever.
No one doubt the stepping chair?
The stepping chair should be here
in the Nishi-no-Maru
I think so.
In any case, it's an incomprehensible story;
I have taken her into my hands
Was it inconvenient for you?
No, if you had taken her in, that woman would have
faced severe punishment at the Takino residence
Anyway.
You should firmly grasp the heart of the great lord,
Everything won't go well
See?
Yes.
What happened to Sekiou?
He met Omiyo and
he will go to seek the judgment of the lord from the main keep,
Lately, I value the General's decisions more than the head family's. Is there anything you would have done differently?
Not really.
Please be silent on the orders from the head family.
Please do not hesitate to acknowledge anything that you think is important
Also, when the shogun's family is crossing over and having a discussion with the great elder,
Make sure to understand the situation of the conversation without missing any details
We get it.
I would like to address the lord of Mukojima
Sanada shinano is waiting for you at the entrance.
If there is something to discuss, tell him to come
to Mukojima.
then I will meet with the great lord.
Miyo.
I have a maid named Tomi who was recently introduced to me by Omiyo.
Where's she from?
As far as I know, she was from Shimada Matazaemon
Six years ago,she was transferred.
To Moyaku?
Yes.
I need a background check on her.
Ask Shitamura, in Hachibori,
Please check her.
Akame Ryume know everything.
please forgive me for being played with
What's wrong?
I have leg pain.
My shoulder numb,
do you have any pain?
There is no pain.
I have been frequently asked from the main house.
but what do you think about being old lord at Sanada?
I think it's too early.
You think so?
or will I decline?
Yesterday,
I inquired about the princess's mood
and had the pleasure of meeting your grandchild,
She has big eyes and so pretty.
How old is she now?
She's 6-year-old.
Please visit her once.
Yes sure.
Talk to her about things then.
I have been repeatedly urged to follow up,
but the matter of the heir must not reach
I have to talk to her in secret about the succession.
I believe you are indebted to the Shoguns.
It could be.
I'm getting old too; I need to decide on the future quickly,
Shall we decide on INUCHIYO as the successor to INUYOSHI?
We have to get that approved first.
Yes.
That's right, I should write this down
Are you getting fat?
There's no way to get fat.
I'm getting slim.
You must be forgetting about me.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm taking care of you.
You have many women.
I can't trust you.
I'm old.
my body can't keep up with the passing time
It's no good now
Don't say like that.
Are you leaving from Miyo?
Stop suspect me.
I only need you.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I can show you what's in my heart if you want
Is it alright if one person takes it?
Sure.
Thank you very much.
Will Inuchiyo be the successor?
I heard like that.
Tell me the detail.
I'll tell you
as I suppress my soaring heart in vain,
alone in a dream that remains unfulfilled,
Who's the name of opposite?
Koei is coming.
Koei from Chigenji?
Is he that the monk?
He resembles Kikunojou.
I didn't know Rui and Harino were together.
She is a strategist.
I am just dozing off, lost in a dream,
If it is just a prank, it is too late for him to wake up
I don't want to see the color of that.
My heart aches when I think of you.
From Ruri.
For Koei.
For Koei?
Is he a monk in Hanryu?
He is resembling a actor.
Tell us more detail.
I'll tell everyone.
Oshinomoto.
I wanted to see you.
Someone saw me
Your face?
No. how about you?
Don't worry.
Let's think of it as the usual fox-shaped prank
Come in.
Whoa, you're Ochiai
This is Makoto Shimomura from North city.
It's been ages.
Do you have a maid's errand inside?
Nothing.
She resembled someone I know quite well
Who lives in this residence?
Matazaimon Shimada's
I see.
I'm busy now, see you later.
Thanks for your hard work.
Could you close that and keep an eye on the inside of the gate?
According to the letter that you sent recently,
it seems you are still supporting otaki
Please forget about him
You must grasp the proof sooner than that
Wakizaka Awaji is counting on you.
It may be difficult, but for the sake of the greater good,
you must take action
Ok?
Yes.
What happened to the missing step chair on the day of the cherry blossom viewing?
I can't find it,
Still missing?
or did someone take it away?
It was the paint on the chair that caused her to fall.
then there is no way we can live like this
Oharu is visiting you.
She's here?
Oh really?
I informed her.
Sorry for being late
I'm glad you came
Dear sister, Lord. How are you?
but I'm grateful to hear that
you are doing well
Thank you very much.
Today, I received a special notice,
and I thought you might want to see us.
How's shinnozuke?
Yes.
I want to be your apprentice too.
Are you?
I hope I’m not causing trouble for the neighbors
Let's take our time to talk
How're you?
I want to be your apprentice too.
I'm glad to hear you're doing well,
I don’t know much about the situation,
but I’ve heard you have a challenging role,
and that worries me
Sometimes, when I think of you,
I can’t help but feel concerned
There are times when I can't sleep all night
I'm sorry for that much
You also owe a debt of
gratitude to this lord for raising you
I understand the feeling of wanting to be helpful even at the cost of your life
I really don't want to take life for granted, no matter what
Yes.
please don't forget what I've just said
I get it.
After all, we are just two
brothers in heaven and on earth
Even if we have to live apart like this, at least
we should know that we are both safe
I never take my life lightly
Please understand.
This is now on sale at Chōjiya
This makeup is very nice.
For me?
This is the Myojin charm
Please apply it to your body,
thank you
From the top of your head to the tips of your toes,
You have completely acquired.
You'll look better.
You look better too
I have adapted to the lifestyle of the underclass, you know
I wish you would stop by my place,
but I don't want that
If you show off,
it would be a problem for me
When did you start saying things like that?
There's a strange-looking guy wandering around
Really?
Where's lord?
In back room.
Who's he?
He seems a craftsman.
Hi, this is Rokubei.
Did you come?
The sis is here?
I think my sister is over there
Hachobori is chasing her.
Outside?
I would like to head to Mr.Wakisaka's residence with nei
but could you help me bring her out smoothly?
I'll leave later.
I get it.
You can't stop talking.
Our lord has granted us permission.
I would like to ask you a few things.
Yes.
It seems you visited the mansion,
but Is he an acquaintance?
I am here for my practice
Lord Shimada's practice of the Tomimoto?
It is a bit too early for singing practice.
Today, we had some guests come over
Speaking of which, there seems to be another female guest.
Yeah.
I didn't get to meet her.
but I have some errand towards Mr. Shimada?
Well....nothing.
Nitaru
We are still waiting for your announcement, Mr. Daimon
I see, I'll see him.
Take care of him.
Sorry for making you wait.
I'm glad you came with Nei.
What can we do for you?
Today, in the main keep, I received a stern reprimand
from the Shogun along with the elderly ones,
I have also heard that the Shogun has expressed some dissatisfaction
Don't worry.
Stay here.
As you know
The Ogosho decides everything.
Although I am the general, I have no decision-making power.
He said you were accepting
But he's had enough of you.
I see.
Hayashi shigonokami
Hayashi Shu is a god of good fortune
They are trying to improve their status
If they get to the top, the right path will not be opened.
The elders also made their decision.
But they don't know anything about you
Everything must be done in secrecy
If our actions fail,
You have to cut your stomach yourself
You have to take pride in this action.
Matazimon,Nui
You guys make an effort
Are there any problems with OKU homes?
Yes
There seems to be some trouble there
I see.
Rui.
You are not here to investigate OKUJO.
The goal is to correct the political disorder that lies beyond it
Their research is the first step.
But this is a skill that only a woman can do
Listen, I'm counting on you
Yes.
Sekiuo is in Ishinomaki with Ushinomaru, right?
Apparently Negi came before him.
Really?
I've suspected she was coming to the castle for some time now.
So?
She has been working in Sanno rooms for 4 months now.
Her rise is so fast
Sekiuo did it?
Did he notice something? Perhaps?
Nui
About Omiyo
On the surface, she is said to be the daughter of Sekiuo
but in reality, she is the daughter of the
head priest of the Yanaka Kannon Temple
I didn't know that.
Recognizing her beauty,
she was adopted as a daughter
and became a favorite of Ogosho
As a result, She does what she wants
She is a very greedy woman
Are you back?
even though I have returned,
you won't wake up?
I feel just right at this moment
Just leave me alone
Hey cone on, what's going on?
Please look at my clothes
I was followed by a strange man
What kind of man?
I'm glad you care about me
Hachioji.
Hachioji?
He's there again.
Are you really listening?
Yes.
I tried to run away from him
I'll go around the moat of the storehouse
I finally went all the way to Shibaguchi
and just got back,
Did you make it?
Oh no.
Can you do a lesson today?
I was lazy today
if you keep that up, the dojo won't thrive
Where do you put the noodles?
Can you put it in the strainer?
So why Hachobori chased you?
It seems like he was watching a decent mansion
The lord was out with his sister.
I thought if I just helped them out a bit,
You shouldn't do such useless things.
I wanted to be of some help
You don't have to ride on her's coattails too
The young woman went to Oku house.
I don't really understand what he's thinking
Isn't it okay?
She works very hard.
and that doesn't sit well with me
It's fine that he took in and raised the daughter
But she is unaware
the lord hasn't done anything to owe her
sister went to the castle as she wished.
It's all the same either way
Things that will continue from now on
Don't do something foolish
If he does that, he'll be forced to commit seppuku like my father.
The lord is worried about you.
By the way, your body is really hot
Come on.
Look, what happen.
I've heard that there is a doctor
around here, right next door
Thanks.
Today, all the doctors are off.
She is seriously ill, so please
We'll pay.
Well then, I don't need any money
I see.
A car will be prepared.
I kindly ask for your assistance
Sorry, but we cannot meet your request.
You seem to be dizzy.
If you are like that, I don't think you can do your job.
There's nothing we can do
Wait.
If I am  drunk, Do you think I can't work?
But how can you manage if you are so drunk?
I don't want to blame it on alcohol.
I'll take care of it
I see
Well then, please
Get ready
Then, bring a wear over the top
Currently, a doctor has come
Come in
Please handle her with care.
She suddenly felt unwell while out.
She seems to have breast pain
I see.
Does she have a stomach ache?
No.
It hurts you?
if the patient ate anything unusual
this morning?
Not really.
If that's the case, Does she have tuberculosis?
If so it, ok.
What do you think?
I want to talk to you alone.
Does she have a husband?
Why you ask like that?
Well, I asked something unnecessary
Let me just offer my assessment
This is a celebration
In other words,She got pregnant.
What is your name?
I reside in the realm of Shiba Shinmei
I am called the town doctor, Ryo An.
Don't tell anyone about this.
If you carelessly leak information to others,
it could endanger your life
doctor should never speak about their patients' matters
Please rest assured
Ogosho..Ogosho..Ogosho..
Please hurry and Ogosho...
Ogosho,He was struck down by illness.
Ogosho was struck down by illness.
How's he?
He's still not good.
lord is here.
In the unlikely event that the shogun remains as is,
No, that can't possibly be the case
Calm down
Calm down, calm down. What happens if I rush?
What doctor say?
The doctor says it's a stomach ache
She has a lot of worries.
and I never imagined she would suffer from various illnesses,
If she doesn't die
If her illness continues, this house will be in a lot of chaos.
Gohonmaru will take action
Echizen and Inaba will do something.
Miyo.
Please take care of her together, you and Miyo.
even if the shogun were to visit.
I see.
If this was going to happen, I should have written her a letter of approval.
Is he hopeless?
we must not give up hope
Is there anyone here?
I am Tomi.
Inuchiyo just has arrived.
I see.
She's a creepy woman
Should we kick her out of the Awaji house?
No, no, let's leave it as it is for a while
Inuchiyo.
Lord.
Inuchiyo has come to see you.
She's Inuchiyo.
Does anyone know that you were pregnant at the castle?
only one person know in my room.
There's no need to worry about it.
It's not even been talked about in Oku yet.
The elderly people of Mukojima are also worried about this.
Sekiou knows about us?
Just in case, I told him
Does he know I'm pregnant?
He said you should just rest at home.
What do you think?
I am very honored
If I could do that, I would feel very relieved.
I have an acquaintance who is a skilled doctor;
You can have an abortion
Are you giving up on this child?
You can rest there for a bit and then go home.
Are you saying we should kill this child?
I will surely give birth
What do you think about castles?
I plan to quit due to illness.
and at this age,
I never thought I would feel this joy.
Please let me give birth to your child
I kindly ask you
I feel that strongly
I understand your feelings,
but how will old lord say?
Old lord?
Okumura
You tried to get away with using me
What are you talking about?
It must be so
You think Inuchiyo will be successful if he gives birth to an heir.
You are planning to abandon me
You are over thinking.
I truly think you are adorable
Don't get me wrong.
Are you sure?
Trust me.
No matter what old lord say
Is it your child.
Even if I am being taken care of at the mansion,
You have no right to give me orders.
I will definitely give birth to this child.
I want to have this beautiful child
Maruniumebachi?
it's an Item who wear Nishiki
It's a luxurious item with the plum blossom
design inlaid in wood on a silver fitting
If we're talking about it
it might be something from around Hongō
Actually, I felt the same way
The feelings of the Kaga Maeda family
Wait a minute then
The shogun's charm
The daughter from Omiyo
So that's why she went to marry into the Maeda family
So, if we speak from that angle,
it means we can also know the name of the maid and the man's family name
Well, that's about it
She asked the local doctor to examine her.
She is really naive.
So she's trying to keep this a secret
I made a few threats.
You managed to improve the price.
Let this story be heard by Iimura's man
he'll probably jump at you with their eyes changing color
There's no sake.
Ok
Yes, the conversation is quite lively
Tonight, I will settle
down here
Since the two of us have started drinking anyway,
let's just go with it
When we drink, we can't stop talking.
If only I had become a doctor who could imitate drinking without limits, I would have been more popular
That's your good point
I hope you can marry soon
What are you talking about?
I've been targeting you for two years now
But he married with you.
I've made up my mind not to have a wife.
What Kikukawa say?
You blurted out unnecessary things about the root story with Kikukawa, didn't you?
You said that Inuchiyo would be the heir.
You tell too many secrets to other people.
What if main house know about it?
I’m sorry.
I'm giving you a role
Through Kikukawa, Don't try to relate to Miyo.
She's definitely going to give birth to a child
She does not wish for promotion or involvement in local politics
You can leave the matter of Kikukawa to me,
OK?
as long as Kuga's side
delivers this to Hongo through the maid,
It seems like a love letter
Excuse me.
Please Give me orders
Did you manage to send someone to Hongo?
Yes, just before.
Received a reply from Okumura?
but the messenger has not returned yet
since it has been over an hour and a half....
He will return shortly.
Please encourage sweating by then
Let me have it, please
Your makeup seems to be smeared
Why not wash with hot water?
Thank you very much.
I will do that.
If you need help please let me know
Where is my dress?
Excuse me.
I have brought a kimono for you
That?
Yes.
Lord said It was more discreet to wear it.
For a while,you should wear this.
There is a man called Ogushio here.
Please.
Are you here?
You have become more feminine.
Okumura is coming?
He will be arriving shortly
I'm jealous of Daizen with a woman like you.
When will the baby be born?
The doctor said in 3 months.
Did you see a doctor?
Surely it's not a doctor from Jochu, right?
He is a doctor in a town called Ryo An
doctor in a town?
You did something careless.
He is a doctor in Shiba shinmei called Ryo An?
It's ok.
It's a problem if a woman becomes pregnant in a house where men are not allowed.
Do you realize this is a big problem?
What happened?
You.
Who are you guys?
Are you alright?
my real master was next to me
I don't know who you are
I have no idea
Are they thieves?
I think they are different.
What on earth are they?
Were you saved?
Master, let me get in
My boss has caught
Ryoan?
He just received the order
but because of night
I was told to follow him just in case
However, halfway there, he was surrounded by 5,6 samurai,
and he was taken straight to a large mansion in Mukojima
House in Oki?
My boss told me to let you know if anything happens to him.
They must be the people who came to this house last night.
Is something wrong with the neighbor?
It seems he was attacked again
I'll be right back
Where?
Mukoujima.
Did she have a forced suicide?
She was dumped by a man, they say.
She's stupid
She's beautiful. what a waste.
from that back gate.
This is the Nakano sekiou mansion.
I see, that makes sense
My boss should be safe?
but it might be too late
He should not have examined her.
What should I do?
Don't go home first
Please let Toyoharu know that I might be late
Uemochi
who?
Hold on.
Wait!
who?
I apologize for intruding without permission,
I wanna see your garden.
Without any notice, How did you get here?
Nakano Sekiou's garden is awesome.
I've always wanted to see here.
I believe it is a place where one cannot expect anything even if one asks properly,
How did you get here?
What a nice garden.
It's awesome.
Catch him
There is an intruder.
Where?
Light up
Something suspicious has sneaked in
How many?
One person
One person?
He must has been investigating a doctor
Alright, capture him.
I caught him, so please come quickly
I'm sorry for being late
I heard that a drowned body was found.
who are you?
I'm curious about it.
She was a woman of 26,7 years old, she was pregnant
she was pregnant?
The allowance for Collection of drowned bodies will be submitted all at once tomorrow morning
Thank you very much.
It seems that he has something to do with the drowned bodies.
What can I do for you?
Did you find out about the identity?
It was handed over to the person who came to pick it up
Which one was picked up?
The magistrate's office took over.
It was taken by the magistrate's office?
Yes.
It was taken by the magistrate's office...
Mr. Shinnosuke is here
What's going on with Shinnosuke?
Rokubei, it's rare to see you.
How are you doing?
Shinnosuke, please wait a moment until I finish writing this
Take your time
I have only brought something that I think
will please you.
and then I will take my leave
What's that?
Please finish it.
I would like to see that item first
What's that?
Here
What's wrong with this?
Is this the first time you've met with Ofumi?
Yes.
She's Fumi, my younger sister
This is Shinnosuke
I am a small trader, but I am also
allowed to come and go to the castle
We will wait there.
Please.
I haven't seen Shinnosuke for a while,
but he looks good
He's always easygoing
or perhaps it's about who the owner is
Wait a minute
The letter has just been delivered
According to the document
there was a man called Kikukawa a few days ago
It is said that he requested a
lodging at Myosenji Temple in Azabu
Myosenji Temple
Yes,that's it.
This is the temple that Ryoan mentioned
That's the Kikukawa that got pregnant.
So, to erase that secret,
did they attack Ryo An?
It could be.
Is the drowned person Kikugawa?
No, I really don't understand anything
They say the magistrate's office has taken it over
magistrate's office?
I will visit Wakizaka tomorrow
and show this
Well then, I will take my leave
Stay here.
When I think about Ryo An
I can't stay here
Is he alive or dead?
You helped me by
jumping
You are always complaining.
I am just concerned about Ryu-an's well-being out of neighborly kindness
; how long has this been off?
It is 8.7.
I hope this flower decoration is wisteria,
but you don't really like the peony?
Shino was at the recent meeting with the Oyato
family After seeing the Fujimusume from Fukushima,
I can't find any peace unless it's at Fuji
I didn't know about that.
Fum is thriving.
Otomi
I've read this
Is there any other supreme and unusual book?
Let me see.
How about this one?
This is about retaliation?
Yes.
a woman's revenge on her enemies
This sounds fun.
Let me borrow this.
Please take your time
Please lend me something too.
Yes, yes, please take a look
What are you doing?
The text you read
comes from where?
I know your very important secret
I am the Ochiai Kyudo
I have been wanting to talk to you once
What can I do for you?
I will show you your secret
Can you come there?
If you take a look,
you will know that the item is right there
before anyone notices, please go.
Oh
I believe you've seen this before.
I've never seen this before.
No?
I have no idea at all
Not known to you?
I see.
If you don't know, there is no choice.
I'll take it somewhere.
Don't do that.
This step was painted with lou.
It is a stepping chair that someone offered on the day of the cherry blossom viewing
there will be nothing left to hide
I have kept this hidden here until today
Do you understand my feeling?
If there is anything I can do for you
from now on,let me know
and I promise to be of help to you
Mr. Ochiai
I need the stepping chair
Are you asking me to hand over that?
I can give it to you,
But it depends on what you do.
Please meet him one more time
I will definitely hand it over at that time
It's a notice for the afternoon
It's already early, so go ahead
Shogun's residence have just returned.
Did you tell the General about it?
Through the deity of Inaba
I mentioned that he should not take the chopsticks in front of the person.
but just to be sure, let me convey it once more
I hope it will work well.
He either uses chopsticks or he doesn't.
If he uses chopsticks, the plan fails.
I hope you will recover soon.
Aren't you going to start with the chopsticks?
Thank you for your hospitality, even if I don't eat.
Please take care
I would like to leave
Mino.
Why didn't he use chopsticks?
Tell me.
Please Forgive me....
He didn't eat it because he was wary that it was toxic.
perhaps poison may be mixed in,
What?
poison may be mixed in?
Are you sure?
I'm sure
Mino
Shogun wanna kill me?
I'm sorry
Bring paper and ink
I got approval from old lord
He wrote?
No one come
How was it?
It seems that yesterday, about three elderly people were brought.
Perhaps one of them was my boss.
Ryo An was not included.
He might be still in the house.
I don't know if he's alive.
Yasuke-san, let's go to Kozukappa
Please wait a moment
You mentioned something that cannot be ignored
Who are you?
Are you local here?
What were you guys talking about?
We must have met somewhere
I don't know
What were you guys talking about?
We must have met somewhere
Where was it?
That's right, let me hear your name
My name is Mizukake Nigenosuke.
You're rude.
I need to ask you something.
Come with me.
Sorry
I am also quite busy
I will give you a punishment
For what reason?
I have the right to ask.
You make quibbles.
There is more than enough water in the moat,
but unfortunately, there is no ladle, so there's nothing to be done
You bastard!
This must be a house with a small pillar
Yes
Where's your boss?
Don't you understand?
He's not here.
What can I do for you?
I need to ask you something.
What is it?
Are you a woman?
What's the hell?
What can I do for you?
Actually, it's someone I know
I think he was brought here and buried
Man or woman?
He's 51 years old,local doctor
I have no idea.
Ask my dad.
He'll be back eventually
Oseki-san!
My clothes is ready?
They are in shadow
Not yet?
Don't touch it.
It was worn by a drowned woman.
Is this the kimono worn by a pregnant woman brought from the magistrate's office?
That's right.
How did you know?
She was carried here.
She was age 27,8 beautiful women.
we buried her with Oseki-san.
Would you sell me that kimono?
That?
I'm willing to pay whatever price you ask
If you buy that belt, I'll sell it.
OK,Oseki?
It's not mine.
Sorry to call you out on such short notice.
Wish you guys could have seen this sooner.
Please
We kindly appreciate it.
Please take a look.
Have you nominated Inuchiyo as your successor?
Old lord approved it at Nishinomaru Oku today.
I'm sure your hardships were immeasurable.
My efforts have been worth it
Each of you should first feel relieved
With this we have nothing to fear from the original family.
If approved by the Old lord, the Shoguns cannot go against it.
But there is no relief yet.
I am aware that any enemy may appear from anywhere
We know.
Then let us celebrate this day by coming together for a moment
My successor is....
It was decided
Inuchiyo will be adopted a child
When she comes of age she will be a general.
What?
That is...
Who did something like this?
Who's the hell?
It seems even you was surprised by that kimono
What?
Well, that's because it's a kimono that was put on Kikugawa
Poor thing
Kikukawa's body was moved from the magistrate's office.
She was treated like a fool, buried in a hole like a dog or cat,
The kimono and belt are returned to you.
Who's the hell?
Come on.
Be quiet and listen to me.
Sekiou
Did you kill the town doctor,Ryo An?
Is he still alive?
There's an intruder here.
You look so evil
Who's the hell?
Tell me your name.
Dakatsunone.
Let the endorsement speak for itself; indeed,
You were trying to control it with the approval of the Ogosho.
Some people don't agree with that.
Is anyone there?
The legacy of the Shimada family.
Did you see it?
Get after him.
Capture him.
Damn it.
The back of the north was open, and so he was the north back gate
This music is good
I am praying for the recovery of your lord's illness
You came to get the stepping chair, didn't you?
I thought you would definitely come,
but I won't keep it in the same place forever
Anyway, I waited
I wondered how I could meet you
I was so consumed by that,
but you have come to an end
Were you waiting that long to meet me?
Are you sure?
I don't need to lie
I can do anything for you
So come on.
What are you going to do with me?
Still don't know how I feel?
If what you say is true,
please show me the evidence
What?
Yes, if I understand that,
I will follow your heart
What's that?
The other day, Ochiai-san told me to consult him about anything.
I see
I have a request
What's that?
Mr. Ochiai always accompanies the maid
when visiting the temple
You have also made a stepping stone to the temple
You are the truth
If you can see the truth in me,
please show the letter in that manner
show the letter?
I would like to read such
a sentence once
Do you want something like that?
I will show it to you
Promise me
Please fulfill my request instead.
This is not good idea.
I can't hold back.
Please
What happened to the real thing?
What's wrong?
The way these tiles are stacked is bad.
This method gets someone hurt.
It's over there
Climb that peace and into the garden
Did you hear any sounds of fighting inside?
He said I had going home first.
Oh my god.
I don't know if they are here or not
I can't call out loud
Yasuke, Run!
Hold on.
Capture him.
She is very suspicious.
We have procured such women.
What a nice.
Where did you bring her from?
She was at the back east gate, so we caught her.
What kind of woman are you?
Why did you observe this mansion?
I did not observe it
You're lying.
There was one more man,
but I let him slip away
Do you understand that this is Nakano sekiou lord's mansion?
I have no knowledge of such things
To be honest, We will get you naked.
I didn't stepped into the mansion
but why do you have to capture me just for walking outside?
We suspect you.
What kind of woman are you?
You don't seem like an amateur
You can use me however you like.
She seems like an interesting woman
What kind of woman are you?
I'm teaching singing
Are you?
Are you a singing teacher?
You seem like that kind of person
Can you sing?
Try singing there
My song can't be sung without a shamisen
Don't be greedy
You are always trying to act clever,
but you are really nothing special
What did you do with the woman's corpse?
We will take care of it shorty
Shut up!
Look at that.
Why is the discarded kimono with the belt?
You bastard!
Did you kill the town doctor?
We have buried him in the the Ushigome.
Last night, someone sneaked here.
Daizen, those subordinates of your are completely useless
They can't even catch one.
Sing quieter.
Don't be loud.
What's wrong?
I’m sorry.
Hold on.
What a awesome.
She looks just like a certain person.
Bring her to Hanare.
Yes.
Forgive her.
Okumura
What?
That woman...
Do you know her?
Excuse me.
Get on your knee.
She.
She is indeed a creature of the same hole
What's your name?
I'm Haru.
Do you have any brothers?
Do you have a  younger sister?
No.
No?
You are lying.
Daizen.
Let Shimomura-san deal with this woman.
Tell him to be strict.
I get it.
Ogosho is about to die
Really?
Hayashi is here now.
Is he getting die?
Please get ready
I get it.
If he dies, read that his approval in front of all of you.
Please
I get it.
Wait
Do you really think you can escape?
This woman should be dealt with severely.
You are going to die here
Kill her.
Stay down.
Capture him
You.
Why you are here?
I'm worried because you didn't come back
I knew it, You were Sekiou's subordinate.
Don't worry about me, just run away
How about you?
Don't worry
Go to your uncle's house
Yes.
You.
Don't worry
Will you run away?
I won't run away today
I feel different than I did yesterday
I will reveal all your secrets
Just bring it.
You are disrespectful.
This is the Lord's approval.
What?
His approval?
What are you going to do?
Don't ever give him that letter of approval.
Come on.
His sword skills were very effective.
He finally got the Lord's letter of approval.
The approval letter left Sekiou's hands.
Will Shinnosuke take away that certificate?
Or Sekiou will take it back.
This document of approval would have a major influence on the shogunate's political course.
Meanwhile, In Edo Castle, is adding to the great elder's critical condition.
THE END