Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kage o Kiru / Cut the Shadow (1963)
This is Sendai's castle, known as Aoba Castle
As the largest castle in Tohoku, it is very spacious
The number of people working here is said to be over 35,000.
Of course, they are not always working
But still, it is a considerable number.
It's Itsutsuhan
It's 9 pm current time
This congestion seems to be due to the truth of the worker, which is the same now as it has always been
What the hell you are?
There're a lot of workers
Beginning with a morning meeting
Lord is coming
He will give a singing
The young man inwardly doesn't seem to appreciate this morning meeting.
They would be able to sleep that much better in the morning without it!
He will give a speech
Young men these days are not good
They are flaccid.
They must respect our lord
I worked harder when I was young
I think this is very hard for young people
When you're working so hard, you can't even doze off.
But
They are working here
Right now we are at peace and the only job we have is to inspect the weapons.
So they can doze off
Don't sleep!
Do you work as a boatman?
Me? I don't
Your rowing was superb.
You're stupid!
It's just joking.
You are no use
Where's he?
He's at home
I know
He's looking around house
Oh he's working
I admire him very much
I’m going to see him at work
Hold on
You shouldn't go
Don't worry
I will guide you
I want to see him working hard
I am very grateful to him
I am disappointed that his son has become so bad
So I want to see him working hard
Hold on
I will bring him here
I'm still young enough to climb stairs
you had better wait here for him to come
Get out of my way
I want to see him working hard
Hold on
You stupid!
don't raise your voice.
I'm sleeping
Jodai is here?
Are you kidding?
Excuse me
Why you are not working?
I'm frustrated
is your job to sleep?
I was really sorry
The castle tower protects from foreign enemies
In short, it will be the last stronghold of the castle.
That's right
If a foreign enemy enters the castle, we will shut ourselves up there.
There we will wait for reinforcements and defeat the enemy.
In that case, the top floor of the castle will be LORD's home.
Even if the battle is fierce outside, he must rest here.
I was trying to see if he could sleep well here.
You may have been loud, but I didn't mind, and I slept peacefully.
I think that your snoring was so loud that people outside were surprised.
The tower of Aoba Castle is wonderful!
Thank you very much
I can't talk with you
So please leave
I heard you're always flirting with women
I have to explain
If I am popular with women, is it my sin?
It's up to women.
It's none of my business
You're stupid.
I hope you have a stable family
do you want me to marry someone?
I can't
No one wanna marry you?
No no. opposite
no woman is worthy of me
I heard that your daughter is very popular.
Yeah, kind of
if so she can be my wife
Your wife?
Please think about it
You're stupid.
I don't wanna have my daughter marry to such a man
Are you alright?
I'm alright
It was close
It was okay because you hid early
It was not ok
he was talking about that girl
Look at that
That's Lord's palace roof
How about that?
That's Lord's wife palace
There is only one palace in a castle
Here has two
But
Originally there was one, but later there were two Palace
It doesn't matter if it's big or small
So They built one of the same size but it's not the same
Over there is much more luxurious than here
I'm called a lord, but she's called GOZEN-sama
What do you wanna say?
you shouldn't have a better wife than you
You'd better take a commoner's daughter as your wife
Don't worry about that
we are not your case
KUBOU's daughter and JODAI's daughter are different
There is not much difference between a general's daughter and a commoner's daughter
It's too noisy
Hey
It's boring to be in this crowd, so why don't we go out for a drink?
You intend to marry JODAI's daughter.
No way
It's not true?
You are annoying
there was such a story
I said I can think
Everyone talk about it
Oh I see.
I'm popular
Anyway, everyone had a good laugh.
Everyone had a good laugh?
they said there was a big difference
I thought she was a very modest woman
she doesn't have a pretty face
You are the worst.
She's so beautiful
Have you seen her?
Not
She must be beautiful
I never trust gossip.
Rumor has it I'm a playboy.
I'm a playboy?
No.
You are a pure boy
I never trust gossip.
I'm back
Please come to Dojo
Dojo?
Someone wanna battle with you
Again
A man who wants money to drink
It could be
I'm tried. Give him money
Samurai must fight according to the rules
I have to fight against such poor people
How much you want?
1 ryo
Ok I will  hit your arm
Give up?
Ok I will bring it to him
Can you lend me 1 ryo?
I can't.
You pay 1 RYO every match
I know but I have no money now
Your father's subordinates had more than 30 people
But now, your subordinate is only me
I appropriate you
I just want you to return the money I gave you
You know how much?
you haven't paid me a bonus for four years
Cash rebuilding is 58
30% interests
That's just small money
I have a lot of assets
Thank you for coming to work early today.
In this way, I changed my appearance.
I love to play at night
It seems that tonight is the last night
Why?
You were found?
Gozen will come back suddenly
Really
When she comes back. I'll lose all my freedom of movement
Please wait a moment
I need money.
Lend me 2 ryo
2 ryo?
I can't
I'll give it back
You should ask the Lord
He has no money
Jodai control his money
I have talk of marrying a rich woman
Marry?
You're kidding
Gojodai's daughter
That Sendai girl?
That is an unprecedented occurrence, isn't it?
Naonto is here?
Gojodai
Thanks
I'll give it to you in celebration
No one here?
Thanks for coming
What a messy room
Not a single piece of furniture that was there before is missing.
that is very precious
I sold it
You are stupid
I sold it to pawn shop
The interest is 7%
How about the picture?
it was exchanged for eggs and rice
Lord
What's wrong?
I will go to play to Yagurashita
Yagurashita?
Enjoy
I don't
You don't drink?
Take it easy
Shut up
You look good
I couldn't bear to see you
I haven't paid in a long time?
I will pay the money
I'll support you.
Please bring him to here every night
Chu-san
Chu-san?
is a nickname for my name
Can you look at my palm?
Dirty!?
I can easily hold a woman's hand by doing this.
I was leant this
Dirty!
Hey old man
old man?
You are not young.
What do you mean by dirty?
He's good at joking
Since I was very poor when I was little, he wants me to be happy.
I'm glad, if it makes me feel better.
He's a really sweet guy.
but he has no money like me
But I really love you
When Gojodai come?
Well.....
what are you hiding?
She comes home earlier than I thought
maybe she'll come home tonight
I know but I can't stop
Let's have fun,
Here's good place
After work, alcohol is very delicious
Are you afraid of your wife?
Stop saying it
Don't call me old man but Sho-san
Chu-san
I'm sorry
she comes home without contacting me
Lord has come home quickly
Where's Gojodai?
He's still drinking
Come!
What have you been doing?
I'm sorry to have to excuse you. I have an urgent matter to attend to.
That's not what I meant.
I came here because I have something to do with you.
I came to say something I forgot
my daughter wants to marry you
but I know what kind of man you are
I will tell her that you play with women every night
she may be very surprised.
But I think it's better than marrying you
you should hit your head and die
I want you to return the money I gave you
She choked.?
No, she was just trying
Not Naondo but Gojodai's daughter
No no
GOJODAI made a joke about him in front of his family
She told me to marry me
She doesn't know how you are
We should tell Gojodai how you are
So Asked Gojodai to go to Yakurashita
then see how he was playboy
He refused to have her to marry him
but she didn't change her mind to get married
She said she would hang herself without permission
damn it. what the hell about the play boy
You are just play boy
Who told I"m pure boy last day?
I didn't have good eye
You came here to marry Kiyoshiro-san's daughter, didn't you?
I didn't mean that
I just happen to come here
Sorry I have a guest
Please stay here
Please pay all the money that I paid
That's supporting money for me
I will make sure you pay
Master
Sorry, please come here
I will make sure you pay
Hi
You tricked me and played with Komachi
Did I? No way
I heard you're going to marry Jodai's daughter.
It could be
but the story is not true
she is very beautiful.
She won't marry a man with no money like this
But you are popular among women
Thanks for saying so
I consented to this marriage for money
I hate that kind of woman
What do you mean?
She's totally ugly
You have a guest from Date
Please come here
Go to see her
I'm dake's daughter.
Thanks for seeing me
Thanks for coming
Mr. Date's daughter, SADA, has arrived.
she didn't sneeze
I'm Shogen's daughter,Sada.
My father told me to come see this mansion being repaired.
I didn't want to come here, but I came to mind to come here for marriage.
I wanted to preview this place for my wedding
I appreciate your concern.
Here is too old
It would be quicker to rebuild everything here, but please take a look at everything
Thanks
Please look at the room
Here's reception room
She did sneeze
Here's guest room
I'm Botan.
I am always indebted to your husband
Please take this.
Please come to see me later
There are a lot of strange maids here
Please guide me
Here's living room
Lord
Is she Yagurashi's girl?
What are you talking about?
Shogen's daughter is getting married, so I was thinking of celebrating
Excuse me
What's wrong?
Lord is here
Lord and Jodai's daughter are here
Please keep going
Why would you marry Mr. Shogen's daughter?
She's nice,right?
I'm sure you'll regret it later
I wish you happiness and happiness in the future
Excuse me
Don't be shy.
Come here
Please keep the promise
What?
My father told you
We'll do something before sex
What the hell?
Oh I know. You mean it?
Besides working as a lord, you also work in kendo.
You are famous for your high kendo skills.
After this, please fight Sada in the dojo.
If you lose, please go to kendo training.
I don't have to go to the Dojo
We can fight here
did he have a showdown with her?
you should be more careful
I think it's a very good thing for Sarah to face off against him.
I want to see them face off
Thanks in advance
I will do my best to fight you
Stop!
Let me fight more
It was nice fight
Thanks for showing me
I told you she was strong
If you feel frustrated, you should practice Kendo with all your might.
I hope it's good for your life
You were in Edo for half a year, but you were more interested in women than kendo.
You can't beat that woman with that
Don't worry.
I'm better than her in terms of ability
I met a lot of women in Edo, so I became very good at dealing with women.
I'm not sure if your technique will work for your wife.
I'm sure it will work
Does it hurt?
Take care
get ready for the bath
I want to take a bath and then have a drink
Please come Dojo
you fool me too much!
I'll definitely beat you!
Last time I lost, but I also trained at EDO
I got much better
Are you ready?
I took revenge on you
After all, lying is bad
Oh you are here
It's nice to have you here.
Don't worry about money.
Let's drink together
Orusui is calling you
I'll be pissed?
You don't practice at the dojo, you just play around
Let's go
OKOK, I'll be back soon
Oh my sword
This is Samurai's must item
Oh I can't walk
Call cab
Hey,get ready and go
You stupid!
I'm shame of you
I'm sorry
I'm not mad at you playing around
because I’ve been doing the same
Drink and play around
But drink first-class liquor and hang out with first-class women
you play right
So I've  called you
I thought you would scold me
Let's have fun
I think you have a very different way of thinking.
Don't flatter me
I think you are more wonderful than Jodai
Cut it out
I really think so
Sorry I'm late
Oh you come here
Thanks for coming
She's Kimiryu
She's nice right?
you are so amazing to praise
Please drink
you stare at her too much
my face is not beautiful
Please stare at me
I was a little worried
What's that?
Never mind.
Give me a sake
I'm happy to meet you, so I'll give you SAKE three times.
He'll treat me tonight.
I can drink a lot
I'm glad.
Let's have fun
it's not so good to be around him
Why?
he is famous for playboy
I don't think so
You are pure man
Yes I am.
Sendai people call me so
be careful with money and power
I'm not concerned about money
I want to support him
You mean it?
I mean it
Let's drink together
Good night
I'm home
Welcome home
Can I order?
You can't
Can you buy sake for me?
I heard she's your aunt
Your aunt is very kind and beautiful
Ok I'll go to buy
Everyone was worried because you didn't come back while you were outside.
It's bad to drink alcohol with my parents
I heard a lot of rumors about you
About me?
About your wife too
Don't get jealous
You fall in love with me so I picked up you
Do I fall in love with you?
How did you know?
All women like you fall in love with me
What do you mean?
My wife looks like you
You were kicked out of the house after losing to your wife.
Oh you know that
They told you everything
they said you were such a bad man
Why don't you practice kendo instead of just playing around?
I don't feel like doing it
I heard you're a kendo master
It's bad you lose to your wife
That monster wanted to fight, so I fought her reluctantly.
that monster?
My wife
We are in an era of peace, so we don't need kendo skills.
Japan has 260 clans
However, the top of them is not necessarily a kendo master.
I think I'm not bad
But she has appeared.
She's not honest
If she's in love with me, my physical appearance is irrelevant.
That's the difference from you
She was too proud to find a reason to marry someone like me who had no money.
She's trying to make me a respectable man.
She is delusional.
It means beautiful story
Give me a break
I won't let her do what she plans.
Gojodai,Shogei Date.
He's here to give you gifts
What? He's not here?
He knows Gojodai comes today
Bring him from Dojo
Well..but...
The Geisha you called has not come.
Don't be disappointed
She didn't come last night too
Toda is the same
Toda?
That Takegaki's?
He comes every night, and He finally took her out
He finally took her out?
To where?
He's good at teasing women
Look at that
Damn it
What's wrong?
What are you going to do?
You're stupid
Gojodai
Yes I am here
Why you come here?
You told him,right?
I asked him to bring me here
You know what? I am away from my wife.
I want to have fun in Edo too
Gojodai is here
Gojodai is here?
Oh my god
Why?
I have to go
Excuse me
I really hate that old man
That's funny
What's wrong, Naondo?
I don't feel like playing with My dad
Don't call me Dad but Bros in front of girls
Bros?
Good evening
Edo girls are here
You look so nice
I'm shy
I'm Sho, nice to meet you
nice to meet you
Please
Dad
Call me Bros
Does she look like someone?
Who?
Sada
No way.
Woman like her shouldn't be here
Oh,If I look closely,I can see a little bit of her.
But she's much better
Are you people trying to bully me?
Oh you look unhappy
What's wrong.
Let's have fun
I'm very afraid.
I can't have fun with you
This is our work.
Don't be modest
Thank you
Someone wanna dance with me?
I will
I like you
What dance?
Anything happy
You wanna dance too?
No way
Are you running away?
Let's have fun!
Where are you bringing me?
What's wrong?
I feel that Sada is here
No way
Why did you refuse to have a sake from the Geisha?
I'm too shy at beautiful woman
It's weird, Gojodai and Kimiryu are first meeting but they look too friendly
I'm his son so I know how he plans
I'm going to Sendai
Sendai? for what?
I'll check if Sada is in Sendai or not
Play
Practice
Again
Take your arm back little bit
How was it?
She's there
Is that so?
I'll see Kimiryu soon
Kimiryu is absent these days but I'll try to call her tonight
I found out.
I can't believe why you made this
I'm so frustrated
I know How Naondo is
I'm counting on you
Please wait until the waitress returns.
It's waste of my time
Wait
Kimiryu has been ill these days
But she told me to come for you
Why you doubt me?
I'm not lying when I say I have a cold.
I've come here all the way for you
I see, I get it
Serve me
No way
Don't get upset
Will you marry me,Kimiryu
with me?
I really mean it
What's wrong with your wife in Sendai?
I'm leaving from her
You are my wife is very similar
I can't stand with her attitude
But you are not
I want a woman like you
Suddenly the wind seems to have changed direction.
I think Your wife resents her skills.
There is another way for a woman to be happy.
I'm sure She thinks she's happy.
I don't think so.
She wants to lose to you
But she deliberately doesn't want to lose
I bet she is sad all the way
How you know?
I am a woman.
I understand woman's mind
The water is deep around here?
It's not shallow
If I don't come out, please help me.
I'm counting on you
I've decided to live with you in Edo
I can't
Kimiryu
Stop it
I'm sorry I'm drunk
Don't be upset
Since you are recovering from illness, you can go home early.
I'll see you off
You fought me in Sendai, didn't you?
I want to have a serious fight with you
I can't fight seriously
Hold on.
Tell me the reason
A hitman has no reason to kill you
I'll get the woman
Hold on.
Help me
Kimiryu
How much you got paid?
I'll pay you twice more
I'll pay you 3 times more
I'll pay you 4 times more
I'll pay you 5 times more
I'll take it
You are good business man
Recently, prices are getting higher and life is very difficult.
Can I get it?
we were hired for 10 ryo.
So give me 50 ryo
50 ryo?
You don't have the money?
I have
So give it to me
I will
Right away
Kimiryu
Get out
I don't wanna see your face
You're really bad
you are really sissy
without Tatewaki I would be dead
You have abandoned me and gone.
I’m really disappointed in you
You are scam of man
You will die without anyone liking you.
Hey big news, Naondo has come back
Really?
he comes back after a year
As soon as he came back, he applied for a match with Sada
he said he wanted to have a match with her in front of us
this match is very important to him
he can't afford to lose this game
he might cut his stomach if he loses
If he wins, he may hit her
I feel scary
I hope the match will finish soon
But all is not lost when the match is over.
This is not a simple problem to solve
Naondo
Lord
I was worried about you so I came to see you
did you improve your skills?
I don't know
Why you don't know?
My teacher taught me everything and said all you had to do was polish your mind
So you leant?
I don't know
But I think my heart has grown?
It doesn't make sense if only your heart grows
You have to win to her
Be sure to win
It's time for the match
Please follow the rules of martial arts and fight properly.
Ready
Thanks in advance
Same here
Stop!
You made it!
congratulations!
I was going to cut myself if you lost
A man should never lose to a woman
Don't you think so?
You made it!
The money you're lending to Naondo is fixed at 4 years' wages, isn't it?
Cash rebuilding is 58ryo, isn't it?
It's 61Ryo
I lent him more in Edo
Interest is 3% per year?
I will give you 100 ryo
You're kidding.
I don't mean that I want him to return
I thought you went to Edo to return the money.
I'm not with that lazy master for the money
I expected to see him as he was today.
You don't know anything
Please
But
I'm asking you
hit me harder
Was it too hard?
Sorry
Forgive me
Gozen
Call me Kazuko
but
Kazuko
Lord
Please forgive me
I'm a woman, but I had too much pride in my work.
I have humiliated you so many times.
I think this is a lifelong sin
But I didn't do for myself
Trust me
I love you with all my heart
Hold on
Kimiryu
Serve me
you knew everything
I was confused first
Start From Gozodai,Orusiwaku,Tatewaki
And Sagai, they were all together
I was sorry
I feel ashamed of myself
You tried so hard to get me back on my feet.
I really got impressed
I didn't understand a woman's heart
I practiced for my stupidity
It's thanks to you that I won to her
I'm so glad
did it hurt when I hit you?
My bad
Serve me
when did you know?
Because I used to hang out with a lot of women,so...
I was in this room looking at the mole behind your ear.
I saw it in the boat
Sada
Yes
You won't beat me tonight?
Look at that
That's Lord's palace
How about that?
That's Lord's wife's palace
There is only one palace in a castle
That palace is no use.
There will be empty from today
Lord
Congratulation
Last night I slayed my woman's shadow
In return,I am tired
I'm sleepy
How about you?
Same here
Shall we have a nap?
I drunk with my wife for the first time in long time
I stayed over night
I am tired
I will sleep here too
Hey
Don't play Drum today
And so it was a quiet afternoon at Aoba Castle.
Since then the noon drumming has been discontinued.
THE END