Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
A morning in Greater Tokyo.
Salaried workers from the surrounding commuter towns gather at the station.
the population swells
to hundreds of thousands,
and the days continue like poking a hornet's nest
When the sun went down and night came,
there were no people around and it was as quiet as a graveyard
Only the sound of footsteps echoing through the night sky
Even though it's work, patrolling late at night is extremely creepy.
It is said that dozens of people died in accidents before this building was completed.
and it is a mysterious thing that may be the curse of those victims..
Strange things happen sometimes.
Kaidan Otoshiana / The Ghostly Trap (1968)
A ghost story?
When Iwahashi from the Staircase Development Department finished his overtime and tried to go home,
He said he heard the sound of typing coming from somewhere around the room where there was no one there
At first, no one believed it
A security guard named Sakabe said that he had definitely heard the sound of typing coming from the documentation room and it caused quite a fuss
But these days, is there ghost story?
But document section's workers are afraid of it.
Isn't it the ghost of Nishino-kun who disappeared?
Stop talking nonsense and get to work
Sorry.
Ghosts? stupid..
Apparently  typists said they didn't want to sit in the seat where Nishino-kun used to sit
Why?
When they sit there, they feel unwell.
They get Headache or loss of appetite
Is it true?
They says because of Nishino-kun.
Is she really dead?
I don't know.
In this era, such irrational phenomena never occur
Chief.
I can only find this one copy of the document room,
but there is one more copy,
I've been looking for a long
time,
it's okay, I'll find it.
This has happened before
The memory of this fate must have permeated this room?
Such a foolish thing would not work.
It was all done with careful calculation.
And already half a year has passed
At that time,  I was still president secretary.
This is a company that has a large presence throughout South America
There is a possibility that the numbers could grow
It's possible that number could be ten times higher next year
I thought Mr. Hancock would sign a contract with Jizo Industries.
Luckily we and they can make a deal.
you guys gave up too quickly.
It is entirely my fault
This time, it was a good learning experience
Please let her wait a little while.
Your daughter is here.
I'm going to ask her what she needs
It may not seem like a big deal.
Actually...
Mr. Hancock's sudden change of heart was due to Kuramoto
He made it.
I'd never heard of that before.
I've always thought that Kuramoto was a useful man
He only went to a night school or something, but he's good at languages
And he has courage.
He managed to settle things with Mr. Hancock
Sorry for the wait
I think the president will be done meeting in about 20 minutes
I don't need my dad.  Will you coach me in golf again?
The president's daughter is here again.
She's come to see Kuramoto-san?
Of course.
I wonder if they'll get married
President likes him.
then he got big fish.
He'll be executive.
But he has a girlfriend?
Even if he has a girlfriend, he'd dumped her and get married with President’s daughter.
No wonder.
Wanna have a dinner tonight?
But if the president...
Don't worry about dad.
Yes.
I'm serious...
yes!
Again...
Golf?
You don't see me these days.
You are so cold.
You are so stupid.
Yes.
I was so busy
Won't you kiss me?
The first time you kissed me was in an elevator
You forgot?
Wait.
It might seem weird
Is there something I want to talk to you about?
I can go to your room tonight
May I?
Well...
Are you busy?
I'm having dinner with a client tonight, it's a bit inconvenient
Kuramoto.
When did you start playing golf? When you were a student?
No...I'm still not good.
I went to night school.
I also attended university at night
I live a life of poverty you can't even imagine
How did you learn English?
I was living with a foreigner.
There I washed the dishes and mowed the lawn
As I take care of the dog, and I learnt English.
You're awesome.
You were late.
I had a job
You don't have to hide it
You met the president's daughter, right?
Are you jealous of me?
You're stupid.
I'm not interested in her.
I've got something to talk about. Seriously
You want me to marry?
I know.
Women shouldn't say that.
Why?
No!
Now, if I get too tired of anything, I start to hate that woman
You're smart so you know what I mean.
You
This may be a bit surprising for you, but can you marry my daughter?
She seems to be in love with you
I agree with her too
What do you think?
I'm sure you'd be able to handle that wild girl.
Not at all, she's a wonderful young lady
This is a lifelong issue for you
so please think about it.
Of course, if you don't feel like it, you can refuse even though she's my daughter
No way...
Hey.
There's a news.
What?
president's daughter and Mr. Kuramoto is finally becoming serious.
Really?
As expected, it's from driver information so he made it.
He is good at getting things done,
envy him?
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't jealous
The President's Daughter Anyway...
He'll be executive.
I have something to tell you.
I'm busy.
The president asked you to marry her daughter to you?
Where are you going?
Follow me.
What do you wanna talk?
Don't pretend you don't know.
Did you hear?
Of course you turned it down?
Tell me.
I can't turn it down that easily.
Why?
it would be different,  it's from the president.
So what about me?
Of course, I have you
I've reserved my reply
Please decline immediately,
but..
It's like an order from the president
Nishino-kun
I slept with Mr Hancock for you.
Don't say that.
I'd say.
I honestly didn't sleep with that foreigner.
It was so painful I could die
You said it would help you if I did that.
I'm grateful
If you thank me, so why don't you turn down the offer from the president?
Let's talk a little more calmly
The offer from the president has a certain charm that I can't give up
No, it's not that I'm into her daughter.
If I get married, I'll be guaranteed a position in the executive ranks.At the very least, I will be promoted to department manager.
How wonderful is the position of department manager for an office worker?
If I become a manager, I can do my job the way I want to
Well, more than anything, I want to show everyone.
Those who looked down on me
because I was poor.
So what?
You're saying I have to give up?
Don't get me wrong.
At this point, let's make a cold decision between us
What do you mean?
Listen.
I don't think marriage is necessary for us
Marriage is a stupid, boring formality
You and I have a deeper relationship
You did great job.
you've done all that for me
The boss's daughter will be my wife for formality only.
In other words, she's a wife for special occasions
You're my lover
I hope You'll understand.
You said it nicely, but in essence you started to hate me
Not really, but I might not like you if you talk about marriage too much
It's ok if you don't marry me
If you hate me that much, I'll cut you off
In return, I'll make it impossible for you to marry the CEO's daughter
I'll tell the CEO everything that happens between us
That will ruin your marriage
No matter what happens, no matter what happens,
I'll never give you to anyone
You're mine.
Washida.
Did you make up your mind?
I would be happy to accept your request
I know she's a selfish girl, but I'll be counting on you
I'd appreciate your help
anyway...about the wedding.
I'd like you to come over to our place for dinner sometime.
Thank you
Now, what should I do with that woman?
Hold on.
What are you doing?
It can't be helped, since this is such an important matter
I'm busy.
I have to prepare for class now
But
What do you wanna talk about?
My thoughts on marriage are as I said the other day
I'm going to marry the president's daughter
But this is just a way to get ahead
It's a loveless marriage,
I'm pregnant with your child
Eh?
Your baby.
Are you sure?
Really.
How do you know it's my child?
It's your baby.
Your child may be Hancock's child.
You are a terrible person.
You think I'll give birth his baby?
Get an abortion.
I thought you would say that.
I hate kids.
Okay? I'll give you the fee.
No,
I'll give birth. It's your child.
Stop that stupid idea
I'm not being ridiculous anymore
You're trying to intimidate me?
but I won't be intimidated by that
I want to give birth
I think I'm getting in the way for you.
But I won't break up with you
I won't let you marry the CEO's daughter
I thought you were a little smarter.
How much more proud you would be if I were to succeed
You know?
I don't care if you get promotion.
I have already soiled my body for your promotion.
I want that reward
I'll give it to you, what reward would you like?
I wanna be your wife.
To avoid being an illegitimate child.
you're more of a villain than I thought
It's you.
I'm a pure-hearted person
I've gone too far,
please give me the reward.
I just can't do that.
This is a once in a lifetime opportunity
I'll never take this chance, no matter what you say
I'm going to be your enemy.
Hold on.
Where are you going?
I'm going to president office.
Are you sure?
of course.
If you talk , I can kill you.
Go ahead.
Kill me.
Come on.
Don't be loud.
You'll think about it again?
Which one?
I lost.
You marry me?
It can't be helped.
Oh CEO.
Turn down the offer.
Hold on
Don't rush.
Are you confused?
No
I'm in a hurry.
Let's go.
She have a concussion
Well, it's nothing serious, but I'll take an x-ray later just to be sure
She's three months pregnant
It hurts.
Before the marriage, I'm going to promote you to a higher position
That would be better for public opinion too, so .
thank you
But I still feel like the business manager is too much.
I don't think so.
You are now a person who does belong to the basic department head
I knew you were useful, so I kept you with me.
In that case, people who are much more senior than me would be under me
I don't think you need to worry about that
Yeah.
You'll never be the next president if you're that weak-willed
Don't talk too much.
About your honeymoon,
How about you travel around the world for two months?
That's awesome.
It would be a good opportunity to learn from this
experience by visiting our branches.
Please have this.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for today?
Did you like the steak?
I made it.
It was very good.
I wish you had told me that sooner
You.
Please take it easy today.
Mom,please.
Renoir?
It's real,
it's amazing
Our grandfather get it.
It must have been quite expensive.
Did he say 30 million?
Are you interested in this kind of thing?
I was born poor, so I have a weakness for this kind of luxurious atmosphere
Kuramoto-san
Dad said he wants us to live in a house near them when we get married
Of course.
it's okay if Mom and dad is near you?
I don't care.
That was a good thing
I know I'm happy, and my dreams come true
I am happy too.
I can't believe I got to marry someone as wonderful as you
You've been my idol since the first time I met you
Me too.
Money and CEO's chairs.
Everything are going to be mine.
How do you feel?
I have a headache
what the X-ray results are?
I don't know
I never thought it would turn out like this
Sorry about that
You probably wish I was dead
Don't say bullshit.
If I die with my neck bones
I wonder what's been
going on with you by now.
Don't even joke around
But I won't be killed
Are you insane?
Maybe you hit your head and went a little crazy?
I'll revenge you.
I'm gonna ruin your marriage
Don't get so excited.
My head hurts
Don't get too excited,
just calm down and listen to what I have to say
I've made up my mind
I'll turn down the offer.
I was about to make a mistake because of materialistic calculations,
I was an egoist just like you said.
Please forgive me for everything that's happened up until now
Why are you still angry?
First,
I can't believe it unless you turn down the marriage proposal to the president first
I'll definitely go to work tomorrow and refuse
Not tomorrow, say no now
Now?
You can just call now
It's late.
Look, you can't refuse after all.
If you don't say it in front
of me, I can't trust you.
Then I'll call him.
Is President Yukawa there?
This is my secretary, Kuramoto
Yes, I'm very sorry to bother you so late at night,
but I would like to speak to the president
for a moment
Sorry.
Are you the president?
Were you sleeping?
I'm very sorry for the late.
but it's actually about your daughter
However, I think that this is too much for me to accept,
so I will have to decline
No, please don't feel bad about it
I will express my feelings again tomorrow, but please forgive me
Hung up.
How about this?
Ah, I'm exhausted.
He was in a bad mood and maybe He'll fire me.
Sorry.
I need to be done about this woman quickly
If things continue like this, I'll miss out on this great fortune
Now, where should it be?
Are you working overtime today?
Yes.
I have to put together the rundown for the
president's speech by tomorrow
You need my help?
See you.
Yes, How about the underground water tank?
Hold on
What would happen if the dead body started to decay in an aquarium?
This water is drained to the water boilers and hand washing facilities in various areas.
The water is dirty and may clog the water taps
Hair may get caught in the pump valve
Yes, here is better.
If you put it here, it's complete. There's absolutely no risk of it being discovered
Hello, it's me.
Did you took off your bandages.?
That's good
Is there anything wrong with the baby in your belly?
Don't worry.
People say that the president is in bad mood.
I turned down the marriage proposal
I was happy.
I also felt refreshed.
I'm happy
I want to talk to you about various things about marriage.
about marriage?
I thought we had to do it soon for the sake of getting married for the baby.
Well then, let's talk about that.
Come here?
Where should I go?
I'm still at work and working overtime.
Is there someone there?
I'm alone
I get it.
Please come to this secretary's office at 8:30
Don't let the guys from work see you
It's okay, I'll sneak out.
Yes.
Sorry I was late
see anyone?
I didn't meet anyone.
Let's go.
I'm happy.
It's going up.
53 minutes
Today, I would like to thank Haruo Kuramoto and President Yukawa for their marriage
Congratulations to Midori on their marriage
I would like to extend my heartfelt congratulations
to everyone who attended the reception
I finally gave up hope in the face of poverty and humiliation
In those dark and miserable childhoods I dreamed of the glory of today
Our round-the-world trip finally reaches its final destination, Hawaii
Right now, Midori is truly filled with happiness and it was a dreamlike honeymoon
They'll be arriving in Tokyo on the 12th.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Is everything ok?
Nothing?
Were there any personnel moves?
No.
Documentation specialist Nishino Etsuko is missing.
Did she get married or something?
No, she just disappeared
Missing?
She hit her head on the fire shutter
She hasn't been seen since
We contacted her parents and tried to find her, but they don't know where she is
Did you report it to police?
Apparently they filed a search request with the police,
but the police don't seem to know anything about it
I was surprised. There are surprisingly many people who have disappeared
Apparently there were 90,000 people there last year
There're a lot.
Etsuko Nishino's brother is here.
He would like to meet you.
Me?
Get through in the reception room.
Sorry to have kept you wait.
I'm Kuramoto.
This is Etsuko's brother, Nishino Fumio
Thanks.
You live in Saitama?
What can I do for you?
About Etsuko.
I came here often but
At that time, you were traveling.
I was in abroad.
Actually, I was surprised to learn about Nishino-kun's thoughts for the first time today
Still no clues?
So I was waiting for you to come back
Why is that?
There are people who say that
my sister had a very close relationship with you.
So I thought maybe I could find out something
if I asked you.
We dated at work
We had no private matters.
I heard from doctor.
My sister was apparently pregnant
Is that true?
she was in a deep relationship with someone
I'm looking for him.
Yes,
Do you have any idea what it is?
I don’t have any. I’m in a completely different department.
I see.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help at all
I'm currently at work
so sorry for bothering you
If there is anything I can
contact you right away
please
What happened ?
did you do this?
What are you mad about?
Don't leave your stockings on
Let me sleep a bit more, my head hurts
Your head?
I couldn't sleep
I had a scary dream
What kind of dream was it ?
the automatic elevator stopped midway.
It's pitch black and there's a power outage
No matter how much I call for help, no one comes
That's ridiculous.
Wake up.
It's really stupid that ghosts appear in a refreshing company?
Don't say stupid?
Who said that?
The driver, Ikegami, told my dad the other day,
but you're not stupid enough to believe a story like that
I'll be working a little late today
Are you still here?
Thank you for your hard work
Is it true that there are ghosts in companies?
I have headache....
It was 8:53.
What does this mean?
The sound of type writer. A voice that sounds like it's coming from the bottom.
Surely a ghost is here?
It must be my imagination
Hello?  Oh....Nishino-san?
I'd like to meet you for a moment, but I won't bother you
Yes, I'll be waiting for you on the north side of the building
I'm sorry for calling you
out of your busy schedule,
Were you able to find something?
I still don't know where my sister is, but I've been trying to look into her social circle
Finally, I found one person
The man is a buyer named Hancock
A letter arrived at my sister's apartment from this man
From the contents, there was a relation between them.
He's in Brazil right now
In that case, he is someone who does business with us
I didn't know.
I don't know what happened.
According to the man's letter,
he will be coming to Japan soon,
so I'd like to meet him when he arrives and ask him about it
But I feel like my sister is no longer in this world
What do you mean?
She might be dead
Why do you think so?
I just somehow feel that way
suicide?
No.
It seems like she was murdered.
That wouldn't happen.
I'm sorry to bother you when you're busy
This is going to be bad for me.
Hello?
Something has happen, please come
Someone is here.
No one is here.
I saw someone here.
but it's just your imagination, manager
I saw her with my own eyes,
it's strange
I don't understand. I just can't understand
Was it just my imagination after all?
What's wrong?
Don't turn on the light.
Keep hugging me.
More.
You are violent.
Why you hate me?
Sorry
Something is wrong, tonight.
Get out.
What's wrong?
I'm neurotic.
That's a hallucination
It seems that once something dies, it cannot be held back
Let's check the body again
The body should still be at the bottom of the pipe shaft
Is he okay?
He had two stitches in his forehead, but there is nothing wrong with the bones
so there is no need to worry
Considering it was a traffic accident, it wasn't serious.
It was good.
Is he painful?
I was given a sedative,
but I guess it's still painful from the wound
You.
He's having trouble with something.
Is he okay?
In the case of an accident, the shock remains, so that's probably why.
what's wrong?
The door is shaking.
Where have you been?
I was talking to my dad.
Take a bath.
My dad said that
He said he'll buy us a new car
Well, I'll go in first
What happened?
there's a power outage
There is a candle, please light it
Thank you.
It's an illusion. Illusion and illusion.
What's wrong?
Is she still alive or am I hallucinating?
There's no other way than to see it with your own eyes
First I need to check the pipe shaft where I throwed her body.
Thank you for your hard work, Mr. Manager
I just came to pick up some documents.
Oh, I see
Are you okay now?
Yes, I'll be going to work from tomorrow.
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work. Mr. Kuramoto from Nippon Trading has just arrived
He came here to pick up a document.
OK.
there's no one else left
Thank you for your hard work
Are you going home?
Good night.
Her body isn't here....
It seems she has come back to life after all
Good morning
Good morning, I forgot something to tell you.
When the manager was on leave,
Nishino Etsuko called me
When was that?
It was there last Saturday,
I asked her where she was but she just hung up without saying anything.
But now it's clear that
she's alive
Good morning
Someone act like that.
I'm absolutely certain that Nishino Etsuko is dead
Who do it?
Yes,
the president is calling you.
Okay,
power outage?
Etsuko?
You!
You killed my sister, right?
THE END