Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Katei no Jijo / A Family Matter (1962)
I wish I had 500,000 yen
I have 50,000 yen in my bank account.
50,000 yen... that's 1/10.
Do you have it?
No.
Not at all?
Just little bit, 10,000 yen? But if this is the case,
Just 10000yen?
we might not be able to get married for a while
For the time being?
Maybe a year from now?
It may be two years
or maybe never
I don't like that.
I've been saying that for a while.
My older brother who paid for my college education like a parent
Now he's  trying to issue a dishonored bill.
Is the problem different?
It's the same
My brother's family is in such a difficult situation
I'm not going to get married with a cool face
Can I say that?
Please use my 50000yen for him.
Thank you.
But He needs 500,000 yen
It'll help a little, right?
It's like a drop in the bucket .
And I don't want to cause you any trouble
Don't worry.
Ah, I've come to your neighborhood. Let's say goodbye
I'll bring it to you tomorrow
I feel sorry.
You don't like me?
No way.
Really?
Really.
Fumi is late.
Oh, maybe she is working overtime?
or maybe she is at bar with a guy now.
You shouldn't talk it carelessly.
It's not lie.
I saw the scene properly.
What's he like?
Well, I guess I could say he's handsome
But he's not really to my taste
What's he like?
What should I say?
You know,like Ginnan.
Ginshio?
No...
Gin-nagashi?
Yes,that's it.
What's that?
You know the old words.
It was nice bath.
I washed all my body.
Oh...
I was charged 500 yen.
This wine is the finest from France,
so I'll have to split the cost
Yes..
You don't have to pay.
You are a customer.
Welcome back, Fumiko.
She's late.
I'm home.
What were you doing
You're fined
I’m sorry.
Happy birthday to you
Blow out the candles.
One breath.
Dad? Are you alright?
I'm alright.
Turn it on.
let's have a toast.
Thank you for all your hard work, Dad
Thanks.
This is delicious.
Let's eat
It's ironic that the day of my retirement is my birthday.
But they all became good girls
Seven years ago I was at a loss as to what to do when your mother died,
But they all grew really well
I have retired, but luckily my next job has been decided
I'll work at a real estate company.
He says the monthly salary is 30,000 yen, so it's not bad.
That's fine
By the way, I received 1.5 million yen after tax as a severance pay.
Oh, 1.5 million yen!
Of this,I have 1 million yen in deposits, for a total of 2.5 million yen
Oh yeah.
Yes, this is it
Hey everyone, come here.
Wow, there aren't many 1 million yen.
What are you talking about? It's 98 times your salary
You do a lot of calculations.
I work at accounting department.
You're probably about 90 times
The problem is how to use the 2.5 million yen
The easiest thing to do is to deposit it in a bank or put it in a loan trust
I think that's a good idea, but I have another idea
The 2.5 million yen will be divided equally among the five people, including me.
with 500,000 yen each.
I agree.
I'm against it.
Oh, why
This the money our dad got.
What belongs to the father belongs to the daughter, right?
I don't think so.
What do you think, sister?
…Well,
wait a minute
The reason I thought of this is that this 2.5 million
yen will end up being used to help everyone get married
So I fear it will be unfair.
If We spend too much on the first thing, We won't have enough for the next thing
I hate the idea.
Me either.
I am the youngest so I will definitely have disadvantage.
So we're all going to share it
Kazuyo, give everyone 500,000 yen
But...
it's okay
everyone is already grown up
You can take responsibility for yourself, right?
I'm not needed.
Miyako, don't say that
You're the only one in the house who don't work.
You have to leave this house someday and get married
If you don't treat me equally, I will be in trouble
OK I will take it.
Well, how you use this money is up to you,
but I want to make sure that I've just given you all your marriage money
Therefore, I would like to be released from my
financial obligations as a father as of today
Are you relieved of the pressure?
However, I'm happy to give advice on mental health.
of course, you are our father after all.
Future living expenses...
As before, you will have to pay 20% of your monthly salary. I will pay 10,000 yen
That should be ok.
Your income has decreased, so it's okay if it's less
Yes,
I'll give it because I don't have to save money for everyone anymore
By the way, one last thing.
I also want a little freedom
What's the hell?
Are you gonna for walking?
I woke up at 6:30 like usual.
Well...Miwako, listen to the dream I had on the night I retired
This is a dream from 30 years ago when I was a new employee
I made a mistake with calculation and the boss really scold me.
You couldn't forget it because you were bad about Math.
Plus, the chief passed away 10 years ago
Even though I thought I had forgotten, I couldn't forget
Is that so?
Welcome.
Good morning
Is your father there?
Yes.
Yoshie-san's aunt is here.
Good morning.
Well, it's pretty clean and the flowers are in good shape
I'm sure Miyako-san, 'll make a great wife
Oh, are you eating now? Excuse me
From today , I am in
a comfortable position.
That's right
My husband is jealous of you.
But now that time has come,
it feels like my life's work is over
and I miss my work.
Retirement means basically a declaration that
from today on you are an old man.
Don't say that, your new second life is just beginning
Actually, yes, I'm talking about a matchmaking.
As you know, I have four girls,
but they are all single.
If you have any good men..
Please introduce us in a raw.
You are all really lovely ladies.
They are picky.
I was raising a child on my own.
it must have been difficult
By the way, about the marriage proposal?
There is a nice woman for you.
For me?
Is it okay to take this?
I feel sorry.
Never mind.
It's natural for me to devote myself to you,
I really appreciate your feelings.
so please use them
Really? Sorry. I'm heading home now
You can check out what's inside
I don't need to look it up.
I'm sure there is 50000yen.
But just to be safe
500000yen.
What on earth is this?
I really want you to use it
...Oh, I'm going to call my brother
I have to make him happy
Excuse me
Are you alone?
No.
With a guy.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Oh you are here.
There's no table.
Come on,please wait.
Go there.
Thanks.
Excuse me
I'll clean it up right away.
You came after all.
You retired yesterday, didn't you?
I thought you wouldn't come again
I was worry about you.
I'm glad.
Hey, do you want to eat somewhere with me tonight?
I was thinking of eating here.
It's boring here.
Thanks
Let's go somewhere together
We+ll be alone?
You hate it?
I don't mind if we're alone,
please just have one of my feelings
I will tell the boss that my brother was sick,
Let's decide the time to meet.
Excuse me
Yes
your companion will be arriving shortly.
but would you like to take a bath?
Ok.. Yes.
that's right. Let's take a bath
The bath is here
Then, here is the toilet
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
I want to join in too
You can't.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't be shy.
I wanna have a bath.
Hey, come on.
give me a break.
Why?
I've never taken a bath with died my ex wife either.
If I go in with a woman, it'll hurt my heart
Oh really? Too bad. Well, it's fine if I just want to wash your back.
Let me do it.
You're pure.
I like you
Thanks.
You love me?
Of course
How much?
A lot.
Can you show me the evidence later?
Okay, I'll show you
Then, say I'm a man.
I'm a man.
That's great. I'm happy.
Have a beer.
what's wrong? Are you cold?
No.
Have a beer.
Thank you too
Please.
Thank you for your hard work
You know what?, when I get drunk,will you treat me?
I will.
I'm so happy.
Cheers.
Instead,
When you get drunk, I'll treat you too.
I'm excited.
Have a beer.
I'm a man.
If this happens, I'll never let you go
No matter who comes, I'll never let you go
When we're married and time has passed, this night will be a fond memory
I'll be good wife.
I'm counting on you.
We can definitely get married?
My brother won't allow us to break up even if I become hate you.
I wanna see your brother.
Sure.
I want to get married as soon as possible
I want to do it as soon as possible too.
Let's make our memories.
We're getting married.
May I?
What's wrong?
Thank you.
Do you know him?
No.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Let's go home tonight.
Why.
I have to go home.
Wait a moment
What just happened.
It's too late if it became bad reputation at the company,
so if you decide to quit, I'll find you a good company to work for
You're selfish.
That's for your sake and for mine too
See you.
Hey.
I hope you'll stay here for the night
I'm sorry.
Instead, I will put it into action as soon as possible about Atami.
Promise me.
I'm a man too
I'm so happy, You know what..
I never dreamed you'd have such a reliable person
Not so much,
You're play boy.
You've been seducing women until now.
No, that's not true.
Being widowed by my wife..
I'll be your only woman from now.
Yeah.
If you don't understand, I'll kill myself!
Don't scare me
Bros.
What's wrong?
The lady here's been asking me for a
while now if I should open a small restaurant
That kind of money is difficult, isn't it?
Yeah.
but if I had 1.5 million yen, I couldn't afford it
- Whew, that's about it
So, this lady said to me, why don't you borrow 1.5 million yen from you?
Me?
But I told her that no matter how much it was,
I couldn't be so bold as to ask for it
But I don't rely on anyone else.
Of course, since I'm borrowing it, I'll pay the interest
I wonder if 5 percent a month would be okay?
But it's 6 percent for a fixed deposit.
I think if I had two years I could get the money back to you.
I'm confident that I won't cause any trouble to you.
Say I'm a man.
Unfortunately, I don't have that much money.
You have a retirement bonus of 1.5 million yen
No, I gave them all to my daughters
Is that a lie?
it's true
- You can take it back under paternal rights
I can't do that.
Oh yeah.
that's the kind of person you are.
You don't seem to care about me at all.
I'm thinking about you
Never mind.
Tama-chan.
Hey.
Please excuse me
Hey, what's up with Tamako? It's my friend.
Can I have the bill?
Bill?
Please pay it
I'll pay it.
How much is it?
23,000 yen
How much?
It's 23,000 yen
Dad
where have you been?
Isn't today your day off?
I have some business to take care of in Shinjuku, for The bank and other places.
You're late.
I had to work overtime.
You've been working a lot of overtime lately
Yes.
Oh, it's Kazuyo there.
Sis.
We took same train.
You're late.
I had to work overtime.
It's been a while since you worked overtime.
I'm busy these days.
Recently, there is a strange woman around our dad?
I don't know where is she from
Dad immediately refused it.
but there's no need to refuse
It's nice to see flowers bloom on dead trees
Dead trees are terrible.
He was like "I want to be free".
Dad want a wife?
He's back.
I'm back! -
Welcome back.
Oh, that's what I though.
It's mine.
I found you there. you owe me.
You can buy some for yourself.
You have 500,000 yen
I want to eat ochazuke.
Yes, me too
This milk is expensive, so please don't use too much
You're stingy.
Wanna have meal.
I don't want.
What's wrong?
Is it okay.
I'm just a little tired
Sis.
Our father received a marriage proposal
Oh really?
That's good.
that's not good, isn't it? There were some nosy people out there
You guys have to get married before me.
Where is she from?
Apparently  Mrs. Yoshii's accentance.
Apparently she's unmarried and has one son in the third grade of elementary school
So she's taking the kid?
No.
I'm not getting married.
Because everyone else is going to get married anyway,
Then dad will be lonely.
You'd better married her.
I don't know about you but I won't get married soon
Well, that's fine
Anyway, what happened to the 500,000 yen?
How about you?
I deposited it in the bank today.
I saved up some money too.
How about you?
Same here.
It's really Ochazuke
Thanks.
What happened to Shina-chan?
I started a part-time job.
lending at high interest business.
lending at high interest?
It's our habit to always become a poor before payday
Sometimes it's hard to live. It's really helpful to have someone to borrow money easily.
That's right, that's helping people.
There is no irrecoverable debt. All we have to do is work hard at the accounting counter.
How about 1% a day?
365% per year.
OK.
But I wonder if the section chief will get angry
I won't get in trouble. Even the chief will come and borrow it
You have to boldly announces that you will open a money lending business to earn your wedding funds.
I think I'll give it a try
gave me 3000 yen, 4000 yen, and 2000 yen
1000 yen fro me.
I lent them a total of 10,000 yen
That 10,000 yen is unavoidable,
but please stop doing that in the future
Why?
spending money like that make you a vulgar person.
What's the hell?
You know, it's not the same as investing in mutual funds or stocks
It's easy work.
You doesn't need to do such things to make money
Did not you distribute them with respect to us?
it's better to listen to the advice as it is
I don't know.
I don't do it to make money,
I do it for human research
People reveal their true colors in front of money.
And then you write a paper?
I won't write a paper,
but maybe I'll find a good husband.
That doesn't mean it's masculine
Whatever.
Hi.
Good morning.
Did you see her?
OK.
She looks young.
She's actually pretty good
She still have a lot of energy.
Good morning.
good morning
Is there anything I can help you with today?
Oh no.
Good morning.
What is this?
I heard it's for preventing arteriosclerosis.
Is the working well?
I have no idea.
Hey Mitsuzawa-san?
how's your blood pressure?
The upper number is nothing serious,
but the lower number is 98
If the lower number is higher, it's dangerous.
I see.
Oh yeah.
Hello, hello, Kyowa Shoji,
please wait a moment
Managing Director: Oh,
it's from Misawa-san.
Mitsuzawa? Ah, it's Mitsuzawa-san who has retired
Hello, it's me. Mitsuzawa
I'm working here starting today
I put on a ridiculous comedy this morning.
Suddenly I realized I was standing in front of the elevator over there
Thirty years of habits are scary
So?
So, actually, I have something to talk to you about.
It's about my daughter
Would you like to have lunch with me?
Yes, thank you
At 12:30
Thank you, I'll be waiting
This Endo is a friend of mine from long ago
I joined the company as a female employee, but he is an executive and I am retiring.
I think that both the eldest and second daughters
will find suitable partners and get married
the youngest child's Shinako will be ok.
She's very mature.
But I have to do something about the third sister,Miyako.
She's a very modest girl who doesn't go to work and just runs the house all the time
I'll let Yoshiyuki planning to go to France
When?
In 4,5 days.
So please forget about marriage with Miyako.
Apparently Yoshiyuki felt sorry for Miyako
and was thinking about marrying her
That would be a problem for me
Being friends is being friends
I want to think of my relationships beside friendship as something different.
what?
Take a look at it.
I would like to resign this company.
Are you quitting?
Yes.
Why?
You want me to quit, don't you?
Hold on.
Hey, do you have
other plans?
No,
I'll be responsible for you
for the rest of my life
so please marry me
I have a wife.
I too am scared of this kind of life and I can't stand it, so I'm saying goodbye today
You are still adult.
You told me that you would get married  with me someday.
What are you talking about?
No...
Let's meet at the hotel tonight'.
No.
What?, I can't accept this.
Get the invoice together.
but it's better if you break up.
I wondered why you stuck with him.
When I was heartbroken,
He said something so kind to me that I couldn't resist
I'll forget about her.
Come on, have a drink and put on some cake
I can't drink.
Alcohol is just like water so let's have a toast
For your second life.
What are you doing next?
I wanna do something with 1 million yen.
The chief gave you that money for breaking up?
No.
He didn't pay me anything.
I even paid for the hotel
My father was given 500,000
yen each when he retired.
He's a good dad
And I have 150,000 in savings
I'll get about 150,000
yen in retirement benefits,
so that'll be 800,000 yen
Plus I can borrow another 100,000 yen from my sister
My youngest sis started a loan sharking business.
Wanna be madam at cafe?
There's a place in this neighborhood that sells drinks for 700,000 yen
Apparently she's planning to leave and get married soon
I wonder if I can work at a coffee shop.
Yes, it's possible, you're beautiful
Hurry up and go now
you still have the qualifications.
Behind that movie theater
Here.
Welcome here.
Let me introduce you
She's classmate Mizusawa Kazuyo
Nice to meet you.
I came here about the store,
Please come in and sit there.
I talked her about this cafe.
two coffees.
Actually, I was able to start this business with the little bit of money my husband left me and the insurance money
it's going well.
but I didn't intend to continue it forever
and I was planning to remarry if I found a good partner
I was just doing it to bridge the gap until then
When my husband passed away, he told me to definitely remarry
I don't like being independent either
I like rely on someone
like this.
Are you sure?
However, I recently heard a wonderful offer about someone I was taking care of.
Excuse me.
Here it is.
Are you Mitsusawa-san or something?
I'm Mitsusawa Kazuyo.
Where do you live?
Kichijoji
What is the name of that father?
Heitaro
Heitaro Oh, really?
I see.
Is that so?
You are Misawa-san. I understand. I will own you this shop to a cheaper one
Hey! Mizusawa-kun!
Mizusawa-san
Is that really impossible?
100,000 yen is outrageous
Don't underestimate me.
Whether good or bad, it's
about helping people.
Anyway, let's have some tea!
Masasuke Imagami and Kiyoko Nozawa can get married with just 100,000 yen
it really cost 100,000 yen for the apartment
deposit and the minimum wedding expenses
They don't have to get married.
Even if you say that
It's been two years since thy started dating
It's none of my business.
I hate the calm manner.
This is the way I do business.
I'll be their guarantor, so why not?
You're the guarantor, so I can't trust you
Now I can bear the insults no matter what people say
The two of them are married and work together, Monthly income will be 30,000 yen
From that amount, they pay back 5,000 yen every month
With the bonus, they can probably get back 20,000 yen
With just your feelings, a happy couple can be born into this world
Your money is also important,
so how much money can you
making by getting in between them ?
Am I making money? That's rude
You know I'm not bad guy.
Because you are too enthusiastic
That's because we're friends.
Male friendship is a big thing
There is a saying that if you see someone being kind, you are not kind
They are here now.
We are here.
Hey.
We were supposed to meet here at 4 o'clock
This is Shinako Mizusawa.
This is Shosuke Imazeki, this is Kiyoko Noda.
Have a seat.
Now, Mizusawa-san has kindly agreed
I'm relieved too
Could you please say thank her.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
That's very helpful. Thank you very much
No at all.
now that it's come to this
I'll treat you to dinner tonight.
Okay, okay, let's go out
Let’s talk there.
Thank you very much.
I'll take 230 yen. Please wait a moment
Mitsuzawa.
What?
Sorry, I need about 2000 yen
What do you mean?
I only have 100 yen.
I'll write the written acknowledgment of debt tomorrow
Thank you very much.
I want to meet your bros.
Yes, eventually
eventually?
Please meet my dad.
I hear your sisters got 500,000 yen each, right?
Yes,
I wonder if one of them
could lend me 500,000 yen
What's wrong?
I just lent you 500,000 yen
The cashier at my brother's store took it and ran away all.
I will have my brother write an IOU and pay you interest.
I can't tell everyone that
It's impossible, absolutely impossible,
that's probably true
That would be impossible
Are you upset?
What should we do?
If this is the case,
we'll just get married without anyone to stop us
Or do you not love me that much?
Well then, that's okay?
Good evening
Who are you?
It's none of my business.
You're rude.
You've been following us.
Oh no, I was just taking a walk,
now go home
I've seen your last moments,
so I know it's none of your business.
Get out!
Don't hit me.
Hey.
Are you alright?
You're evil.
Sorry.
Did it hurt?
Are you in love with her?
No matter how much you fall in love with her,it's pointless.
Is that so?
Let's go home, Remember,
oh, I'll remember It's a pleasant memory
Well then, take care of yourself. Oh, it's nothing
They are late
I made sweet red bean soup.
I'm grateful
I can't make it as well as my mother,
but it's all good
Next month is the 7th anniversary of my mother's death
Yes.
So you're going to hold the memorial service in Kyoto?
I'm sorry for making you play the role of a mother for so long,
but I like being at home.
It tastes good.
Well, I'm glad.
You see, I met Endo-kun today
I heard Yoshiki is going to France.
I know. It's fine
I don't have anything anymore
Really?
I'm sure it's not a big deal, but it would be nice if you said that
I don't care
This is the second time I've beaten you
Don't lose confidence, it's not your fault
When Inaba-kun got engaged to you
I thought you were the first to be happy in this house
However, Inaba-kun unilaterally rejected  marriage the day before the wedding.He's bad
At that time, Endo's son became
close to you and sympathized with you,
It made me very happy
Endo and I are colleagues who joined the company on the same day
One of them will be the senior managing director and I will retire as a section chief
However, as a person I don't think I was inferior to Endo
I thought I had walked my own path straight and proudly
Yes.
However, Endo doesn't like my existence
I didn't want to marry my daughter,
who is an ordinary retired man, to their son.
Dad, let's not talking about him.
I don't want to be excited because my blood pressure goes up when I get excited
Welcome
Hello,
I've been waiting for you. Come in
Excuse me.
This is 3rd sis,Miyako.
I'm Yasuko Aizawa.
Nice to meet you.
Hold on.
Come with me.
Where's Fumi?
She's washing.
Call her.
Why were you here?
I listened to Mood music,I like the atmosphere.
She's here.
What kind of person is she?
She has bright personality
Ah, I guess we need to buy a new washing machine after all
It's a step backwards from civilization.
Nice to meet you, I'm the youngest, Shinako.
I'm Yasuko Aizawa.
It's a nice Sunday
I was supposed to go to Enoshima and see the whales today,
but I got stuck there
Because
There's an aunt here, right?
Don't call like that.
It's ok.
I'm not a young lady anymore, so I'm sorry for the whale.
Don't worry.
You're too young to have big kids
It seems too good for daddy.
Oh my, maybe it's me who is the wasteful for him.
Have a tea.
Do you like jazz?
I love it
I played the violin when I was young
Really?
You were cool.
I bought  MJC's new record, but will you listen?
Don't say that.
Please call me, Dad.
Okay
Ah, what do I have to call him?
we had a meeting last night, right?
Ah, okay
Are you working?
I can't write well
What?
I was asked to write for the in-house magazine at
my previous company, even though I was retiring
Well, let's see.
When I looked at people who retired in my youth,
I used to think they were an old man who reached the end of life
but now that I'm in that position,
I don't think it's that bad at all
I like this phrases.
My son's mother said that I might get married
Then he told me what will happen to me
Well, of course I'll take you with me
He thinks it's better to have a dad too
She's Fumiko, the second one
Welcome, nice to meet you
I think you have good sweater.
It's better to wash this my hand.
It's good exercise too.
it helps to keep you in good condition
The motor in my washing machine went out,
so we had to choose between buying a new one or throw it out.
After a month of deliberation, we decided to throw it out.
Come on.
Dad's here
She's My friend, Yasuko Aizawa
Welcome.
Hello, I'm Yasuko Aizawa. I'm sorry to bother you
Today is Sunday so she came to play
She helps me a lot.
Thank you
Please, please
Want a cigarette?
Thank you very much
This area is really quiet and nice
Sometime raccoon appeared.
Five or six years ago.
You talk so big.
Is that bad?
Yes, there are. It seems that there may still
be remnants of the Musashino Tanuki around here
I have heard such a story too
That's right, even
raccoons have a desire to survive
I will resist civilization.
Wanna eat apple or
persimmon?
Take both.
Umi-chan and Nishina-chan
How are you guys trying to attract attention?
It can't be helped.
You are not good to do a play.
Sorry
She looks nice.
She's not thick.
She is magnificent.
She's not arrogant at all.
what do you think?
I think I could like her.
Oh, um, would you like one more cigarette?
That's fine
Is that so?
Well...
Thanks.
I feel like my life just passing by
It's not over yet, is it?
It's over.
It's just the beginning
People say that as a compliment.
Apparently the age of death for men has now been extended to 70,
so is that right?
Yes.
I'd met you before.
Oh I remember
What?
He's embarrassed so
He's pretending to be upset.
Don't you think she'd be suit for father?
But she's got a kid.
It might be fun to have another little brother
What about you, Miya?
I just want to make my dad happy
Affairs Department
Hello, hello, this is Affairs Department
Ishibe?
I'm Mitsuzawa.
I'm sorry for the other day.
There's something I want to talk to you about
Please come to the rooftop during lunch time
Wanna have a lunch together?
You're annoying.
I would like to enjoy having meal with you.
How about some eel?
First, 200 yen, 250 yen, plum, 300 yen
There's no need to force yourself.
Let's wait for the next one
What do you mean?
I've been hoping to have more
opportunities like this with you from now on
I'm sorry,
I thought you'd say that.
Why did you do that?
Because I like you.
Wait a moment
I love you and I want to marry you
I refuse it.
Why?
What do you mean why?
I have someone special
That guy is a loser. He works for Sumida Industries, one of our clients
You know very much.
I know his authorities.
Sorry, he has bad reputation.
Excuse me. this is a human rights
issue
Thank you for waiting
let's eat eel
What's so good about a guy like that?
He's kind and caring
and not at all creepy like you.
Please leave me alone.
I can't leave you alone
Those who love have the right and the duty to protect the object of their love
it's a matter of rights and responsibilities?
but I know it's a tough one for men
but I'm already engaged
But you're not married yet
I think I followed you that night and stole you.
You probably don't think
I go to places like that all the time?
I'm relieved to see you're still inexperienced,
so you're still a virgin
However, you seemed quite psychologically unstable
From now on, don't fall for that guy's words
It's none of your business.
No you can't. for your happiness and for my happiness too
Well then, let me tell you
how much I fuss over your hairy heart
You don't want to hear it
No, I'll tell you
If you beg so much, I'll listen
I received 500,000 yen from my father and lent it to that person
Why?
Because I love him.
You see?
You're stupid, you're such a fool
Have you finished?
What happened? I haven't finished yet.
Thank you for your hard work
Yes, hello
For you.
Hello, this is Mitsusawa
Aizawa-san?
Which Aizawa-san are you talking about?
Oh, you forgot?
Oh my god. Where did we meet?
I'm Aizawa who visited you last Sunday.
I'm sorry
Did you remember me?
Thank you very much.
Could you please spare me about an hour tonight?
But what do you want?
I'll save that for when we meet so I won't tell you about it now
Please come to the cafe called "Akai Tobira" in Shibuya at 8:30
This is the cafe that opened today
It's a red door
Please
I wonder if my dad will be angry if I
start a cafe like this without telling him
Why?
Because it started with your own ability, so don't worry.
but I've been very grateful to you
Same here.
Welcome.
You finally opened.
You're the first customer.
Thanks for doing the renovations so inexpensively.
Not at all.
We're lucky that, There's an interior designer on the second floor
The trouble with this person is
He order curry rice at a coffee shop
Are you still eating curry rice?
Yes please.
That's good.
Thanks.
You should hurry up to get married.
I think I'll find a good man soon.
Yes?
my daughters are encouraging me to remarry
That would be nice
but the woman is strangely unresponsive.
I wonder who she is.
She's too open.
I think that's pretty good.
How can you understand if you don't even see her?
No, we are always responding to requests
I just wanted to say something about the world
Do you have a girlfriend?
No, I'm enjoying my freedom.
I have a daughter after all
Would you like to come
and hang out for a bit?
I pretty much understand what you mean
Don’t they all already have a lover?
Hello, please wait a moment
Again, from a woman
Again?
You're popular among women.
Hey, hey, you shouldn't make fun of old people
Hello, this is Mitsusawa
Yes, Mi-san, I'm Tamako
I'm sorry for the other day.
Are you upset?
But I still like you the best.
I want you.
What can I do for you?
I wanna meet you.
Please come over tonight, even if it's just for a little while, I'll give you a special service
OK?
I'm happy.
See you, oh yeah, the store has changed
Shibuya Shibuya Touhou Fugetsu
Eh, not Daiei?
Oh, I get it,
there are too many movie theaters
Seriously, let's go out together tonight.
Sake or anything?
Both.
That's fine.
He's there?
Welcome.
Mi-san, it's been a while. I missed you
Hey, stop talking like this. It's Tatsuta from work
Pleased to meet you. I was lonely
Well, you know, I'll have some alcohol and food
Yes, take it easy tonight
How's her?
Wow, she really loves you.
But you have to be careful with your wallet
Do you understand why I don't want to remarry?
Huh? Yes,
I don't want to remarry and have my wife be jealous.
and I don't wanna waste time I have left of my life
So I don't get re-married.
But isn't it okay because there is no freedom in life?
You're young but you have no sense, do you?
Open the door.
Please excuse me
Your section chief is really kind,
he's not the section chief anymore.
You're so kind to other women too?
Don't say that.
He all knows about me well.
Have a sake.
No,
Tatsuta is guest tonight, so please go ahead
Oh yeah, have a sake first.
Well then, please feel free to have some.
Hey, let me have some too.
Thank you so much.
You know what?
What's wrong?
Do you know why I called you today?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You're mean.
Stop it....
I saw a dream about you.
This was a very embarrassing dream.
What kind of dream was it?
Guess that.
When I woke up, I missed you so much and loved
you so much.
I called Mi-san today, prepared to be scolded
Then you don't get angry at all
This is how you came here
I won't leave you from me anymore.
I’m sorry.
What's the matter?
I want to go to the bathroom
It's okay if you go.
In the meantime, I want you to get as many important things done as possible
Please.
Where's is the bathroom?
In the back of the hallway.
Mi-san.
What?
I can't really tell you
I'm embarrassed.
What happened?
I'll talk to you later.
We'll go home then. I agree
It's the perfect time for the Akai tobira cafe.
Bill please.
How much?
5,300 yen.
It's too expensive.
Take your change.
Thank you.
Please come again.
What happened?
Tonight I finally understood the true identity of that woman
I must have looked pretty stupid, right?
That's no good
Is it true that it was a farce to discover the woman's true identity?
Really?
You looked so enjoyable.
I wanted to find out the truth,
Were you able to find out?
That's right,
that woman was trying to get me to pay 100,000 yen
She has to do something with your wallet after all.
Apparently I look like a real amateur
I'm sure everyone can see you as nice man
Don't make fun of me.
Here?
Yes.
I see, it's a red door.
Welcome
We've been waiting for you. Please come in
Dad, you are late.
Let him sit there.
What's wrong?
Everyone, today is the opening celebration.
Here's Kazuya's cafe.
Kazuyo's?
Dad, please hurry up.
He's Ryukichi Takita who work together
Nice to meet you.
Please have a seat.
Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Sugimoto, who owns a decoration company here
He helped me this time.
I am Sugimoto
I am Mitsusawa .
So, what happened to the company?
I quit.
I didn't ask you
What happened to this store?
Um, I gave my store away to her.
Your store?
My classmate used to run a bar nearby
And the place I was introduced to was Mr. Aizawa's shop
You quit your job and
started a business like this.
That's great business.
Shut up.
Why did you quit your job?
I think it's good to be independent
You are still a stranger,
so don't be so casual about barging into my home
Dad, she started the business with that 500,000 yen, so isn't that okay?
That 500,000?
Yes
I shouldn't have shared that money
You are not being realistic.
it doesn't matter if I'm not being realistic or not.
Anyway, tonight is a happy night, so let's have a toast.
Let's do it.
I don't have a cup
Sorry, Bring a cup for him.
Tatsuta.
You're going to betray me?
But that's not what I mean
I'm sorry.
I think I can drink better here than the restaurant we just went before.
Oh,Were you drinking somewhere?
No..
We just had some coffee.
Yes.
but that coffee was no good
It's expensive and very bitter.
You should have come here.
The coffee is also very delicious, isn't it? Let's have a toast
Yes, let's have a toast. Congratulations
Thank you
Welcome.
Sorry we are closed.
but it seems that it's opening today.
Good evening.
Sorry, we've closed the shop for the night.
but you have a lot of customers there.
They're very special people
I guess I deserve some special treatment too
I refuse. Please go home.
Don't say things like that
I want to drink beer too
Hey you.
If you want to drink beer,
there are standing bars around here
Mind your own business.
You are an unnecessary customer
Do you know what kind of guy I am?
No, not at all
I was the manager of the company where she worked.
Really? Then you must want to become a manager soon.
Okay, let me say.
With her...
If you continue talking, I will charge you.
it will affect to her.
Hey you.
That's enough now, go home
What's the matter?
nothing.
That woman and I are...
What's the hell?
Hold on.
I think you know the reason I left the company.
Congratulations Iwasaki-kun and congratulations Kiyoko-san
Everyone has already congratulated them.
I have nothing more to say
I'm just jealous, he's a lucky guy
I'll end this by confessing that I want to get married as soon as possible
Next, I would like to ask Shinako Mitsusawa to speech.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
Do it.
No problem, you're the sponsor
We need to speech.
Excuse me.
Before Ms. Misawa, I would like to say a few words
To be honest, the hardest part about
getting married was finding an apartment
I was renting the second floor of my brother's house
This Noda guy is a little strange
Kiyoko..
Don't push yourself too hard.
She's being looked after by her uncle
To rent an apartment, a deposit of 100,000 yen was required
In other words, Nobuko Misawa lent us the 100,000 yen
we needed it for our wedding
The 100,000 yen was something she had received
from her father's retirement pension as a wedding fund
We intend to pay the money back within a year
Please Mitsuzawa-san, please don't get married within a year
That's terrible! No, no,
no, no! I'm not saying never
I ask you to take responsibility for borrowing money for your wedding funds.
According to Hirose-kun, the two of you plan to get married someday
If possible, I would like you to marry after a year
Hold on.
So, thank you so much for being so happy with my little bit of help
I think I did a really good thing
But the thing about Hirose-san was a real surprise to me
I will now revoke it again here
He drinks a lot and is the best in the world at making me snort
As for my opponent, He's a complete failure.
Chairman, please make an emergency motion.
I would like to give special
permission to speak.
Thank you
I would like to sue her for defamation regarding her statement just now
In fact, she was so embarrassed
So She insulted to me.
and will not pursue a lawsuit
What's the hell?
We too will have a happy marriage like Imazeki-kun
Please look forward to it.
You shamed on me.
Can I not be angry about this too?
You're trying to tear me apart?
You're the one who tore me apart
I feel like killing myself I was about to kill myself
Suicide?
You were exaggerating a lot.
Let's have a meal.
I'll treat you.
What's the hell?
You're borrowing money from me anyway,
It's ok because 10% daily interest.
I will write an IOU tomorrow.
I can't.
but if you lend it to me, you'll make money
I get it.
You're borrowing money from me,
and deceiving me, marrying me, and plotting to default on your debt in the name of marriage
Don't say such pathetic things
Do I look like that bad man?
If I have suck an idea, I'll be much more successful.
Anyway, I'm going to quit being a moneylender
You quit?
I'm in trouble.
If you want to improve your score even a little, never borrow money from me.
What's the hell?
What a shame for you to be so considerate
It's proof that your heart is turning to me.
What's wrong?
Hello!
Oh, it's you!
You seem to be waiting for someone?
You must be waiting for Nagata-kun.
Could you please go to another table?
I get suffocated when I'm face to face with you
Ah, I'll leave as soon as Nagata arrives, so that's fine
Ah, I'll get some coffee, bring it over there.
There's something I want to talk to you about regarding Nagata
I don't want to hear any insults
You haven't seen him lately,right?
He's busy for a reason.
He's getting married at the end of the month.
He's getting married?
That's exactly.
with me for sure.
But it's not true
He's going to get married with Fumiko Kimitsu, the daughter of the president of a financial trading company.
You're lying.
I did my research and he quit his current company and became the managing director of a financial trading company.
It's a win-win situation because it helps my brother get promoted at his company and also helps me get promoted.
It's a lie
Who believe that?
Why you don't believe me?
I didn't run around and investigated for you. See you later
Did you wait long?
more than 40 minutes.
I’m sorry.
I'm busy at work day time and take care of my bros at night.
No matter how many times I call, you aren’t at home
Let's go out.
Thank you
Hold on.
Let's go in　for a bit
That's bad.
Why is that?
I mean,we're not married yet, right?
You forced on me the other day
No, I regretted it a lot later
I'll confess like a man
Is there a reason you don't want to invite me to a hotel anymore?
I invited you tonight just to try it out.
Well, Let's go
I think I heard it all from Ishibe-kun
I'm getting married with a woman at the end of this month
What about our promise?
Hmm? Well, it's like it never happened.
You say that very frankly
No,you know
If you love me, you'll understand, right? For my sake,
Don't you think about my happiness?
the 500,000 yen I borrowed from you..
Well, I'll give it back if that happens.
I'll just throw that stuff away
Oh my god.
I'll pay you back the money I borrowed,
whether you throw it away or not
Because if I keep borrowing money for no reason, I will be hindering my career advancement.
You're an egoistic monster.
Everyone is egoistic
Everyone thinks they're cute
This time, too, is a once in a lifetime opportunity for me
I have to take that chance
Is it your chance to marry the president's daughter
and become a senior managing director?
Of course.
because as a salary man, you advance up the ladder
Just try acting like a normal person
I'll ride the train all my life and punch a time card, and that's how I'll grow old
Isn't your father a good example?
He's a great man
Don't look down on him.
Excuse me
Anyway, I'll give you your money back
Instead, One year installment payment please.
I will pay the interest rate be 10%.
Well, I'll send it to you every month
Hey
Mitsuzawa?
It's raining.
Let's go
You're going to catch a cold.
You were just watching us?
Yes
Did I looked pretty stupid?
Kind of.
You can despise me.
I won't.
Let's go.
Ishibe.
I know that, I know that,
Stop crying.
It seems that I ended up to win.
Come on! Strike! Good ball!
When did you come?
Just right now.
He's only my son.
I know
Oh, why?
I just felt so.
Let me play with him.
Kazuo-chan, He's Tatsuta-san's uncle
Hello.
Come on.
Mitsuda-san and Mikako-san came to Kyoto for the her mother's 7th death memory.
See, you've known it many times
I know that one day you will be the housewife here
But I still don't know
Well, the system has already been decided
So you're just staying around like this,
You're a reliable young man, I'm counting on you to support me
Come on, I'm gonna hit it
Both Fumiko and Shinako will be bringing their friends along
I know we're planning to have a drinking party in the evening
I wanna join you.
Come on.
That's not the way to swing a bat,
I'll hit like Nagashima.
Whoa.
who's that?
You can't play baseball in a place like that.
Shit.
Mom.
Hey, our mom grave is around there.
The valley is Mt. Toribe
Dad, if you ask that person to come to our house?
that person?
She's a nice person
I feel bad for my died wife.
It feels like we're close now, and I'm sure that will be a joy for your mother too
But...
Dad needs to stabilize his behavior
Everyone can't go to their wedding in peace, right?
If I get married, will you get married too?
Yes, I will
If I find someone nice.
how about Tatsuta-kun? Eh?
I think he is a good young man
I wonder if I'll be rejected again.
Not at all
Because Tatsuta said so
I'll leave it to your father
Well then, I guess I should make a decision too.
You can take your time, right? Huh?
Well, yeah
I feel sorry for an old lady like me,
I feel so honored
I think you and Miyoko are well matched.
Why you push me?
Once everyone's is married, I will naturally be married with someone.
Let's have a toast.
For our happiness.
Thank you.
Oh? It must be Kazuo.
Oh, that's right.
Did you forget something?
Yeah.
This.
See you later.
Well...
Sorry I made you surprise.
I love you.
Thanks for waiting.
What do you want to eat?
western food? Japanese food?
I wanna eat a steak.
Okay.
Don't push me.
THE END