Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kaze no shisen / The Hidden Profile (1963)
Natsui,The teacher is surprised.
Why is that?
You don't look like the kind of guy who'd leave his bride at a wedding and come here.
It can't be helped because it's work.
I hear you and the bride are going to meet at Asamushi Onsen.
She's probably there.
No wonder.
Well, Natsui-kun is very popular right now, so his wife will have to put up with him.
We had to shoot with the same photographer for the next series.
Please don't worry about me.
If you want to take pictures, you should go to Mt.13.
Mt. 13 is just beyond Goshogawara?
Is it good place?
There's nothing there.
I'd like to go there.
You're supposed to be on your way to Hokkaido with your bride.
You don't have to go to Mt.13.
But if I miss it, I'll have to wait a year until next year.
Young people are so short-tempered.
I feel sorry for your bride.
Excuse me.
Yes
Your husband is arrived.
Will you eat first?
I'll take a bath first.
Did you have a meal?
I've been expecting you.
You shouldn't do that.
My work is irregular.
It's easier for me if you don't have to wait for me.
I'll show you to your bath.
You're welcome to join us.
I'll take a bath later.
Have one drink.
Don't worry.
Just for toast.
I'll have a glass of juice.
Anyway, congratulations.
I'll help it.
Have you seen my work?
No, not yet.
I see.
Are you interested in photography?
No, I'm not.
My job is not like a regular working man's.
I don't know what I'd do for a job.
My life is hard enough for the money.
I want to ask you for a favor.
Even if we live together from now on.
I'd like you to stay out of my life.
I'll stay out of your affairs as long as I can.
I understand.
Then we'll reschedule your trip.
We are going to Mt. 13, which is a very lonely place.
I really want to go there now.
If you don't feel up to it, you can wait here.
I'll go with you.
To be honest, I'm not confident that I can make my partner happy through marriage.
That's not true.
I'm sure you would love her.
You can think that once I'm married, I'll settle down.
But that might take a long time.
Or forever.
That's not true.
Don't think about all these things and just get married.
Someone's dead.
Just over there.
Stay away.
Here.
Let's carry him out.
What are you doing?
I'm asking you.
The kids called me, there's a dead body.
I'm a photographer.
She's your wife, isn't she?
You are a troubled people.
This will take some time.
I'm really sorry to have bothered you.
He killed himself.
I see.
If it was a homicide, you guys would have been in trouble.
You're on your honeymoon.
It's cold.
I'm sorry we had to reschedule.
No problem.
I just don't feel like going to Hokkaido anymore.
Anywhere is fine.
Can we stay here?
Unfortunately, we are currently fully booked here.
Let's go another inn.
That's a passenger plane from Tokyo, landing at an airfield in Sendai.
Some passengers use this flight for their return trip.
It lands at Haneda at 7:25.
It seems kind of early to say goodbye like this.
Let's have tea somewhere.
It's better to say goodbye like this.
A simple goodbye would be more appropriate.
Why?
I don't want to ruin the clean air of Sendai with a coffee shop in Tokyo or something.
You're not leaving like this, are you?
I'd like to drink a little sake alone.
I'd rather go home alone.
I'll take the air of Sendai home with me.
If they find out that we met in Sendai and came back together, they'll misunderstand.
My mother is a very nervous person.
But she believes everything I say.
Please don't worry.
I'll be in a hotel for a week from today.
What are you thinking about?
About your husband.?
Thinking about Ryuzaki is pointless.
He's living a carefree life in Singapore.
It's been ages.
I'm on my way home.
See you.
I was in a hurry to get back.
Let's have another drink over there.
You just said good bye.
Then come to my place.
Sorry.
You have to come.
Let's go.
Roppongi
Where are you taking me?
Put on the radio.
A hotel.
Give me a break.
What's the matter?
What?
Don't pretend you don't know.
It's been half a year since I've seen you.
I have work to do.
What are you talking about?
The customers are disappointed when you're not at bar.
Where have you been traveling?
I went near Sendai on business.
If you're near Sendai, you must have been in Matsushima.
Not for work, but with someone,right?
You're drunk.
You’re cold.
Go back to Namiki-dori.
I'll have it.
Excuse me.
Mr. Natsui is here.
Send him into the parlor.
Does he know Shigetaka?
Yes, he's a friend of mine.
You'd better not keep him waiting.
Hello.
When did you get home?
This morning.
You must be tired.
Not really.
Where's your wife?
I left her at home.
I can't wait to meet your wife.
How was your Honeymoon?
Thanks.
How was your trip in Hokkaido?
I changed my schedule and went to Mt. 13 on the edge of Aomori Prefecture and then to Matsushima.
When did you go to Matsushima?
The day before yesterday.
Where did you stay?
At a ryokan called Boryokaku.
I'm sure it was beautiful.
Madam.
I guess my marriage didn't work out.
What are you talking about, just after you came back from your honeymoon.
What happened?
I'm worried that you're in such a bad mood.
You're not responsible.
But I'm the one who recommended to get married.
We seem to have different personalities.
You've only been married for 10 days.
I was wrong.
Does that mean an arranged marriage?
Or does it mean that you did not have a relationship before marriage?
In that case, I would have blamed you.
When my friend was a matchmaker.
You said there was no need for a relationship.
I did.
That's how I felt at the time.
I was going to marry her no matter who she was.
I mean that I shouldn't get married for the time being.
I'm not sure I can love her.
At the same time, I don't think she loves me either.
Even if our feelings are not immediately reciprocated, it is something that will happen in the future.
I don't know how to explain it.
I think she and I both had a kind of resignation about marriage from the beginning.
Chikako is the daughter of a decent family.
She's still nervous.
You should be nice to her.
There's something in her past that's keeping me away from her.
No one is without a past.
I'm going to devote myself to my work.
What happened between her and me is no one's fault.
I just wanted to talk to you.
Chikako is here.
Yes, I understand.
Tea is ready.
You guys just got married, but your wife is always staying at home.
You are not strict.
That's because you're both responsible for each other now that you're married.
He can't do his job if he keeps talking like that.
I'll do it my way.
I'm not gonna change who I am just because I'm married.
I mean, the thought of living with a certain woman for decades scares the shit out of me.
What's the hell?
I mean, if it makes you feel like you're doing your job, that's fine, too.
I guess the game is on at the upcoming exhibition.
Let's see who comes out on top.
We're ready.
Thank you very much.
I won't be writing for a while, but I will return home once a month.
I'll be gone on vacation for about two weeks.
How're you?
Aya,I wonder if he was called back to headquarters.
It says "vacation", so I guess he's going back to Singapore.
I wonder why he's going back to Japan now.
Shigetaka must have a woman living with him over there.
I don't know.
You must have married into an unhappy family.
I see you're going through the same trouble I am.
I understand.
Even though I can't see.
Aya, please stay here as long as I live.
I don't have long to live, so please be patient until then.
I'm going home.
Say hello to Yoshiaki.
Ayako.
Let me know as soon as you know when your husband will be back.
Take care.
Aya.
Just leave him alone.
Think you are the one who grew up in this house.
I think you're holding back too.
No...
Ever since my eyesight got worse.
He's become completely uninhibited and seems to bring something with him every time he comes over.
I wonder if antiques are useful for his business.
I'm not going to let Keiko take care of me, even though she's my daughter.
Mother, I'll always be with you.
Hello?
Oh Ayako.
How are you doing?
I was wondering.
I'd like to see you tonight.
Would you mind if I came to your hotel now?
I know you're busy.
I'd like to talk to you directly.
It's already late.
I think it's better if you stay at home today.
Stay there.
I get it.
I'm sorry for being so selfish.
Ryuzaki will be back soon.
That's why I'm feeling a little restless.
See you.
I'm home.
Chikako?
What are you doing?
Welcome back.
I didn't know you backed home.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm asking why you're here.
You're an idiot.
Who'd come here alone now? Let's go home.
You're shivering badly.
Because I'm cold.
Were you waiting for someone?
If You were, it wasn't me.
I just felt lonely being alone.
If you're lonely, why don't you just ask him to go home?
I thought you were working.
Good night.
Your work is still the best.
You are the top.
I lost and you won.
I'll win next.
The newspapers will pay attention to us.
It's good for our group.
Oh Kuse's here.
It's very crowded here.
Thank you so much for all your help.
I talked to our cultural director and he told me to post the feedback as soon as possible.
We've all been waiting since this morning for you to evaluate us.
Let me take a look.
Natsui-kun, you look very good.
You've really improved your skills since last year.
You have a mysterious power.
I didn't expect to run into a dead body.
I was questioned a lot by the police.
I forgot to say... and congratulations on your wedding.
I see you've settled down now.
He married old-fashioned.
Hey.
He was lucky to meet a suicide corpse.
He went to a strange place on his honeymoon.
Mr. Kuse went to Matsushima.
You went there too,right?
To Matsushima?
I'll be sure to take a look.
What, six more days?
I'll make sure to visit you.
I think this color is very nice.
Yes.
Mr. Kuze is an enthusiastic man.
He brings Mr. Kuwabara with him.
But he's a strange one, isn't he?
I hear he's very close to Mrs. Ryuzaki.
Don't say bullshit.
Why?
Oh she's here.
Come on in. I'll show you around.
Keep going.
See you.
You're awesome.
Please join me for dinner.
You're the only one who can congratulate me on my future.
Am I bothering you?
Just a little.
I'm still a housewife. I'm busy.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
Where?
Kichijoji
It's too far.
Around here ok.
I'd like you to do as I please for today.
I think I've succeeded.
What's in Kichijoji?
There is a restaurant that serves delicious country cuisine.
Isn't your husband supposed to be home by now?
He's always late.
Don't you miss him?
I miss him.
Sometimes I wish he was a normal office worker.
Oh, everyone at work is jealous of you.
It's an unusual job, and I hear he's a big star.
Let me show you a picture.
He took this.
What's this?
I don't know what it is, but it's beautiful.
It's still a lot better than being a regular office worker.
How's your workers?
We're fine.
Oh, yes, Mr. Ryuzaki.
He's coming back from Singapore tomorrow.
Thank you for the food.
It's been a long time since I've had something so rare and delicious.
I never thought I'd be eating at a place like this with you.
I can't believe it.
Don't be hesitate.
Shall we go home now?
My mother's waiting for me.
The most precious time passes so quickly, doesn't it?
Excuse me.
Check please.
Call a cab.
Would you like to wait 20 minutes?
It's busy today.
5 minutes by car
I'll go on foot.
It's cold.
I'm fine.
It's been years since I've walked in the fog.
Ma'am.
As I told you before, my marriage was a failure.
I'm afraid it's only going to make us both unhappy.
What's the hell?
Your wife loves you?
I can't get a grasp of her feelings.
But I think that's understandable.
After all, I myself can't give my heart to my wife.
It's my fault.
Why do you say that?
What?
You know.
And you're asking me because you know.
I can't be married to anyone.
I'm not saying that my wife is bad.
I married too soon.
What are you talking about?
You married her.
I know there's no point in making excuses.
I never said this to anyone.
Is this the first time you've told me that?
I would like someone to be honest with me and tell me.
I always think for myself.
You're talking to someone.
I think that person is much more mature, much more thoughtful, and much more attractive than I am.
Don't give me boring advice.
Let's go.
I'm sorry if I was out of line.
But for the record, just the thought of having someone like that in your life irritates me.
You may despise me.
The fact that my marriage was a failure is also because I met you before.
I don't want to hear it.
It's fine as is.
If it doesn't reach your ears, that's fine.
I don't feel comfortable doing this anymore.
I've always loved her.
You know how I feel.
That's why you asked me to marry her.
When I heard about it from a friend, I thought it would be a great match.
You tried to keep me away from her.
Don't tell me.
you know Kuse.
Why are you suddenly saying that?
I'll confess.
The image I have drawn near you is Kuse.
I know him.
If I see him, I will at least say hello.
Don't say that. It's rude.
I'm sorry.
I can't even look up.
But I wish I had met you long, long ago.
There is a peninsula jutting out from the east of Kyushu, isn't there?
It's called Kunisaki Peninsula.
A cultural zone was established there in the 12th century.
Now it's all gone, and the only remnants of it are the Buddha images on the cliffs.
Here's your coffee.
I want you to go out there and photograph with your own eyes the remains of an old culture that has died out deep in the mountains.
What do you think?
I'll do it.
Our magazine has a reputation for respect.
It's a big project.
I'm counting on you.
Hi.
Welcome back.
How's your mom doing?
She's fine.
She's very much looking forward to you
Welcome back.
As soon as you get off the plane in Japan, the air is damp.
Hey, look at that.
That woman standing in the lobby.
The girl who went to headquarters before.
She's here to pick you up?
No way.
I forgot her name.
Chikako Nonomura?
What kind of business did you come to Japan for?
why do you ask me that?
It's so sudden
It just occurred to me.
Are our important documents still in that safe?
Go to the Prince Hotel in Akasaka.
Why don't you go home tonight?
That won't be necessary.
What's wrong?
I'm tired.
I'd like to stay here tonight and relax.
I beg you to excuse my selfishness.
my mother's expecting you.
Tell her I said hello.
Mr. Tsuchiyama.
I'd like to talk to you... if you'll stay here.
Ayako, let's go home.
Thank you for coming all the way .
I'll get ready.
Can you at least look at me when you're talking to me?
Sorry.
You go out without telling me and you come back without telling me.
That's fine.
But if you're asked, at least answer.
If you're gonna have coffee, bring a cup.
I'm not the kind of man who would have a problem with your past.
Now that we're married, I'm very curious about our life together.
I'm sorry.
I don't care.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm a selfish man, but you're selfish.
right?
We're just two people living together, but we're both living in our own separate worlds.
I'm leaving for Kyushu tomorrow.
It's perfect... to be alone with each other... to think things over.
I can't go on like this.
So Nonomura became a photographer's wife.
I don't know the details.
How long have you been in a relationship?
Not much.
I wonder if what happened with you was the reason she left the company.
I have no idea.
But she came to pick you up at the airport.
I guess my wife knew about her.
You know, one day your wife showed me a picture of that girl and asked me who she was.
Is Chikako Nonomura an arranged marriage?
You seem to care a lot.
It doesn't matter.
You're the one who dumped her.
Please do some research on who her matchmaker is.
You shouldn't do that.
I'd feel sorry for her if she goes crazy.
Maybe it was my wife who got her married.
I can't believe it.
She's like that.
I hate women like that.
But she's doing well.
She's not my wife, she's a decoration in the Ryuzaki household.
She just takes care of my mother.
I don't know how she put up with it.
She wants to leave, but I won't let her.
I'll divorce her when she wants to be with me
Ryuzaki Speaking
Have you heard from Shigetaka?
No, nothing.
I see.
It's been three days. He must be busy since he left.
He's a selfish man, isn't he?
He doesn't care about me anymore.
You think too much, mother.
You should take it easy on yourself. It's not good for you.
Thanks.
I have not had a single day of peace of mind since I married into this family.
Shigetaka's grandfather and father were both socially respectable people.
But when they entered our house, they were very slovenly.
Mother.
It was hard for me.
I don't have anyone to listen to my complaints.
I'm just trying to take care of this house and keep it and grow old.
But it must be a family that deserves it.
Everyone in our family has lived a spectacular life.
You think so?
Oh yes.
You should go to higetaka's place now.
He lives in a hotel and there might be some inconvenience.
Anyway, tell him to go home.
Madam,there's a call for you from Kuse.
Hello?
I suddenly wanted to meet you.
Could you come to the usual place in Hibiya?
I see.
I'll be there.
Hello?
This is the front desk.
There is a lady named Ms. Soeda.
Soeda?
Let her through here, please.
We are police.
There's a Ryuzaki Shigetaka staying here.
Yes.
Room 416.
Please come in.
I knew it was you.
It's been a while.
I recognized you when you said Soeda.
That's a name I've missed.
It used to be a common name between us.
Now it's Natsui Chikako?
I heard it from a friend.
Have a seat.
You came to Haneda the other day.
I was hoping you'd be here today.
That's one reason I didn't go home. I was waiting for you.
I'm surprised you found me here.
I called the office.
Yes.
I ordered coffee right away.
We often had coffee together before.
Please leave.
I was surprised when I saw you at Haneda.
I was so happy.
It was nice to see you remember me after the way we parted.
Two and a half cups of sugar, no milk.
You're a coffee drinker.
I think Ryuzaki has returned to Japan, and I am no longer at peace with that.
You are Ryuzaki's wife, so I can't help it
I can't get my feelings in order.
I am also relieved that Ryuzaki is staying at a hotel.
Why don't you talk to Ryuzaki again?
Maybe you can get a divorce.
I can't.
Besides, I want to stay in that house as long as my mother is there.
If you're tied down by that...
We'll end up like this forever.
I was drinking alone by the time Ryuzaki's plane arrived in Haneda.
I couldn't stop drinking.
Sorry.
I too was inconsolable and all I could think about was you.
You and I will grow old, tied to a life with someone we don't love.
I'm lonely.
Your wife must be lonely.
She's fine.
We've been strangers for a long time.
He's just stubborn and won't leave me.
It's a strange life.
I've been with a lot of women before I met you.
I'm a flawed man.
I thought it would be mutually beneficial for both of us to leave my wife, and we've talked about it a few times.
But every time I do, she turns away.
You know we're both unhappy.
I don't know how she feels about that.
She loves you.
Is there such a way to love?
I don't want to.
That kind of egoism, that kind of love.
You must be running out of love for this man.
No, sir.
There are all kinds of men out there.
I've been thinking about that recently.
I heard Natsui-kun got married.
I know how Natsui-kun felt about you.
Please don't talk about Mr. Natsui
Was it Ayako who suggested marriage?
I'm sure his wife is a lovely woman.
I just find his heart somewhat pathetic.
You and I are both people who know the horrors of marriage.
Please don't talk about Mr. Natsui
While we're here, I want to forget about everything else and think about just the two of us.
Even if it's just a dream.
Just Kuse and me.
You are as selfish as a child.
Only to you.
We'll only be together for a short time.
I don't want to talk about other people in that short time.
Are you and your husband getting along?
I never thought you'd be a photographer's wife.
Love marriage?
What's up with that?
You won't tell me what's going on, no matter what I ask.
I'm leaving.
Leaving?
Then what are you doing here?
We haven't seen each other in a long time. You could stay and talk some more.
I don't think I have anything to say to you.
You're a curious woman.
You're mine.
That's why we're here.
Get your hands off of me!
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
I'm leaving.
When I left you, I told you to marry someone and happy.
But you're not happy.
I'm leaving.
I'm not the same person I was before.
I'm going abroad.
It's no longer possible for us to continue like this forever.
What will happen to me?
I want you to forget who I am.
Pretend you've never met me.
I can't.
You're going to marry someone else.
That's your new start.
I'm in the mountains of Kyushu.
I'd like you to hear me speak frankly about my feelings right now.
Ever since I married you, things have been different between us.
I'm not really sure if this is my fault or yours.
Before I knew you, I was attracted to a certain woman.
You may think it's terrible that I'm telling you this now.
But at the time, I believed that we could have a happy family without having to confess this to you.
I had thought that marriage would take her out of my heart.
But I guess I was wrong.
I'm sure you have your reasons.
But I'm not going to ask you about any of them.
But at this point, you and I need to separate, live separately, and think things over.
I will continue my trip to Kyushu for a while after this job is done.
After you read this letter, I ask you to take your own liberties.
When I return to our apartment, I want you to keep all your things out of my sight.
I will not ask you where you are.
I'd like to hear what you have to say about Singapore and put it in our magazine.
I don't want to show my face in such a place, since I'm back on personal business this time.
I would like a brief article and one photo
My photo?
I'll bring my photographer, Natsui, to visit you when it's convenient for you.
Natsui?
I saw your letter.
I really think you are right.
I think we had a strange marriage with too little understanding and not enough wisdom.
I was not worthy to be your wife.
I was a wife who could not serve you in any way during our short time together.
I am deeply sorry.
I thought your work was wonderful, even though I didn't know you very well.
I wish you the best of luck with your work.
Our exhibition was a great success, and I'd love to have you organize another one.
I'd like to introduce folk dances from around the world.
That's good.
So far, all your projects have been a success.
Give it a try.
Let's get started on something plan.
I have a phone call for you.
I'm sorry to call you at a time when you're so busy.
I'd like to talk to you again.
I'll be waiting for you at 7:00.
I'm sorry .
I'll be waiting.
I'm glad to hear you're doing well.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're well, too.
I'm very well, but I've been unnecessarily busy.
Welcome home.
The magazine people will be here at 1:00, so please put them in the parlor.
They have a cameraman coming.
You have to stay with us.
You're really busy, aren't you?
I'll be back later.
Did Shigetaka tell you anything about the house?
He asked me to hold off because he wanted to see the inventory.
Inventory?
What would he do with such a thing?
Singapore and other Southeast Asian countries have very strong ethnic feelings.
They're very antipathetic toward whites, but extremely friendly toward Japanese.
If we can take advantage of that sentiment, Japanese exports could still grow considerably.
Welcome.
That's enough.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to introduce you to my wife.
I'm Sumiya.
Mr. Natsui, it's been a while.
Did you know him?
Yes.
He's been visiting us from time to time.
I didn't know that at all.
Have a seat.
Have a seat too.
Natsui is still young, but very talented.
He had an exhibition recently, and it was very well received.
I wish I could have seen it.
I don't mean to be rude, but...
Of course you're still single, aren't you?
I got married about a month ago.
Congratulations.
Then this must be the best time for you.
Of course you're married for love.
He did arranged marriage.
That's unusual.
Who's your matchmaker?
Your friend?
Where did you go for your honeymoon?
He was too busy with work.
He met the bride at Asamushi Onsen.
It's a busy trip.
Speaking of Tohoku, you stayed in Matsushima, right?
Ayako.
I heard you also went to Matsushima just a month ago.
Alumni reunion
It's funny how you bump into people you know in the strangest places.
I have another job, so I'll leave you now.
Why don't you take it a little easier?
I have to go back to Singapore again.
I wonder if you will come visit her again while I'm gone.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Send them.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
I'm the first to know you've been to Matsushima.
Of course you're not alone.
Natsui..
He's childish.
You didn't need to tell him.
About Matsushima?
There's nothing for him to worry about.
Or is there something wrong?
I heard Natsui's wife ran away.
She's not gonna like him.
How did you know about that?
Someone very curious.
He looked it up for me.
The matchmaker for Mr. Natsui is a friend of yours and a friend of yours.
You've gone to a lot of trouble, haven't you?
You shouldn't meddle too much.
I'm going back to the hotel.
I'd like an inventory of our property.
Senpai.
You look busy.
It's always like  a war.
Do you go home?
I'm meeting someone at 7:00.
Since you still have time, there's a restaurant in Shinbashi that I know.
Please take a peek at a restaurant for us commoners once in a while.
I'll buy you a drink.
Right now, what I'm covering is a move by the Metropolitan Police Department's Investigation Division Two.
So the culprit is an intelligent criminal.
But they've been in secret communication with the Crime Prevention Unit.
with the Crime Prevention Unit?
That, apparently, smells a little like a big case.
I think that's smuggling.
You think so too?
You're my senior.
I followed many cases 10 years ago.
Hey New face.
How's it going?
She's a nice girl.
She came alone and asked for a job.
Girls these days are brave, even amateurs.
I'd better get going.
Ryuzaki 416, please.
Thanks.
Did he go to the hotel with the inventory of your property?
I don't know what he's going to do.
My mother's worried.
We'll have to wait and see.
Is that what you're talking about?
About Natsui,
She's Chikako.
Is this his wife?
She used to be a typist at the same company as Ryuzaki.
He dumped her?
Ryuzaki thinks he's done with everything once he's gone to Singapore.
He doesn't mind that much.
Did you think you could save her by having her marry Mr. Natsui?
Before I came here today, I was invited by a young man at work to a bar in Shinbashi.
She works there.
I heard her calling Ryuzaki.
I was wondering what kind of woman she was.
I thought Mr. Natsui would make Ms. Chikako happy.
I really thought.
I heard from Ryuzaki today that they have separated.
Chikako-san visited him at the hotel too.
hotel?
I've done a terrible thing.
What is he going to do if he finds out about Ryuzaki and Chikako's relationship?
I thought that once she was married, she could put the past behind her.
I can't believe that Ryuzaki is still in such a strong form in Chikako-san's heart.
Did you not think about how long and how hard it takes for a human being to forget a single love?
Natsui and Chikako
I'm sorry.
The power went out.
Please wait.
Were you burdened by Natsui-kun?
You were the ideal man for Natsui-kun.
If you'd asked him to marry someone,He would have... even if he didn't want to.
Don't talk about it.
Everything is my fault.
I don't have the right to blame you.
I didn't realize the pain
I'm the pathetic one.
You can't work in a bar.
I can't have a regular job now.
What's so good about Ryuzaki?
Don't tell me what's good or bad.
Picking him up at Haneda is like exposing a woman's weakness.
I don't have a choice.
If I hear he's back, I'd like to see him.
He dumped you.
But you still want to see him?
I'm afraid that if I don't do anything, I'll be stuck with Ryuzaki for the rest of my life.
Stay strong.
You're Natsui's wife now.
He does not love me.
If Natsui had told me he loved me even once...
I wouldn't have gone to see Ryuzaki.
If Ryuzaki really loved you, he would have left his Wife.
It's not fair.
I'm going to see him.
You shouldn't.
I need to know exactly what he's really thinking.
And then I'll decide what I want to do.
You shouldn't.
You'll only get hurt.
I don't think I deserve to be beaten up after what I've done.
I'm only human.
I'd like to live my life defending myself as much as possible.
But just being afraid of me getting hurt
I'll never be happy.
Right?
Yeah.
I can't live like this.
I don't care how much it hurts, I just want to be loved.
I love him.
I'm stumped.
Just say no.
I bet he doesn't show up here either.
Mr. Seimiya of Infinite Japan magazine was angry too.
They won't even ask him to do portraits for every issue anymore.
I didn't think he'd want his wife to run away from him and ruin his work too.
Let's dance.
Let's dance with me.
Go ahead.
What a professional photographer could get away with if he'd just missed a portrait.
You have a reputation for being arrogant these days.
That kind of smugness has no place in this society.
You're only as good as the trust you're given.
I don't care if you don't have a job, just leave me alone.
You've changed.
You're not the same person you used to be when you were going around like a work fiend.
How did you remember this place?
I'll take care of it.
Same one.
How much do I owe you?
You don't have to pay now.
I've got some money.
It's been a while, so I thought I'd settle up.
Don't worry.
I haven't even kept the books in order.
I'd settle up.
What do you mean?
About you too.
I hope you are joking.
I'm serious.
I knew you'd say something like that someday.
Something's wrong.
Kuse.
It's been a while.
It's serious, isn't it?
Did you get in a fight?
Don't make Madam cry too much.
Madam,
Let's have a drink together to make up.
Let's drink.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry, but...
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
I'm sorry.
Send me the bill later.
Hey, what are you doing?
Is it true you're not working at all?
It's true.
You're an idiot, you know that?
What are you doing here all alone?
I'm just disappointed.
You mean Mrs. Ryuzaki?
I know you loved her.
Is Mrs. Ryuzaki the reason you separated?
Talking about Chikako is useless.
We couldn't make out.
She's nice.
Don't talk about Chikako and Ayako anymore.
Naoki!
What's up?
Kuse left me.
He sees someone.
I know it's a rumor anyway.
Don't get any ideas.
Those two are nothing.
You know about it.
About what?
If you don't tell us, I'll come after you.
it's a just rumor
Tell me.
I'm just trying to come to terms with my feelings.
Ok then I tell you.
I'm the wife of the branch manager of Meiwa Bussan.
Her name?
Mrs. Ryuzki.
She's beautiful.
Are you alright?
This is Kuse.
Did you know that your husband was having an affair outside the home?
No, ma'am.
She's not a whore like us.
she's a wife.
The wife of the branch manager of Meiwa Bussan.
Her name?
Ayako Ryuzki.
Do you know?
Ayako Ryuzki?
She's beautiful.
I'm Ryuzaki.
this is Kuze.
I'm sure you must have been surprised to hear from me so suddenly.
Have a seat.
I'm surprised.
You said the story seems to be related to my wife somehow.
Did your wife ever mention the name Kuse to you?
I was in Singapore for about a year.
Then let me ask you frankly.
You never heard about the relationship between your wife and my husband?
What?
This is Natsui.
This is Ryuzaki.
I'm sorry to bother you, but I need to see you right now.
I just need an hour of your time.
Please come to the grill at the Prince Hotel.
By the way, Mr. Natsui, do you know a man named Kuse?
Yes.
Actually, the reason I asked you to come here today is because I would be very grateful if you could tell me how well you and my wife are acquainted with Kuse.
I don't know much about them, but I think they are just acquaintances.
I've heard rumors that someone named Kuse has seduced my wife.
That would never happen.
It's unthinkable.
Aside from my wife.
For someone like Mr. Kuse, who is doing such a socially respectable job, it's a pity to just start rumors.
That's slander.
Who said that?
The madam at the bar who Kuse had left her informed Kuse's wife.
No.
She and Kuse are clean.
Thank you for your opinion, and I'm relieved to hear it.
There are people in this world who make all kinds of rumors about other people's wives, you know.
Have a meal.
I don't think that would happen to your wife, Mr. Natsui.
You mean my wife?
Of course, there is no need for you to worry.
I heard that your wife left you.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm puzzled by the rumors about my wife.
I was concerned about you in your senior capacity.
Don't worry about me.
I don't think you have the right to imagine anything strange or dirty about Kuse or your wife.
I am Ayako's husband.
How much Ayako has suffered because of you.
You have had various adulterous relationships since you were in Japan.
Do you have the right to accuse Ayako-san as her husband?
Young people these days don't know how to be polite.
That's you!
Natsui.
Before you talk about others, look at yourself a little.
How about it?
Why don't you reflect on why you're hated by your wife?
You guys think I don't know anything.
I'm a more careful man than you might think.
You just made a strong argument that my wife and Kuse are nothing.
You're protecting Kuse, aren't you?
I know everyone.
It's not just about my wife.
I know Chikako left you, and I don't know where she is.
Chikako?
Sorry, your wife
Instead of messing with married women, get a hold of your own wife.
That's why she's running away.
Wait,Natsui!
Welcome back.
You're still awake.
I need to talk to you.
Do you know the madam of the bar Clarendon?
Yes, I do.
Michi Yamaoka called me.
She told me about your relationship with Ayako Ryuzaki.
What?
Since I don't see you anymore, we're married in name only.
So I don't care a bit whether you have a cabaret girl or a bar madam for a lover.
I've given up on that.
But when I heard you had such a relationship with another man's wife, I couldn't stand it.
What?
We are..
You guys are?
It is true that Ayako and I are in a relationship.
But it's not the kind of relationship you're imagining.
You're despicable.
She's dirty too.
No, you've got it all wrong.
I've met Mr. Ryuzaki.
I'll ask him to look into Ayako
You...
You are here.
I've been looking for you.
What do you want?
You can't talk to me if you're trying to be decent.
I'm just trying to show you something.
Read this.
I'm not working. I'm not reading this.
Here's a review of your work from Mr. Kuwana.
I'll read the last word.
Anyway, what's the reason I haven't come in contact with Natsui's works lately?
I will truly miss Natsui's work.
I greatly admired his experimental ambition and unique techniques.
Stop.
There are people waiting for your work.
You have to work.
I'm sure your wife cares about you.
She's a woman who is into my business.
I don't think so.
Even during the exhibition, she came to see it three times, hiding.
Chikako?
The first time I showed her around.
Then people deliberately pretended they didn't know her.
She saw how many people were in front of your work, and she looked happy from a distance.
How can you do a good job if you can't even make a home?
This way, I know everything about you.
You're a lot richer than you were two years ago.
Let's make love again like we used to.
Old love?
It's not true.
What's the matter with you?
You once said...
You told me you loved me and that we should be together.
But And when you left for Singapore, you said, "This is what love looks like, forget about it.
I didn't have a choice.
I don't want to.
I don't want that kind of selfish love.
We are an adult.
We need to make love with our bodies.
I'm going home.
I won't let you go.
You came to the airport, you came to the hotel, you came here voluntarily.
You came here of your own volition.
I thought that if you were willing to drop everything and truly love me...
I'd be willing to leave Natsui.
You don't exaggerate like that.
I'm not going to put my future on the line for a woman who became someone else's wife.
I was such a fool.
Your heart is so pathetic.
I'm ashamed to think I'm willing to throw away my life for someone like this.
I had this thing that I was willing to die for.
This is a scissors with which Natsui cuts the film.
What are you doing?
Don't be stupid.
You must be Shigetaka Ryuzaki.
We are from police.
This is a warrant for your arrest.
Please come with us.
Something happened?
Ayako-san's voice is very different from usual.
I'll see you and talk about it at usual place.
What's wrong?
Let's go to Kawaji Onsen.
I'm sorry, I decided on my own.
Kuse.
Consider me your wife tonight.
Please.
Yes.
I couldn't be yours at Matsushima.
It was all right then.
There were things I couldn't have in you, too.
Not tonight.
Tonight, I am your wife.
I want to think that forever.
I don't know what the future holds, but for now, it's enough.
Why do you say that?
If this moment lasts, it's like eternity.
What if it doesn't?
Don't think about that.
Think of me as your wife for tonight.
Why do you say that?
I'll never let you go.
You're my wife forever.
Talk to us.
Let's me hear it.
I'm afraid to tell you.
I want to hold off as long as I can
Please.
Until this fire is extinguished.
Ryuzaki was arrested.
Eh?
He's being held at the Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department.
What's going on?
He was working with Japanese smugglers in Singapore.
Is that true?
A member of the group was arrested, and the police found out about Ryuzaki.
Ayako.
You're going to confess it tonight and leave me.
Right?
You're going to leave me.
You can't get a divorce now that Ryuzaki's been arrested.
Not because I love Ryuzaki.
I was going to make you my wife this time, no matter what I had to do, no matter how long it took.
You can't.
Seeing my mother when the house was raided made it impossible for me to abandon the Ryuzaki family.
You should have left him earlier.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going to stay with the Ryuzaki family.
So you won't think of me?
I won't let you go.
Good morning.
Your wife left on an urgent errand.
She just left.
I need a car right away.
Your wife gave me this.
I am so sorry.
Please forgive my selfishness.
I said I would stay in Ryuzaki for my mother's sake.
I'm sure you must feel very sorry for her.
But that is not why I am leaving you.
The more I love you, the more a heavy sense of guilt about Natsui and Chikako spreads in my heart.
Please forget about Ayako.
I will not see you again. I will bear it and say goodbye.
Hello?
Your car is ready.
I don't need the car anymore.
Sado?
I'd like to work for the Bureau of Communications.
You don't have to go there.
It's country side.
I'd like to work there.
For how long?
Natsui is here.
I'll be there soon.
Six months or a year?
Until retirement.
What's the hell?
I'm so glad you came.
I was afraid you wouldn't come even if I asked you to.
I have no face to show to Kuse or Ayako
No, that's what we're saying.
Please forgive Ayako's mistake.
She's already been punished a lot for that kind of thing.
Ayako has a childish, childish old-fashioned streak in her.
She thought that you and Chikako would be happy together.
I should have been more pleased with Ayako and Kuse.
That's impossible.
I don't need that bullshit blessing.
You had no choice until now.
Ryuzaki has been arrested.
Please make Ayako happy.
Natsui.
I may be transferred to Sado in the near future.
I've separated from my wife.
I told her I was going to live on Sado Island for the rest of my life, and she said she didn't want to be a part of that kind of island life.
I doubt we'll ever see Ayako again either.
At least not while we're young.
Why would you do that?
I don't know.
Maybe it's because I love her
Maybe it's because she loves me.
Humans are weird
Kuse
When I learned about Ryuzaki and Chikako, I fell in love with Chikako all over again.
Do you laugh?
A man who started loving his wife with such a pathetic love...
I am sure you will be happy!
You must do a great job for Chikak!
I'll at least pay attention to the magazines when I'm outside.
I will do it.
Chikako?
Welcome back.
I'm sorry.
I'm bad wife.
I came back here on my own. Can you leave me here?
I'm sorry.
I'm not going anywhere.
Good.
I won't let you go.
Two months have passed since we parted.
I felt as if I were walking in a dream
Our mother passed away not long after that.
Shigetaka's mismanagement has destroyed my mother's zest for life, who had been defending the Ryuzaki family's pride.
It is thanks to my mother's efforts that Shigetaka and I have decided to divorce.
Now that I am finally a free woman, I am busy getting my affairs in order.
I made the decision to come to your side after seeing what happened to Natsui and Chikako.
I really feel lighter in body and mind.
Please consider the day I leave for Sado as a new beginning with you, with whom I will no longer be parting.
THE END