Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
I've finally turned to 30
Marriage Counseling / The Passionate Spinster (1965)
Kekkon Sodan (1965)
This wig is trendy worldwide and is used in place of a hat
This is durable and can be used in the bath.
Can we take a photo together,Furukawa?
Thanks
Oh torii, I think I don't need to be taken
Never mind
I'm looking forward to your wedding next year
I won't get married soon.
I feel like playing more
I'm still 23 years old
Thanks
He's Takabayashi
Ogoshi department's
He's a Don Juan, isn't he?
Shimako is worried about getting married
They are same age
I wonder how she feels about turning 30.
It's kind a sad
Next is your turn.
Let me know about your wedding party.
I'll come from Hamamatsu
I'll be waiting there
She's having a hard time getting a new job right after getting married.
She got married right away because she was relocating.
I see
I was asked by her to take her to Hamamatsu when I was relocating
Hamatatsu is his home town
You made their connection.
It's kind of
Tsurukawa
I thought you've gone by car
My boss asked me to see off at airport by car
Shall we get a cab?
Where are you going?
I'm going by bus to Mejiro
I wanna go to Shibuya too
I'll get Toyoko line from Shibuya.
This will be convenient for me.
Sorry to bother you
Your kimono gets dirty if you get on a bus
Takabayashi from Ogoshi department store likes you guys
He said you guys were lovely
Only for young girls, right?
No way
Or just my Kimono?
Give me a break
He's good eye for women
I know that
He's famous
How about you?
I don't
I am taking care of my sick wife
I'm sorry
How's her?
She's ok
The sickness is annoying
She always stay at hospital?
Yes
does she move?
I think she don't have to change the hospital
You'll go with your kids?
Yeah, I will take them
It's hard
I'm used to it
Stop at Shibuya
Shibuya, OK?
Thanks
I'll stay in the car
It is very difficult to get married in Japan today.
A business called a marriage agency that introduces marriage partners was established
The percentage here is Women for 60%, men for 40%
The most age range is 26 to 30
The ratio is so unbalanced
Men want younger women Women want men's height and educational background
There are 24 public match making centers in Tokyo
120 in Japan
And there are more private match making centers
It's easy to start this business
Yes we are
We Introduce women after joining
Sorry
Did you fill in?
A man who graduate university
Up to 35 yrs old.
You don't care how he looks
But his height is over 170cm
It's ok if he drink, but he must look after home
a man who does a man who does not interfere with his wife not interfere with his wife
He can live together
These are really common case
You are educated and beautiful
I'll introduce you a man now
Wanna see him?
Asako
He graduated from Tokyo uni, 29yrs old, work for west Japan industrial
He'll transfered to L.A so He wants her to go there together for 3 yrs
Do you afraid to go abroad?
I don't care
Wanna see him?
It cost 1000 yen for admission, and another 1000 yen for introduction fee
Is there company house in LA?
Yes
I'll need to take over former people
Do you need to learn English?
It will work out
How many Japanese people there?
I guess about 10.
They told me they sent more people
Sorry but I need to go to Haneda airport to see off my boss
I'm sorry
Please keep eating
It's urgent
I'll call you later and talk more
I'm sorry
Please stay as it is
Hayakawa called me just now
He told me he needed to go to Haneda airport to see off his boss
Oh so on the way?
He seems to like you a lot
What do you think?
He's not bad
But I need more time
Sure
He'll be your partner
I'll arrange you next meeting
Can you come here the day after tomorrow?
I'll call him to arrange you next meeting
I'll visit you after working
He told me you were so lovely and looked young
You must be virgin
Micchan is late
She is having meeting
She is having dating
With Yamashita?
She see him everyday
They must get married soon
She worries about you
She's old fashion
I don't care if my sister get married earlier than me
You looked after her very well.
She's very appreciate about you
I'm glad about that , but
It seems I bother them
Don’t think too much
I'm too old, unmarried woman
But I hope someone likes me
You hope I leave this home,right?
What are you saying?
Do you have a world map?
Yes
Let me see
For what?
I just wanna see it
Tea, taste good
Oh right
It's same tea
Thanks
Are you going to travel
Kind of
Come to my house?
My sis might be there
Maybe next time
I don't care about your sis, but
It's late
I know how you feel
I'm home
You know what?
Men are so terrible
Hayakawa told me you were educated and very neat
and he wanted to take you abroad
But he had a match making date with a girl who was 24 years old introduced by his boss
After meeting with me? at Haneda?
He liked her because she was young and graduated from Japan women uni.
He must be fond of her because of his work
I feel sorry about him.
I will give you back the fee
I'm sorry for that
I'm in trouble.
I don't need this money
I'll keep this next introduction fee
Next man looks nice
Next man ?
You should broaden the conditions for the men you marry.
There are many opportunities for you.
Meet men as many as possible
I am the third son of a farmer in Nagano.
I like to use electricity
I work at my grandfather's shop.
I graduated from high school and college in night school
I know nothing beside my specialties
You might hate it
I will work at Asian Textile right after graduating from high school.
You have better education than I
I know nothing
But I'm sure I'm good at about electrical things
I'll own my shop soon
Eh?
I know but
You are not kid.
You don't have to listen to your parents anymore
I can't count on you.
Sorry
He's so terrible.
I feel sorry about him
I know you listened to our conversation
I was so upset
I'm sorry
His uncle is opposed to your marriage
He told me you were 30yrs unmarried woman.
Something must be wrong
I've wanted to introduce a man.
Wanna meet him?
He's rich and nice but
But he's little old
How old?
Before 50
You can't?
Don't be rush
I'll keep connecting
Cheer up
There will be next chance
Excuse me
He told me you were 30yrs unmarried woman.
Something must be wrong
He's rich and nice but
Before 50
He looks younger than in the photo
He lives in Wakayama
He own orchard
It is said that he is expanding his business
He often come to Tokyo for his work
See the Remarks column
He lost his wife last yr and has 2 kids
But his grand mom look after his son
So you don't have to worry
Smell good
I feel nostalgic
This remind me of my childhood
Your dad worked about ship?
He worked for Nippon Yusen
Did he die in a submarine attack?
I just remembered
He worked around a dock
I forgot the name of ship
It was nice ship
Since he worked on land, he would often bring me along.
It taste good
Another beer
I get drunk
No worries
I just remembered about my Dad
We brothers and my mother went to pick up my father at the port of Yokohama.
We were so small
my brother and sister were still babies
I remembered somehow
My father brought me foreign sweets as a souvenir.
I was glad
He must be nice
We often ate at restaurants like this on the way home
I forgot the name of restaurant
he liked tatami very much
he often slept on the tatami
I really miss him.
Sorry
Why?
I feel like I am with my dad now
Don't get me wrong
Never mind
I'll be your dad too if I get married with you
you should be more proactive
you should seduce him
He's mine now
the wedding will be later
he promised to marry me
you changed into a kimono
I couldn't put on the kimono very well.
I thought you should rest a little after eating breakfast.
Are you still sleepy?
I'm not
do you regret what happened last night?
So you forgive me
Let's have a meal
Tonobe-sensei's motto is a clean marriage.
She might get angry with us
It may not be a good idea to decide to get married immediately after meeting once.
So Let's say this
If you come again next month, let's meet again and I will report to her
tell her you're going on a few more dates with him
I'm too honest
I'm sure she will understand you
I'll give you pocket money, so please buy whatever you like.
don't worry we are dating for marriage
I am grateful that you paid the accommodation fee for the inn.
Don't be serious
Last night I received something precious from you
I wanna thank to you
this is great
This might be too much
I don't think so
He must like this
we are not married yet
When you go on a date, you wear new clothes, don't you?
free to imagine
That's what I thought
Furukawa
I'm here
A phone call for you
From your boyfriend
sorry to call you
I'm in a lot of trouble
What's wrong?
I thought I should let you know right away
I was so disgusted with myself.
I've been doing this job for a long time, but I'm disappointed in myself.
I was tricked
He's so bad
About Hidaka?
Yes
He liked you and I felt safe
What happened...
I've been doing this job for a long time and I've also done research on men.
He gave in to temptation..
What happened?
don't be surprised
he has a wife
She's still alive
Oh no
I know how you feel
I feel same
I wanted to sue him
but I worried about my business reputation
I thought it would be fine to give up if it was such an arranged date.
I think it would have been nice to know what he was like before you got married.
Shimako
Don't be sad too much
I’m in a lot of trouble
he clearly promised to marry me
Carelessly
Carelessly?
I slept in
I was stupid.
I was tricked
Yes you are
Very
I certainly introduced him to you
I feel responsible
I wanted you guys to have a clean relationship
How was it?
That's what I thought
I was surprised that you had sex with him
He told me and I guessed what happen
I think he is honest
He lied to you but he really likes you
So
I heard that you received 20,000 yen from him.
I refused but he gave me
But you got it for sure
he thinks the money is settled
He may think you slept with him for the money.
You're so mean
Don't be loud
Listen,this is very important
You got the money, so if anything happens, it will be pursued.
he might say he bought you with money
It can't be helped
What if everyone know
police may also be involved
You know prostitution is a crime, right?
Our business is also getting a bad reputation.
they might say we're a brothel
I will lose everything
I'm sorry
don't apologize to me
you were just deceived
there are bad people in the world
Bad women use agents like this to make money
It can't be helped
Have you seen Asako?
men watch her
men watch her?
Yes, I asked him to watch her
It can be said that protection
I'm afraid she will be escorted by the police
I have to take responsibility for that
I'm watching her so she doesn't do bad things
It can't be helped
I would like to introduce her and receive a commission.
I can protect you too
I can ask someone to watch you
That's good for us
Where are you going?
You look down
come dance with us
I will introduce you to a good man
Let's go
Let's have fun
Where's Torii?
I broke off my engagement with him
he has feminine and old values
There are many men who are better than him
Let's go
Let's dance
I wanna dance with you
Let's have fun
Leave me alone
Lady
It's too noisy here, let's go outside
Now?
Let's go to a quiet place
I'll go home
Get hands of me
Stop it
What the hell?
Let's go
Bye
OK
You are so drunk
Sorry
Do you remember me?
This is Asako Yoshida, who worked with Tonobe
Did you get better?
she is your colleague?
She's so bad
Don't get discouraged if you fail once
they are so terrible
she says she's a virgin and gets married
If you want to play with her, you should earn money with the agent woman
My friend own an apartment without being there for two years
You will be the owner of the building
I'm not kidding
she expects from you
she is very business person
Don't tell her
I heard that you had two arranged dates.
Do you know two of them?
they are her bodyguards
one of them looks like her husband
she tested you
She said she didn't have the man you wanted, so she did it to make you give up.
That's the life
you should be smart
don't worry someone's watching you
If you work with her, you may find a good man.
She says she'll match make as soon as she has a good story
That's good, isn't that?
Was Shimako-san laughing too?
she's so simple.
Did you tell her?
I told her that Miyako built an apartment.
did you play well about me?
That's bad
I told her something
I wish she knew about me
I'm not a yakuza so I don't want to do bad things
I hope she can earn money doing what she likes
Life is good even if you don't get married I will tell her
I know she wants men
she lost her virginity at 30
When I get married, I plan to be your father as well.
He really loves you
you are really stupid
I broke off my engagement
You'd rather run an apartment and make money
I was worried because you didn't get out of the bath
I'll go out now
Oh Hidaka.
When did you come?
Oh I see
are you the person before?
She doesn't seem to go to work these days
I will contact her and get back to you.
I gave you a hard time and I want you to be happy
Do you have any problems if you quit your company and use your retirement allowance?
I'll work again later
You want me to marry,right?
You need money to get married
I will not marry a man for my money
But it is rude to marry without money.
I can talk to my grandfather, who is rich, and we will be fine.
If I go to a marriage agency, I can make as many matches as I want
I'm in a marriage agency so don't worry
I hate marriage agencies
why do you hate?
The Tokyo Metropolitan Government and ward offices also operate marriage agencies.
your thoughts are old
you have express mail
you are writing a letter of resignation
Are you planning to play with your retirement money?
Yes.
Let me see the mail
I think she's in the mood
She is so shocked that she doesn't want to see you for a while.
you'll be fine if you have a little patience
Women can't forget their first man
Sure
you'll be fine if you have a little patience
You have a lot of matchmaking partners
that woman with big eyes?
I have to go to toilet
There is also a toilet inside
Shimako
I thought I had the wrong person.
are you on your way home?
shall we talk somewhere?
How about going to Atami?
how is your companion?
Did you see?
Yes. I have to go
Hold on
I know how you feel
I have my own reasons.
I didn't mean to fool you
Get hands off of me
Oh Tsurukawa
Takabayashi
I was looking for you
you had a very hard time
No way.
You helped me
I was so surprised that you helped me
Did you forget about me?
No no.
I was happy that you from OGOSHI department found me
I am very honored.
It worked well
It's the second time I've been surprised by you
I saw you occasionally at the company, but I was very surprised about you at  Kadota's wedding.
you were so beautiful
About my clothes,right?
Yes
Yes but
You were a beauty that matched that dress
Today you yourself are so beautiful
you really are more beautiful than before
I was surprised by that
where are you going?
wherever you like is fine
OK. so Let's go somewhere with me
I'm starving
What should I do
Do you feel annoying?
I'm shy.
I'm starving too
I thought you left the company to get married
I meant to that.
but I do nothing but doing matchmaking
do you come to atami for that?
It would be nice to have a date in Atami
he gives you diamonds
It would be nice if so.
But It doesn’t work well
You are very demanding of others
I always get rejected by men
Men don't realize how beautiful you are
are you not going to get married yet?
I am not popular with women at all
I hear you are popular with women
I have a bad reputation
To be honest, I'm very weak
I have a problem
We just met, but I have a request for you.
For what?
can you be my fiancee?
Just for the time being
you want to run away from a woman?
That's right
I think she will run away if she sees you
Please help me
Oops
It's strange to play with you
You are dancing very good
don't you drink?
I’m already drunk
I'll have another one
Welcome
It's been a long time since I met you
is this your first time here?
she is very beautiful
I thought you were a geisha
I really admire you
she is going to be my wife
I brought her here to educate her.
That's what I thought
she is too beautiful for you.
you should keep her in the alcove
when is the wedding?
End of march
it's nice to do it in the spring.
where are you going on your honeymoon?
Of course we will go to Kyoto your shop is nearby
Please visit us
Kyoto in spring is very beautiful
please drink more
I know you drink a lot
We are on our way back from Atami
You guys were in Atami even though you didn't have a wedding?
Did you guys go to preview the honeymoon?
I went for matchmaking
It's very old-fashioned to have a matchmaking
You are very old-fashioned
It can't be helped
If I don't take her home, I will get angry from your family.
He has a lot of things going on with me.
Why are you grinning?
Whatever.
I may be drunk
I feel so pleasant
you came home late
you worry me
did you eat dinner?
I had
with your friend?
With nice person
Was there a wonderful person at the class reunion?
I didn't go to the class reunion
I met him at Tokyo Station on my way home.
Who?
If you don't eat, I will clean up the meal
Go ahead
I also told you about Mr. Takabayashi of OGOSHI department store.
Mr. Takabayashi ?
He was the manager of a department store and was able to do business with our store from time to time.
He also attended Ujiie's wedding
He's playboy
You stupid.
I go to bed
She's turn to be crazy
Don't talk about her badly
He's popular for play boy
You know him?
I don't know
Shimako told me.
He's so play boy in the company too
You sure?
She told you about him too
Why she has something to do with him?
She knows that,right?
a woman's heart is hard to understand
a woman's heart is hard to understand?
You're too noisy.
I can't sleep
You'll get cold
All men are don Juan or wolf
I wanna eat fried noodle
Me too
What the hell.
Shimako wanna eat too?
She won't eat.
She mast have eaten beef steak with him
Department store chiefs don't get paid much.
But he's business man
It costs a lot to play with women
He is cheating on the deal money.
Don't think too much
He's not thief
Women like strong men
What's wrong?
Where are you guys going for honeymoon?
That's good place to go
It's lovely in the spring
I'm going on a business trip to Asian Textile in Hamamatsu, so why don't we meet at a hotel in Hamanako?
Are we going for honeymoon?
It might be so
We can't?
Why do you laugh?
We are supposed to go to Kyoto for honeymoon,right?
That's for real honeymoon
This will be fake honeymoon
You are nice.
This is my business trip so I can't change the place
I'm afraid to see my grandfather
There is no chance.
You just stay at hotel
Are you Mr.Takabayashi.
There's a phone call for you
Oh Sensei
What the hell, Shimako
Who's he?
I happened to meet my ex college
Are you having an affair?
No way
It is against the rules to date men for free.
Excuse me
How did you find I was here?
So What can I do for you?
Well, what should I do.
I ask you to pay the unbilled money
Or ask you to arrange our date
Oh about unbilled money
I know you wanna ask me to wait
Ask me for date
Anytime is fine
Who the hell the girl
You are open minded
Can you forgive about Hidaka?
He's here, Atami.
He can meet you anytime
You can play with him
I know you want me to go
I know everything what are you doing!
Trust me
I know how you trick women
I won't leave from you even if you get married
You get it?
Cut it out, Madam
Leave me alone
You are too noisy
You should give up
Hello?
He hang up?
You deserve it
You seduce him
Shimako
Good luck
Leave it to me.
You too
You idiot
To Jotokai
Can we trade only half of the items?
We are in trouble with our business.
I see
Possibly even a criminal case.
I was rehired by Asian Textiles on the verge of bankruptcy and I don't want to cause problems.
I get it.
It was bad timing
We don't care if we lose 3 million yen
I also talked your boss
He told me that he gave some rebate money
So this is no problem
2,300,000 yen as a breach of contract fee can be paid as expenses.
Thank for your advice.
Thieves will steal again, won't they?
In short, I'm thief.
You can't forgive thief
I'll be over
Shall we run away to Hong Kong together?
I did nothing wrong
I'm kidding
Shimako
I'm too bad
Sorry I was something wrong
I couldn't hold back
I love you
I'm not good enough for you
I'm too bad
Never mind
I'm bad too
I'm really too bad
Don't say anything.
I'm bad too
I'm not the woman who you think of
I've played with many men
It doesn't matter I am play boy
This is a different matter.
I have punched a hole in the ledger of $3 million.
A client company was absorbed by an Asian textile company.
If the transactions had continued, the bookkeeping irregularities would not have been discovered.
I thought I worked out
no one will protect me
Of course I will be fired from the company
He may file criminal charges against me if I don't make money in the next few days.
I might be in a jail
I'll make up the money
If we paid only half, he might have settled out of court.
I can't ask you to do that
Why?
It's a joke that I'm in jail
this is just business failure
this is very common
Forget what I said
Don't be serious.
Let's have fun
I was sorry
Forget what I said
It's a very nice lake
I want to ride a boat
Let's go now
It's too late
It's still bright
Damn it
No...
don't worry so much about money
You're very kind,Shimako
I never sucked my mom's tits
You're like my mom
you are my only friend
I can't trust anyone
I only need you
I don't care if I die
let us die together
We're not over yet
Shimako
I'm going out
I'm going out.
What's wrong?
Have a seat,Shimako
I need to talk with you
What's wrong?
You are strange
we are worried about you
For what?
I will tell you the truth
You're lying
What the hell?
This is from Mikiko
Yes from Kyushu
You went to Mikiko's place in Hamamatsu, didn't you?
I went to hamamatsu
But she said...
She wasn't in Hamamatsu because she was traveling.
I will tell you the truth
I didn't go to Hamamatsu to see her.
That's what I thought
I decided to get married with Takabayashi
What the hell?
I thought you would like it
I finally found my partner
But he is...
I went to Hamamatsu with him
you are not pure
your thoughts are old
I know he has a bad reputation
I don't care if he's a playboy
It's not big deal
no one believes I’m not married yet
That's the life
I think he and I get along very well
I want you to take my words seriously.
I don't mean that
I'm serious. so I went to Hamamatsu
I wanted to get along with him well
I'm serious.
Marriage counseling was meaningless
You didn't help me when you worried about me
So I'm right
I feel sad to hear that
I gave you a lot of trouble
I feel bad about it
Mitsuko and Takeshi too
I know how you feel
Get married and I'm just leaving this house
Shimako
This is a happy occasion, so don't cry.
Excuse me
Who's there?
Congratulations. Ok
I don't care who you marry
I can do a background check on him
This is a marriage agency
No way
you still don't understand
You say marriage marriage without worrying about a matchmaking partner
He's upset.
can you take responsibility?
it was not possible to stay outside
A day trip from Atami was possible
I know you used Asako
You had an affair in Hamamatsu
I was not
you didn't meet the matchmaking partner
You had an affair with a man
Our business is very trustworthy.
I can't stand your behavior
You are much more educated than Asako
I won't give you much explanation
It's not good to have an affair with a man
you know the rules?
Do you know what will happen if you break the rule?
I'm sorry I'll be careful from now on
I won't be fooled by you
we take business seriously
we are credit first
Ok anyway
you will be punished for breaking the rules
You’re scary
What the hell you are?
It's not so you
you have sinned a lot
you were playing with a 50 year old man
crying can't solve the problem
Hey guys
don't be so surprised
We won't attack you
We're not Yakuza
You should listen to us
Go with him
I have nothing
Follow him
just follow him and work
You'll get paid
you don't have to worry
Let's go
I will forgive you when you have successfully completed your work.
I'm very sorry that it didn't work out
it's my responsibility
Thank you
Yes
we won't bother you
so don't worry
Thank you
she is waiting for you in the drawing room
Come in
nice to meet you
have a seat
Do not be shy
you are very beautiful.
You're Shimako,right?
Please make yourself at home
what should I do tonight?
Tonobe told me that I should just put up with it for one night.
If I tell you what will happen in advance, many people will quit.
the flowers are blooming so beautifully.
Have you eaten dinner yet?
Please prepare a meal for two
Sure
You eat differently than she does.
last time I failed
I think it's better not to tell her in advance this time
I get it.
I'll do that
I tell you
this is really embarrassing
my husband is already dead
I live here with my son Akihiko.
When he was a child, he was a very quiet and intelligent child.
He got lost in the mountains when he was in high school.
he was rescued three days later
he went crazy
These days he seems very crap
But his body wants girl
he seems frustrated
he attacks me sometimes
Other than that, I want to fulfill his wishes.
But I can't handle this
I've been thinking a lot
But It didn't work out
I want to ask you this
Please sleep with him tonight
Please listen to her
You were surprised when I asked you this?
you thought this was very dirty?
It can't be helped
Tonobe used to be a nurse and I met her there.
I sometimes ask her staff
I've never met a beautiful woman like you
I really feel ashamed to ask you for this
I think your parents will be surprised to know this.
I feel sorry for that
I don't care if you refuse this job
Are you hungry?
Let's have meal
Please start
I hope you like it
don't think anything
Please start
I'll do it
I will meet your request
Are you sure?
there is another house
bathroom is there
Your pajama is here
He will come around 9 o'clock, so please talk to him normally.
He is sometime very shy
Thank you in advance
Thank you for your hard work.
Akihiro was there?
He was in my room so I told him to wait in the bedroom.
I am very grateful to her
Mom
Yes
your mother is not here
this is my mother's room
I saw her.
Please get ready
I see.
Hold on
Are you ready?
I'm ready
Why she is not here?
do you hate doing it here?
Come in
thank you for coming Mom
I'm not your mom
don't lie to me
she's made a fake of herself here before
I know the difference between real and fake.
I punished the fake
she was the devil
it's terrible
The devil wants me to stay in this room and never see anyone
You love me, but you're the devil's command, and I'm imprisoned here
I really hate it
I want to kill my mother and eat her body
are you scared of me?
I'm not
Ok then I'll kiss you
Is that enough?
Akihiro
it's very quiet
looks like it's going well
I hope so
They are ok
I'll take a bath with you and wash you
I wash you
I hate taking a bath
Can I suck your boobs?
Go ahead
he thinks I’m his mother and He treated me nice last night
I have the opportunity to meet many men through this kind of work.
But this is the first time I've slept with a man with pure feelings.
I was sad to leave him this morning
I really appreciate you
It is very unusual that he was able to make contact with women quietly.
he was always rough with women
I really appreciate you
do you think his illness will be cured?
You are the first to express such hope.
Madam
I gave TONOBE-san a thank you note for you.
This is the tip for you
Please take this
Takabayashi,
This jade hairpin is said to cost 500,000 yen.
I will sell this soon
If you combine that with my retirement allowance, it will be close to 3 million yen.
I think they will be happy with that
they won't sue you and you will be saved
Do you want to meet Mr. Takabayashi?
Is he here?
Oh you don't know about it.
Come with me
We had a hard time.
he died
he died.
We're in trouble
Don't go in because the police are still there.
Police said that he committed suicide with a hostess in Ginza
I think she killed him
I think an autopsy on the corpse will reveal the results.
I think he was poisoned by her
She's his girlfriend
I feel sorry
she will soon feel better
She doesn't have any worries about aftereffects and there is no problem.
Thank you very much
Please let me know if she feels pain
Police is here
Police?
Come in
I have something I want to ask her when she leaves the hospital.
Are you her mom?
Do you know about name of Tonobe Riki?
I will ask her about it
Take care
Tonobe Riki?
Female?
Takabayashi...
That person has nothing to do with him
The marriage agency she runs has been exposed.
Read this
Asako Yoshida reportedly informed
She once came to our house to invite Shimako
I just remember
Mom
Do you feel pain?
you take a good rest
The doctor says you can leave the hospital soon.
I'm glad it wasn't a big problem.
sorry for worrying you guys
It can't be helped because this is a traffic accident
I should be more careful
I laugh at my stupidity
I feel sorry for him
you don't have to feel sorry for him
I feel sorry for Kyoko who died
she was going to marry him
That's ridiculous
I should have been hit by a truck and died
I think you still have a chance of getting married
After you leave the hospital, please relax in the hot springs.
I wanna see Mikiko
I think it's good over there because the air is good.
I thank you
I haven't done anything to you
you took such good care of us
give me my handbag
Here it is
Open it
The wrapped item is inside.
This?
This is a very expensive hairpin.
This doesn't suit me, so I'll give it to you
this looks very expensive
If I sell this, it will be worth 500,000 yen.
500,000 yen?
Sis
Are you going home?
I was surprised
you didn't care about your surroundings
Police visited her?
How did you know?
the receptionist told me
It seems that Takabayashi was using the company's money illegally.
I am glad she did not marry him.
How's her?
She'll be fine
That's good
I'll see her
do you go to school?
I don't go to school
Mitsuko looks upset
She told me to quit school
I hope you too quit college and become a pimp.
Mom,I was wrong
Please forgive what I did
I'm sorry for the trouble I've caused Mitsuko and Takeshi.
I won't give you trouble anymore
I like this lake since I've seen this first time
I decided to commit suicide at this lovely lake.
No one around me.
I found what was love first time when I was at 30yrs old
I'll feel it at the bottom of this lake
Furukawa!
I'm here
You'd a hard time
You ended up coming here
Here's good place
Yeah, here's memorable place
Stop talking about it
That's too much
I don't mean that
You've left what you have done to this lake
Here's the place where you start your new life
You were born here
Sorry but I read this
This wasn't pasted.
You don't need this
Ok, wanna come to my home?
You need some rest
You guys
Furukawa!
It's been a while
You know her?
Yes I know
So we don't need to introduce her
You're cheeky
You guys know her?
We are introduced about her by aunt
I'll take care of your bag
You want something from me?
Hold on
I don't have any souvenirs in my bag.
It's OK
I hear you were on business trip in Tokyo
I went your home on the way
I worry how you are after you left the company
Did you see my mom?
It's a long way around, but let's see the dunes first.
Great view, isn't it?
So nice
I'll show you more
I'll show you around later if you like
You only know the surface of the lake
Life is hard
there's no end to what you can do if you care enough
Not only you but I do
I hear your wife passed away
She was sick and stayed at hospital all the way
She doesn't need to feel pain anymore
You are terrible
Really
It was hard for me to look at her.
I'm sorry
Forget about this story
Good things will come to you
Life and view are same
In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity.
Don't be discouraged. Cheer up.
They two are a good match.
Of course
You two are a good match.
What?
Finish?
What the hell?
We're not finished yet
THE END