Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kemono no Tawamure / The Frolic of the Beasts (1964)
I can't believe this sun and that sun are the same.
What are you doing?
Get down.
Come in.
You received another letter from her.
Thank you very much.
This smells like a woman.
You are stingy.
Let me smell it.
Cut it out.
Will you go see her as soon as you get out of jail?
Are you envy him?
What's the hell?
What she said?
Tell me.
Shut up.
What's the hell?
Damn it.
I'm only thinking about getting you out of jail.
Sometimes I get very anxious.
Please work hard at the prison until the end.
Please come see me as soon as you get out of jail.
Please come.
I wanna see you.
Please listen to my request.
If you don't like seeing me, you can go home.
I'll clean your clothes and your room.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't come to pick you up.
I can't leave that person behind.
Please understand me.
But I will pick you up at the bridge.
I don't wanna see you but I want to apologize to that person.
I'd rather not have met you.
Is Madam here?
Yes.
This is a gift from our president.
I'll give it to her.
He asked me to give it to her.
Are you new worker?
I'm part time student worker.
A new staff member is here.
Thank you for your work.
This.
It's a very hot day today, isn't it?
Please rest.
Do you still have a job?
I've finished.
Come in.
Serve him a drink.
I'll do it.
This is not what I ordered.
Shall I exchange it?
Don't worry.
It's our fault.
Come in.
That is a very beautiful flower.
Yeah.
Growing flowers is difficult.
Are you into flowers?
I like beautiful things.
That's unusual for young people.
Shall I show you?
This is awesome.
Look at this.
This rose is very beautiful.
Are roses the king of flowers?
Some people call Yoron the king of flowers.
This is the flower called Alba.
This red flower is a hybrid Catria.
This is a very beautiful flower, isn't it?
This is too much for me.
Men like this flower.
The petals of this flower are like a vase.
This is a flower that eats insects.
This is a flower that tempts
It's weird.
You are a coward.
Look at this.
This is awesome.
This is a mysterious flower called Jim.
white flowers are rare.
This is awesome.
If you want one, I'll give you one.
Really?
Don't worry.
Are you also studying at Toa University?
Yes.
President is my senior.
Are you a student of the Faculty of Culture?
I'm a law student.
However, I have read all the books written by my president.
But his writing is very difficult.
He really likes writing.
But I hate it.
His books are very valuable.
It just has rarity value.
Since you are studying law, will you become a judge in the future?
I don't like people judging people.
But why are you studying law?
Laws judge people.
I'm just into it.
Only God can judge humans.
God?
It could be.
I have to go back.
This coffee set is perfect as a gift.
If you want something a little more luxurious, you can find it here.
It's a little expensive, but I think you can afford it.
His wife is nice,right?
I'll have this.
Thank you very much.
Please deliver here.
We'll handle it.
Please.
Thank you very much.
Did you deliver it to your wife? She said she wanted something different.
Whatever.
Let's go out to eat after work.
I want to drink alcohol with young people like you.
I envy you because you have no parents, siblings, or relatives.
I hate people with guarantees.
And you have a lot of money.
My dad left money to me.
But I worry.
No problem.
You can work at out store.
Thanks.
You're 21 and alone.
You are free.
Do you sometimes consider yourself a romantic?
You have a beautifuk future.
You'll only have happy future.
You would not be anxious about your future.
I have.
I'm sometime frustrated.
That's your beauty.
I've lived my life with the wind in my sails.
It's a good thing you can be angry.
So you're saying that I'm an average person.
I'm just envious of your purity.
Give me water.
What are you doing?
Gymnastics?
Radio exercises.
It's a great feeling.
My wife is strange.
I've never seen a woman like her.
She's beautiful.
That's no way to treat a woman your age.
My wife is strange.
She's never been jealous.
Wives are usually jealous.
If you get a wife you will know.
She's not.
She's never surprised.
I've seen her shoot right in front of her, and she'll just lightly turn her head away.
I'm sure your wife is very good at hiding her emotions.
Maybe it's her ego
Nice point of view, good analysis.
That's probably about it.
But you think she does not love me?
She loves me a lot.
I can feel about her love.
She's hiding her emotions.
She pretends to be cool like water.
I'd have sex with a girl in front of her if it would make her heart flutter.
And I have to tell you, I don't hate her.
I'm ashamed to admit it, but...
I don't hate any woman who loves me.
Even if it's my wife.
He's got this new mistress, she's stripper.
She's from Southeast Asia.
He likes tanned women.
He was dating with fisher woman before.
What happened about the nurse?
He was dumped.
I don't understand what he's thinking.
He has a beautiful wife.
You know, no matter how beautiful it is, something's missing.
It could be.
And..she's coming.
Welcome.
The oysters you delivered the other day, I still don't like them.
I'm here to exchange them.
If you had told me, I would have come to exchange them.
I was just coming by.
I'm sorry, sir.
I made a mistake.
It's not your fault.
This is what I want.
This?
It's next to it.
I'll deliver it to you on my way home today.
If it's convenient, you can bring it with you.
My husband took you to the bar the other night?
You've been drinking to talk about me, haven't you?
No way.
Be honest.
He told you I was strange?
He must have a mistress when he'd talk about me.
He's sick.
It's just so sad.
His new girl is a stripper from southeast Asia.
You guys know about it?
You know that, and you're really okay with it?
So what?
I'm used to it.
It's not an insult.
I can't live if I can't feel.
You don't feel jealous at all?
He wants his wife to be jealous.
You want me to be jealous?
You're so nosy.
I've had enough of your nosiness.
Have a drink.
You know I can't drink.
I wanna make you get drunk.
I feel disgusting.
Try it.
What's so good about it?
Just like you like flowers.
You don't understand.
It's better to make a melon or a banana or something.
You're so utilitarian.
Maybe that's what keeps you from devouring him.
I can't understand about you.
You know, I was warned by that man today about your dilettantism.
Who told you?
It's all right for you to be unfaithful.
You don't have to go to the trouble of informing everyone in the shop.
I'll fire him.
You don't have to.
He worries about us.
He's innocent compared to those who whisper about him behind his back.
But he's a bit much for a hired hand.
Don't get upset.
I have to go.
You don't need to worry about what he just said.
Ma'am.
I'm really sorry about today.
But I couldn't keep my mouth shut.
You don't have to worry about that.
Excuse me.
Thanks for the other day.
You probably don't know how funny her is yet, but...
I think today's blinds are a little cooler.
Like this.
She's crazy.
How dare you.
She's not as beautiful as my wife.
She's fool.
I'm sorry.
She's a bit of an exhibitionist.
That's what I like about her.
How dare you.
She's got a way of making love that's... hilarious, and sometimes she gets a little crazy.
I'll get crazy and have sex with her.
Compared with my wife, My wife is too boring.
She's too ordinary.
What do you mean?
It's a wonder you're not tired when you play with her.
Come on, Dad, let's go home.
It's over.
Get dressed.
I don't have to.
She's like that.
I'll leave.
Excuse me, but could you go home and tell my wife I'm not coming home for a couple of days?
That's unusual.
He never told me when he won't back home.
Sorry to tell you.
It's not your fault.
He's just trying to pick on me, as usual.
I'm afraid I tell you.
But you're not going to solve anything if you just suffer.
It can't be helped.
It doesn't solve anything.
It's a maze of suffering with no way out.
I know.
Our  president is completely arrogant.
From our point of view, he's a terrible person.
He doesn't care about you in any way.
He may have lost his youth.
But he played around a lot.
What I can't forgive is the fact that he sacrificed his wife.
He's a terrible person.
Ma'am.
Anyone there?
She sometime is like that.
Cerebral anemia?
Do you have any alcohol?
I'll just have a glass of wine.
Call doctor.
OK.
I'm alright.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to say it.
Don't worry.
Thank you very much.
Koji.
What?
Open the drawer.
You'll find some papers in there.
Read them.
It's all about my husband's women.
About Machiko
Did you ask to do this?
Yes.
I know everything.
But don't ever tell my husband about this.
I'm happy just to know.
It's the only thing that keeps me alive now that he doesn't know.
You must keep it a secret.
If you betray me
I'd die.
How often I am frustrated with that person.
What frustrating and strange days they were.
An unhappy, desperate woman and a carefree man
and me, hot-blooded and sympathetic
I guess I didn't realize at the time that the simple scheme hid a terrible trap
Yamada-san, Kinoshita-san, go to the first ward.
The only abnormality I can think of is some low blood pressure, but that's just my nature.
Dizziness like yours has a strong name: dysautonomia.
Are you experiencing any intense anxiety or worry?
No.
It will go away when you get some rest.
It's not a disease.
Your body is in good health.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting
It must have been hot.
I should have given this to you.
What's this?
I found this.
I'm curious.
Why?
I've been here for two hours now and I didn't even notice.
It's like this fell from the stars.
It doesn't matter.
Throw it away.
How was it?
Doctor said no problem.
I'm old.
You're still young.
But I look at my husband's face, and I think we're both getting older.
Let's not talk about your husband.
It's an uncomfortable subject for me as well.
You're not the only one.
You're not the only one who's unconsciously talking about it?
It's my song.
Can't I sing this song?
You want me to sing in the chorus too?
Do you want me to sing with you?
No way.
It's a cowardly song that's all pride and no courage.
If you fight with your husband, I'll give you any advice you want.
I don't want to hear you complain without a fight.
What are you mad at me for?
What do you want from me?
You're being selfish.
What right do you have to tell me what to do?
What's the hell about it.
Have a seat.
It's too hot.
I'm leaving.
Ma'am.
Shall we visit him tonight?
To where?
Machiko's apartment.
We'll find they are having sex.
It makes you to fight with him.
This is good idea.
No way.
Why not?
Because.
Because if I see it, it's bound to be even worse than what I know from the letters on the paperwork.
You're a coward.
A kid like you wouldn't understand.
You're just too afraid to face reality.
If it makes him upset,It will work.
If I see the look on his face and he doesn't panic, It's all over.
That'd be fine.
Why can't I stay like this?
If I go like this, you won't be harmed.
You're lying.
You can't go on like this.
I can't tolerate lies that have nothing to do with me.
Anyway, I can't stand this grotesque reality.
I want to destroy this grotesque world.
Do you hate him or me?
Both.
It's Tuesday, isn't it?
I'm sure he is visiting that woman.
Why you are here?
Koji.
You are here too.
How did you find here?
I'm sure she appreciates you.
Just shut up and go home.
I think it's counterproductive to ask me to leave with that kind of attitude.
That's not so you.
I wouldn't be able to go home either.
It's a bad idea to bring things to a close at the last minute.
We have to be concerned about her position.
Go home with Koji first.
You're so terrible.
I have been holding back.
I love you so much.
I believed in you.
You're so terrible.
I've waited so long for your heart to come back to me
I love you so much.
You're so terrible.
Please leave now.
Go home with me.
The saint said that man was born to suffer in this world
He also said that man cannot live without making mistakes.
By mistakes, he did not mean that we make mistakes.
It means to hate others, to envy others, to bully others, to fight others.
We all have greed.
This greed is always centered on oneself.
Because you try to push your own greed, you will never find peace of mind.
Your underwriter's name is listed as Yuko Kusakado.
This is the wife of the victim of your disability, is it not?
Yes.
I've never heard of anything like this.
The lady's letter says she wants to take you back because you committed the crime for her own good.
I guess it's called humanitarianism.
The money has arrived.
Give me the note.
You will be taken in by the victim.
You will never make a mistake again against the victim.
If you're even a little nervous yourself, I'd be happy to consider changing underwriters.
Don't worry.
From now on, you will live a life of gratitude.
When the going gets tough, remember your life here and persevere.
You are never to come back here again.
You swear?
I swear.
Please.
Welcome back.
Thank you for everything you've done for me.
I've been waiting a long time for you.
You look so nice.
Thank you.
I'm glad to see you're doing so well.
You're looking better than ever.
A villa?
It's halfway up that mountainside.
I'd like to have a few words with you before we go.
I know you do.
That's what I thought, so I brought you this.
It's a village without a single coffee shop.
You don't care about your house?
About him?
He's at home today. He's eating lunch alone.
That's better than meeting him out of the blue.
Of course, he's very eager for you to come.
He's made himself at home like the Buddha.
There are no mirrors in prison.
Of course I don't need one.
But when I'm getting close to getting out, suddenly I start to worry about my face.
I worry about how I look to humans.
So, as an inmate nears release, he wants not only his number, but his face.
I had no choice but to put a dustpan outside the windowpane and use it as a mirror.
Look.
You've never changed.
There's not a shadow anywhere.
You haven't changed at all.
I'm sorry I never got to visit you.
And the reason I gave in my letter, it's because it's true.
He's too sick to be away from home overnight.
As you can see, he's in a state of flux without me.
I'm sure you are satisfied.
What do you mean by that?
I mean that he's not going to run away from me again.
That's the first thing you were going to say when you came out.
Oh, my God, that's such a horrible thing to say.
If you said that, everything would be so screwed up.
Promise me you won't say that, please.
I didn't mean it like that.
They're talking about us.
I wonder how long we'll be rare.
It's hot day,isn't?
You shouldn't walk around with your eyes down so low.
Going out?
I'm just visiting my parishioners.
You always bring flowers, don't you?
He is.
Welcome back.
I'm glad to see you're doing well.
Come visit me when you get settled.
I've told that monk about you and everything.
He's a very nice man.
He's my confidant.
He immediately agreed to invite you.
I don't like the monk much.
The churchwarden at the prison was a monk.
I didn't like him
Don't talk to me about prison.
Here... here...
There he is.
He's messy.
Clean your face.
He's Koji.
Not Kori but Koji.
Don't you remember him?
Koji.
Hello.
That's strange.
He's been able to say it smoothly from the beginning.
I'll show you around.
Now this greenhouse is where we do our business.
Tokyo Gardening is doing business with us out of kindness for old time's sake.
Actually, we'd like you to help us with this job.
That man is our helper SADA.
It's not that the work is difficult.
It's just the temperature control that's a little tricky.
But I think you're going to love it.
There are still a few.
These flowers.
Cymbidiums?
You gave it to me when I first came to see you.
I'm surprised you remember it.
Koji.
I wonder if you drink water with relish.
Wanna drink?
okay?
Come on, let's go.
I'll show you your room.
Your room is on the second floor.
It's very well-ventilated, so you'll find it cooler than downstairs.
Please come.
The wind from the ocean comes through best in this room.
I was going to get down on my knees and apologize to him, but I couldn't.
I really feel sorry for him.
It's over.
No, it's not.
You've been paying for your sins for three years.
That's another issue.
Just because I've been socially punished doesn't mean I can apologize to him.
He is the one who should apologize to you.
No way.
I must confess, I didn't think he was terribly different.
So the moment I saw him, I suddenly got choked up, and I forgot to say I was sorry.
It's called aphasia.
He understands a lot of what we say.
He just can't speak.
He's forgotten most of the words he speaks.
So it's normal for him to be frustrated, but he's so laid back.
Maybe he's more serious than that.
But it's easy to communicate.
Yuko.
What kind of variety is this?
It sells well as the Kannon flower.
You been in this business long?
This wife taught me everything.
I used to be a fisherman.
You have wife?
She ran away while I was in the army.
Even if you're like your husband here, you still have someone wonderful like his wife.
Kids?
One daughter works at a music factory in Hamamatsu.
She's a troubled girl
What?
Like her mother, she's play girl.
Hey, your tea is ready.
Come on.
You getting used to the job?
Yeah.
We're going for a walk.
How far do you go every day?
There's the Kendo Post Office.
The postmaster's wife makes tea every day and waits for us.
Sometimes I go to the harbor when I'm in the mood.
Let's go for a walk.
We are off.
Ko-chan.
Hold your stick.
You want me to come with you?
It's okay.
She has a hard time.
Ko-chan.
I'm out of talcum powder, but there's some in the bedroom.
Koji.
Don't worry. Come in.
Thank you very much.
You're going to take a bath, right?
Then get in now, because you're wasting fuel.
Don't be shy, go ahead.
You should close that door, so the wind doesn't blow through.
I forgot... what happened to your college transcripts?
I sent it out from jail.
I'm sorry.
Do you plan to work here for the rest of your life?
Let's take a bath together.
He's an idiot...
He wants to take a bath with me and you.
I thought you just took a bath.
Hey.
What's the hell?
Welcome.
Oh Kimi.
When did you come back?
I came back on the 4 o'clock boat.
I've been on vacation for a week.
You're growing up again.
Have a drink.
I got a bonus so let's have fun together.
Give us a lot of beers.
I'd like to make a toast to you.
Who's him?
I don't know.
No?
He's just poor boy.
Do you work at Kusagado Greenhouse?
My dad works there.
You are Sada's daughter?
Yes, I'm Kimi.
Let's drink with us.
You have to put it in my mouth.
Don't mess Up Your Mouth.
Ko-chan!
I want you to accompany me on my walk today.
I don't feel comfortable on my own.
The three of us are going on a picnic to Otaki today.
It's far.
I think we have about half a day.
Can you walk?
I can walk.
We'll have to be adventurous.
The only thing to see in this village is Otaki Falls.
I know.
Otaki, it's a big waterfall.
Not Ogaki, Otaki.
You are stupid.
Let's take a picture of the three of us together.
three of us?
With Otaki in the background.
I'm in the middle.
How I wish we could stand side by side like this at the grave.
I don't want to stay with you in heaven either.
Do you know who in the world out of the three is sacrificing the most?
Do you know what sacrifice is?
No, sacrifice is a word.
It's such an abstract word.
We're doing a test right now.
Do you know what sacrifice is?
You are stupid.
This.
Do you know what kiss is?
Say kiss.
Don't you understand?
I'll tell you.
It's like this.
Stop it....
Don't make him suffer.
I don't.
I don't want to be your tool.
You've been a tool from the start.
You like me,right.
Why do you laugh?
Stop laughing.
He has a face like this.
He's laughing.
I'm leaving.
Why?
I can't keep your company any longer.
You are after all the same kind of people as this man.
All you care about is your own well-being.
You think I'm a slave.
You think of yourself as a victim.
It's ridiculous.
Hold on.
Ko-chan.
Hi.
I've been waiting for you.
We're all going swimming in Urayasu.
Wanna come?
Sea...
My dad is coming.
See you.
Welcome.
Yes.
Where's master?
He'll come back soon.
Did my daughter say something to you?
No.
She's nice.
She's always playing.
No way.
Anyone want this ukulele?
I want.
This is my treasure.
I want to give it to someone who I love.
Really?
Yeah.
The person who gets it that wants you for themselves.
Really?
You swear?
Yes.
I'll get it.
Stop it.
Stupid.
I don't want to give you my body.
Let's go.
Hold on.
You want me to give you the ukulele?
I'll be waiting for you in the pines over there tonight around 7:00.
I hear you are virgin.
Yes.
You're pure boy.
You think so?
I mean, it's so rare these days.
I've been exposed to all kinds of dirty relations between men and women since I was a little boy.
My father brought his Mistress to live in the same house with my mother.
He was crazy.
He was like an animal.
I was so frustrated.
All men are animals.
You're too.
I'm not.
How are you different?
I'm at least a human being.
That's because everyone thinks they're human.
It's just that humans have a sense of sin, but beasts don't.
I don't know if it's that hard to understand.
Do you like me?
You know I do.
Do you?
I like you.
Liar.
I'm not lying.
You like the wife at the green house.
I know.
I hate her.
I know you lover her so much.
But I don't care.
It's not my business.
Hello?
Hi.
It's hot, isn't it?
Come in.
You don't feel hot?
You're drooling.
I hear you were play boy before.
I heard you were very popular with the girls.
Welcome.
Don't make fun of him.
I'm leaving today.
Did you see your dad?
No.
He is in green house.
I don't wanna see him.
Why?
Is Koji here?
He's gone to the temple.
What do you want?
Kochan.
Fumi is here to say good bye.
I asked her to have lunch together but she had no time.
I'll give you this.
I told you.
I only give this to a person who I love.
Take care of this.
This is my soul.
Take a bath.
You smell bad.
Don't get out.
Stay here.
You know why I'm here?
I put a pin in her hand.
I can't stop thinking about that look on your face afterwards.
You thought I was jealous of you, didn't you?
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't get jealous.
I just hate such a rude girl.
I use a pin to stick.
Just like you used spanner.
Don't talk about that.
I've changed my mind now.
Same here.
You don't have to.
I put on sin so you wouldn't have to do anything you regret.
You put on sin?
What's the hell?
I didn't ask for any of that.
You're just being selfish.
What's the matter with you?
You think you're the only one who can take the blame.
You should have gone to jail, too?
Are you trying to atone for your sins with me?
It's impossible.
You can't hold back about the life in a jail.
I envy you.
You've paid for your sins.
I don't know what to do.
I want to die thinking that I will never stop feeling like this.
There's no reason for you to die.
You're just trying to make a living taking care of that man.
You don't understand anything, do you?
Come in.
It can't be helped.
I'm not good.
Come in.
You smell like black man.
You hate it?
I like it.
What's wrong.
Let me come in.
You can't.
You told me cum in.
You care about him?
We can't do this.
You are coward.
Yuko?
I'm here.
What's the matter with you?
Cold...
Cold.. it's cool.
Cool.
I wanna sleep here.
It's cool.
I want to sleep here.
Want to sleep here?
Shall I lay out the bedding?
I want to sleep here.
Here you go.
For Tokyo Gardening,
Kannon Bamboo is 68
Ananas rosea 68
Gomu décoras is 1,2,3,4...
Kochan.
Please deliver these to the temple again.
I'll take care of it.
Gomu décoras is?
It's always hot.
Thank you.
They are sleeping together.
In one room?
Her husband is crazy.
Really?
Hello.
I'm sorry about all this.
I've been meaning to have a long talk with you.
If you're not busy, why don't you come by?
I'll make some tea.
You must have a lot on your mind.
If you have a problem, it's better to say it
The soul is shy.
It huddles in the dark and hates the sunlight.
They're like perishable sea urchins.
Let me tell you something.
You're troubled by Lady Yuko, aren't you?
I know.
It can't be helped.
Everyone in the village is blaming you and her.
Some of them are even talking about the ugly baby she's going to give birth to.
But don't worry about that.
Let those who want to say it.
You're more troubled by the voice of your own conscience than by the accusations of others.
Of course you are.
But it's noble.
It proves you have a conscience.
That's why they call it "suffering equals bodhi".
I've heard that story a lot from a church priest in prison.
Then let me ask you.
Do you want to be an animal?
Or do you want to live like a human being?
I think I'm human.
Yeah.
If you don't want to be an animal, you'll have to leave this village.
You can do it.
Kochan.
Can't you sleep?
Mr. Sada, how do you know a typhoon is coming?
I can tell from the birdsong.
You can tell from the birdsong?
I've heard stories about predicting the weather from the morning grill.
I've never heard of bird calls.
I can tell from the starlight.
Because I was fisherman.
Kochan.
It must be hard for you.
Your husband is crippled.
I'm used to it.
Your business..Sada and...
Koji works hard.
I hear he's nice.
I envy you.
We all talk about you.
The monk is worried about you.
He worries if you don't hear anything bad
She's here to watch our flowers.
I'm too busy.
Bring him to take a walk today.
Don't worry.
I will come again.
He's used to it.
Put him shoes on.
Take care.
It's hot,isn't it?
I don't understand you.
Why do you keep smiling like that and tormenting me and your wife?
You hate me,right?
Why don't you just say it out loud?
You're willing to say what's convenient, but when it's inconvenient, you blame it on your illness and keep it deliberately vague.
Right?
You's making fun of me.
I've never seen anyone as obnoxious as you.
You don't even want to look at me. You think I'm unforgivable, don't you?
Right?
Hot.
Hot?
It's hot.
You're playing a monster.
You're acting very well.
But you know what, I'm gonna peel that monster face off your face.
I'm getting understanding.
Your death won't bring me and your wife together.
And as long as you're here, she and I will never be together.
It's your conspiracy to create this weird environment.
We can no longer kiss without guilt.
That guilt turns the taste of a kiss to ash.
You set us up so we'd be guilt-bound about everything.
That's what you wanted for so long.
Revenge on us.
Right?
Hey listen!
You don't have to look so serious.
The truth is, you're happy with how you are.
You're having a wonderful vacation, continuing the glamorous life of the past and the womanizing that has gone out of control.
You enjoy laughing at our suffering.
That's the laughing.
You're trying to drag us all down into a big, dark hole with your laugh.
What do you hate about me?
Tell me.
It's my fault I picked up a wrench in the hospital yard?
I thought you left that there beforehand.
Your plan was nearing completion when you moved into the bedroom next to mine.
Me and your wife sleeping together in front of you.
If I have sex with her in front of you, that's what you want.
But I can't do that.
I don't want to become the beast you want me to be.
She was about to be the beast but she couldn't.
You knew this and seduced us.
You knew there was nowhere to run, and you hunted us down.
That's what makes this so much fun for you, isn't it?
I’m better than you.
I go to catch the prey, but you just wait for the prey to be hooked.
What do you want?
What do you really want?
Go home.
Go home?
I know, I know.
But first, you're gonna tell me the truth.
Until then, I'm not letting you leave.
I wanna die.
You wanna die?
What should I do?
Tell me.
Ko-chan.
I hope the greenhouse is okay.
I wanna die.
He's sleepwalking.
Ko-chan.
He says he wants to die.
I feel like I'm in a cave.
It's like we're trapped in a cave with no way out.
It was a mistake for me to come here.
Why?
No, you don't.
You're holding him in your arms, and you're asking me out.
Don't talk to me like that.
I was just worried about you getting out of jail.
I've had enough of those excuses.
You've had your fun in this weird life.
You have no intention of leaving him and escaping this darkness.
Besides, I'm sure he'd love to see us embrace in front of his own eyes.
I can't take it anymore.
I have to get out of here.
I don't want to turn into a beast and chase you around.
Are you leaving without me, Ko-chan?
Tell me.
Are you leaving without me?
Don't you love me?
We love each other.
Was that a lie?
You didn't love me.
If you love me, please don't leave this house.
I can't live without you.
Stay like this.
Isn't it bad?
If I stay here, I have no choice but to die myself or kill him.
Don't say that.
Please.
what are you going to do?
I will make his wish come true.
I ended up giving that guy what he wanted.
Oh yeah,
He expected me to be sentenced to death.
Thank you for coming all the way from far away.
I am KIBE, a church worker at Sendai Prison.
I've been expecting you.
The bones of Koji Umemiya.
He had no relatives, so it is a blessing that you have taken him in.
He was a poor young man.
I hear you've already built a grave for him.
Yes.
That's because Yuko asked me to do so.
Is Yuko the girlfriend who received a life sentence?
Yes.
Have you met her?
The girls are in prison in Tochigi.
So I haven't.
I see.
The morning after the typhoon, I was tidying up the garden.
It was a terrible storm.
Your greenhouse was safe?
No, sir. We didn't sustain any damage.
That's good to hear.
Are we going out together?
My husband died last night.
Really?
I killed him.
You told me that if I didn't want to become a monster, I had to leave this village.
But I finally couldn't leave.
And I had no choice.
I hope you understand.
I just want you to understand
We're going to the police now.
We wanted to ask you to come with us.
When this young man was sentenced to death, Mrs. Yuko received a letter from the prison.
She asked me to erect our three graves side by side.
She wants to build her grave as a counterfeit while she lives.
Yes.
The villagers were very much against it.
The graves of the deceased husband and wife would be enough.
They say it would defile the cemetery to put up the grave of that young man who was guilty of murder.
She sent me this photo asking for a grave to be built like this photo.
Because of how pathetic her wish seemed
When the young man was executed, I had the three of them built graves.
As a matter of fact, Umemiya had asked me to do something about the graves before her execution.
He knew that she wished to have their graves built.
He asked that his grave never be built.
I beg you not to place the three graves side by side.
Please throw my bones into the Izu Sea.
I ask you to smash them to pieces and scatter them in the currents of the sea.
Umemiya didn't want to expose the traces of his cursed life to people's eyes.
The idea of losing his remains to the sea is very typical of him.
I was also troubled by it, since it was said by a man who is now trying to become a Buddha.
I listened to him as he was, thinking that there was no need to disturb Umemiya's mind at this point.
I was actually relieved when you were able to build his grave here.
At least the Buddha cannot be happy without a grave.
Thank you for all your hard work.
That's it.
Grass management is difficult.
These are magnificent graves.
Now the young man can go to heaven in peace.
I will worship him.
Please.
THE END