Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
What did you say?
Who is worse, those in prison or those on the outside?
Of course it's worse for the people out there.
I have to back to work.
See you
The biggest problem I have with life here is the lack of women.
I'm way too popular with the ladies out there.
It can't be helped
A Fighting Dog (Inu/Dog Series #2)
Get out!
You will be punished later for this
Will you protect me?
By the way
You are about to release from prison
Yes I am
I see
If you want a tattoo, come to me
Is there anything good?
My wife will take care of you
What the hell?
Are you crazy?
Ok that's fine
I'm an idiot, so don't call me an idiot.
My wife loves handsome men
Damn it
Bros!
What are you doing to me?
I feel so good
What are you doing?
Get out!
Why should I leave when he is taking a bath?
Get out anyway!
You can take a bath
Enjoy having a bath!
Here it is
Enjoy your meal
We had a hard time
It was Nice bath
You all look difficult.
Get your meals.
My meal is small
This is bigger
Don't we have a raffle for the meal?
What the hell you are saying about?
There is no such logic here.
I eat anything whenever I want
I'm starving after working
Get lost from here
I can't see the rice because it's not well ventilated
What the hell you are!
Damn it!
We are eating
Hey, you are good singer
Would you like to introduce an entertainment agency when you are released from prison?
Thank you very much
You shouldn't look at them too much
He was trading 1 box for 500 yen
What the hell?
Why do you guys hit me because I'm not doing anything
Because your face is very easy to hit
No way!
Why do you hit him once a day?
If you hit him I will fight you guys
Are you sure to fight with me?
Just bring it!
Fucking kid!
Stop it...
Bros!
Stop it
This is for you
Thank you
Why did you get caught by the police?
I was operating a fraudulent taxi.
I had a problem with a customer for a fee
What is your relationship with Kamoi?
I have nothing to do with him
Because he has a strong fight
So I like him
Hey stop fighting!
Stop !
Get back to work
Hey stop fighting!
What are you guys doing?
I went crazy because there are no women here
You guys should get together in the locker
Do you preach us again?
126!
Yes
Good
I'm 256
Am I OK?
Good
Hey come here
Hey 117
You
What? me?
What the hell this?
What's this?
Today we were made a lot tougher
But we were only extended from prison
That's no problem
You helped me today as well
What?
This is a cigarette
Did you buy this from Komori?
I didn't.
I got it in secret
How can I make a fire?
Use here
You have a good idea
It tastes good
Really?
What's wrong?
Koichi
You are good man
There is a smoke
Give me it
Thanks
You can smoke too
Please make it
Smoke it
Bros
We should say good bye soon
If you are out of jail, do your best
Thank you
Please come visit me when you are out of jail
We're waiting for you
I will go if I feel like it
Please come
I want to get a pistol
Ok.
Leave it to me
I know many vendors
Out of jail...
How many days am I left?
I want to go out soon
Be quiet!
It's none of your business
Good singing
Be quiet!
Stop doing it
Look at me, girl
Be quiet!
I want to write a love letter for her
She's so nice
You follow the rules of the prison
Be quiet!
She's so nice
Make a smile for me
I really like her!
Omachi!Omachi!
You're Omachi!
When did you get out of jail?
I was released from prison long ago
Shut up!
I had a lot of trouble because of you
I am very angry with you.
Don't get angry with me
Look at my car
Did you buy it?
Yes I did
I hope you have reviewed me.
Let's go
What the hell you are doing?
She's our woman
Omachi!
Don't call her casually
She'll be my wife.
Get out from here
I wonder if my face is easy to be beaten
Bros, help me soon
Watch out!
It was close
Outside the prison is really dangerous
It ’s safer to be in jail, is n’t it?
Let's go
Congratulations
Who are you?
You are crazy
Please go first
You seem to have been very popular in jail
Were you in the jail?
I have never seen you
Why you know me?
You're so popular
I was on Asahi newspaper?
I came to pick you up at the order of Mr. Komori
Komori?
What is he doing now?
He works in the construction industry
He said he would bring you
There are a lot of sake and women
I reject it
I have a liquor allergy.
And I am too popular among women
See you then
Hey cut it out
Ok, I'll follow you
Get in the car
Don't order me.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Open the door for me
OK
Get in the car
I've learned in the jail
See you then
Wait!
Run!Run!Run!
Can I play this?
Bang bang!
Long time no see
How are you?
How have you been doing?
Oh bros!
Long time no see
I was playing
You are working here
Who is he?
You came at the right time
He's a newspaper man.
I'm Sasaki from the Kansai newspaper
We feature violence cases
What do you mean?
A feature
I see I see
He was victimized by a gang, but he won't tell me anything.
I just got injured in this workplace
I know a gang hit you
I know what's on your mind
No way
He said no.
so Go home
But I know
I haven't had a long time with him so I want to talk to him
Please go home
I see
I'll visit you again
What happened to the wound
I was waiting for you
I'm really happy that you came
That's too much
My dead mother said
Use polite words for those you respect
Did your mother die?
Yes
She wrote to you
She ate too much and died a few days after I was released from prison
She ate too much ?
Your mother wasn't very clever
Because it ’s my mother
This is a really dirty story
Tell me about it
I see that she died with her body straightened
Doctors and neighbors say she died of stomach cancer
They all said so
I told them she didn't die of stomach cancer
She died upright, I said.
and they said I was crazy
They all said so
It's the name of the disease called stomach cancer
Oh I see.
I misunderstood
Is it the name of the illness
Oh ouch!
What did you do with the injury?
I went to get my wife back
Then they attacked me
You can ask your boss to help
My boss went to work somewhere else
He left the car
I want to work but now I can't because I have scratches
I am really in trouble
I will work for you until you heal
What should I do with my wife?
I'll get her back
You can't.
They are too strong
I want you to back her...but
They are strong so much?
Yes they are.
And they have pistols
What?
Pistol?
Real one?
I can't wait to go
This bar is a bar based on the freedom of love
It is 450 yen per hour
If you go from love to marriage and then divorce three hours later, that's your choice.
Be quiet
I'm sorry that the noise around me has inconvenienced you.
Then I will come to the place you have designated.
I wear a dark gray suit with a white rose on my chest.
My name is Nishiguchi
We deal with all kinds of women.
Order whatever you like
OK I get it
I'll visit you soon
See you then
Be quiet while I'm on the phone.
You are not educated
Machiko,Let's go
Me?
I don't want to pretend to be female student.
I was hit last time
I'm already 30
What the hell you are talking about?
Say you are ex female student
Let's go for earn money
What the hell, boss?
Do you properly report your sales?
Yes I do
Your sales ledger is fraudulent.
How did you know?
You idiot
If you've done something wrong, be honest about it.
I'm sorry I did it
What?
Tell me
I bought this ring and I put in gold teeth.
This?
You idiot
Is it this back tooth?
Yes
Don't get carried away
A man want to meet you
Give me a light
You have come here
You asked me to come here
You said you were asked by Komori to pick me up but what is your relationship with him?
He has something to do with my father
Your small business partner?
Ok I get it.
I know there is a woman called Machiko here
I'm here to get her back
You want her back?
Her husband is like my bros
I feel sorry that his wife has run away
Get her back
Wait
Boss
Is he Kamoi,right?
He wants us to back her
Release her
What?
Now!
You help her to return home
I get it
Wait
What can I do for you?
Sales are not good.
We're doing well but It can't be helped
You should work harder
If you say so...
Earn more!
Yes sir
Don't take time for one woman.
You return or not?
We return
You're a man who knows what he's talking about.
Apart from this case, I want a pistol
What?
We can't
I've brought her
Oh this handsome man is here to pick me up
Your husband is waiting for you
I don't like him now
Let's go
Long time no see, Kamoi bros
What the hell
You are using this woman to do business.
I don't mean that.
She got a cold, so I took care of her
We'll return her.
Don't come here anymore
I know
Your husband is stupid, and you too
Because I've been with him
Why do you laugh?
I was waiting for you
Please get in the car
Please get on the front seat.
In other countries, only prostitutes and dogs ride in the back seat.
Please get in the car
I want to go with you
We don't need you
Go home
What do you mean?
Bros!
I want to go with you
See what I want
Can you go now?
Your driver today is more handsome than usual,right?
Yes.
You look like a foreigner
I think so.
I look like a foreigner
I'll drive fast
You are so mean.
You should give me train fee at least
Shall we go for a drink together?
Oh you
This is your train fee
Thanks.
But I have nothing to do with gangs
Never mind.
Let's go
2000 YEN?
It costs a lot
She is so nice.
I really love her. Mimoza inn
2000 YEN?
This is real 2000 YEN
You know what.
I got 1000 yen, so you are twice handsome than I
No way, he is 5-10 times handsome more than you
Wait
She's your wife
Yes, but I have promised you
You take care of my wife after you leave from prison
This is very democratic.
What the hell you are talking about?
Give me, I use this for pistol
You're so mean
You don't like me?
I does not matter whether I like or not
I like pistols more than women
I can't live without pistol
Where can we find a pistol...
Oh, I have to go
Where are you going?
You know where I can get pistols,right?
Don't pretend you don't know
You have?
What?
Do you have money?
Are you kidding me?
I have this much
200000yen?
No
20000?
2000?
That's right
Are you kidding me?
It costs 30,000 to 50,000 wholesale and 100,000 retail.
Can I get a pistol at cheap price?
I'm sorry to say that you've become idiot after you sent to prison
I'm sorry
Why not use the funds to gamble?
I believe you'll win
Bet on it as I sign.
That's fake
Don't be loud
I will send you a sign in secret.
Bet on it as I sign.
Let's do it
Bet,Bet,Bet
Pay it,Pay it,
Pay it,
Ok bed it
I'll give it a shot.
Are you sure?
Take it!
Oh damn it
Get together, guys
Listen to me
3 meals with room, 850yen
Do you want work?
850yen for work with 3 meals and room
What do you think?
Get in the car
I want work
We don't need a man like you
I know a man who work hard
Who? bring here
This man
I see.
He looks better than you
Get in the car
You sure for 850yen?
Don't complain.
Get in the car now
Ok, we close
Thanks
This was easy money
Get off the car
Thanks.
You just gathered these guys?
It was hard
Thanks
I will take you over 8 guys
8 guys are not enough
We need 20 guys for the contraction work
I'll bring more tomorrow
Don't worry
Come here
Come here now
What are you doing?
I paid 350yen per person.
Two escaped yesterday and three the day before yesterday.
You are not in control of the situation.
It might be so
But Someone could be working behind the scenes.
They may be able to hook you up with a better deal than you'll find here.
You think too much
If we lose one person, we won't be able to meet the construction deadline.
Our credibility will suffer.
I think someone is trying to take our jobs and our turf.
You think too much
I will find some more tomorrow
So don't worry.
Let's go
1.2.1.2
You are doing your best at exercise
Do you like someone else?
What are you saying?
I'm just on a diet
That's good for you
What can I do for you?
I just happened to stop here
A beautiful woman lives here, right?
I need more detail
She works in a place called Cabaret Manhattan
She has clear skin and has a nice figure
That person is like an actress
Oh I know her
She lives upstairs
Thanks
Wait
She's not here now
She's not here?
She's out for work
To where?
Hannan Branch of HOKO Bank
At bank?
What is her name?
Yukari Marizawa
What a good name
Let's go
Oh I found her
Hello?
How are you?
You know what
If you want to make a deposit, please fill out the deposit form and come with your seal.
You are so cold.
We are not here to deposit
I want to talk to you
No private conversation is allowed during work.
What?
We shouldn't have a conversation with her, right?
It can't be helped
I'll come back to the bar tonight
Let's go home together
Thanks
I'm busy tonight
That man is waiting for you?
Don't talk about that
It's OK
You shouldn't be with a man like that
I think you can play with other men
Thank you for your advice
Lend me some money
What's wrong?
You had better go to work early
I need money
You can go
How much you have?
I have 3 yen
Stupid.
Give me more
Damn it.
Now she's waiting for me
I have an idea.
Why don't you pawn your suit?
Stupid.
Dressing is very important
This is, after all, a legend from the olden days.
You can't understand even if you talk to you
I can't sell my suits
How do you prepare the money?
Freedom is really hard
I'd better be in jail
How many you have?
1.2.3
9yen
9yen is not enough
I want to be energetic enough to have a fight
Bros
I can sell the car.
I don't even have the money to buy petrol so
Stupid.
That is important for you
I will break up with you when I get a pistol
So keep the car
Thanks
It's so hot here and I'm going crazy
If I had my wife here, she would make money
She doesn't come back for about five days after leaving home
Tabako is gone
Where are you going?
To bank
Do you rob a bank?
I came to make a deposit
I want to deposit 1 yen
Ok I'll take care of it
please wait a little bit
I make a passbook for the first time in my life
I need money to date you
Take your time and do your job.
That dude
Hey you!
I met you in a rare place
Get out of my way
I need to talk with him
You bastard
Calm down
Help me
Let's go outside with me.
Let's solve the problem
Ok
Wow! Pistol!
This is cheap
My homemade ones are better.
Performance is pretty good
Please fix the problem with this deal.
Move him to the far side
That's as it should be.
But I don't know if this really works
This is a heavy trigger
I can only shoot one shot while my opponent has two shots
But This is all right
Take it
Thanks
See you
Wait
We have another problem
What's that?
Don't forget
That man's wife
I returned her because you told me to return
She is his wife so
She is my subordinate
I left her the bar job
I want you to solve this problem
That's a very reckless request
I'm saying right
I owe you a debt.
If I don't return her I have an idea
What kind of idea?
Return that pistol
No way
Damn it!
Ok!
I feel bad.
I will follow your request
Ok I made up my mind.
I want you to supervise the construction site
I'll pay you a lot
So many good and bad things in life
I wonder What is Yukari doing now?
It's too hot
Hey
Are you Dokanshi?
Wait
What are you doing here?
I quit my job in jail and work here
Did you do something wrong and get fired?
This is what I mean when I say that like attracts like.
As you walk around I remember the prison
What's wrong?
I'm the director here. Greater than you
So be careful
Damn it
Go for it
Oh it's too hot
What's wrong?
Are you OK?
Why are you working here?
What?
Don't take a break without permission
Work hard!
I reduce your salary
It's dangerous to work someone you don't know
Dangerous things will happen soon
Anyway we are short of manpower
A man named Kamoi is a very useful man
You like him?
He againsted you in jail
He is a very gutsy man
I see
However, your dog may bite your hand.
Please be careful
He likes Yukari
Thank you for your kindness
Hey!
Come on!
Go straight and turn right and the car will be waiting
Wait
Go!
Kamoi-san!
They are running away
Catch them!
Wait!
Get in the car!
Damn it
I have seen him before
Hey!
What the hell you did it!
I'm sorry.
I won't run away next time
You are stupid
Why did you try to escape?
Don't look down us
Do you guys have a job but have any complaints?
You guys also have a place to sleep
Salary is not 850 yen
But The take-home pay is only 350 yen
You guys are at least paid
Accommodation charges will be deducted from your salary
Are you making fun of us?
Your job is as simple as carrying stones
Wait
Who supports you
tell us!
I have no idea
You?
They don't know
The car was parked.
I have seen him before
He was at the Shirayurikai
What?
You know him?
He looked a lot like him, I just said.
I may have made a mistake
Listen.
Reduce your salary
I don't do such a terrible thing
We will provide you with food and accommodation information but Salary payment is postponed
I work for them because I hear I get paid right.
You bastard
It's no wonder they want to run away
Because the salary of 850 yen is 350 yen
They haven't heard that accommodation and meals are deducted
kamoi
Very thin bed and poor food
I understand that you all want to run away.
Shut up!
If you don't want them to run away, treat them better.
If so, no one will run away
You guys think about that
Why do you guys keep quiet
Go back work!
Where are you going
It's none of your business
Follow me
Can you let him say what he wants to say?
Why not use a whip for them
I know
Don't get carried away
Oh you
Is my leg injured okay?
You are good at speaking
You made one mistake
What?
The company pays 1200 yen per person
1200yen?
He pinches 350yen from 1,200yen
You are such a pathetic man working for him.
What?
Say again
I can say as many times as I want
You are a really embarrassing man
I did a weird job
I'm really upset?
Do you quit your job?
I still have something to do.
About you too
Can I play with you tonight?
I'm playing with you now
I mean, on the bed
Don't get angry with me
I have never slept with a woman since I was out of jail
There are many women in Japan
You have no mood
I'm an honest man
But my mother is with me now
Oh your mother is with you?
She will be back in a few days
You should take good care of your mom
I have no mother
I went to jail because I got into a fight with a group of DAIKO who tried to destroy my mother's grave.
I see.
You're so sweet
I'm glad you understand me
I want a drink
You drink too
I can't forgive that dude
I was waiting for you
You back home late
Please eat this
I've been drinking a lot
You got a pistol?
I finally got it
Good for you
I can't live without this
By the way, what your husband do now?
He is a taxi driver now
I was worried about his work
He looks like an idiot but he's pretty smart
He contacted the police and took him home for free
He's so smart
In addition, he was allowed to eat for free at the police
I think he's really smart
He might think that way because he's stupid
He's back
Oh right
Why did he knock on the door
Come in
I'm Gamo
Why you've come here?
What's wrong?
I'm angry with your attitude.
So I can't sleep
Can you go out with me?
Sure
This is a very quiet place
By the way.
I hear You were dumped by Yukari
I didn't want to get in the way of taking care of his mother
She has no mother.
She's lonely
I see
I guessed her weakness
Actually Yukari is Komori's woman
I see. His woman
So Komori is his mother
It can't be helped
The only way to get her is to kill  Komori
I would not want to rough them up like that.
Love is free.
She will approach me later
It is guaranteed by the Constitution
I am confident
You are confident
I can support you
What you said at work is correct
That man is so black-hearted.
kamoi
If you kill him, that organization will be ours
We can share the benefit
You think very well
He is more black-hearted than Komori
You are also pinned 350 yen
You make me kill him.Then you call me the police.And you get Yukari-san
I know everything what's on your mind
What?
You are trying to kill him and get even greater profits
You really have a bad personality
I will break up with KOMORI after the deal
It doesn't matter to me what you and KOMORI are like
Anyway
You are good at shooting.
Can I borrow it?
Light?
I will always reimburse you for any damage to the lighter.
Then see you
Are you out of home?
Are you out with your mom?
I'll visit you again
He's stupid
Word hard!
Humans work better than machines.
Yes you are right
I want to talk with you.
So come to locker
Choose what you like
This is so great
It's same type of mine
How did you get this?
Somewhere in south
You can use this if you clean up
I used to sell these, but had to stop because of a police investigation.
There is no one else to give it to but you.
You are so kind
But I would like to hear your terms of exchange.
Can you kill Gamo?
That's what I thought
I need to say, I like to play pistols but don't like to kill people
Killing people is not worth my job.
If you kill Gamo, I will leave to manage the night bar to you
If I kill Gamo, I know you will kill me
You all have the same idea.
Gamo asked you?
I have no idea
You might as well kill him yourself.
You have many henchmen.
You can use your pistol better than GAMO.
You kill him, you free the girls in the club too.
You are so kind
I don't want a used woman.
I decline it
What did you say!
I only keep our first promise.
And moreover about Gamo
He also love Yukari
So watch out him
Bring Gamo
Listen, 5 guys escape
5 guys
When I give you the signal, run and run.
Don't be panicking
I get it
1,2,3,4 bills
Work hard!
They are escaping!
Catch them!
Wait!
Leave it to me
You damn it!
You should hide!
What the hell?
3 people for now
Oh they are coming!
Wait!
Hurry up!
Damn it!
Oh my god
What the hell!
You are fucking dude!
Don't get violence to me
Boss
This guy
Bring him
Me?
There's no one but you
Bring them too
I will take care of this guy
Yes sir
Come here
What are you doing to me?
I was just asked by someone
Who asked you?
I can't tell
I can't breath.
Let me go
Oh you
He's just henchman
The master is elsewhere.
I tried to ask him for it!
Why you killed him?
I tried to stop him
I think KAMOI is doing this.
Kamoi?
What's wrong?
I heard gun sounds
He was leading them.
Kokichi
Kokuchi
Say something
He's died
You look peaceful.
You're stupid
Who killed him?
I ordered.
Do you have anything to complain about?
He had nothing to do with it
You shouldn't have killed him
You used him to escape workers
What?
You've changed your mind?
A friend today may turn against you tomorrow
I definitely didn't take advantage of him.
Do you think I won't fight back against you people?
I can fight you at any time!
Bring it on!
I hate the guy who used him
I work here until I find the guy
Don't pretend you are great
Shut up!
He gave me the cigarette he was hiding in his underwear
I'm very sorry
I hear Kokuchi was died
You're down in the dumps.
No way.
I'm so upset
You keep quiet?
Yes, I'm just looking
Your nerves must be completely paralyzed.
You don't seem to be human
Shut up!
My nerves are different from you
Sing good!
Do you remember me?
You drink a lot tonight
I am mad for the first time in a long time.
What happened?
What?
What do you think of me?
I don't think I hate you
So you mean you love me
I'm going to your house tonight
Did your mother go home?
She returned this morning
She boarded the plane for the first time in her life
Oh by plane
I think your mother will be very happy.
You did good job
You did something really good
Please enter as it is not locked
Thank you
Have you been waiting for me?
Come in
Have a seat
I hear you are very respectable.
Me?
You are different from me
Don't say that
I seriously think so
You are Komori's woman, right?
Right?
Don't pretend you don't know
You deceived me
If you're a man I'm hitting you
I didn't want to fool you
He told me to keep you in his group
I don't want to hear your excuse
You thought I was surprised about komori?
I like you regardless of him
Are you shedding tears?
I want to apologize to you
It's too late
My friend was killed by him
My friend had a really bad time
I want to get revenge for him
Damn it!
It's already morning
I will fight Gamo and Komori from now on
Don't go.
It's danger
You should run away from Osaka
I can't
I have a relationship with you so I have to fight with him
I have never escaped in my life
What will happen to me if you fight him?
I have no idea.
Up to you
I see.
I'll be free
Yes that's right
I hate him so I fell in love with you
You lair
It's up to you.
Don't look at me like that.
I fell in love with you
He has something to do with other gangsters.
Do you think about it later?
They will revenge you
I don't think I'm after it.
Even if they attack me, the fact is that KOKUCHI is dead.
I need more pistol bullets
It can't be helped
One pistol bullet is enough for me.
Good
See you then
Wait
What?
Please back home safe
I don't know what will happen
pistol bullets!
It's match!
This is enough
bet
Hey! where's Komori?
He's outside
You should bet here
You're not good at gambling
That's right
How is it?
You're the winner
Ok got it
You lost
Shut up!
You wanna play?
I hate card games like this
I like games like this
What the hell
Kokuchi is my friend
Who's kokuchi?
He was killed by Komori
I want to kill him but first of all I will attack you guys
Why you are here?
Don't get in the way!
You can save time
You help me
Anyway thanks
Here we go!
Wait!
They are bullshit
Did you see my ability?
You run away somewhere
I'll be back.
What you will do?
I'll beat Komori and Gamo
But before doing it
Yukari?
How do you know?
I am a newspaper reporter
You like her,right?
I'll support you
You're so kind
But don't worry
Don't kill them, Ok?
You're so kind again
I don't want to go back to jail anymore
You should go
See you
Don't tell the police until my work is done
Take care
What?
Kamoi kills komori
Komori kills Kamoi, so we are left
I love you from the beginning
You seem to have a romantic relationship with Kamoi
The two of us will end up in a romantic relationship
Don't pretend to hate me
I won't let kamoi give you
Stop it
Yukari!
Gamo!
Hey!
What are you doing?
You killed Kokuchi
And you try to rob my girl
I won't be fooled by you anymore
What?
I have some advice for you
She is yous
Do you trust me?
I have proof
It's dangerous
I have eyes on my back
Stay away
Tell them I won't run away
Tell Kaneda to wait at the construction site
That's all.
You go now
I have a temper with a pistol.
Where did the stupid KOKUCHI go
I really miss him
I want him to come back soon
Where did the stupid KOKUCHI go
Where did he go
Does he really come?
I'm sure he'll come
Don't move
If you move, I'll kill everyone
Maybe there is a rat in the house
Listen to me
I have a temper with a pistol.
I can drop you into hell
Are you ready?
It's no use shooting me too
You just waste your Handgun bullets
Gamo!
Kill him!
Even if you shoot a lot, it won't hit me
Oh my god
It's very fast.
I recommend you to the Olympics
Stupid!
How many guys we have!
Hey,what's wrong?
Come on,Komori and Gamo!
I have business with them both alone.
Oh
Escape from here!
Don't do bullshit!
You bustard!
Kokichi
I have taken your enemies.
The fire engine came earlier than I expected
I shot the other guy so he wouldn't die.
Take a rest for a whole
See you then
Have the Tenchi Group and GAMO Group been over?
The police are investigating now
Because it's their job
Why are you crying?
Because I'm glad
I end up to be free now
That's right?
But we are dangerous to be here
We should move the place
We can't be together?
Let me stay with you
It's ok but You will have a hard time
Really?
Take me
But I don't have a job
You must be prepared.
Never mind
I don't want to live in bondage.
I see
Do you really love me?
You are really woman.
Because Women all over the world like me
We should take a rest
The sun will soon rise
I'm tired because I've been playing westerns
What's wrong?
Come here
The phone is noisy
Hello?
Oh you
How did you find here?
You will write a special article
What?
I just received new information.
Komori and others are chasing you and your woman
Are you with her now?
What?
None of my business?
You are with the woman.
You guys are in big trouble if they find you.
You're okay, but the woman will be killed
Leave the gun and the woman and leave the hotel quickly.
It's for the women
If you have a pistol, you will be in violation of the law due to illegal possession.
And I'm worried because you might kill someone
Leave the gun and the woman and leave the hotel quickly.
You get it?
Don't be like a thief
You realised
You told me to take me out
I'm not lair
I'd better not be on your side
So you would be in big trouble if I were here.
I don't mean that
I don't want to be with Komori anymore
I want to escape
Don't get me wrong
You’re free now
Enjoy on your own
Right?
You know what
You shouldn't be with a guy like me
Don't get me wrong
I didn't cheat on you.
I have a weakness for women's tears.
Don't worry.
I was glad you said you would take me and run.
I'm happy with that.
Yukari
kamoi!
Oh you
Did you wait for me?
What happened to the pistol and the woman?
They are in the hotel room
I lost a woman and a pistol again because of you
That's for you
What the hell
Can you take care of her sometime?
I have another favor of you
You know Machiko, Kokichi wife, right?
She is..
Give this to her, and say good luck
I'm counting on you
kamoi!
Ok I get it
Thanks
And
Did you really leave the pistol and woman?
You insist.
The woman is sleeping and the gun is..
You have it!
I am popular with women
But I'm not popular with pistols
Kamoi
I know I have illegal possession, but I can't live without this
Please keep it secret as it will not be used for bad things
You wrote a good article, so your monthly salary will go up.
See you then
Wait
Kamoi!
THE END