Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Boat man
What?
that ship is stopped
It seems that the engine is broken, so we should help
let's get ready
Oh that's Ryujinmaru
Is the boatman Mr. Sakai?
I heard that they are using that ship.
But why are they here near Edo?
Maybe that ship was swept away from upstream.
If so, they are in danger of their lives
Are you safe?
We're here to rescue you
there seems to be a little problem
You and me and...Senta
Inosuke, we should go
You guys wait in the ship
Where are you?
No one here
Captain
i didn't find anyone
I didn't either
We're here to rescue you
What's the hell?
There
Yuki no mosho / The Man Who Disappeared Yesterday (1964)
Excuse me
I heard there was something big
This is very big problem
I've been working hard here for the last two or three years.
Gojodai might get married
IS that big problem?
There has been a lot of pressure against the government recently.
the government is crumbling
Nagasode can't do anything
The person is highly respected among them
he is very trustworthy
you should understand him better
you should advise him
i understand his character
Oh I see
We should be careful
he's been acting weird lately?
What's wrong?
he has insomnia
he is helped every night by women
This is rice cake shop signboard but this is bad meaning
However they are working very nice
Do you know why?
I read Ankoro rice cake shop masuya
You won again
How about this?
30RYO is gone from my room.
Only three people entered my room.
I questioned those three.
One said he didn't know they had that kind of money.
One said he lifted the safe when he cleaned it, but never opened the lid.
One said the person who lifted the safe during the cleaning was in a hurry, so that person was the culprit.
Do you know who is the culprit?
Kosho
You won again
How did you know?
You got three people together and said you ran out of money.
The kosho only know the how much is the money
It is too easy for me
So boring
Ichizen has more interesting story
Okata's?
He has an interesting crime-reasoning story.
Don't be humble.
I'll be your subordinate from today
Their riddles are boring.
But I want to solve the actual case myself.
I think Roju told you
I didn't know that but
Roju told me to introduce me one case
Do you have any complaints?
Well..nothing
That's good.
I'm going to solve the case starting today.
You'll be police?
I think this is good idea
I name my police name
Sabae Shinnosuke
What do you think?
Sabae Shinnosuke?
Sabae is the name of the land where I was before I became a general.
Sabae Shinnosuke
I think this is good name
So are you ready to work with me?
I get it
Bring him to the room
I'll go soon so get ready for the crime
I worry about him
I worry something happen to him
We'll be punished
Let's give him a simple case and get it over with quickly.
Find a safe case that anyone can solve.
Look for cases that are not too easy.
What's wrong?
you don't understand me at all
By the way,Chuko
Chuko?
You are Chuzaimon before Tadasuke
That is too good name
Please make my name too
You are Ishigoro
Ishigoro?
You are just stone
Where's the house?
Oh we passed
Get serious
I'm SHoemon minoya
Tekishita gonron did what work here?
he is usually very drunk
Who benefits most if Gonroku is killed?
What do you mean?
There is always a conflict of interest when people are killed.
GONROKU drowned and died.
We must investigate it
His cause of death has already been determined.
We've already established that he died drunk.
The boatman may have been paid to testify.
Bring women who related with Gonroku
Bring women?
Women are often involved in the case.
Gonroku was not into women
We must investigate it
Come here
Please take care of them
In short, anyone is fine
We will only match the results with him
i don't want to follow him
I'll pay you
Women are often involved in the case.
It is women's fault that Shogun fell.
beware of beautiful women
Women are the ones who control the country.
Who's that?
She is the only woman related to GONROKU
It seems that you even leaned your waist
let us ask various people
What are you going to do?
Me? let me see
The Gonroku case has been re-investigated
DAISHIN's son has come to like playing police
he said he wanted to solve the case himself
It seems that they could not refuse his request
That's why they gave him a case that had already been solved.
they ask people to trick him
Where's him?
Where's Gotoshin?
He went there
sabae shinnosuke
shinnosuke
What's wrong?
sabae shinnosuke has disappeared
we have to find him
Did you find him?
No
He must be around here
Who?
Oh Kaneshiro
Give me hot sake
He's my old friend
I'm Ohashi Kanehsiro
I'm sabae shinnosuke
Are you from Hacchoubori?
why are you running away?
well
do you play police now?
You like it?
Today's first day
Running away on the first day is still an amateur
It could be
it's a silly story
Trust me
It's strange that there's no one on the ship even though I'm buying food preparations
that's a ghost ship
I'm scared
Minokichi
Something happened to Ryujinmaru's ship.
I told the story and no one believes me
The ship is back today
What's the hell?
All crew members were present
Are you sure?
You are totally lair
this is a small hard fish
Yummy
Shogun and daimyo does not know how tasty is this
UE heard you saying that this incident was all fake
he got angry and disappeared
i forgot to shut them up
I'm sorry
I'm sorry too
we have to look for curry by the end of the night
It's old here but you can rest
Here's good
Watch out your step
Thanks
Here's Kaneshiro's house
It's surprisingly comfortable to live here.
You drunk too much
you don't seem normal
drunks are everywhere
He's dead
I know this guy, He was in Ikariya
Minokichi?
Hi,Senta
Are you back?
Can you come?
he dies instantly.
very skilled killer killed him
What's wrong with him?
he wasn't killed here
can you solve it by yourself?
why you think so?
his wound is big but there is little blood
He was killed elsewhere and brought here
I think Kiku returned from Ikariya with him
He was curious about Ryujinmaru and went to see it
we parted on the way
What Senkau did there?
I washed the blood off my body
blood ?
I killed a stray dog on my way home
I am taking the dog home now because it was edible.
winter dogs are so delicious
Why don't you try it too?
why did he bring his corpse here?
he and i lived together.
He threw this corpse into this house by mistake.
Where is the riverbed where this grass grows
Ahead of Okawa
I'm sure he was killed there
Why do you think so?
this was in his clothes.
And he has a lot of grass on his body
Watch the Ronin
Are you scared?
You are coward
The town of Edo is good for escaping, but bad for chasing.
why did you do this?
I thought it was not good to leave it down all the time
That is my job
Oh I forgot you are police
Thanks for your work
Who's he?
he's my friend and he lives here
how long has he been living here?
Since a month ago
Since a month ago?
he has insomnia.
he hasn't been here for a month
Thanks
It's hard to sleep at night
I'm sorry
Hey
You don't have insomnia.
Where are you going?
I'm going to eat seafood rice bowl
The owner of the shop was Minokichi's employer.
You are enthusiastic about last night's incident
I am very concerned about that incident
The owner is an old acquaintance
he has one daughter
Ohashi is visiting you
Bring him to the room
Here's ok
but
Anywhere is fine with me
If it is not horse house
We don't have the horse house
But there's a noisy house
He's my friend
Hello everyone, I'm Sabai shinnosuke
He looks like Shogun
Where's Kawachiya?
He just went to the division office.
to the division office?
I found this from his room while cleaning.
I am solving a case. When I'm done, I'm going home.
Don't do anything with me
MINOKICHI's body was given to KAWACHIYA
Sorry to disturb you
What's the hell?
Do you know who I am?
Are you crazy?
You're insane
Catch him!
Boss
MiNO was headstrong but compassionate.
Even that noisy woman obeyed MINO.
I'm a noisy woman so you didn't let me know he was dead?
Boss told us not to tell you
I believe our boss didn't tell you
It's not woman and kid's business
Yes I am a woman and they are kids
Taosaku
You told about Minokichi to the kids
and you made them to help your work
I wanna ask you about the ghost ship Minokichi said
We stayed at Sumiyoshi ship
The four men in the Ryujin Maru were pale.
That Ryujin Maru back in Edo safely
What is the ship's cargo?
MINO's Lumber
Teacher, I found him
Where?
Minoya
Minoya?
Just this?
Not enough?
I need 30 Ryo
You just killed one boat man
I am being chased by the police.
Someone saw my face
It's your fault
We must be vigilant.
We must kill all those we suspect.
Will you stop this weird game anymore?
weird game?
It is not good to have victims other than MONO.
What if he attacked me?
You know about Mino?
I know nothing
Master
It took me three years to gather that amount of gunpowder.
We couldn't collect large quantities at a time because it would fool the officials.
It didn't take time If Kawachiya helped me because he has big ship
We must kill all those we suspect.
By the way, Takeuchi will leave from Tokyo
Kawachiya is so upset
Yeah
What's wrong?
I have a concern about my father.
He was so kind before but not now
Since when?
3 years ago
Minokichi was killed about he doesn't wanna involve in that
I suspect him
But it’s hard to ask him
Ronin or Minoya is suspected
Teacher
Takeuchi was here and doing something
When?
Just before. He said he was waiting at Ikaiya
Sorry to have kept you wait
who was he with?
He was alone.
I was in the kitchen so I didn't know
He didn’t steel money
he was killed to keep his mouth shut
But why
I'm worried about the Sumiyoshi Maru's boatman controlling the officials.
The culprit thought he was the second most dangerous after Minori
The criminal went to the safest place,Gotembacho location.
What do you think about this?
so?
I go to the Gotembacho location
I'll let Kahei out of the place
and take him to Mino
A more important culprit may be found
You'll be in danger
Kikou might be staying there
You can't find it without taking a risk
Not all the officials know my true identity.
I mean I'm fake police
That's strange
Kahei has already been released
Is Mr. Kawachiya his sponsor?
I asked a official in agent
I'm not fake
Shall we go to the agent?
No thanks
I think someone picked him up before I came.
Anyway thanks for your work
He found you were fake?
kahei wasn't there
We were too late
It will be more interesting
Kahei
someone is provoking me
He will be appeared soon
I hope it takes big prey
are you good at kendo?
Just little
I worry
are you good at kendo?
Just little
But better than you
You're good
I'm not too good
Official is coming
Damn it
To nagoya?
I'll but something and back to Sakai
Then I'll go to Hirado
shall we live peacefully here?
Don't worry.
The ship I'm on, Ryujinmaru, is very fast.
Ryujinmaru?
The ghost ship?
Did you hear from Minokichi?
he was killed because he talks
did you know why he was killed?
You were on the ship
When I got home, I heard from a fellow shipmate
This is for you
10 Ryo
It's not big money
I'm afraid something will happen to Edo
What do you mean?
For example, fire or earthquake
If a disaster happens, use that money and run away.
Just in case
Take care
Don't tell anyone about me
Bros
I think Minokichi's death has something to do with Ryujinmaru.
Minokichi was talking about Deryujinmaru at Ikariya
That's what Minokichi said as a joke.
He's good at joking
While he was talking about it, SENTA told Ryujinmaru had returned.
Minokichi went to check
He was killed because of it
I can't believe it
I be;live Takeuchi killed him
Takeuchi often go to Minoya.
Minoya use Ryujinmaru
so
but
Shut up
Takeuchi had 30 ryo when he was killed.
I think it's a big amount of money as a reward for killing Minokichi
I think there was a reason for killing Minokichi
In short Ryujinmaru...
he must have had some secret
I see
Kahei thought that he would be killed next to Minokichi, so he escaped to prison.
But he was released by someone
Then Someone killed him
Senta or Jurosuke will be killed next
We are closed
Sis
Bros
What's wrong?
I came here under the name of Takekoshi-san.
Acquired 1300 guns
Kanto type 300
Kansai type 300
Let's invite DAIMYO who is dissatisfied with the current shogunate.
As Shinnosuke said, I think MINOYA killed my brother.
Why you don't go there?
You aren't Samurai?
Go to Minoya or go to police, why you don't act?
What if we do that?
You should attack them
There is something they are trying to protect even by killing people.
but
shut up
leave me alone
He really look like Shogun
I don't think he will come back easily
He said he would come back as soon as he solved the case.
He will be safe
What do you mean?
Our lord will arrive in Edo tomorrow.
tomorrow.
If he doesn't come back by tomorrow, we will be punished.
what are you looking at?
This was owned by SEIKICHI who was killed
I hope this gives some clue
What's this?
This is for Ju from Minoya
So Seikichi got this code and went trip
he talks things he shouldn't talk on the way
Then he was killed
Yeah
what does this say?
this is about the well
about the well?
In short
innocent
This is going to be this
no plan
let's decipher this
This is going to be this
And next
This is going to be well
you have a special talent
I need more clue
I wonder what Minoya is thinking about next
Minoya is killing senta and Minosuke
If they get killed their Kids will be in trouble
a lot of other people are in trouble
What are you going to do?
Search for RYUUJINMARU
you can't
RYUUJINMARU's sailors are not allowed to land and stay in the ship all the time.
To solve the case, we have to board the ship.
It's hard to say,i have to go home today
Because I was with you, I came to understand your character well.
a special guest is coming to my house
a special guest ?
you have to welcome the guest?
Your house is going to be corrupt
I have no idea
But I'll be in trouble
It can't be helped
so?
i go alone
you sure?
I have save people's life. and I need to find some reason
luckily i have no home
when will you go to the ship?
I will go when the night is coming
Go ahead
I won’t go
You told me you went alone
You've changed your mind?
Will you go ?
are you okay to go alone?
It's better
Hey
Kaneshiro
What are you doing?
I tried to solve this case myself because you don't act
You're stupid
You should hide yourself
Teacher
Oh you
I wanna pay them back for my bros
Get out from this ship as soon as possible
Oh there is no boat
There is a boat I took
Oh that's nice
How about you?
I'll stay here
I wanna be with you
Don't act like kids
Kawachiya's daughter and cram teacher?
And there is another one
You should go back
Bring Zenzaimon from Kawachiya
Now we have a reason to rob Sumiyoshimaru.
This is an ordinary well.
This works nice
Hey
Bring the Samurai here from DOJO.
Ryujimaru will depart with Sumiyoshimaru tonight
Oh you
Dad
What's wrong?
Kawachiya, you guys stay here to the death
Our Samurai surround you
Kawachiya!You turned down my offer.
Cram teacher supper Kawachiya to get us in trouble
I'll give you a fire, but don't try to escape to use this
There's a lot of gunpowder here.
Kaneshiro
Oh you are here
I believed you were here
I didn't know this was all gunpowder.
There's a lot of gunpowder here.
I'm sure there are a lot of guns too
Ryujimaru load the guns
The crew told me they brought guns from Izu island
So the ghost ship has some tricks up its sleeve.
Just before the four SUMIYOHI sailors were about to board, the RYUUJIN sailors all jumped overboard.
So They made Ryujimaru like ghost ship
I get it
They pretended to be empty
The Shogunate has a bad reputation these days.
There are quite a few Daimyo who against at The Shogunate
So Minoya tried to sell Guns to Daimyo for big money
Yeah
They told me the don't care who win or lose.
We just want money
Did MINOYA tell you that they have a lucrative offer for you?
3 years ago
They have held a grudge for three years.
All is my fault
I was wrong
Dad
I've only worked with MINOYA once, three years ago.
But I felt guilty and disassociated myself from MINOYA.
But Minoya always ask me to lend my Sumiyoshimaru
Minoya wants you to work with them
They often blackmail me
I ignore them for my daughter
I put up with it
Dad
All is my fault, sorry
I was unaware of these conspiracies.
They are so evil.
I can't forgive them
I know Minoya is evil but there is more terrible guy
Shogun is the worst
They don't get along with each other, and some take advantage of that.
Shogun is ignorant. so stupid
Yeah, Shogun is stupid
His associates are idiots too.
They should talk more.
Yoshimune is not stupid
Are you close to him?
He have to train more
I definitely won't get angry
You are not shogun.
You don't have to get angry
Yeah
Ok now we have to think about how to escape from here
I wonder how they bring those a lot of gunpowders
I'm sure there is another exit
Let’s take a look there
They will head to Amagi
We will go to Oshima by Sumiyoshimaru
We can dispose of DAIMYO, which is against the Shogunate.
Whats should we do?
Let’s go out
We can't
I have a good idea
Ok watch out
Who are you?
I am a crook.
crook?
What's wrong?
I'll help them
You can't
Let me go
Are you Chuko?
Chuko?
Who are you?
This is a message for you?
I'm at Minoya
There
You guys must beat them!
How are you,Chuko
Good job
I'll back in Minoya
You can't.
We don't have time
Please leave the rest to me
Please go home
Stop here
Kaneshiro
Are you alright,Ue-sama?
Lord is coming
Where's Ue-sama?
he hasn't come back yet
I heard he's being searched now.
Because Mr. ECHIZEN taught him to play strange games
If he doesn't come back on time, we will be punished.
He won't forgive us
Lord is coming soon
What should we do?
we have to die and apologize
Are you ready to die?
It can't be helped
Ue-sama is back
i was relieved to hear that
Thank you
What are you doing?
You guys get ready early
Yes sir
We welcome our lord
Oh..you
Sensei
What? dainagon
Your biological mother is related to Dainagon
I've been worried about Kawachiya since three years ago.I wrote a letter to my sister saying that I could not rest assured about the life of my adopted daughter OSONO.
DAINAGON knew that.
He used a fake to go to the EDO first to check on the status of KAWACHIYA.
His sister objected, but he forced himself to come to EDO.
Sister...Kaneshiro is cool
everything is settle down
Problems with the generals were also resolved through discussion.
Your house is very bad
You too
Look at that
From Izu to Amami,Those are warships for sinking enemy daimyo.
And this way
Look at the right
That is the place for you
Thank you.
I really appreciate it
THE END