Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Mountains and Rivers of Wounds
(A Public Benefactor/The Tycoon) (1964)
Hello?
Oh, it's me
Yes
Is everything OK?
Yes everything is Ok
I'll be there around 5 pm
I'll wait for you
I will wait at 7:30
The bath is ready
Is Ikuo here?
Ikuo?
You are strange
He is Takeo,Not Ikuo
Oh yes, Takeo
Is he here?
He is still in the school
You don't even remember your child's name
You are such a cold father
Hello?
Yes..Ah
I will call him
Yes. it's me
Are you chairman?
I'm Iwabuchi
I'm sorry to disturb you
I have two consultations, so please give me instructions.
Ok, what is it?
One is about the apartment under construction
What happened to the apartment?
A representative of the anti-construction group wants to come to your house tomorrow morning between 9:00 and 10:00.
Who is running that opposition
Because when the building is completed, sunlight will not come in.
Residents from the north to the west are protesting
How many people all together?
49 people
Is it a house or a store?
Most of them are houses and stores.
Some of them are like boarding houses
In short,they want money
They say they wants money?
Do they want us to stop the construction?
It is a request to stop the construction
I see
Ok, I will meet them
Tell them to come to my house at 9am tomorrow morning
Umm
What is the other?
The other is about Shigeya Ikeuchi
He wants us to build a new train line,right?
Umm
Let him meet Ryutaro first
Let's study our company for the time being
Let's do various things
Ok,You can give him 10,000 yen just in case
OK
See you
He is coming back soon, right?
Yes
Welcome back home
What did you do without turning on the light?
Your father is here
Let's go say hello to him
Tell him I have a headache
Don't be too selfish
Let's go
A little is okay
Ok?
Your father will feel bad if you don't go and say hello.
So please
Is school hard?
It's not big deal
I see.
You are in the second year of college,right Ikuo?
You also made a mistake in the child's name
Oh, he is Takeo
What are you studying at university?
You asked the same question 3 months ago
You don't even know what I study
You named me when I was born, right?
Yes you are right
I do a lot of work every day so
I'm too busy to remember
I leave my wife to take care of your things
Why are you always busy with work?
Because I want to do the work myself.
I think you don't have to make so much money
I know You have a lot of property
I don't work for money.
So for what?
Generally, businessmen are doing business to make money
So they fail in business
I am doing business for society
Therefore Society supports me
That's why I get my money without any effort.
The money I earn will also invest in new businesses
Does it make sense?
What will you do after you graduate from college?
I'm thinking of writing something
Writing?
How can you make a living with a job like that?
I can't
Do you like drinking?
I like
So Let's drink
No thank you for now
You should drink with him
Are you happy,Dad
I've never wondered if I'm happy these days
Right?
You have lost the power to think about
the important issues of human well-being
So what the hell?
Have you ever thought about your wife's happiness?
Takeo
Don't worry
Have you ever thought of my happiness?
You just gave me and my mother money
My mother is a woman
You only come home once or twice a month
My mother has been waiting for you
Have you ever thought of her loneliness?
Stop it,Takeo
I am a illegitimate child
Your name was not on the paperwork when I took the college entrance exam.
I've grown up with a very narrow shoulders.
My mother hides your shoes as soon as you get home
She'd be embarrassed if anyone saw it.
You have no idea how unhappy she is.
Business for society is good
I think it's good to build apartments
It ’s also good to develop train routes.
But
I have a favor of you
Please make my mother happy.
Mom
Will you break up with that father when I graduate from college?
I'll get a job and provide for you.
You are still young.
You can find someone better
You just serve that guy now
He was laughing after you went downstairs
He says you are a strong and very funny guy
He gave you some pocket money
He told me you go on a trip with this money
Mom..I'm sorry
Oh, good morning
Good morning
It's bit cold in this morning
I think so
Snow was piled up on Mt. Fuji
I slept on a new duvet last night
Oh You received it
How was it?
It was warm and I sweated
Warmer is better.
Did you stop coughing?
Yes
It tastes good
Good morning
Did you give the pickles that arrived from Kyoto to my wife?
Yes
What is Akihiko doing?
He gets up early this morning and eats with his wife
I see
How is golf?
Is it fun?
Yes
It feels good on a large field and sunny days.
Would you like to go once?
I don't wanna go
Our chairman has come
Hello?
Take your seat
I saw your opinion
I understand why you are against building an apartment
I want to ask you something
We announced 10 months ago that we would build an apartment with 1 basement floor and 7 floors above ground.
You all knew that, right?
We know that
So why are you guys protesting now?
Underground construction has already been completed
If we stop the construction here, we will lose 50 million yen.
What do you guys think about this
You say it's a big loss if you stop the construction but
We don't mean that you stop all the construction
We are OK if it is a 3 story building
If it's a 7 story apartment we disagree with it
It ’s a little problem because it does not get sunlight.
Do you guys understand the current situation in Tokyo?
Tokyo's population is already over 10 million
Furthermore, the population is increasing by 280,000 every year.
Tokyo makes a lot of metropolitan housing but
The housing problem is becoming more acute.
So Our company is building a building for the people of Tokyo to move into.
Anyway, the next plan is one of them.
But
It's true that Our house will be in the shade
We can't accept it
If you are going to build the apartment, I want to make sure you don't cause any trouble.
See New York Paris London
The center of their city is all skyscrapers
Here is a big city with a population of 10 million.
Not suitable for sunlight
You think it's common case?
If you think so we will fight in court
We are weak poor people, not powerful people like you
But at least we will claim damages
You say you'll all be damaged
But Did you calculate the profit?
When that apartment is completed, the number of rooms will be 312
624 people if two people live
The number of customers in your shopping district will increase
You can also raise the price of the product
You guys can make more money
If we pay for the damages
Will you share your profits?
We have prepared
Thanks
It's been a whole
Sorry for keeping you wait
This is a greeting from Arima
Please
Please take this
We don't want this
Please take this for the time being
Please
This is just greeting
Chairman
Our company is doing well.
Everything is as planned
Yes
It's double compared to 3,4 years ago
Because the number of people living in the suburbs has increased
It ’s because Tokyo got a fire in the war.
By the way
How is the construction of the apartment going?
Managing Director
Our chairman has come
I see
It was close..then excuse me
Good morning, sir
Good morning
There is a bus route change meeting at 1 o'clock, right?
Yes,The road plan for Tokyo has changed
We applied for a change in our bus route
Where is Ryutaro?
The president will meet with a man named Suguya Ikeuchi about the case you said in the phone
Yes
Kazuo
What?
Who was the woman?
She is a clerk organizing the boardroom
You don't have to worry
What is called?
Her name?
Let me see... I think she is called Fukumura
You
Yes
Tell her to serve me another tea
Will you organize the tools?
Do you have any work recently?
any work?
I don't know
You have some secret,right?
I have no idea
A strange person has come
I was asked a lot of strange things
What were you asked?
The business card is there,right
It's a detective station
Whether we are officially married
How many years have we lived together
How much my income
I was asked something like that
He didn't ask about me
I was asked about you too
What kind of person was your mistress before
Who is your recent mistress
Why did they come to find out?
They were asked to investigate by someone
I wonder who asked
Anyway, you're doing something suspicious
I have no idea
Is it okay with cold rice?
After all Those who came back from France are great
This painting is wonderful
Did you want to go too?
Is it ironic?
Is there whiskey?
Of course no
What are you doing?
I will buy whiskey
Your friend Mr. Kanbayashi, Mr. Hakamatsu, all support their family
Why don't your paintings sell at all?
They are not artists
I don't imitate them
Are you dissatisfied?
I am dissatisfied
I get it
Did you meet Shigeya Ikeuchi?
Yes I met him
He said he wanted to meet the chairman in person and tell a secret story
In short He wants you to make a new train line
I see, whereabouts?
Oh but it's not good
Our company looked it up 6 or 7 years ago,right?
Oh
That's it
Is there still a US military base?
There is
I see
We made this small hot spring town the last station, right?
Oh I see
This is a plan to connect to the railroad tracks of the Japanese National Railways
This is interesting to me
Ryutaro
Can you look it up in secret?
Yes
Don't tell him.
Get a new map along this line
And look up the population
What kind of factory is there
Investigate the power situation and water situation
I heard your route plan from my son
That plan does not work
Our company made the same plan seven years ago and did a lot of research.
In the end it didn't work and we abandoned it.
Why my plan does not work?
The train runs with passengers
Make money with it
But how about this line?
Rice field field forest wilderness
And there is a small town and a US military base
With this, even if we make a train, we only pay for electricity
Carrying radishes and pumpkins does not make a business
Oh..I see
Why did you plan a train route?
Does it have something to do to you?
Yes
I just want my land to be bought high
And I want to retire
So I thought it would be nice to have a train.
I see, I get it
We can buy the land if it is cheap
Because we are doing various businesses
How many you have?
There is about 20,000 tsubo
There is a highland of 10,000 tsubo
The rest is grassland
Will you buy it for 1000 yen per tsubo in total?
Let our real estate company visit the site once
Please consult with him
Yes
Real Estate Managing Office
Yamaguchi-kun?
Oh Shokichi
Can you come here?
I want to hold an executive meeting tomorrow
Can you gather?
Yes
Bus real estate train apartment all?
Yes All of them
Yes
Please buy this man's 20,000 tsubo land as soon as possible
He says he sells for 1000 yen per tsubo
Dad,Are you planning a route?
I don't know for now
Please keep it secret
Yes
That line was investigated by us 7 year ago.
However
At that time, the development officer in charge
Jinzo Sanuki, was planning the same route.
For our company
We abandoned it because the route is unprofitable and has no future
Sanuki also abandoned it because he thought it had no future.
How can I say...This is a problematic route
But our chairman reconsiders it again
I think he has some new ideas.
Please explain it
You're not learning enough.
Things are different now and 7 years ago
Tokyo has a large population
There are few places for humans to live
Moreover, the price of land is rising steadily.
Office workers can't buy a house no matter how much they save money
So What should we do then?
It ’s also a political issue and
The life of the citizens of Tokyo is also a problem
Does it make sense?
So things are different on this train line than they were seven years ago.
There's nothing on this train line.
There are only rice fields, fields, forests, and a small town.
I think there is a future because there is nothing
Ok guys, listen
There are many passengers in hot spring towns such as Atami and Ito
But Who is really profitable?
It's a hot spring inn, isn't it?
Trains should not make a profit on their own
We have to make a comprehensive development plan centered on trains
We can get to Shinjuku from here in less than an hour,right?
Here is in the commuting area
Build apartment complexes, build supermarkets, etc.
Playgrounds and baseball fields are also good
Orchard ,Natural Zoo
It is also good to make a golf course
In short
Passengers who once got on the train
No matter where they go or what they do
Keep customers out of all our related businesses
This looks like a trendy oil refinery
In short
This is a refinery of everyday life
It would be great if this could be achieved
What about the funds?
Borrowing money from a bank or an insurance company is a great way to lose money.
I'd like to discuss it with you guys today.
Each companies
Or individual
Find out how much money we can raise right now.
In short
Suppose we raised 3 billion yen
I will buy up the land on this planned route with that money
Buy 3 million tsubo for 1000 yen per tsubo
Then the train route plan will be announced
If we get the green light from Tokyo, the land will triple in value.
So if we sell half of 1.5 million tsubo
4.5 billion yen will be income
This will fund the route plan.
Are you Ms.Fukumura,right?
Yes
I have something to do with you
Can you come with me?
To where?
To upstairs
I brought her
Take your seat
Are you 28 years old?
Yes
Do you enjoy your work?
It's not an interesting job.
I'm just organizing the paperwork
It's not hard
How much is the monthly salary?
22000yen
There are some other overtime allowances
How much money do you have saved?
5000 yen or 6000yen
Then life is hard
Sometime I feel hard
Your husband is Yoshiharu Sakai?
Yes
Is he a painter?
You and he are not officially married
Yes
You're not registered?
No
Why is that?
It does not have any special meaning
You don't have any kids?
Not yet
Are you unhealthy?
I am healthy
Um
How many years have you been working?
It's been 8 years
I hear the paintings he drew don't sell very well
True
I hear he wants to go to France
Yes
He says he'll get an evaluation after three years in France.
He can't go because he don't have money
Shall I buy his painting?
Are you buying?
I'm glad but
You haven't seen his painting yet
I have an idea like this
You are poor now
You are poor and support the man
No one buy his painting
If you keep doing this, you two will fail
You get tired and he loses confidence
By the way
To be honest
I came up with this because I liked you
Listen
I hired a detective to investigate you
You're happily married, and I have no say in the matter.
I hate making people unhappy
You are in great trouble now
But there is a possibility of breakthrough
You and he will be separated for the next three years
In short
He goes to France for 3 years as he wishes
And he returns home as a wonderful painter
I will buy his painting for the travel fund
I will pay 150,000 yen a month for his stay in France
I will take care of you while he is away
You could buy a much nicer apartment.
We will be separated when he returns
If he's in great shape, you're in good hands.
I'm sorry but I refuse
It's ok if you don't like
You should talk to him
You want to make him a top painter, right?
That is your number one wish, isn't it?
You have to sacrifice something for that
This is a kind of deal.
Moreover It ’s a deal that I ’m going to lose a lot.
This is something small
You have worked hard for many years
This is the reward for it
Don't worry,take it
There is no deep meaning to this.
Katsuhei Arima Buy my painting and let me study abroad in Paris
He sends me 150,000 yen every month to France where I am
I think there are some exchange conditions
I was so upset
He said he would take care of me while you were away
That's why I thought
I refused properly
Ok so This story is over.
I don't have to ask such a person to buy my painting
True
But I worry our life
What are you talking about?
You can't afford to go to France
There is no choice
Take it seriously
I don't want to live in poverty anymore
I think you are a luxury
You are only thinking about going to Paris without thinking about making money
That ’s why you're often ridiculed by other people.
I don't care what other person think
What do you think about me?
I think you are lazy
I work hard but
You are being just lazy
If you go to Paris, I don't think you'll succeed.
You think so?
Do you look down on me so much?
You really want to be Arima's mistress, don't you?
Then you don't have to live in poverty
Did you get money from him?
I got it
But it's a reward for years of service.
That's an excuse
How much he gave you?
You want to study abroad in France,right?
Yes,I heard you were going to buy my painting for that.
I'm glad for that
I brought 3 paintings today
Wait wait,I will see your painting later
So..that woman
She is Fukumura,right?
Yes
I talked to her the other day but she didn't agree
I think you should talk to her again soon
Because I can't give an opinion
My principle does something that benefits that person
I want to do something that benefits that person
I want to make such a relationship
Actually, I've been thinking about it for the last three days
Sometimes I was angry with you
But this is a divisive idea.
I felt that I needed a rational way of thinking that gave up my emotions
You're a big businessman, so you're thinking about things thoroughly.
I'm so impressed
We can't do anything even if we make a train line here
We can buy here cheaply because there is nothing
Business is to make a profit from nothing
A train is built in this town and an apartment stands
And here will be a cultural city
What, Kaszuki?
chairman,Kazuki is here
You sure? see carefully
I can't see it well because of the dust but
I'm sure he is Kazuki
Why he is here..
He has a train line plan
I know he can't miss this chance
Only me and him can take this train line
There is no choice.
We will be competing with him
If you want to compete, we have to buy land first
The license for the route is OK later
It ’s important to buy up the land
First, let's do a survey to form a specialized department
Ah..welcome
Please
Sister, chairman is here
Yes
welcome
We were ready when you called.
The bath is ready?
I will check now
Take care of my cloth
Yes
Good evening
It's rare you come alone
or someone will come later?
Yes one person will come later
A woman
Oh your lover?
That's right
No way
That's true
Who is she?
That's not good
Is Tomiko fine?
She is fine
My son is a college student.
He is very cheeky
But he is fine
I will check the bath
I know the Chairman better than anyone.
It doesn't matter if you're rude, but please tell me the truth
The Chairman likes women who say things clearly.
That's why the chairman loves the most selfish women
He is a mysterious man
Why did you call me here?
Well...I want to hear your story while eating
The food here is very delicious
Do you drink?
I can drink little
I don't drink tonight
Are you on the lookout for me?
Yes
You don't have to do it
I don't do anything weird
Sakai visited me the other day
I don't know much about painting, but he's a good Yong person
I told him that I would pay the travel expenses whenever the procedure for foreign travel was completed.
You bought him
I think it's despicable to bribe person with money.
I don't think so
I showed him the conditions and consulted
He promised to be happy with my conditions
This is a deal between us
I know I will lose, but I showed him the conditions
Because I like you
I want to buy you too
You can always quit if you don't like it
I'm not going to fire you even if I quit
You came here because you were also interested
Why you came here?
Tell me
I just want money
Ok..anyway come here
What do you use the money for?
I don't like poor life
I don't understand how I feel
I sometime do not understand why I am alive
It ’s like I ’m fighting poverty
Even with cavities I can't go to the dentist.
Even in winter, I'm cold because I can't afford a coat.
It ’s not fun, but I just have to work to live.
I don't come here if I have enough money
The rent of our apartment is also delinquent
I can't give birth even if I want a child
If I have a child, the three of us must starve to death.
You know we don't have any money, so you bribe us.
I think it's despicable to bribe person with money.
That's too bad
I understand how you feel
It ’s not good to overdo each other
I feel sorry you are poor now
But There are many poor people all over Japan
I'm just trying to make you happy
Does my act look bad?
If so, there is no choice
Ok, then forget this deal
Why did you bring me here?
Is it bad to bring you?
You brought me here to buy me,right?
That's right
Is it problem?
Then you gave up the idea?
Because you don't agree
Anyway there is no choice
I see
Then it was no use for me to come here
Yes it was no use
I came here because I wanted money
I don't want to live in poverty any longer.
I should die
Why do you stop this deal suddenly?
I understand
I won't do you bad, so leave it to me
I will make you happier than ever.
I have three mistresses besides my wife
The two have been mistresses for over 20 years
and another have been 16 years old
I gave them each a home.
These women live an ordinary life.
People say it's bad to have a mistress
But If it makes the woman happy, that's fine in my opinion.
I was very poor when I was young
Poverty is evil
Most criminals in the world are poor
The world today is never good
The gap between rich and poor is too big in today's world
A really good world is
Even people without money can live a normal life.
My heart aches when I see young, beautiful women living in poverty.
I feel like drinking
He is Asao Hisayama, who was appointed as the land manager from the materials section manager.
Thank you for your hard work
Not at all
Build a residential area by laying train tracks
We must first buy the land to develop it
You are in charge of it
It's the most important work right now
Does it make sense?
Yes I get it
Yes
Toshihara-town 2012
Here it is
I'm sure you have 20,000 tsubo
I have about that much
Will you sell the land to us?
Around that hill
By the way, Can you really do train routes?
Train?
I've heard nothing
That's not something we talk about in the company.
I did a survey before and stopped because it wasn't profitable
I see
Someone asked you about that?
I thought Mr. Arima would make a train route
By the way, about the price of land
You talked with Chairman Arima for 1000 yen per tsubo.
Yes
But was it a little too cheap?
I think that's fine
There is other buyer
He says he will buy it for 1200 yen per tsubo
Is he Shinzo Kazuki?
I think Kazuki wants to buy
Yes...well...
He seemed to want to buy
So He has plan to build a train route here
I don't know about it
But He often investigated the train
About buying your land.
Yes
He said he wanted to buy
So He said How much?
Well...
Take your seat
He said he can buy at 1200yen per tsubo
I see
You made 200 yen.
Since it is 20,000 tsubo, it will be 4 million yen.
Yes, thanks to you
Sell it, he will be glad
Yes
So he wants to build a train route?
No,Arima wants to buy land because he wants to run a farm.
I see, he wants to run a farm
That's interesting
What kind of seed does he sow
So did you tell him I have a plan for building a train route?
Yes
He said the train business has a deficit
He said having a train would be good for the farm business
He is cheeky
Sorry I was away
Where have you been?
To Haneda
I went see him off
I see
He has gone
It's foolish for him to let go of such a beautiful woman for three years
In a capitalist society
Politicians are on the side of capitalists in every world
In short
It is the rich, not the poor, who support politics
Japanese politicians have been so since the Meiji era
Japan's fiscal and monetary policy depends on large corporations
There is a tendency for capital concentration
Therefore, large companies and small companies
There is an inevitable gap between large retailers and micro retailers
This disparity will increase as the nation grows.
Here's a good example of the relationship between department stores and retailers
In the case of eihoku department store, it was founded in March 1957.
The president is the famous katsuhei Arima
Seihoku Department Store was founded in the spring of the following year after the department store law was enacted.
Of course there was opposition to local retailers
They launched a tremendous opposition to the Ministry of International Trade and Industry and the Department Store Council.
Department store law is a law for the government to protect small and medium-sized enterprises
The government must deliberate nominally
Of course, local ward councilors supported them
The Ministry of International Trade and Industry did not have the courage to overwhelm the opposition movement and grant Arima approval
So the Ministry of International Trade and Industry called Arima and asked him to withdraw it temporarily.
Arima got a week's grace and left.
Then he interviewed seven retailers individually.
He succeeded in removing them from the opposition movement
It was speculated that there were various black transactions
Arima said it couldn't be extended once the two-year contract with the retailer expired
And Arima demanded they leave.
Arima controlled the protest well
Arima successfully deceived them
Teacher, he is the son of Arima
He is Yokota,right?
Heijiro Yokota's father is Katsuhei Arima
Yokota
I hear you are the son of Arima Katsuhei, Is it true?
What's wrong with it?
I am also his son
So you may be a brother
What's wrong with it?
It's nothing
You think so?
I don't think so
What are you asking me for that?
There is no particular meaning
We are in a common position
That's why I wanted to talk to you about things.
There is nothing I talk about with you
I just know you are the son of him
I'm unhappy to hear it
You just let me know my father play around woman a lot
I like my father, It can't help...
I also hate my father
I don't want to hate my father anymore
I want to talk with you more
You seem to be escapist
I can't talk here so can you come my home?
No
My mother is his mistress
I'm angry with him when I see my mom
I don't want to see his other mistress
I have to leave
Do you know Seizo Hashizume?
No
He ran a bag shop in the Seihoku department store
I see, I can't remember well
In 1934, the Seihoku department store launched a retail store,right?
The contract expired so I asked them to go out
Seizo Hashizume is one of them
I see
He committed suicide by train last night
The reason was that he couldn't open the store because he was kicked out of the department store.
He suffered and became mentally ill
Do you have any thoughts?
What do you mean?
I think his suicide is your responsibility
We work under the department store law created by the government
I think the responsibility for that lies with the government.
For example, do brokerage firms take responsibility when a stock crashes?
Will the bicycle promotion association take responsibility for those who commit suicide after losing a bicycle race?
But morally I think you are responsible
Excellent products from the United States may enter Japan and Japanese manufacturers may go bankrupt
The business world is very competitive.
Do you go to his funeral?
I won't go
Do you want to send someone else to do it?
No
Oh you, it's a problem!
Akihiko goes crazy after evening
Kazuo is here now
Is it his usual illness again?
Just leave it, It's not big deal
Don't you love him at all?
Don't ask me stupid things
I like Ryutaro,Junko,Setsuko and Akihiko
Then think about Akihiko a little more
He is no use
Isn't your useless son adorable?
You said you like him but I think you forsake him
He is amnestic.
He can't work properly
It's just a random job.
There's work he can do.
He is amnestic because you got him to work in a department store for a responsible job
You ruin humans
He has a weak spirit so he can't do any work
You are no use too
It ’s your fault that he ’s not good.
Kazuo brother
Can I burn incense from now on?
I should buy flowers
I know you liked white flower
Is red flower bad?
Is that right?
white flower
What would you like?
Akihiko-kun
It's not your fault
You were the eviction clerk at that time
It was very terrible
If the war is a mass murder by the state, it's a legal fraud
You are much purer than us
Brother...white flower
What is better?
Actually There is a serious incident
I think I should talk to you directly
I think the order is different.
But Please consider
Ok tell me
My college friend works for the Ministry of Transport
He contacted me secretly
Regarding the train license from Takiyama Station to Mategi Station
Kazuki Shizo seems to have applied for a license to the transportation office.
You've been waiting for me since the morning to make that report me?
Yes, I thought it is very important issue
You are the land manager,right?
Yes
What is the land manager's work?
What about land acquisition? I heard that it is not progressing
Sorry
I know he submitted the application since yesterday morning
What?
You go to the site!
Only one contact person should be at the head office
You may stay there to buy the land
Understand?
Buy 1 million tsubo
Yes
Hey,Please call the chairman as soon as possible
I know how you feel but Half of your land is thickets and the rest are fields
Excuse me, but how much is your annual income?
If you sell that 5000 tsubo for 2000 yen, it will be 10 million yen.
Even if you manage 10 million yen at 6% per year, it is 600,000 yen.
You make a profit of 50,000 yen every month
The monthly income of 50,000 yen is big
Hello? Is that chairman?
This is Hisayama speaking.
A lot of land brokers in Tokyo came
Landlords are getting bullish
Give them something
If they like alcohol, bring 10 foreign whiskeys
Give his wife a kimono or something
Give a present that makes his wife happy
If we can get a lot of land at once, it's a cheap cost
Yes, I'll try
Takeyama site office
Wait a min
Department cheif, phone call for you
Hello? What can I do for you?
Can you go home now?
What's wrong?
I don't want to be with my mother anymore
I will take my child back to my hometown
There is only one Yuichi at home so please go home early
I don't know what are you talking about
Did you fight with our mother?
You know what your mother looks like
Have you stopped renting other apartments?
I'm too busy now
I'll be back in 3 days so please wait
Then I will go home
I'm looking for an apartment now
I try to separate to live from my mom when I'm done with my work
You think I'm wrong?
You think your mother is right?
I understand!
In other words, payment is postponed and money is made
And Use another payment for it
And fill it with another payment
This way you will be forever profitable
That's how you buy and sell land
This makes money without bothering anyone
You can buy an apartment right away
You are busy.
You have a hard time with a house problem
I can talk to Mr.Kazuki if you are interested
But I want half the profit
(Buddhist sutra)
I'm sorry.
Our chairman worry about you
Thank you for your concern
You were too busy to take care of your house
I also feel responsible
You don't have to
You should do another job for a while
I know you've been through a lot.
I'll be fine
I'm alone now, so I can work hard
He said he is alone now, so he can work hard
That's not good,Let him other work
There are many bad conditions
His family is not good.
Let him other work and bring young worker from estate department
The last one or two months are important
You have been transferred to the labor department
I can't accept it
It has been decided
Work is still in progress.
No one understand my work
I have various promises.
It won't work if I leave
We already have a replacement in the field.
Has it been decided?
I want to go to the labor department after taking over the office work
I wish I could have money...
I could control my company's money and buy the land you bought...
I have invested all my money in the land
In a few days I have to pay back 2 million yen to the company or there will be a hole in the books.
Ikeyoshi-san
Can you ask Mr.kazuki to take care of my issue?
Please
I don't have to buy these small lands
I see
There is something wrong with this land
Yes
Mr. Arita's land manager is eager to sell.
I won't buy
I don't want to be seen by Arima with strange eyes
Ah, are you chairman?
He was debilitated because his wife committed suicide a week ago.
He was chasing after
I reported to the police that way
Ok,Watch out for newspaper reporters
2 million yen is just like a retirement allowance
What about the funeral?
Anyway, go as an incumbent manager
Use the company's money to pay for his funeral.
It looks good
Hey,Please bring some snacks
Is there anything you can eat?
Look inside the fridge
There is only milk and orange in the fridge
Oh I see
I don't know about people who drinks
You should buy anything for me
What would you like?
It's common foods
What do you do outside every day?
I'm learning driving now
It's interesting
Can you buy a car for me if I got the car license?
There is a garage near here
What do you do when I buy a car?
I can go to play golf
Sometimes I also drive with you
Are you sure there is no snack?
We have chocolate.
You are bad girl
Can I see Yokota-kun?
Yes, can I ask who are you?
I'm Katayama, can you call him?
Are you his school friend?
Yes I am
Please wait a min, I will ask him
Heijiro! Heijiro!
Yes...Um
What's wrong?
I'm here to play with you
Anyway come in
Excuse me
Bring me a tobacco
Yes
Your house is the same as my house
I see, he likes this
Take your seat
Serve us tea
Yes
You smoke nice tobacco
I smoke by Arima's money
What do you think of Katsuhei Arima?
Does he have to be the same as you think he is as I think he is?
I and you are brother-in-law, but you don't have to worry about our father
It ’s okay because our mother is different
She is my mother
Her name is Kaneko Yokota.
In short she is his mistress
She is not ashamed that she is his mistress
I look down on her
It can't help that I'm her child
Take your time
It ’s not good to blame your mother.
You should blame your father.
I looked up Arima's business yesterday
There are two suicides this year
But His business is growing
In short, he is bad person
He's a bad guy. He can do big business.
Good guys can't do.
Big business is done by bad people for their own benefit.
He doesn't care about the suicides
Do you approve of his methods?
Yes
I'm not humanist
The world today is not a place for old-fashioned thinking.
So do you approve he has 3 mistresses?
I hear now he has 4 mistresses
I hear she has husband
He gives money and let him to study in France, and get her
He thinks she will be happy
Even if his mistress is happy, her son is not happy
Women are stupid
My mother is also a fool Your mother is also a fool
I'm going to get rid of my father when I get a job
So I told her to separate with him later
What did your mother say?
She can't separate with him
I was surprised
I will join my father's company when I graduate
Arima's son holds an executive position at Arima's company
Even a mistress's child is a son
I'll make up for my life there
What if he doesn't get you into the company?
If so, I set fire to my father's company
Earlier you said you looked down on your mother
I love my mother
I think my mother is also a victim
She knew I was a illegitimate child when I was born
He did nothing during her ten-month gestation
I can't forgive it
What do you think about your mother?
I think it was last spring
I had a quarrel with my mother about it
I choked my mother.
I really tried to kill her
But my mother didn't resist anything at that time
So I couldn't kill her
Let me play
Yes
Wow! nice shot
Try it
With your right elbow
Extend your left elbow softly
Yes
I did it!
nice shot
Try again
Yes
Residents of Koshiya-gun, Takeya-cho have been hoping for the opening of the railway for many years.
since we, Seihoku Electric Railway, applied for the route
Cooperation promotion is being deliberated in the local village council
Our company acquired about 820,000 tsubo of land along the line
We are seriously hoping for the completion of this business.
Please give us approval as soon as possible.
We investigated the land acquired by Seihoku Electric Railway
They are buying two parallel lands in one place
The two lands are more than 1 km apart
This is really weird.
In other words, Seihoku Electric Railway is acquiring land for other businesses, not for the train business.
We have a variety of businesses
We run housing and entertainment facilities
More than that, the Kanto development company is not ready to open the train
They bought 500,000 tsubo of land along the same line
They have no intention of doing business
They are profiting from manipulating the price of land.
What do you think about this point?
I've improved since you taught me golf
I'm glad
You will improve your golf because you are honest
You think so?
I want to play good soon
I have to go
Nakamura-san.
Is he working here?
He is a trainee called Arima
Arima-san?
Do you know the Seihoku Electric Railway's chairman called Katsuhei Arima?
He is the son of him
Oh I see
Why he is here?
They have plans to build a golf course along the line
So Arima has sent him to study about it
Promotional movement for Seihoku Electric Railway is taking place
The promotion federation has also been formed
However, according to the results of our research
Seihoku Electric Railway acquired residents living along the railway line for money
And made them start this promotion movement
They gave the prefectural assembly members 200,000 yen
They gave the mayor 50,000 yen
They also gave the town councilor 50,000 yen
Regarding that matter, land acquisition was very difficult
I persuaded the locals to buy it
It's not corruption
I want to ask you another things
Chairman Arima of Seihoku Electric
Railway meets with the chairman of the
Japanese National Railways and Ministry of Transport bureaucratsonce in February and once in April at a restaurant.
I think this is an acquisition.
What do you think?
Well...There may have been such a fact
But it's just a round-table conference
I hear that Mr. Kazuki of Kanto Development holds such a meeting every month.
Isn't it true?
I heard they meet at a restaurant called Harutake in Akasaka
You look around a lot of golf courses,right?
I don't go much now
I used to go around golf clubs in the Kanto region.
Which is the best?
Well.. I like Sakuragaoka golf club most
Can you bring me there when you are free?
Yes sure
I want to go far like Atami and Ito
You don't have to take care of your house?
I am Mitsuko Fukumura
I am Akihiko Arima
I'm free
Do you have husband?
I'm alone
In areas where there are no plans to build a train
They were advertising that the train would pass there
In addition, they were promoting malicious lies
So the people of the area,they fought to buy and fight for the land.
They plan to sell the land waiting for the land price to soar
They are planning to make huge profits with it
Do you think this is a legitimate business for Seihoku Electric Railway?
To be honest
The area for which Seihoku Electric Railway is applying for approval is between the town of Rose and Koshibara.
It will be extended to Oyamada-cho, another 8 km away.
This is scheduled for the second phase of construction
This has also been applied for approval by the Ministry of Transport
This is the fake information from the inside of Seihoku Electric Railway
Don't bullshit!
As you know,Tsuchida of Kanto Development said something strange at the principals' meeting yesterday
In short,he said we're just waiting for land prices to skyrocket through our hoax,right?
If true, that's important
It's Involved in my honor
I think some real estate agent planned it
We have to deal with it properly
If it was a real estate agent, let's catch the culprit and have them run an apology ad.
I get it
So...
It's not a big deal so you should investigate it
It may take a few days, so please go to the site
Yes, I understand
Hey, come here
You don't want a child?
I don't want
I promise to break up with you after 3 years
What if I had a child?
I will pay you child support.
And I can share my assets with you
You and your child will never have a problem in life
That's not fair
You're going to keep me forever,right?
You don't want?
I don't want
Hello?
From Mr.Iwabuchi
About the case...
As far as I research,I got an unexpected result
I'm in trouble
You don't have to be in trouble.
Tell me
Actually I contacted those real estate agents
But They all said that Seihoku Electric Railway is starting to buy up
They told me to go to the registry office
Then I went there
There are?
Yes
Who is the name?
Although it is not officially registered
It's 7500 tsubo
The name is Masanori Arima
Masanori?
In the name of my grandson
Um
So Kazuo has bought the land
He has come here
Hello
It's getting warmer
What can I do for you?
Will you treat me a meal?
What is a consultation with me?
You within the last 2 months
Between Koshibara and Koyamada-city
You have bought 7500 tsubo land by your child name
I know it's registered
I know how much you paid the contract
Is it true?
Yes
No matter how much land you buy, it doesn't matter to me
Are you the one who spread the rumor
that the Northwest Electric Railway will
extend its line to Oyamada and made
a plan to increase the price of land?
I want to ask you about it
I didn't know it was you.
I wanted money
I'm sorry
You are not poor
Right
I'm not poor
But All the property of my house is yours
and my wife's
It's not an asset I have at my disposal.
I studied literature
I want to study German literature
To be honest I don't want to work with you
I want to make money on my own
I want to make you, my brother, and my wife proud.
I don't mind being poor, I just want to go somewhere far away
with my family
I know how you feel but
Did you think of my position?
We had no plans to build a train, but you lied to them.
That is, if it came from the Arima clan.
I'll be the one in charge of that.
We have to apologize to the world
As you wish
Let's break our ties today
There are two ways to decide where to locate the station.
One is to build a station in a place where there are many people living.
There are many passengers
But it costs a lot of money to acquire land for the station.
I don't build a station where there is already a town
I build a new city around a new station
Acquire about 50,000 tsubo at the place to build a new station
Build a new station in it
And there will be a shopping street around the station
Land prices will gradually increase
Even if we build a station in the grassland, it will become a town in 5 or 6 years.
Does it make sense?
This is my opinion
Do you have any other opinions?
I think people along the line will oppose us
What is the opposite?
It means that even if the train opens, it will not be convenient.
I think it's good for the development of the region
Then I think the people of the supporters are dissatisfied
It can't help
Train line development is also a public project
It's not something we do for the small benefit of their residents.
Regarding the acquisition of the railway land currently planned
6000 tsubo on the hill near the NOMI river
Kanto Kaihatsu has acquired about 16,000 tsubo of land between NOMI
River and KASHIJIMA
They do not accept the acquisition of our railroad land
Kazuki said he'd take care of the registration process later after the sales contract.
That's why we couldn't find it in the registration search.
There are many other lands like this
Change the planned location of the route
Divert them away from Kazuki's land.
Is their planned route area changed?
Arima is strong but not a businessman
This is an amateur's idea
We are not thinking about creating a new route from the beginning
Our land is getting more and more expensive because they are making noise
Thanks to Arima
We should keep the land.
Don't sell to the last minute
Let's wait for his action
Where are they going to build the station?
They don't build stations in town
They build a station 1 km away
Something will go wrong
Okozuki-kun,
Contact Yoshida on Tonejima and see what he can do.
Yes
We have doubts about your way
Listen
You say that the train is a public works project. So sell the land.
So we sold the land cheaply
But
You bought up a million tsubo of land unrelated to the train
They are trying to raise the price of land
We are just farmer
We can't live without a field
Every land is 2 to 3 times more expensive
Because you bought the land!
True!
I heard that the station will be built far away
Is that true?
If that's true, it's a scam using public utilities.
In some cases, we will all sue Seihoku Electric Railway.
We understand.
We are investigating immediately
We have negotiated sales with many people
So there may have been a misunderstanding or lack of explanation
We apologize for that.
Wait!
Bring chairman!
Find out what kind of person they are
Find out what they are making noise for
Kazuki may be supporting them behind the scenes
The chairman of that group is an innovator named Fujita.
In short, the price of land will rise steadily
He supported the farmers and local people
His plan is to consolidate the ground.
Is the Conservative Party still the main force in Matéki and Tone Island?
Yes mostly
That whole area is Conservative territory.
I see
Then let's leave it for a while
The problem will resolve itself over time
Are you talking to the police?
We are greeting for route approval
I think that would be fine
Hi
Chairman
This person wants to meet you
Koichi Makita?
He is a local representative and conservative on the new line
About the problem with the new route
As you may know
Residents along the line are dissatisfied
If you leave it alone, public opinion will be very noisy.
It's not good for your business either.
Fujita, a convinced town councilor, is a problem
He is a very good politician
I just worry about this
I have a strong relationship with the locals
I'm going to do something about it while I still can.
So I came here today to hear your opinion
There are many types of protests
The opposition movement of the left wing system is the most dangerous
They have an ideological foundation
They're campaigning against something they believe in.
In this case it is difficult to buy up
It will be difficult if an investigation comes in from the police
I think you don't have to worry about that
Conservatives are town councilors and leaders
They are under your control
It's rude to say but They act according to their interests.
So it's easy to buy
It's wrong
Never mind
Anyway
You are the best leader in that area
Therefore, I would like to continue to use your help
Nice on
I get burned
Stop it, I don't like, stop it
Where is my pajama?
In bedroom
Give it to me
I'm cooking now
Help yourself
What did you do today?
You might get bored
I'm not bored but busy
What did you do this morning?
I went to beauty salon
What did you eat for lunch?
Why you ask me?
I worry you are bored everyday
Never mind.
I enjoy my life
Where did you go in the afternoon
In the afternoon..today
Today is Wednesday, right?
Cooking school
You go there
I'm good girl,right?
What time did you get home?
Around 4 pm
Why?
Someone visited here?
No one visited
A man
It's strange
I never see man visitor
He sat here and smoked with you
One cigarette has lipstick
Another cigarette doesn't have lipstick
This is a cigarette that a man smoked
You are strange
Do you doubt me?
Speak honestly
Who?
Not a man
A woman
A woman came to sew clothes
Why her cigarette doesn't have lipstick?
I have no idea
She probably wore high-end lipstick
How long he stayed here?
You doubt me so much
About 30 mins
I see
I think you are lying
I don't think women who can work have time to smoke
There are about 10 cigarettes that the person smoked here
Did she smoke one cigarette every 3 minutes?
This person is definitely a man
Can I stop by here?
No? I'm sorry
Maybe next time
I don't want to put you in this room
My life is a secret
Find out my identity.
It's interesting
You can't understand my way of life
I couldn't keep up with my dad's thoughts and dropped out of life
I was studying theater when I was a student
I fell in love with an actress and was scolded by my father
I've been fine since I met you
Will you meet me everyday,Mitsuko?
What are you thinking?
If I keep living like this, I'm going to get worse and worse.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I don't know what I'm living for.
You just have to do what you like
I don't mean that
I'm wrong as expected
So Shall I bring Sakai back from Paris?
I don't want to see him anymore
So, that man
You don't fool a man too much.
You are too attractive for men
I need nothing
Can you separate with me?
Separate?
That man knows me?
He must be foolish
Oh here
I don't want to go
You can go alone
Let's go together
You have the same problem as me
My father told me to come here
He will treat me a meal
Why you afraid?
Hello?
One more customer
More dishes, please.
Certainly
When do you guys graduate?
The year after next.
I came to talk to you about that
I see
Can I work at your company?
I have a lot of companies.
Which one?
Your main business is the train business,right?
I want to work for the train company
Then take the entrance exam
I need to take entrance exam?
Of course.
Everyone take the entrance exam.
That's strange
Did Ryutaro Arima take the exam?
He didn't
Why?
He's my successor.
But Son-in-law Sokichi took the exam
He became a son-in-law after joining the company
It's more profitable to have a son-in-law than to have a daughter-in-law.
We are your son
You made Ryutaro the president.
We also want to be an executive
We are all your son
There is a distinction
Do you mean your wife and mistress?
It might be so
We are the child you gave birth to
You are logical
Do you agree with him,Takeo?
In principle I agree with his opinion
But I don't expect anything from you
To be honest I don't want to see you
After graduating from college, I will part with my mother and live alone
He is trying to escape reality
I think it's defeatism
I want to use you
I want to take advantage of your social status and wealth
You have a duty to help us
A corporation is a business entity
We will cooperate and manage for the development of business
Your way of thinking is fundamentally wrong
You are thinking of using the company for your own benefit
We don't need such a person in the company
I'm explaining to you as the person in charge of the company, not your father
So you won't let me join your company
Right
So,Please recognize as your child because it will be a problem when I join another company
People who are ambiguous about their fathers don't get into good companies.
I disagree with it
Do you know what it means legally to recognize a child?
I know
I read and memorized the entire Six Laws.
There are problems with the Family Register Act and the Inheritance Act
Under the Family Register Act, if you acknowledge, I've been your child since I was born
Under inheritance law, I'll get billions after you die.
I am Shoko's child so I get half of them
I will probably get 300 million yen or 500 million yen
I see
You want my legacy
You're black-heart-ed.
Go home
Tonejima-cho stop position change request meeting
Seihoku Electric Railway is a for-profit business, not a public project
We have cooperated with the construction of a new line for Seihoku Electric Railway
Because We thought that transportation would be convenient and that it would be beneficial to our lives.
That's right
But Seihoku Electric Railway ignored our request
They say they will build a station 1 km away from the city
1.Pay cooperation money to farmers whose land has been forcibly expropriated.
2.Land not used for railroads should be returned to its original owners.
3.Build the station in the center of the station as the local people want.
That's right
I'm working 30 years into the future.
The Protesters aren't thinking about the future
Those people should be forcibly bribed or something.
The people are all selfish
Their opposition does not last long
I think their opposition will last a couple of months at most.
Even if the train station is built far, they will be happy to go to take the train.
A lot of people who are planning to oppose the new route are coming to the company right now.
They are protesting and ask us to meet you
Makita is not here?
Makita deputy?
He is not here
He is no use
What shall we do?
Hello? wait a min
Phone call from Makita deputy
Hello? This is Arima speaking
Hello? This is Makita speaking
I heard that the residents of Takeyama Town went to protest there.
Yes, It's very lively
Would you like to come here too?
I thought you would come
But I don't see you
I was wondering what happened to you
Then I'll be waiting for you
Kikukawa-kun
Yes
Only representatives of protests should enter the room.
Bring others to the roof
Tell them to wait a while while you review the request at the board meeting.
(Opposition movement song)
I've asked you to do this before, and this is the result.
So you didn't do anything
It can't be helped if you make an effort
You are not trusted from them at all
Or you don't have power
Tell me
Please tell me your opinion
Don't misunderstand
I've just been inconveniently busy.
I was careful but it didn't work
I was very busy in the Diet
Stop making excuses
I'm building a train line, so it's important to have a relationship with that community.
So I have to have a relationship with the political leaders in the area
So I was going to work with you
If you don't cooperate with me I have to find another person
Then I will help another person instead of you in the next election
I support that person and I think about our business development
I think like that
Does it make sense?
Are you threatening me?
If it's to your detriment, it's blackmail.
It's not blackmail if it's in your best interest.
I don't mind either
Many people are coming to protest today
How do you control them?
If you do nothing I will do something
Wait, I will take care of it
They are my locals
If I talk them, it will be solved gracefully
Cheif, Our chairman is calling you
For example, when a station is built, a shop is needed in the waiting room.
Or We need more kiosks on train platforms to sell newspapers and cigarettes.
about running a concession stand
We recruit from residents along the railway line and give them business rights
We will announce like that
If I do this,Among the protesters
People who want to make money will apply for it.
Then those who are protesting will lose.
There are many small advantages like this
We're going to make things work like this.
That's nice idea
You're very resourceful.
You should be a politician
Are you planning to build a school?
Yes,We're going to have a groundbreaking ceremony soon.
It is a science-based four-year vocational school named Seihoku Gakuen.
I will make it in the kosihara-city of Takihara
I would be grateful if you could take over as a director and get involved in school management.
I'm very grateful.
Good evening
Hi,Papa
Hi
It's been a while since you've been here.
You seem to live with a beautiful woman
There's a rumor going around here.
I think I will marry
Did you find anyone nice?
Yes kind of
I agree with you to get married
You look happy lately and I'm glad
How old is she?
I don't know well
She is not so young
Around the same age with me
She has never married before?
I think so
I don't know well
You should check it carefully
Where did you meet her?
At golf club
You should know her background
I don't care about her background
I also had a time at a mental hospital
Good evening
I want to talk to you a little
I have a visitor now
Sorry
Then I'll wait for a whole outside
Can you come tomorrow?
Just little OK
I told my mother about you
About that
I'm inconvenient today
Anyone is here?
I have a visitor now
Who is the visitor?
Please go home now
Akihiko-san
I can see what your father is doing here.
You came here to break our marriage
But I'll say it clearly
I'm already 28 years old
I can decide my life on my own
I'm leaving home.
I'm not going to be your watch
I will do my best with her no matter how poor
So Please go home!
You seem to want to marry her.
But You can't
There is a reason
There is no such a reason
Don't get involved with us anyway
Please go home!
You know nothing
She has a husband
He is Sakai Yoshiharu, a painter
He is in Paris now
Mitsuko-san
Is it true what he said?
Is it true ?
It's true
And I am your father's mistress
Dad
Is it true ?
Are you trying to take revenge on me?
No at all!
No!
No!No!
Akihiko tried to commit suicide
What?
He took a tablet
What he took?
He took sleeping pills
It's not a problem
Is he conscious?
He is still sleeping
He came back and stayed in the room.
I thought it was odd, so I peeked into the room.
He is stupid
Mom, let's go
What are you talking about?
let's go
Then mom and mom have a special relationship.
Yes
Then I don't think there is a need to file a proceeding
If the father and mother discuss the issue and report the recognition.
That would be no problem
I have asked my father but he refused
Is it profitable for you to be recognized?
I have both mental and material benefits
What is your father name?
He is Katsuhei Arima
Katsuhei Arima.....Seihoku Electric Railway's Katsuhei Arima?
Yes
So you are his son?
I see
OK
We accept proceedings for recognition claims
Hello?
Hi, it's me
Hi, what happened?
I haven't seen you in a while
Sorry. I've been busy
Are you coming to see me tonight?
No, I can't
That's too bad
I'm cooking your favorite natto now
Is Eijiro there?
He is still in the school
What can I do for you?
He sued me
It is a cognitive proceeding
Listen
He needs to be legally recognized as my real son.
I don't know what it is
Never mind
He has disgraced my face.
He wants money
He's after my fortune.
I'm sorry
He will come back home soon, so Please come here
I don't want to see him
He is my son for sure
I will never forgive anyone who opposes me
My Father is ignorant.
I filed a proceeding
It's just an excuse
I understand his position
He think I'll lose if he complains to my mom
That's not fair
He is using bad means
I understand your thinking
the apple doesn't fall far from the tree
He took good care of you
I'm not going to bother him
All I need is for him to recognize me.
If he cuts off with us we can't live
Please withdraw the proceedings
You were more than happy to be his mistress.
But I have no choice to be his son
I demand my legitimate rights
Mom
I've found a apartment near my school. I will live there from tomorrow
What will you do when you move into the apartment?
I want to study alone
I think it would be good for you too
Why?
Why do you think so?
I don't want to see my father's face
Dad is easier to get here if I'm not here
What's wrong, mom?
What's wrong?
You don't hate me anymore, do you?
What are you talking about?
I didn't say that
I thought you won't come here anymore
I thought you abandoned me
I come back home every Sunday
I leave home because I love you, mom
Takeo
Let me sleep here tonight
Can you sleep besides you?
Chairman
Thank you for everything
I leave without seeing you
Please forgive my selfishness
It's not serious case
There is nothing wrong with his brain
Will he get better?
I think he will get better
If he has a strong personality, he won't get sick
He is a mentally weak person
He is in that greenhouse.
You should go there
It's ok if I talk with him?
No problem
Hi
You seem to be fine
I brought some fruits
Our mom was going to see you, but she got cold
She asked me to see you
Is he also mentally illness?
You can't tell who's mentally illness from the outside.
You think I'm the only one with a mental illness
You may also be mentally illness
Our father is completely mentally illness
He is strong and shameless
He doesn't care if others die or his subordinates die
And he makes mistress one after another
He's crazy because of the wealth he's saved
I read a newspaper
Father seems to build a school
Yes, today is the groundbreaking ceremony
He's working very hard.
So he is mentally illness
Will he educate the young men?
What kind of education does he do?
He can teach nothing
Brother, tell him
I am against your school
If my dad really builds a school, I will announce my dad's badness to the media
If it didn't work, I'm going to kill myself by jumping off the roof of his school.
I'm going to kill myself!
Hey, don't be mad
Ok, so I will come to see you again
(Groundbreaking ceremony saying)
Madam
I have a favor of you
OK
Tamiko and kaneko
I will cut relationship with them
They have your children
Actually they are already old
You may get angry if I say it
Old mistresses are worthless.
You are too bad
And the kids are already college students
I don't think they would be comfortable with me attending their home.
So they file cognitive proceedings and leave home
I think it's better to break the relationship with my mistress for the sake of the children
So you are asking me to tell them about it?
That's right
You're the only one I can ask.
So How much you owe them?
Well...How about 5 million yen?
That's a lot
I also wanted such a master
In our case, it was just 300000yen
So can you?
I have no choice
It's hard to tell them about it
I'm in trouble if she cries
I know how you feel.
I will pay you the reward
I will be free
By the way, Is Mitsuko fine?
I separated with her
Oh really?
She left home
She is missing now
Then you have no place to go home right now
That's why I'm here
I need to look for new mistress
Do you know anyone nice?
Is Geisha girl OK?
They are easy to pick
They can easily be mistresses with money
Do you take good care of your mistress?
His mistress seems to be a businesswoman now
Right
If they quit my job as a geisha, they'd be bored.
So in the daytime she goes golfing with her boyfriend
It ’s not so good to deal with geisha.
I see
Miyo-Chan
Can you call Komamo-san?
Tell her where she will go, and Ask her to come here
How old are you?
Are you already 60?
Or you are younger?
You don't have to care about my age
I'm not virgin
Yes I know
I will obey anything if you give me money
But I hate being called a mistress
I feel insulted when people say that to me.
So keep it secret that I'm your mistress
It's selfish, but please understand
Which means I'd like to pretend I'm only having an affair.
Don't spend the money in my room
I will save all money
When you dump me, you'll give me a handout?
About 1 million yen
Yes, sure
I'm glad
I will start a business with the money
I'm thinking of opening a beauty salon
Oh that's good
If I'm in love from now on, the other person will surely be a poor man
I hate marrying old people, no matter how rich they are
It's a waste of my youth.
After all,I want to marry a young person
Don't you think so?
This document does not have the father's name
No, there is no
Is there any reason?
I am the son of a mistress.
I see
We don't use such words now
It is written in the Six Codes that I am a son
But Actually I am the son of a mistress.
Will your father acknowledge?
Now I'm suing it in the family court
What? Are you son of Arima?
What kind of person is he?
He is a solid and good young man
Is he spy?
But if he's a spy, he won't call himself
Hmmm...ok
I will meet him
I will bring him
But why don't you join Seihoku Electric Railway?
You can join the company without taking the entrance exam
My father refused to join me
Can you come?
He is our chairman,Kazuki
Take your seat
Your dad and I are close
It's ironic that you want to get a job at my company
Do not misunderstand.
I am seriously hoping to join your company
That's ironic
Your dad is my competitor
He is great business man
The train will open soon
In addition he does an education business
I've heard rumors that he's getting a medal from the government.
I heard that you have filed a proceeding against Arima for a request for recognition.
Is that true?
That's true
Is it possible for you to win?
No at all
Why?
He's your father, so it's natural to recognize
I think so but
He refuses to legally acknowledge it.
That's not logical
If this goes to trial, you'll win.
I see
But I have no legal costs
Shall I support you?
I can help you
Thank you very much
But this is a matter of blood between parent and child.
I want to solve it with him
Do I Pass Your Company's Entrance Exam?
You will probably pass
Is Heijiro in?
Well...I'm alone today
He has gone to the mountain with his friends for a few days
He seems to have taken the entrance examination of Kazuki's company
I hear Mr.Kazuki met me during his interview.
He thoroughly opposes me
Hey Kaneko, Listen
I will not recognize him under any circumstances.
I am also stubborn
So you can tell him
Withdraw the proceedings
If you can't, I won't give you what I promised the other day
What do you mean by that?
You won't let him join your company
So it's free for him to join any company
I can't tell him to withdraw the proceeding
He is your son for sure
I...Listen
I won't give you money unless he withdraw the proceedings
Understand?
Yes I get it
I need nothing from you
You are too selfish. Please do whatever you want
He has his own thinking
I think he is doing right
Hey,Kaneko
when you have changed yourself?
I will now file a cognitive lawsuit in support of Heijiro.
Sell this land to make legal costs
This is my duty as his mother
This is the important thing that his life takes
The request of the opposition movement union is 5,000 yen every two months
The bus labor union is also 5,000 yen in two and a half months
Department store union is 2 months
Hotel labor union is one and a half months
They are requesting a reply by the day after tomorrow
The biggest problem is the train union
They will go on strike for a long time
Depending on our reply, they will go on strike soon
I have experienced a lot of strikes
I will know the result
I wouldn't be surprised if the train stopped for 4 or 5 days
But now is not a good time.
It's not a good idea to prolong the fuss and get involved in the opposition to the Takeyama Line.
I'm sure the union folks will think of that too.
Accept a little bit of their request
Instead, be tough on them next year.
Get ready now.
Let the noisy person get a job title
Put them in positions such as chief or section chief.
Then gather people who are supportive of our company policy
Do you want to create a second union?
Yes
I will prepare funds of 200 million yen and 300 million yen
You must act in secret.
Makita-san
From now on, advanced technical education is required
Reduce general liberal arts departments and increase specialized departments
I see
It develops Japan
Technologyd countries dominate the world economy
I noticed it so I will invest in it
I have no profit but this is a national business
I think you are right
I will talk about it when I meet the Minister of Education next time.
What is master doing?
He is in ready to go
Congratulations on receiving the medal
Congratulations
Katsuhei Arima
You have been in the transportation business for many years
In developing the area along the railway line
You have developed society and contributed to the industry
I would like to commend you for your achievements
Prime Minister Takeo Ikehara
How do you feel about receiving the medal?
Not particularly good or bad
I heard you start an education business
Education business is hard to make a profit
I don't for profit
I do for society
I see
By the way I hear Heijito Yokota is your son
He took the entrance exam for my company and passed with excellent grades
He is good young man
You kidnap him
He seems to have filed a proceeding for recognition against you.
Yes
You should recognize him.
Let him write that you recognizes but does not give property
This is the best way
Chairman
Excuse me
Chairman,There is a problem
School is on fire
School is on fire?
How much?
I don't know well
I just got a call from the head office
I hear our school is on fire
Don't make loud voice
I'm leaving here at 8 pm
Find out how much damage it did.
You go there first
Yes
I guess someone set on fire
Chairman is here
How much damage ?
Only classroom
The glass in the main building was just broken
Please arrange a disaster recovery related company
Yes
Please be sure to make it in time for the entrance ceremony
Someone set on fire as you thought
I will not return you home unless I speak honestly
I know what you did yesterday
Someone gave a secret notice
What did I do?
Please speak up.
I'm uncomfortable with suspicion.
Are you uncomfortable?
It's an exaggeration
Then I'll tell you
You set on fire to Seihoku school last night
You have only one parent?
I feel sorry for your mom.
You are unfaithful
Your mother must be crying now
Do you know what the punishment for arson is?
The person who set fire to the house where people live is sentenced to death
Or life imprisonment or imprisonment for 5 years or more
Two years or more imprisonment for arson in an uninhabited building
Well...Will you be in jail for 7 or 8 years?
What kind of grudge did you have at that school?
I said I didn't do anything!
I don't even know where his school is.
What proof do you guys have?
I get it
If you don't admit, stay here tonight
Stand up!
What the hell!
It has long been known that Arima's family has problems.
His life and dating are very simple
When he was young, his mistress went to buy beer when he had a visitor
What is that?
This is your biographical book
I thought I will know better about you
I bought this on release day
All written in the book is lie
I often hear your rumors at parties
They say you are strong and powerful
But never mind.
The more I read the book the more I think you are amazing!
Hello? from Iwabuchi
It's me.
What can I do for you?
I got a call from police about the fire last night
Ok. then?
It seems that the criminal was found
But....
As I told you
It's Akihiko
What? Akihiko?
But he is in the hospital
He's turned himself in.
He said he got out of the hospital last night and set the school on fire
OK
I get it
What's wrong?
It's nothing
He has no hobbies
If he has a hobby, he can turn it into a business
He thinks it's his idea to make a business out of it.
He doesn't have a hobby so he doesn't need money
He has no desire to save his fortune
He uses the profits of the business for the business
He is not an old type of businessman
He recognizes freedom of thought and freedom of speech
He understands true democracy
He's a modern businessman.
I have been waiting for you
Your school has been burned
You have no right to run a school
You think I'm crazy, right?
But I'm not
You are crazy
A crazy man build a school and educate people
What will you teach them?
You don't care if other people die or kill themselves to make money.
You buy mistress
Do you train such people?
He has hopeless to get better
The Takeyama line will be open today
That's fine
What's wrong,Mom
Nothing
I just worry about Akihiko
Today is the opening ceremony of the Takeyama line
Congratulations
This is the business I put the most effort into
You can go to see how it looks
I will go to see Akihiko
He is banned from visiting under police guidance
Don't you think he's adorable?
Don't you think you want to see him?
I have no time
You are a terrible person
There is no warm heart in you
I don't want to say this but
You married me because you wanted business money from my dad
I've returned him the money
I don't mean that
He lent money to me and he going to use me
You have got a medal but I feel embarrassed
You think you can control people and the world.
Humans aren't what you think they are.
Dad, about second labor union
We are getting ready for that
Good.
Get it formed before the next fall strike.
I will not forgive those who oppose
So you won't let me to see him?
You can't
It can't be helped because this is a hospital rule.
And he is under police's control
Oh..You are Arima's wife
Please
I got call so I asked police
They don't allow us to see him
By the way, do you know her?
Arima-san
There are visitors for you
Madam!
Look there
Akihiko-san.
I'm here
Akihiko-san!
(Please forget about me)
Banzai!