Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kokoro no Nichigetsu (1954)
I've tried to look around, but there's no sleeping seat.
Can't find one?
Really?
It's fine now.
Thank you for your hard work.
but it's not good.
I want you to have a rest.
Don't call me Madam.
That's what I always say.
This is bad card.
Don't be loud.
There are passengers.
Where's my card?
Where has it gone?
I'm sorry.
Here it is.
Yes this is.
I hate this card.
I'm sorry for being so noisy, really.
Eri-chan, let's stop now
You get excited too easily, so that's not good
Riding the train is tiring
What time do we arrive?
We'll be arrived at 9:30
Would you like to have this?
I'm sorry.
Eri-chan, but you're too weak to do anything
You're too lazy.
You really need to sleep better.
I apologize for the inconvenience, but she had a drink before getting on.
Oh, Eri-chan, you are too heavy.
This person is causing trouble, so please sit here.
Eri-chan, it would be rude to lean against her.
Don't worry.
This space is available, please.
I sincerely apologize for the inconvenience.
I shouldn't have brought someone like her.
I was persistently told that I should definitely take her to Osaka.
Osaka is a lively place, isn't it?
Where did you board from?
From Okayama
Okayama?
Speaking of Okayama,Rice is famous.
Where to?
Tokyo.
Well, I'm glad we could go together.
I am the type who can't sleep on the train.
Wanna eat oranges?
Don't worry.
It's tough to sit all night, isn't it?
Have a Cigaret?
I know you don't want.
Arrive 9:30 to Tokyo.
Shimbashi is just a little earlier.
How long does it take to get from Tokyo Station to Ichigaya Mitsuke.
about 10 minutes by taxi
Oh, it's your first time in Tokyo?
Yes.
Well, it's tough to be alone
If you'd like, I can accompany you
It's not far from Tokyo Station.
Don't worry.
It won't take long for one taxi, and I think I can go by myself
I see.
I'm worried about something, you know
I got on from Osaka, right?
Actually, I felt that way from the moment I saw you.
I'm sorry
It's because I like someone like you
I thought it would be a bit romantic
Please have a sandwich.
Oh yeah.
I'm giving you my business card
If you happen to be in Ginza, please do stop by
I assure you,I am nothing suspicious.
please do stop by.
Thank you very much.
I've really started to like you.
Please have a  sandwich.
in from the countryside to Tokyo
People flowing in under various fates
This person, Reiko Minagawa, also ran away from her mother-in-law in Okayama and is now in Tokyo.
In a hurry, the local authorities
Feudal marriages are still common in rural areas.
Reiko also did it at home because of it.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Yes, it's here.
Here's Sanyo dormitory.
Just a moment.
I think he's here.
Isomura-san, it's a phone call.
Is it for me?
Yes, it is.
Hello? This is Isomura
I'm Minagawa.
Minagawa?
This is Minagawa from Okayama.
from Okayama?
Are you Reiko?
Yes It's Reiko.
So, I came out to Tokyo.
When did you come?
Where are you now?
I'm in front of Iidabashi Station
I'm at the public phone in front of the station.
so come over here right away.
It doesn't take much time to get here from Iidabashi
Ah, but
Your place has more guests from Okayama Prefecture?
Yes.
Yes, it seems that there are mostly students from Okayama Prefecture here
Um, if I happen to be seen by someone who knows me when I visit there...
Hello?
Isomura-san
I ran away from home.
I understand.
I'll head over there right away.
It's Iidabashi Station, right?
I'll wait at the station entrance.
As soon as you cross the bridge, there's the entrance to the station, right?
Yes, I understand
Then I'll go right away, it should take about ten minutes
Don't be rush.
This is my shoe.
How long does it take from here?
it should take about ten minutes
even walking would take about ten minutes.
Oh, I'm really sorry.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Yes it is.
Is Isomura there?
He just went out.
When was it?
It was about 1 hour ago
anyone came to visit me?
I just received a call again,
A woman?
Yes. Her voice was beautiful
She said she would come here?
She just asked me if you went out.
Excuse me.
Is this really Iidabashi?
Iidabashi?
Yes.
Since then, no one has come to visit?
No one has come to see us.
That's strange, no phone calls or anything?
No.
He acts weird.
He's always like that.
Yes, yes, that's right.
Ah, it's you from earlier.
Mr. Isomura just left right after coming home.
Ah, wait, wait a moment please
It's a telegram from Kenjiro Okada
Oh from dormitory superintendent.
Hello? I don't know because Mr. Isomura has also gone out
Isomura has gone back and forth on this road between Iidabashi and the lodging countless times.
However, Isomura, who is somewhat laid-back and not yet accustomed to the city,
He does not notice that there are two entrances to Iidabashi Station
Iidabashi Station has two entrances: one on the Iidabashi side
and the other closer to Ushigome.
Hey Isomura?
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for someone I promised to meet.
is it a woman? Well, I don't wanna disturb you.
but it's fine now.
No matter how long I wait, She won't come.
At what time do you promise?
She called me at one point.
Well, hasn't it been five or six hours already?
She stood up you.
Yeah, let's go home
but It wouldn't happen.
Did you make a promise to meet here?
the entrance of Iidabashi Station
Then did you go over there too?
over there?
There's another entrance.
As I thought
Go there.
This way is faster.
Excuse me.
was there a young woman around here?
Yes She was.
She was a young and cute lady, right? It seemed like she had been waiting for quite a while
So, it was just about fifteen minutes ago.
It seemed like she took a taxi there.
Hello?
Yes, yes,
Okane?
that's right.
She visited there?
No one has come even once
Not at all
If it's Isomura-kun, I'll take care of it.
please wait a moment.
I'm switching with superintendent now
Hello? Hello? Hello?
He hang up the phone.
It seems it was from Isomura-kun?
Unfortunately, The phone hangs up, but I think he will be back shortly.
Did the maid not hear the name of the woman
who called Isomura?
It seems that she didn't say her name.
That's why I sent a telegram
It's your fault, you know. It's proof that your supervision isn't thorough
I’m sorry.
I rushed here from Okayama like this,
it doesn't mean anything at all.
Who's he?
That person is scary, right?
In Okayama Prefecture, He's the richest
He built this dormitory for us
That's great.
Shut up.
That call is definitely from Reiko
especially since Isomura hasn't come back, she must be Reiko Minagawa.
He's just gang, not student.
Reiko is my fiancée
He seduced her even though he was a student.
I know everything.
I also know that Reiko turned down my marriage proposal and ran away from home
Everyone is just because of Isomura.
I beg your pardon, but...
The student Akira Isomura, based on his usual behavior,
He's very good man.
You don't have eyes for people.
I even know that Isomura is exchanging letters with Reiko
However, the student Isomura, who is from Okayama, is...
He is indebted to you for your assistance.
That's why he's bad.
He can live in Tokyo without lodging because of me.
But well, it can't be helped
It's unacceptable for a student to stay here.
Get him out from here.
Yes it is.
Is Isomura back?
Oh, Isomura? Please wait a moment
Is Isomura here?
She got a call from a woman, and he went out
Um, hello? he went out with a woman
he still hasn't come back
I truly feel sorry for you.
I see, thank you very much.
Even a trivial mistake can often determine a person's fate
Some seek death for that reason
However, some unexpectedly find themselves on a different shore because of it
And again, they take a new step into life with a hand grenade
Good morning.
Don't you think that's a bit strange?
What is?
Since Minagawa became the president's secretary
the president come to company early.
Our president is serious man.
Is that so?
Well then, could you call Mr. Kudo
Who are you?
I am Akemi, the president's younger sister.
I apologize for that.
it's fine.
Quickly call Mr. Kudo.
The chief,right?
Yes.
Oh dear, I'm sorry.
I have a small favor to ask of you.
It is forbidden by the president to give you your allowance.
so it's a bit rude, right?
I don't mean that.
I would like to have one person hired as an employee, you know
employee?
He's still a student,
He has to work to support myself
I met him at a pachinko parlor
he's a student working part-time at a pachinko parlor
It's a problem that  he's still student.
But what does the president say?
Don't ask him.
He's a useless president doesn't pay any attention to someone like me
Oh, by the way, I was just informed by his wife
Why don't you hire him as your housekeeper?
As expected, thank you.
Resume is fine.
That’s fine, and the guarantor is Madam, ok?
Is it really true that they say it’s over just like that?
Thank you
Take care of this.
Please repair it.
Help me to tie this.
This is too flashy.
Welcome back.
You back home early.
Have you gotten used to the company little?
The president is a really nice person.
By the way, I can't see Kudo-san lately.
Oh, He just got here the day before yesterday
He was really drunk
Company will pay the bill.
Please don't lend money too much about the others
Thank you.
Rei, you're still thinking about it, huh?
Don't worry.
You can't keep worrying forever
If you're feeling regret, just forget it
I'll do it.
But honestly, I think about what would have happened if I hadn't met you back then
Really.
It was good I could give you my business card, He's still a student, right?
I don't know what students are thinking these days.
Listen, I'm telling you all this too
Don't trust any man too much.
Men often say things without thinking
All men are play boy.
Men hit on women all the time.
but it doesn't always work out that way
In the end, it's a source of suffering
Well, after all, We are women, we are lonely.
It's time for some love philosophy
Welcome.
It's been ages.
Oh, there’s been a business issue in Kobe for a while
Just wait a moment, I will tidy up the room on the second floor right away.
You can come up if you want
Who is the girl down there?
I don't know.
Good morning
Was that OK?
We managed it.
That's good.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Is my bros there?
From your house.
yes, yes, it's me
Brother? Isomura-san is starting to work today.
How long will it be just walking the dog?
I don't know about that either. Ask Ritsuko.
My sister is not here
Can I decide? I will decide, so
please teach me French too
I'm not very confident,
I'll give you more rewards.
Your mother wants to know his background.
He's Akira Isomura, not from Hiroshima but from Okayama.
His family is poor, but he's talented.
He's in trouble after being kicked out of his university dorm.
The reason He was kicked out is....
That is suspicious.
Hey.
Reiko has finally gotten used to life in the building
and has discovered a way to heal the terrible shock she experienced by working through it,
and these days she is already part of the president's desk
She even felt like trying to decorate a magazine with flowers
She take the leftover flowers from Madame's shop every morning
and replace them daily
And then..
Good morning.
It seems like you have quite active.
Minagawa.
What time is the meeting with Shimamura-san?
It is scheduled for eight o'clock.
Thanks.
Um, what is this that you've given me?
Why?
I offered it as a thank you for the flowers
It's you who brings flowers every morning
The flowers are for use at home.
and this perfume is the same.
I was asked by my wife, so I bought two.
But something like this...
even this flower is quite nice
Flowers and perfume are different.
They are the same.
Perfume is something I made with flower.
Please take it.
Thank you very much.
It smells good.
Let me smell it.
This is awesome.
It must cost around 20000.
Don't talk about the prices.
It smells good.
this is something the president gave me.
This is a French perfume.
This is a very luxurious perfume
You really should accept something like that?
He is into you.
Oh, the president isn't like that at all
That's fine, but there are two types of ways men approach things
One is to take a forceful approach.
and the other is to pretend to be serious at first and then reveal one's true self
Which one is me?
You seem to do both
She gradually understand that a job that adds some excitement to life is important
Commuting to work every day becomes enjoyable
Good morning.
Hey, don't you think it's strange?
What is?
Isn't the president coming back later these days?
That's true
don't you think it's strange?
The president seems to be in a really good mood lately
He must be in love with someone.
People are not what they seem
Maybe I should just quit
it seems that the president's wife has some business with you
You are the president's secretary, aren't you?
Yes
Thank you for taking care of my husband.
Do you bring these beautiful flowers every day?
That job is hard
What do you mean by giving him flowers?
Please be clear about it
We haven't misunderstood each other over trivial matters
There is no particular meaning to that.
You're kind.
Did my husband give you anything in return?
I received some perfume from him some time ago.
Then?
And then, I received this brooch
It really suits you, doesn't it? That clothes too?
Well, this was made by my older sister.
I understand.
It seems like I've gotten into a bit of trouble.
This is a diamond brooch
Anyway, This is an order from my wife.
I'm saying that I want you to quit immediately
Moreover, if I talk to the president, he might try to stop you
I'm saying that we should make it look like you are resigning voluntarily
This is like a traffic accident.
Please accept it.
I have done nothing wrong.
Thank you very much.
Osaka is fine.
Oh, thank you very much
Um, I have a bit of a situation, and I would like to resign
Would you quit your job?
Why?
I'm going to quit because I have a bit of a situation
If there is something going on, I can't just stop
And I can't just intrude and ask again
Are you dissatisfied with the treatment you receive at your company?
No.
It's not like that.
if that's the case, then there's nothing I can do
However, I wanted you to stay with me all along
When will you leave the company?
It's better to do it sooner rather than later
Well, starting tomorrow, I won't be able to accept this flower
Thank you very much for everything.
Reiko.
Let's shake hands once as a farewell.
Reiko, I liked you
I wish you happiness.
Reiko.
I didn't notice you.
How do you like your job?
Thank you for everything
Thanks to you, I found job soon.
Did you like it?
I'm still not used to it.
I asked the manager about you.
You wanna meet him?
He's too great for me.
He is my funny friend from the club and a laid-back guy
Yes, let's go with that after all
For now, let's have a meal together
It's better to become acquainted directly for future advantages
But.
it's okay
I'll go with you. What time are we meeting?
I can leave by six-thirty
Then I'll go around back and bring the car at that time
Thank you so much for everything.
Let me see this.
Welcome.
This?
Isomura-san, over here.
Aren't you going to buy a dictionary?
Let's not put that off.
we should go buy a good one quickly.
Let's go.
Let's see them.
How about watching Bra?
Yeah, okay
Welcome.
Look at this.
Well, what do you think about that?
Does this suit me?
I wonder if it's good.
Oh.
Are you Minagawa?
I've met you before, you know
I'm sorry I didn't notice you.
Do you work here now?
I know a little bit about it
I'm sorry, but that's just how that wife is
She is a very old-fashioned person
She is very jealous.
Their marriage is not going well.
Is it my fault?
No.
I think that's the wife's fault.
So when the president found out, he was very angry.
Their relationship is very bad now.
I'll come back later.
but you like him,right?
She's here.
Oh, please come in.
sorry for being late
No, no, no, The manager hasn't come yet.
Please have this first
Is the usual food okay?
Yes please.
It's nice to come to such a calm place once in a while.
What are your hobbies?
Has the manager arrived yet?
it's late, isn't it?
The shopkeeper turned off the lights.
They care about our moods.
I have to go.
There is a light switch there
Where is the switch? I can't find it.
but that's strange
Isn't it around here?
It should be here
Reiko.
Don't do that.
Eventually, Reiko came home completely exhausted.
Fortunately, everyone is asleep
She stood in the late-night streets waiting for everyone to fall asleep before heading home
She didn't want anyone to see her like this
What if Madame sees her?
Reiko?
I'm home.
You're late
You can't sleep in a place like that
Come quickly, please come quickly.
No matter how you cry, I won't understand
Hurry up and tell me, who made you go through that?
I know I'm foolish,
so I understand that you are the fool.
You were taken to such a place
Is he Shinohara?
Sister.
I knew it would be like this.
So what happened to you? Did you lose?
Listen, I didn't sleep with him.
Stop it....
Her fingers are gradually losing strength
Her knees are shaking and trembling, she think it's really over, she see the window.
I had jumped out of that round window and rolled onto the roof.
It was impressive.
I'm glad, I'm glad! Thank you.
It was my fault.
Knowing someone named Shinohara,
I'm sorry I ask you to work there.
After all, this wasn't a place for you
Thank you for waiting
I am looking for a handkerchief.
What kind?
I'm looking for a handkerchief with a beautiful design.
how about this?
Oh
I heard from my sister that you were here
It's been ages.
Kudo told me why you quit your job.
I apologize for the inconvenience
Is this a handkerchief with a Japanese design?
Yes.
I'll take this.
I hope to see you again somewhere soon
Huh? Then please prepare this.
Well then, I'll take two thousand yen.
I'm sorry for being late.
Ah, welcome back! It was such a nice room
I completely liked it.
Madam is here too.
Oh really?
I'm sorry for being late.
Welcome back, How was it? It's a nice room, isn't it?
Thank you for cleaning up too.
oh, could you please hand me that?
You're safe here now
Also, just to be cautious, I rent here down under my name
Oh, by the way put this up.
will you put that up?
I'll help it.
Are you Watanabe-san?
I just moved in today
Nice to meet you.
I'm Onodera Daisaku is in that room
Should I help you?
Don't worry.
I plan to move into another apartment.
Who is he?
He said, "The student across the street."
You have to be careful; students these days are...
Be careful.
Ah, that's Ok.
Welcome.
Do you have any handkerchiefs for gifts?
How about this?
If it's okay with you,
I'm embarrassed.
Do you have no work tomorrow?
would you like to join me for dinner tomorrow
I just made plans to meet with this friend a little while ago
That's too bad.
Well then, please let me know about the next time.
One dozen please
Yeah, Look at them.
Isomura....
bonsoir mademoiselle
Why do you keep looking at my face?
It feels strange to me.
Why are you fidgeting?
It's because you lack composure
Well then, let's leave it at this for today.
I wanna stay with you more.
but I do have some appointment today
Oh, you're so mean.
Have you made it?
Let's drink.
Come in.
Oh you, join us.
I'm busy.
Ah, thank you for this!
Hey, don't rush, sit down.
Isomura.
I was just talking about it.
There are plenty of women in the world.
You don't have to wait outside on a cold day for a woman
How many days now?
It's already the third day
Do you think she will show up?
You should give up?
A beautiful woman moved into the room across the room.
If you take a peek, you might change your mind
I have to go.
Well, you're a pitiful guy.
Are you standing around at the station again tonight?
Isomura?
I don't think she's coming tonight either.
Welcome.
Could I have a handkerchief?
How about that?
It's been turned into a pharmaceutical product, though
So, I'll have this one dozen, is there anything else?
Well, He often buy handkerchiefs
How about this?
They are curious about us
Then I will try not to come as much as possible
At least,we can have a dinner tonight's Christmas.
I would be happy to join you, if that's alright with you.
Please come here.
I'll buy this.
Thank you very much.
Is this Yurakubashi?
Yes.
I'll get off here.
I'll be waiting at Yurakubashi forever.
forever.
Hey.
There's really no need to panic
Well, anyway, I have to go and see
Are you standing there again?
Please go and eat some soba noodles.
The rest I leave to you
He is a very unusual young man.
To Teikoku Hotel.
Sorry for making you wait.
I thought you might not be here.
I'm here.
I'm glad to come here.
Reiko, we shook hands when you left the company, didn't we?
But now that we can meet again
what I said back then...
Do you still remember?
I like you, and I still love you even now
I love you.
Since then, my wife and I haven't been getting along well
No, I'm not saying it's your fault.
It's due to fundamental reasons, but we are currently living apart
And my wife finally demanded a divorce
Eventually, you'll go through that process.
But I feel so liberated.
Is that bad?
I like you.
Sorry.
I met someone.
Who?
I met a man who shocked me.
Is that true?
Yes.
I am heartbroken.
Isomura, why are you just reading books?
Are you scared of me?
None of your friends have been considerate of us.
I'm not scared at all.
Then are you okay being here alone with me?
Well, I am a little cautious too
Because you are man.
There's no need for that
I'm a gentleman.
so I guess I can relax and go to sleep now.
What's wrong? Akemi.
is there something wrong?
Please tell me.
I hate it.
Let me go.
Well then, Please take care of it quickly.
So let's make sure to get.
It's a big deal, I have a problem.
Please leave,Kudo.
When did you come back?
I've just arrived.
I want to get married
Who are you going to marry?
With Isomura.
Hey, you say that so easily
However, if it's with him, I agree
But He's still a student
I can't wait for his graduation
My enemy has appeared.
Your enemy has appeared?
In other words, it's Isomura's girlfriend. He had a girlfriend
At least his ex-girlfriend.
but it's something that concerns you too, brother
Isomura's girlfriend is the Reiko Minagawa who was here
You were surprised, weren't you?
So you can't just stay calm
You like Minagawa-san, right?
Then Let's do this.
In other words, if I marry Tamura-san,
then you'll be with Minagwa.
By the way, both of them are from Okayama.
I'm sure it's something like that evidence
Until then, there were many times I thought it was strange.
Why are you spacing out?
Did you call for me?
Have a seat.
I wanna talk to you about something
I know this is sudden and a bit reckless, but...
Actually, it's about my sister. Akemi has said that she wants to marry you
I had also heard about that from her.
So, I wanted to hear your thoughts on it as well
I think it's something to be grateful for
Do you like her?
I don't dislike her
However, do you have someone else you like?
I want you to tell me the truth.
But that's something that has happened from the past.
Is that person named Minagawa Reiko?
Huh? How do you know that?
To put it frankly,
Minagawa worked for my company as a secretary.
Isomura.
To put it frankly,
I also love Reiko-san.
To be more honest,
I even think that I want to marry Reiko in the future
but of course,
that's just my own thought
By the way, actually today I heard from my sister about you and Reiko
Rather than being unexpected, I was more surprised
Then my sister said that she wants to marry you
I think there are some subtle issues around that,
and I’ve laid everything out for you.
I'm fine with my situation now.
What does that mean?
I don't feel anything for Reiko anymore
More importantly, we never made a promise to get married from the beginning
We just got to know each other during my time in Okayama and had a little emotional connection
So, it was just that we were two beautiful first loves
No, rather, I should have said that I was the one who made Reiko unhappy
Shortly after I moved to Tokyo, Reiko-san also came to Tokyo, relying on me due to her dark family circumstances
At that time, we made a promise in front of the Iidabashi station
Being careless, I didn't notice that there were two entrances to Iidabashi station
We couldn't meet up.
I can imagine how much Reiko-san, who had just
come to Tokyo for the first time, struggled.
Since then, it seems she hold a grudge with me.
I think it's only natural
Since then, you guys haven't seen each other at all?
Right.
However, once we meet again, there will be no way to regain the affection we had that crumbled
Originally, I didn't have the power to make her happy.
How can someone who doesn't even have the power to make others happy have the right to love?
But I finally feel like I've lifted a burden off my shoulders.
Please.
Could you please marry her and make her happy?
Thank you, Nishimura-kun
Thank you for waiting
Thank you very much
Welcome.
This?
Well...
There's a call for you.
Leave it to you.
Welcome.
Hello? This is Nakata
I have something to discuss
Could you please come at the entrance of Iidabashi Station at 8 AM tomorrow?
that's the entrance of Iidabashi Station?
Yes,that's it.
I have a good story for you.
I understand, tomorrow at eight in the morning
Iidabashi
Just as I thought, you were at this exit.
I was waiting at the entrance on the other side for a while
other side?
There are two entrances to this station on the other side
the entrance on this side
and the other one at Ushigome exit.
Don't worry.
The person waiting for you is at the entrance over there.
Well then, may you always be happy.
Isomura-san.
Reiko-san.
THE END