Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Konki / The Age of Marriage (1961)
Sweetie !
Hello?
Welcome.
Namiko sis.
I really like the water pressure.
Ours is bad.
Here's clean.
I like here.
I'll at least offer you some tea.
I even got compliments on the water pressure in the bathroom.
Oh yeah,
Look at this.
Let me see.
This is cool.
I want this.
We are currently busy and are not accepting orders from anyone other than our regular customers.
I'll order it later.
He used money all.
Oh.
Because she is away from him now.
We are miserable.
She'll need the money if she studies at the theater company.
I can only make a little money teaching calligraphy.
Sorry to bother you.
Don't worry.
I came here by chance.
When is the calligraphy lesson?
2pm.
Hatoko will go to theater lesson from 3pm.
I'll have lunch here.
I haven't eaten yet.
Wanna eat noodle?
Then I wouldn't have come here.
I came here while talking with my sister about how delicious pickles are.
Ask her to make it.
Who?
Shizuka.
Here's your letter.
From whom?
Don't you know?
Have you cleaned Namiko and the kids' rooms yet?
You'll be scolded if you don't hang up your bedding soon.
I'll leave you to it.
Wife.
waistcoat.
It's not a waistcoat, it's underwear.
She's busy.
Baya.
Yes.
I awake.
I'm hungry.
Did you know that your husband Takuo has a mistress?
He has a baby now.
Your husband's love is no longer entirely yours
Wife.
Denjiro wanna eat ham egg but there's no egg.
I think there was one egg.
No.
I kept it.
Really?
Where's the egg?
What a strange.
You ate it.
Me?
I will buy some eggs with my money.
Denjiro
There's a salad here, so bear with it.
You're stingy.
It tastes good.
I like your cooking.
Watch out the bone.
What's wrong?
If our mother were alive, if we hadn't gone through all this trouble...
Here she goes again.
We're like housemates.
No.
Yes we are.
Why don't you go out on your own?
No, women can't.
Your brother must be in trouble.
He inherited his dead father's estate.
He switched his business and now runs a Chinzan inn.
You better find a good guy soon.
All the guys in the troupe were part-timers.
I was disappointed when I joined.
I don't care if I'm just looking for love.
Do you have any good men for me?
You are still young, so you should choose your man more carefully.
I'm too old.
I'm okay with men up to 40 years old.
If he has any kids?
He's better off not having kids.
But it's depends.
You have fallen behind.
Yes I'm looser.
I'm 29.
This year?
No.
You look young.
Yeah.
You're 24?
I'll turn to 25.
I feel scary.
What's wrong?
Water.
You are still eating.
Excuse me.
You're just fantasizing about ideals
Will you preach to me again?
I'm right.
I'm just being cautious because I'm looking at you.
All men are the same.
Marriage isn't everything in life.
It's nice to know someone who's been married before.
It's nice to break up too.
I feel like a sellout.
You say that and then nothing gets done.
Oh there is.
I found this here.
I'm sure hatoko or Namiko put it here.
It seemed like I lied.
She played a prank on me.
Have a good day.
What a surprise!
Hi.it's me.
Tell my sister to pick me up around 9:00 p.m. today.
Of course.
You're young, so you should go home early.
What are you talking about? I'm a virgin.
Even if you're not a virgin, the danger is in the same
That's what I'm talking about.
Did you hide the egg?
Egg?
Why I had to do that?
I'm not stupid enough to say that over the phone.
She's so stupid.
Did you know that your husband Takuo has a mistress?
He has a baby now.
No mail came when I was out?
No.
Are you sure?
I'll take care of it.
It would be quicker if I did it with yours.
I don't like it if I don't do it myself.
I see.
Wife.
I'll go pick up a virgin girl.
But you can't walk.
I wouldn't mind losing my chastity.
What are you talking about?
I thought you never had it.
Don't talk so loud.
I've had three husbands.
Not all at once
They died one after another.
You are greedy.
But...
Stop saying it.
Baya.
The light is off.
Namiko told me to turn off unnecessary lights.
Shall I turn them on then?
Take care.
There are so many commands that I'm at a loss.
I'm not very good at this ironing thing.
I'm afraid of this electric thing.
That's right... a silk one.
Don't do that.
Let me do it.
You're good.
A man with a wife like mine is truly a lucky man.
Yeah.
Cooking school, tea, flowers, dressmaking.
Watercolors, piano, embroidery, knitting...
Knitting, Kamakura carving...
And..
French.
Yes.
Gymnastics History Pearls Addition Subtraction Multiplication
That's not a school.
You've learned everything you need to know.
You just don't know how to use it.
I'm like Okubo Hikozaemon.
It's pointless to learn in a broad and shallow way
People like it.
There's a song about who did this to me.
It's all society's fault
Men are to blame.
Men are so blind.
You are Such a beautiful young lady.
But no one want you.
I just had fat legs.
I'm jealous of wife.
What do you mean?
She hangs her waistcoat all year round.
She's not wearing a waistcoat, she's wearing underwear.
She's busy.
She's the one who's shifting this wife.
Men are so blind.
It's like the saying, "A cracked pot with a mashed lid.
Her husband's a cracked pot?
He's a very handsome man.
He is very strict with money management.
Fold them.
Help yourself.
You won't improve at all even if I teach you.
Did the mail come today?
No letter for you.
For wife.
Thank you very much.
What's the hell?
No.
Hatoko.
Wait.
Sweet potato
I'm like a bodyguard.
It's normal to protect young people.
Still, you must have a lot of courage with her.
It helps her, doesn't it?
Is she ok?
She seems not care about the letter.
She's so cheeky.
Maybe she doesn't trust that her husband is having a baby.
She's so proud.
She know she's the only one who got love from him.
She's in it for the fortune.
She thinks that once we're done, she'll be free to do whatever she wants.
I won't let her have her way.
Shall I wash your body?
Don't worry.
She pretends to be a good housewife.
I'd better get you guys to bed early.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
Give me one.
One?
He's finished with his bath.
Bros.
Do me a favor.
I am very tired today
He's boring.
Have a bath.
Have a bath first.
I have to do something.
I'll have bath with her.
You take bath first.
Are there many lines you have to memorize?
Just one line.
Good night. I'll act as nurse.
Then you don't have to read the script.
I'm going to have to say it a dozen times.
I'm sick of it.
I want to quit.
If you have a chance to meet someone nice, you can just quit.
Please take turns taking a bath.
I'm working right now.
We waited for him because we had a favor to ask of Bros.
He said he was very tired today.
Please take a bath quickly.
Shut up!
Let's have a bath.
pass me the glass.
49kg.
That's a lot less.
Glad to hear it.
Oh 55 kg.
You ate a lot at saeko's house.
It can't be helped.
Try measuring my hips
Done?
It's little fat.
What size?
I think you're overweight because you're short.
I won't eat anything tomorrow
You should practice ballet like me.
I'm sure Oshizu tell about the letter to bros.
Denjiro is back.
Hello?
Welcome back.
Come in.
I haven't had dinner yet, so please prepare something.
Welcome back.
I'm home.
You are late.
We were watching a movie.
Let me introduce her
My girlfriend.
Her mother works at my brother's Chinzanso.
Is she maid?
I don't think so?
Head maid?
Manager?
Come in.
My room is there.
He walked a lot.
Wife, if that's her, your sisters see her out and about a lot.
They know her?
Since half year ago.
She's coming over here so late.
Her mom does not care?
I know she use him.
What do you mean?
She thinks he's good target.
I can't believe it.
Apparently her mother gave birth to him while being the mistress of an official.
How could you possibly know that?
Because your sisters told me.
Where's sisters?
They are having a bath.
There.
Good evening.
Welcome.
Thank you very much for the other night.
for taking on so many roles in the troupe.
Not at all.
I'll ask again next time.
There will be a Fukakka play next month.
Fuka?
Fukakka
You don't know what they're doing because it's hard to understand, right?
But she played good.
You didn't play with her,right?
No, but I looked her.
Her acting time was very short.
It was too short.
I was not a passerby.
Please tell your mother to sell tickets to the next show.
Please…
I have a calligraphy exhibition coming up.
Wanna play Majan?
From now?
We have enough people for playing it.
It's beauty time.
Why don't you just sleep until noon tomorrow?
Bros is going out?
Why you care him?
We often see him.
It's beauty time, sisters, so don't push it.
Wanna bet?
Yes.
We can earn money.
OK.
Let's go.
We don't all eat together, so fuel costs go up.
I'm very frustrated with them complaining.
Don't say that. Be patient.
I need you.
Thanks.
I don't need to take a bath.
Ok have a rest.
I have exceeded my working hours so I will take the day off first.
Your husband is leaving tomorrow at 7am.
Is he going to stop by somewhere before he goes?
Your meal is ready at your room.
Ok, let's have meal first.
Baya.
You still have oranges, don't you?
One for each of you
How about snacks?
I forgot if that was the case
Why is there nothing here?
If I buy them, they will be gone before I know it.
I'm sure Bros brought some home from work that someone else gave to him.
She hides everything.
Sis hides it.
Really?
We are not free to eat.
There is always nothing
You think Denjiro eats it?
Don't make him a thief's errand boy.
He's not educated.
I learned a lot from your former owner.
You're getting carried away.
It's okay for the residents of this house to eat snacks freely.
We were born in this house.
She thinks we are leaving soon.
I'm frustrates to live here.
I don't have a life of my own.
What can I help you?
The guests... the lady is staying at sister's room.
I see.
You don't need to carry it yourself.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
I'm afraid I've become a winner.
Denjiro wants you to bring some toys?
What you want?
pat.
Denjiro has baseball pat.
No, pat and tex.
I don't know about it.
You are too old.
Never mind.
Is she staying tonight?
She is bad manners
Yeah, she's really bad.
Do men like women like that?
She won't know unless she live with her.
Even Namiko and her family are graceful to other people.
They used to be nice.
You think they are bad now because of me?
As they get older,their personality gets worse.
Hatoko is now so bad.
Namiko tell her about anything.
I want them to get married and move out of this house.
Don't say that.
But if we don't be strict with them, they'll stay here forever.
their personality gets worse.
They're even worse than last year.
What's the hell?
It's funny, but I think it's serious for the person in question.
The fact that there is no one to sympathize with her must be even more sad for her, since she doesn't have a mother.
She's almost 30.
After all, Saeko-sama.
Their big sister's marriage partner was very egocentric.
They saw her go through a lot of hardships.
That's partly why they think so hard.
When will they get married?
Reach.
You're lucky.
This?
Ron?
I got it.
You made it?
Like someone.
Who?
My sis.
That woman?
She is 29.
Oh she's too old.
She's been Unsold fro a long time.
What's wrong?
I can't see.
Bring my glasses.
It's in the bathtub.
She's sleeping.
Never mind.
you.
Are you sleeping?
Tomorrow ok?
I don't have time to talk to you in the morning.
I'm busy.
You're just sleeping.
Denjiro said he's bringing a girl to stay the night.
Who?
She is the daughter of one of your hotel's employees.
I am in a lot of trouble
Get out her then.
Can you tell him?
You say him.
They are playing majan.
I'm sleeping so you can say it yourself.
They don't listen to me.
Just leave it her.
Her mother might be worried.
Don't worry.
Are you alright?
We don't need to worry about her.
Where did you go last night?
It's none of your business.
I worried.
I slept in the car.
I can't believe it.
You don't have to trust me
I got weird letter that say you have a baby.
I hear you have a mistress, is that true?
No.
Tell us me truth.
If you don't believe me, so be it.
You have no idea what I've been through.
What are you talking about?
I know you had a man.
You weren't virgin.
How can you say that?
I was very disappointed on our honeymoon.
You're just now starting to talk about our honeymoon.
I gained a lot of knowledge before I got married.
You were too much.
You told me I was not kisser.
Don't say that.
Who taught you?
The way you kissed was different from how it was described in the book.
I was going to teach you step by step.
Since then I've lost interest in you
What's the hell?
Show me the letter.
Are you planning to get compensation from me with this plan?
From you?
You're mean.
You think so?
Do you find it interesting to bully someone like that?
Okay, I'll go to the hospital, or wherever, and I'll be vindicated.
It's too late.
You can't prove you were a virgin.
What's so wrong with me?
It's not fun to come home.
That's why I purposely come home late.
If you didn't like me so much, why did you marry me?
I just liked your looks.
Don't think too much.
I knew we should've stayed together you and me only.
That's how you feel, and that's how everyone else feels.
It's your fault.
I worked so hard.
It's a formality.
You're bringing in the fact that you were working for a loan company on your own.
I'm like president, Namiko is manager.
hatoko is chef, Denjiro is co-worker.
You're treating them with class.
I expected the housewife to be the pillar of the family, supporting the stronghold of everyone's trust and love.
You wear a loincloth and makes the maid work
Namiko said that?
If you're good, everyone respects you.
Did you really mean what you said?
Sometimes I'm so busy that I don't have time to take care of myself.
I don't even have time to change the elastic in my underwear when it's stretched out, so it can go down.
My underwear fell down once.
It has nothing to do with your affair.
Don't be loud.
Shut up!
I have to wake up early
Don't lie to me, wake up.
So it's true.
Someone sent that as a prank.
But.
If you don't trust me, you can leave me.
Are you serious?
Yes I am.
Wanna separate with me?
Shut up!
Get out.
Wanna separate with me?
I mean I will get out.
You're terrible.
You insist.
You look funny.
Don't make me laugh, I'll get wrinkles
Oh sorry.
So?
So we went to separate rooms, and we rested.
So you'll sleep separately?
Of course, my husband insisted, so I had no choice.
Marriage is just like going to a maid's house.
A maid gets a day off and a salary.
A maid is much better.
If it's a sex toy, it's not worth it.
It's free.
You think so?
You should divorce him.
You don't have kids yet.
Why don't you get on your feet?
I'm talking about basic human rights.
Why does everyone want to get married?
I can't help but wonder.
I can't work like you.
I'm too old.
What would you do if your husband died?
You have to work.
That's true, but I've persevered this long.
If you persevere, half of the property will be yours.
If that's the case, then you'll have to be patient.
It is doubtful how many people in the world can earn that much in a lifetime of work.
It's a tall tale, depending on how you look at it.
Which would you take?
But if I didn't have love, I wouldn't have persevered this long.
Love can't last forever.
f you're satisfied, I have nothing to say.
And if it's hard work, then it's not hard work at all.
It's time.
Turn it off.
Turn the red light.
He's got money,you don't have  mother-in-law, don't worry about the sisters.
You can control them.
They are pure.
You say that, but I don't have that kind of power.
You're just trying to look good, so they'll want to feel your heart.
They want to see you bare your heart, so they're going to smash your pretensions.
My pretensions?
They don't like your attitude.
I'm not going to let you put a damper on our marriage!
Anyway, he even had a child out of the house!
I can't believe it.
I can't believe it too.
Or if it's a boy and his property is going that way.
But I think that's someone's idea of a prank.
Someone is hoping you'd leave.
He has a girl?
My brother's been a target for a long time.
Women are more likely to leave him alone.
You can't marry a man unless you're prepared for him to be a little unfaithful.
My husband's not like other men. He's reserved with his brothers.
I feel sorry for him.
He thinks it's bad if he makes them look too friendly, so he pushes himself.
If you're so understanding, I have nothing to say.
No man gets a perfect score.
I chose divorce.
You're always clinging on, going your own way.
Oh you.
I can't go out.
I have a fashion show to prepare for.
You don't know that, do you?
You can't just say that out of the blue.
And then there's the silk.
The colors are a little different.
Do you have a deeper color in your company's product?
Please find it and look for it.
I'm sorry.
I'm busy with my work.
Don't be so mad.
I'm sorry.
You've been busy. Are you going out?
Yeah, I was up all night last night.
This pack won't help.
It's hard work, isn't it?
I'm poor and I have no time.
I heard your complaints.
I just wanted to talk to you.
Because if you're not going to break up with him, seeing you is just a waste of time.
And even if he had a child outside, you wouldn't leave.
I don't want to let him have his way.
I see.
Besides, I can't go back to the country and take care of my father and clean up Chestnut Mountain.
I can't do that.
Here is ok?
Yes.
President
Our guests from Kyokuto Petroleum are pleased to know that you are in the OGI ROOM!
I'm glad to hear it.
I heard that the number of attendees will be reduced.
What is our schedule today?
By this evening, we will have two wedding receptions and two meetings.
And for the evening party...
There's a phone call for you, sir.
Excuse me for a moment.
Front desk.
Last night, my daughter Renko accompanied Denjiro to the restaurant.
Ok leave it to you.
I got a call from Tamie.
She said Come to see me tonight.
Why she said it to you?
We were talking about another matter.
You were in the middle of a visit, and I told her I would tell you later.
She was worried that you've been coming home a lot lately.
Tell her not to call me.
Take care.
Oh Tomoe.
Excuse me.
It's been a while.
back home now?
I was just visiting the soap factory, and I thought I'd go home.
How's everyone at the office?
They're fine.
Has anyone quitted working since then?
No.
They are not like you.
Why?
Are you busy on the bed?
Wanna sit?
Don't worry about me.
People are watching us.
The other day, everyone was talking about you.
What kind?
They said you were lucky.
But it seems you have a hard time.
If only I could get rid of my sisters.
Then you will be happy.
Please introduce them to a good man.
I know one good guy.
Who's he like?
My cousin.
I have a picture of him.
But not for me.
He says it's because she's beautiful.
But she have to have a long torso, and not wears glasses,young.
I see.
He.
He looks loopy.
I wonder if they can live on that kind of salary.
His mother has an apartment.
Hatoko can't live with her mom together.
This guy says he doesn't like women with glasses... he's wearing a glass.
He's egoist.
I made it.
He's thinking about genetics.
I get it.
Ok go home.
Why don't you introduce him to my sis?
I also talked to her.
He's not well paid.
The salary of 13,000 yen is too little.
But he has fixed assets.
That's not enough.
He's only son, don't have any siblings.
You'll be like Namiko...
I don't care if he's old.
I don't mind having two or three children
I want to marry someone who has no shortage of money.
I want someone with a fatherly bearing.
I'm offering my youth.
No one will give it to you if you keep talking about ideals.
I had an older brother who died in the war, and an uncle who went to Tokyo University, and I went to a government school, so I didn't really want to go to private school.
But you have to lower your bar a little bit.
Next year, we'll lower the bar.
And my sister, she's going to decide to be whoever she is when March comes next year.
See you.
Are you still looking?
Why don't you meet him?
He might be a nice guy.
It's rare to find someone with a fixed asset nowadays.
You're making an issue out of it, but that's just like you.
Well, I guess I'll say no.
I don't want it to be my fault.
I don't mind dating him.
I wouldn't mind having him buy me a ticket to the theater troupe, or being available to ski or drive with him.
I can say no at the end.
Shall I do that?
It would be very bad for him to do that.
His mother is the problem.
I think I can control her well..
So you want to give it a try?
What?
A test.
A test?
You call the wrong number on purpose.
I see.
What are you going to do?
We can tell who it is by the answer.
What if someone else answers?
I'll say mother.
You know the number?
It says here.
Give it a try.
3.2.1.2
2.4.5
Calling.
Hello, is this wife?
Who is it?
Hello?
Well.
Who is it?
Is that Karasawa?
Your name.
No, I'm not Karasawa.
She hung up.
3.2.1
Do you still call?
2.4.5
Is that Karasawa?
No, I'm not Karasawa.
Hello?
What's the hell?
She' so mad.
That's all.
What time are you coming home tomorrow?
I have a meeting at 12:00.
I can stay till 2:00 p.m.
We can relax.
Nice moon.
Hello, Kasahara here.
Papa? Who?
Wife.
Who?
Well.
I wondered.
She said papa was here.
Hello?
Boya's papa.
Who are you?
Oh wife.
I knew it.
Like this?
Good acting skills.
Realistic.
I'm good actress.
Let's start lesson.
Are you calling your house?
You won't send me home?
Are you all ready?
Here we go.
What's the meaning of Papa?
She was so rude.
She immediately hung up the phone
She's harassing you.
But I got a weird letter the other day.
Let's go to the police station.
Stay like that.
Stop.
Ikeya.
Take this hand down a little bit.
Step back.
Turn around.
How's this?
This is awesome.
That's all.
Thank you for your work.
I hope you all keep up the good work tomorrow.
Excuse me.
What do you think?
Thank you for your work.
Why not make the blue a little darker?
Because it's weak compared to the feeling of the costume.
Excuse me.
Are you busy?
Yeah, we're gonna go to the club now and do a little bit.
Just a little bit.
What?
Watch out for my brother.
He's a playboy.
He's not.
You think so?
Why?
Because he asked me to marry.
Really?
Marriage is a word women love to hear.
He's breaking up with his wife.
Are you going to kick Wife out and marry him?
I wanted to talk to you about that.
Is he serious?
Yes he is.
He has a girl.
Really?
Yes,
Hi Yoshino.
What?
Where's Takuo?
He's left.
I see.
He's gone for Otami?
I have no idea.
Tamie used to be a friend of yours.
I've heard that she owns an apartment building.
Your daughter said.
Renko?
Denjiro,that's what he does, he blackmails the president to get pocket money.
And Renko did too.
They are so terrible.
Where is that apartment located?
It is run by our president.
Did you arrange it?
No way.
Excuse me, I'm in a hurry.
She is very black-hearted.
You.
What's wrong?
I had business.
I'll be home as soon as I'm done.
This is for you.
This is for me.
By the way, I'm going to ask you something.
And is it true that you're going to not give up your Wife?
Well, I'm the first to say it, in case you were wondering.
What have I been working so hard for?
you lied to me?
I didn't.
You did.
She said she was first.
If you leave me, I will go to your house and kill myself by taking poison.
I dedicated my life to you.
You are responsible.
You have to.
I know what I feel.
Don't blackmail me.
You told me to divorce her.
Why you liked this woman?
What do you mean?
You're still kid.
You want money from him?
How did you know here?
I looked it up in the phone book.
I get it.
Don't act weird.
What do you mean?
This is a fact.
You sent the letter?
This is only thing you know.
You have a baby?
Do you want to find a reason to break up with me?
Don't get me wrong.
Don't stay there forever.
You have a woman.
I came here to sort things out.
Come on.
Say hello to your dad.
Hello?
Play there.
Stay here.
She'll leave soon.
What's the hell?
What?
You did it.
What's the hell?
Stop it....
Don't do that.
I'm leaving too.
You're not going to divorce her.
Don't get me wrong.
What are you talking about?
Wait.
Hey.
So you have been threatening me with letters and phone calls?
Well...
Did he threaten to extort money or goods from you?
Not yet.
So she have a purpose to send the letter.
She was complaining to you about something.
I was in bed, so I went out to run an errand.
I don't know about the letter.
Sorry to make you trouble.
Well...so.
That policeman is persistent.
There was no need to call the police.
Wife fell asleep today. I was worried.
What did you say at the police station?
I told him Threatening phone calls and letters arrive
What's the hell?
I asked him to help me find the culprit.
Did you think that was a threatening call?
Do you know about the phone?
Bring it out.
Wait.
Don't tell her about the phone.
You said you wanted to pursue it further.
Please don't take it too seriously.
You said you'd do more because she wouldn't leave.
We should be careful.
It's none of my business.
I think Shizu forced Baya to go to the police.
It could be.
She used Baya.
You're going to take out the enemy?
No way.
Who will tell others about the shame of their husband?
It's none of my business.
You don't wanna involved it?
I'm sick of it.
Wait.
But the case is too small to be a crime.
It's a big problem for you, but... the police can't arrest him yet.
We'll look into it,
thank you for your help.
We're in trouble.
You can't go to the police station.
No...
Why not?
Hi.
We were rehearsing a play.
Yes.
Get up like you're doing right now and say.
Yeah.
I'm not loving you.
I don't want to meet with this person so please decline
Takuo.
I heard you didn't come home last night.
Whatever.
You've been busy.
Are you trying to get pocket money again?
Please go to the dressing room quickly.
I know but.
Nami came by this morning.
About police box?
I just heard.
She's stupid.
She told the police about her husband's scandal.
I can't stand anymore.
Women are completely out of control.
They're just a bunch of assholes.
I told my brother to sort it out first.
Then my brother says I'm wasting my pocket change.
You're selfish.
The best reason is that our personalities don't match.
Then Sizuka is getting a divorce?
The house is a mess for her all year round, and I don't feel like going home.
I hate it too.
Yeah and that letter.
It will be documentary evidence.
If you want documentary evidence, NAMI will write a lot for you.
Because the same person.
What?
She said she was in trouble.
Who told them that?
I didn't tell them.
Oh my god.
I'm leaving.
Welcome.
Congratulations today!
Hi. here it is.
Thank you very much.
I think that's a good place.
Hey.
Me?
Hato and Nami.
What?
It's gonna be tough.
Our bros wants you all to stay home when you're done.
He's pissed.
He's gonna make us buy him dinner.
Why He's pissed?
The letter.
Denjiro
Come home as soon as you're done with Show.
Do you want to go for a cup of tea?
What do you think?
It can't be helped.
We should leave the house.
Yeah we can be free.
The boss's Wife is here.
It doesn't matter.
Mari Ishikawa is here too.
You shouldn't have come here.
It's a fight.
I told about the apartment.
We just got the weekly paper reporters.
They said they went backstage.
We took money from the boss.
We're splitting the money.
Don't do anything reckless.
It was good that he had a child.
How's your little boy doing with his real dad?
Is he still around?
Yes he is.
Don't do that.
You seem to be taking something in.
I'll be with you in a moment.
Please wait.
Wife.
A guest is waiting.
Tell my husband.
Husband.
A guest is waiting.
Ask my wife.
Well...
She'll meet her.
She won't go because you're making her sit
What?
What's a cooking school teacher to do with a man?
I don't know what's going on.
He said you should go.
I have no reason to leave this house.
No.
See the guest.
My husband told that?
Please see her.
I see.
Good afternoon.
Oh Hina.
How are you?
We're in big trouble.
What's wrong?
Anyway come in.
I wanted to talk to you about something.
I brought you something.
You don't have to do that.
Where's wife?
We're in big trouble.
I don't know who will leave from here.
I'm tired now so I'm thinking of taking a little break.
Leave the greetings for later
I'll help you.
Can you make me some of that dried bonito flakes?
I am so tired of doing this.
Is everyone in your family doing well?
Yes.
If your sister is there, you two will move out of the house.
Of course.
What's more important, your siblings or strangers?
You don't have to put up with anything you don't want to, either.
Yes,
We did it out of the kindness of our hearts.
If it says in the letter that you have a child, I get alimony.
You should wait until she says she wants to break up
Yeah.
If the letter is a lie, you can just get angry later.
If she checks, she will know
You have a kid?
Oh my god.
You're so bad.
He is being threatened by the woman.
really?
It's none of your business.
You're the reason this house is unstable.
We are very patient.
I am also very dissatisfied with the food in this house.
The fish dishes are also well cooked.
It tasted bad.
There are also too many bean sprouts.
The potatoes are also burnt black.
She buys a lot of bad ingredients.
That's how she save money.
She's no good at cleaning and I don't want to stay here with her anymore.
I'm having a nervous breakdown.
Are you still doing that?
What do you think?
I have a lot of friends who are better than her.
I can take care of Bros
I feel same.
Are There Any People Like That?
Much better than Renko.
She's terrible.
Mind your own business.
I'll go through with it if I think it's good for me, no matter who it is.
It's okay to have one pure-hearted person in the house.
What's the hell?
Don't get jealous.
Pocket money, please.
No.
In your face.
I work part-time at a department store.
Anyway, I'll let you think about it.
Let's go.
We're going to get organized and move out of this house.
Thanks.
Please pick me up as soon as possible.
Thank you very much for taking the time to see me.
We'll discuss it
Thank you very much.
Are you going to trip?
Don't pretend you don't know.
There is a good matchmaking.
For hato?
Which?
Either.
That's rude.
What's he like?
This is his résumé.
Sis.
Let me see.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Where's my sis?
Look at this.
Takehiko Oyabu?
He's a dentist and he's already running a business.
I'm a little concerned about the name Oyabu.
He does not care of her age.
He's bit old,36.
Not for Hatoko?
For Namiko.
I would like to find someone else for hatoko.
You marry him.
Yeah.
I don't hate marriage.
If you want to leave this house, you should marry into his family.
What do you mean?
Well, let's meet this guy.
This is good idea.
What are you doing?
You're betraying me
Hatoko.
Saeko.
She's not here.
Please gargle.
Then I'll treat your teeth.
I wanna see your face.
My face?
What's wrong?
Take care of this.
How much does it weigh?
About 10kg.
How much?
About 30yen.
Thirty yen? That's pretty cheap.
Don't cheat.
You're stingy.
Never mind.
She's selling all that stuff without permission while Wife is away.
Let's finish this.
I'll say hello to wife.
She like to be called wife while she's away.
It's a complicated state of mind.
I don't know what to do.
She sell them and buy a baked sweet potato.
They look forward to buying sweet potatoes when wife is not around.
I feel sorry for their parents.
Oh.
Do you read this?
The Book of We the Workers.
Hina.
Please eat some.
Thank you very much.
I'll give you my clothes.
I'm just helping her.
She's got a different mother, doesn't she?
Since my daughter died, I've never been closer to her house.
We are like a stranger now.
for the train fare.
Thanks.
You received pocket money.
I come here part-time sometimes.
But she buys these for me.
This is good.
I append to find good one.
Wife is back?
She's back.
Welcome back.
I'm home.
I had dental treatment and my tooth hurts.
Take care.
How was he?
He's very good. He's very kind.
Not that.
How was he like?
His face?
At first I thought he looked not good with a mask on, but then I thought he looked really good .
What do you think?
He's nice.
He's too good for you.
He provides cheap dental treatment to his patients.
Why he does that?
He charges high prices from the rich but not for poors.
Does he have a good reputation?
That's what the people who came said.
Don't you think everyone who doesn't come thinks he's good?
We'll have to ask those who don't come.
That's why I asked at the grocery store.
He is an acquaintance of the dentist.
Have you asked other people?
At Tobacconist.
He buy Tobacco too.
He doesn't.
Because he's a dentist?
His teeth turn yellow so?
I don't know.
He's healthy, anyway.
I wonder if he has a respiratory problem.
I don't think you're overreacting.
I think this is a very good offer.
I think his dental clinic would be great if renovated.
I was surprised to find such a wonderful man.
It would be wonderful if you guys could get married.
What do you think?
Do you like him?
I don't know yet.
You look happy.
Do I have to wear g lasses?
Well.
Isn't it better to wear glasses from the beginning?
It's not right to do it on the way.
Here it is.
They are here.
Thank you very much for your patience.
I'll introduce you right away.
This is Mr. Karasawa.
This is her sister,  Saeko.
I'm Saeko.
This is Ms. Namiko.
And this is Mr. Oyabu.
I'm Oyabu.
Nice to meet you.
Why you care about his bald head?
What is the value of a man without hair?
If he has too much testosterone, he's bald.
I heard injecting female hormones would make some difference.
Why you didn't check his head in advance.
He wore a hat.
He was wearing a white surgical hat.
That's the problem.
Isn't going bald at thirty-six the same as going bald at forty-five?
Yeah.
Better to know from the start that he's not going to go bald, than to lose his hair in the process of getting together.
There's no any dreams.
She goes on your honeymoon, and she's disappointed.
But she is not young too.
Don't say that.
If our sister doesn't like bald men physiologically, you don't have to force her to marry him.
Rarely do people like physiological baldness.
I feel sorry for her.
You're trying to get rid of her.
I'm not just saying he's bald.
I'm trying to reason with you because you have a problem with his baldness.
You all just want me to leave this house, don't you?
I'm a trouble maker.
Women have a lot of stress at home.
That's what's wrong with women.
That's why I let you do whatever you want.
I'm taking care of you guys.
I made my marriage sacrificial.
I have to work hard for this house when we get married.
That's wrong.
You don't know how I feel.
We want sincerity.
Warmth and affection.
It's disgusting when it's done with formality.
You are sounds like Hitler.
He made human body lamp juice.
Showa Gruesome Tales.
We're talking seriously.
I don't have this kind of chance.
I've never had a serious discussion with our brother because he always runs away from us.
You're getting to the heart of the matter.
What do you mean by "you made marriage sacrificial."?
I can't help but feel that this is all my fault.
What does that have to do with me?
I'll fix what's wrong.
What do you mean?
I can't make my own choices?
You sound cold.
I don't like your attitude.
That's why I'm trying so hard to be concerned about you.
You can't marry anyone by looking for flaws
You don't understand that I have been so patient and devoted to this day.
I'm sad.
The women at home are usually too selfish.
Men are too.
You have no right to say that.
I don't want you meddling in my private affairs.
My brother and I are different.
Don't talk shit about my girlfriend.
What do you think about Renko?
Not good.
Why don't you scold him?
I can't even get around to the men's side.
I'll have to start with the women and sort them out one by one.
It's very troublesome.
Are you telling me I'm wrong?
Are you taking me seriously?
The natural phenomenon of his lack of hair is beyond my control.
That's funny.
That's not funny.
Cut it out.
I'm not just talking about his hair.
Don't get me wrong.
We don't.
You know, Mr. Oyabu, when he's alone with me, he's the first one to ask me how much I'm willing to pay for the renovation.
He's cheeky.
A deal and that's what he really wants.
He thinks I have money because I taught calligraphy until I was 30.
He said he wanted to use my money to renovate the clinic.
He's going to marry an old woman so.
This is deal.
I'm still pure.
He's old too. 36.
Who told me he was great?
I didn't know about the renovation fund.
He told me that.
Dental treatment doesn't tell me much about his personality
What did you find out about him?
You are a very irresponsible person.
You know nothing about him.
Yeah.
I also had to go to the trouble of getting my teeth treated.
I thought I did everything I could to remind you of your happiness.
What do you mean?
I know you want us to leave here.
That's what you really want.
Should I just keep quiet all the time?
Women's fight is scary.
I can't stand.
Don't let my bros say.
OK.
I'm not forcing you to marry him.
I'm so frustrated.
Why don't you find someone you like?
You'll never find a better man than him.
What did you say?
Don't say bad things about her.
What are you going to do with me?
Hit me.
Do whatever you want.
Stop it.
I feel scary.
Good night.
Sit down.
Wife.
Please take a bath quickly.
The water in the bath gets cold
Ladies, in that order, please.
I'm not going to clean up.
You don't have to come in here and tell m
Fuel will be wasted
We have to take a bath?
I won't take a bath.
Ok.
Wife.
You guys go to bed.
Good night.
Let's go.
It turns off.
2 mins?
He's not ok?
Takuo.
The doctor came by earlier and left.
He won't die.
What's wrong?
Gas poisoning
I don't know who did it.
I opened the gas valve.
But I had no intention of killing him and taking his fortune.
Let's leave this as your fault.
I turned it off.
This is attempted murder.
He was saved so don't blame her.
He'll be better if he rests for a few days.
I was relieved to hear that.
I think God is punishing him.
I don't think God needs to do that.
Can I talk with you?
me?
What are you going to do about today's lesson?
Of course I'm taking the day off. I can't leave her like that.
is this?
Thank you very much.
Madam, sorry to say this.
I will quit this work.
Why?
I'm scared I might get killed someday
There are so many problems in this house that I don't feel alive at all.
It's none of your business.
Someone might turn off the gas.
I don't want to take responsibility and go to jail.
Calm down.
There's been so much trouble in this house and I'm so fed up with it.
We need you.
My grandson came to see me last month.
Leave your talk for later.
Ok, please think about it.
I'm stumped.
I'll have to think about it calmly.
There's no telling what kind of problems might arise in the future.
Are you breaking up with him?
Yes.
Talking to him will only make things worse between us.
But if there's even a shred of affection left in you, it's better than leaving and being lonely.
Don't let those girls get you down.
But, you know, there's a limit.
I'll think it over.
You don't live a very full life.
You're a good.
I don't expect anything from anyone.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
She left.
I see.
Where's bros?
He will be back by dinner time.
That's unusual.
Denjiro's bringing Renko again.
Do we have to prepare meals for her too?
It can't be helped.
Where's Baya?
Hina brought her boyfriend.
really?
They're going to work together and get married.
They will live with Baya in the future.
Tea.
I gave it to you earlier
I had it all.
I'm too busy.
I'm not asking.
Let Renko make it.
She's a woman.
The food is burning.
Oh my god.
Put his water.
Don't use it.
It won't work.
Say hello to them.
They're going to take me.
I just heard.
My name is Katou. Thanks for taking care of her grandmother.
You act so quick.
They work same place.
I just heard.
I sent them a letter the other day, and they came to me for advice.
They worried about me.
You look so happy.
I think they're going to have a hard time now.
Shall we leave?
Please take care of her grandmother.
Please…
They're going to look for an apartment now.
Why don't you walk her to the station?
Don't worry.
I don't want to get in their way.
I'm sorry to have disturbed you.
Bye.
Have some ramen.
He's quite handsome.
You better find a good guy soon.
Don't get me started on them.
Don't say that.
I'm home.
Sizuka, you're awake?
Good morning.
You sleep really well.
I really do sleep well.
You must be exhausted.
I let you sleep in for a good Sunday.
I'm sorry, but I need to get some rest.
Have you made up your mind yet?
Go back to the country?
No.
I'll get a job.
That's a good idea.
Do you want some fruit?
I bought some.
Welcome.
Yes she's here.
Who?
hi.
Thank you for taking care of her.
Not at all.
This is a thank you for that.
Thanks.
Have you been over here all this time?
Yeah.
I was relieved.
It's a bit of a mess in here, please come in.
Thanks.
I've been having a lot of trouble lately.
Who decided what is a marriageable age?
I believe that people are always in their marriages.
The world is sad.
That's why they became neurotic.
It has spread to us, and we are having a hard time.
A married couple can break up anytime they want to.
It's really that simple.
We've been cutting and re-cutting each other, and there's been no development at all.
We're trying to hold out until our sister calms down.
I'm sure you understand that.
I understand that.
Since I came all the way here to pick you up, let's go home before you cause too much trouble for her.
Actually, I wasn't half expecting you to show up.
Did you really think I was that heartless?
It's not that.
Don't worry about us.
I can't go home now.
Why?
There's too much trouble in that house.
Namiko and Hatoko are at the apartment.
Saeko's?
The apartment below her is about to become available.
We are thinking of selling our current house and moving to a smaller one.
I organize my surroundings in various ways.
This is a nice neighborhood.
Why don't we go for a walk?
We are gonna go for a walk around the block.
I see.
We are going out for a bit.
You.
THE END