Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
The Sisters and I
Do the alignments!
Start!
Make the right group
Good morning
Anyone here?
Sen-san
It's been a while
I was surprised
I was really surprised
See how my heart is pounding
My heart is pounding in my chest.
I called you but you didn't come
Sorry
I thought you don't like me
Why?
You didn't contact me at all
I saw in the newspaper that you quit writing a novel
I was worried
I thought you committed suicide
You are good at kidding
Why did you stop writing novels?
It seems that the novel I write is not good for the Japanese people
I like your humane novel
Your novel comforts people
You tell the army so
Shall I?
You go to jail
That's bad for me
The dance you did was Kurokami?
Yes
I'm glad to see your dance
A bush warbler was just in our yard.
I felt like dancing a little
I'm glad
You remind me of Kyoto
What meal do you want?
I want to eat ochazuke.
There are only simple dishes
That's OK
Here's your tea
Oshima
I'll live here
Make yourself at home
Forever
You can stay here forever
No one live here besides you?
Only me and my grandmother live here
Many people want to work at our inn
But I refuse everyone
That's good for me
It tastes good
I'm going to see the temple from noon
Which temple?
I'll go to Myo-temple
That's good
I decided to go there from the time I left Tokyo
A woman quit her job to become a monk in Kyoto.
I miss her
I was also a geisha in Gion, Kyoto
I quit my  job and live in Okazaki now
You have no sex appeal compared to her
You are so mean
Are you looking for Anjo?
Is she here?
She went to pick flowers
Oh I see
She'll be back soon
Thanks for coming
Did you also come to visit Anjo?
Yes
Are you Shinkichi Yuki?
Do you know of me?
That's what I thought
It's rare for a young woman to come here
Did you see my picture in a magazine?
No
Why do you know of me?
I have known you for a long time
Really?
I am Hisako from a certain restaurant.
Oh you are the Hisako?
I was surprised
Really
You've grown so much
I haven't seen you for a while.
I'm glad to see you again
How's your father?
He died last spring
I didn't know that
I see
I'm sorry
He was still young
He was 60 yrs old
How is your restaurant?
Your sister was married and left
I stopped going to the restaurant because she left
I'm sorry
She's come back
In Kyoto?
Does her husband work in Kyoto?
Or did he serve in the military?
She was kicked out because she didn't fit in his house
Now our restaurant is making bento boxes for munitions factories
My sister makes a special bento for her close friends
I see
My sister will be delighted, so please come!
You should cut your hair
You will be attacked by the soldiers
I don't care.
I can go anywhere
Your sister'll be lonely without you
She won't
I'll be in a shaved head sooner or later.
You're angry that they're taking you to war.
Or you don't like your sister?
Which?
Both
You should get married with me
It's hard for me to be a clerk all the time
What do you think?
You don't know how I feel
What did you say?
Stop it.
Did you finish your cooking?
Please deliver it to the factory when you can cook
Ah
Hisako sister is coming back
Where are you going.Akibo
Do you have any problems with AkiBo?
Nothing
Please come in
Oh you
It's been a whole
I wanted to see you
I'm glad you've come
Please come in
Here's fine
I want you to come in
It's been a whole
Welcome
I heard a lot about you
Hisako told you?
Do you prefer Alcohol to tea?
I hear you are cooking
I learned cooking from my father
Can you cook?
I have no choice but to cook
There are only elderly cooks here
Can you cook local food here
Yes
Can you?
Can you serve it for him?
I want you to eat our local food
Why they kicked you out?
You were there for 3 yrs
I didn't go well with my mother-in-law
I put up with it very much
She complained about my cooking
I was scolded a lot by her
What do you think?
Really?
That's bullshit
I was complained to her that I drank too much and had too much sex appeal
She's so mean
But I put up with it for 3 years
Please praise me
You are not great.
You should have come back sooner.
Let us stop telling this story
Please enjoy our Miso dish
I will eat
It tastes good
Really?
I'm glad
It tastes good.
I'm surprised
It tastes the same as the food your dad cooked.
How did you learn it?
I'm very happy to be complimented by someone like you
I'll serve you a sake
My dad was disappointed that they kicked me out
My dad trained me hard for two years
It was too hard
You're great
It ’s amazing that you girls have a dead father and two women running this restaurant.
I travel with a ban against writing novels.
I was encouraged by you
I will do my best like you
Shake hands with me
I’m horned
Hello?
Eh? To where?
I need to ask my sister
From Who?
Akio is at the Kyoto Hotel so He wants me to come
Please go
You can talk with him
I'm going out
Take care
Akio is having a fight with his fiancé
Don't do anything to me
What do you think about me?
I am your fiancée
What do you mean by that?
Do you know the meaning of fiancée?
The meaning is that marriage is allowed
It means we can get married
That's right
So we can sleep together
We can have sex after the wedding
Have a seat
You don't like me?
It does not matter
I'm asking you like me or not
I like you
You are lair
You just pretended to like me
Don't pretend you are elegant
I am elegant
You are not
Drink it
I'll give you
Stop it
What happened?
Tell me
He forced me
That's no problem
Sister
Did you sleep with him?
Don't make fun of me
Did you have fun there?
We are old but They are young
That's right
You are so mean
Where are you going?
1.2.1.2.1.2.1.2.1.2.1.2.1.2.
I refreshed
Are you going to sleep?
I'll write something
Please set my bed
Sure
I feel sorry for Kiyo
Her mother died when she was young.
And she worked so hard
She got married but she was kicked out
She loved someone before she got married
It might be so
But her dad was very strict
Does she have anyone to consult?
Unfortunately she has that person
She has?
Don't be disappointed
That person is a very serious person in the neighborhood
Can I go talk to Mr. Tamura?
Anyway, my father's first anniversary is over
You had better get married early
It's none of your business
I can't sleep unless I decide clearly
It's not about your marriage
You should go to bed
Ok you can go
Thank you for your permission
I can sleep with peace of mind
You should go upstairs now
You are so pervert
I get it
Let's get ready for the wedding now
Before he changes his mind
Thank you
Thank you for listening to me
I'm sure Toto City's older brother will be happy.
Kiyo
Hello?
I'm here to see you
For what?
I'm here to talk about your marriage
Dad told you guys to have a wedding early
I won't get married
Akibo
Let's go to Kiyomizu together
Why did you say you wouldn't get married suddenly?
I don't like Hisako
What did you say?
I hate her attitude
You loved her,right?
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
I'll tell you the truth
Tell me
To be honest, I loved you
Don't say bullshit
Really
I agreed to marry her so that I could be near you.
Don't tell her that
She will be sad when she hears it
I don't care
I love you
Really
Stop it,Akibo
Let me go
Really
I wanted someone like you
Stop it,Akibo
Let me go
No
I won't let you go
Stop it,Akibo
That's not good
I'll be waiting at Shinoda of Otsubu tonight
How have you been doing?
Are you still awake?
Who's visited me at such a late night?
Kiyo from Totoki
Oh you
Sorry to make you wake up
What's wrong?
She's got drunk
She's loopy
What are you talking about?
I'm a woman with a drinking problem.
I wonder if there was anything happy for her.
Yes there is
My sister's wedding is set.
That's good news
Congratulation
I'm so glad
I want to drink more
I want to drink
You shouldn’t drink much
Why you stop me to drink?
You're not going to celebrate a happy story?
OK let's toast together
I want cold sake
Congratulation
Thank you
That would be fine
Let's sing together
It's too late to sing
Well done
You were drunk, but you sang well.
I can't hold back
You've got a big mouth.
You should go to bed,Kiyo
Oh my god
It can't be helped.
You may catch a cold
It seems she was so happy
She is very much a sister.
She thinks she is her mother.
Leave her alone.
I go to bed
Sorry to make you trouble
Sensei
Don't come here
Never mind
Hug me please
I want to be your woman
Sensei
I'm embarrassed
I can't.
Get up
You take better care of yourself.
You just got out of an unhappy marriage.
You have to find real love from now on
I really love you
You can see me when you are not drunk
Don't say that when you're drunk.
I don't like such a woman
I was sorry
I'll be back.
Good night
I called you
Oume said you were not here
I've been waiting for you here
Where have you been?
Let's go
Where are we going?
I know a good scotch bar.
Really?
You know what?
Okiyo
Please love me
I can't live without you
I can't,Akio
Where did you stay last night?
At my mom's place
I fell asleep in the living room
Seisei called us and worried about you
Why you make a lie?
Where did you stay last night?
I was sleeping on the current bench in the museum
That's bad
I was so embarrassed that I lied
What if you get sick?
Don't do that again
What did you come to do so quickly?
Hisako
Let's break our engagement
Akibo
We do not allow it
Why did you go home first?
I've been loved your sister
We had slept together
Where are you going?
It's none of your business!
Don't go
Boss is here?
Yes
Boss
What's wrong?
Please come to our restaurant?
There was a big problem
Damn it!
Are you thinking of your dead father?
Slap me
What?
What if Hisako won't go home?
You stupid
I didn't want to make a marriage failure like my sister
I tried to be a good female cook
Akio doesn't like such women
He told me so
He told you so?
He doesn't like me
That's bad.
You should separate with him
He's bad.
It's ok if you break your marriage proposal
Wait
Hisako doesn't not say she does not want to marry with Akio
But, Sensei
When kiyoko goes to Hozansan?
Yesterday
Then She came to us that day
Why did she do that
You know what,sensei
Let's have KIYO come here with Totoichi's older brother
Let's talk with us
Well
What do you think?
That's good for you
Let's do it
Eh? she's there?
Hisako is at Okazaki
Hello?
I'm Totoichi
Thank you
Sorry to make you trouble
She'll come
Kiyo hate it
Totoichi's older brother will take her
I am...
going out
Why?
We need you
Leave it to you
This may be the writer's intuition
Something happened to her when she went to talk about her wedding
I think so
She asked me to forget it
I didn't know that
I got angry with her
You also pretended to be a good man
Because
If you had sex with her this wouldn't happen
I'm in trouble
I also feel responsible
So please
I want to sleep with you if I'm in trouble too
I'm honor to sleep with you
You are mean
Bad man
Kiyo
Where's Totoichi's older brother?
He told me to go alone.
What happened to you?
I went to talk about my sister's wedding
He told me He hates her
He told me he loves me
I was upset
You've had a hard life and you shouldn't be so easily offended.
But mom
I thought he was like my brother.
I was very surprised
I know how you feel
I've never loved someone before
I had an unhappy marriage and was only sad
I was in trouble when he said that
But
Wait for me
I was in trouble and came here
You know what
Why did sensei not have sex with Kiyo
He can be pretentious at times.
He is a very troublesome person
I was scold by him
Actually I love him
I don't know why he is so popular with women
I came home dumped and scolded by him.
Then Akibo was waiting in front of house
I was asked to go bar with him
It can't be helped
I was stupid
I always thought of him as my brother.
I did something very stupid
You are so stupid
Yes I am
I did something very stupid
You really think so?
Yes
She came here alone
Have a seat
Come in
Do you girls fight?
I can be a referee
Can you bring the dish
Sure
I made oden for you
Come here now
Thank you
Have a drink
Hisako too
I can't drink to make up
I don't mean that
Let's drink
Drink it
Eat some Oden
How's it?
It tastes good
You just gave in to temptation,right?
Your sister is very remorseful.
She didn't mean to break your relationship
She already had male experience
Young men like people like her
Your sister was trying to comfort the young man
Please understand her
I don't understand
It can't be helped
I know you get angry
I know you can't forgive her
But you are sisters
Please forgive her
No
I'm sorry too
You have nothing to do with her
Say sorry to her
I'll say sorry too
I'm sorry,Hisako
Forgive me
I was sorry
Hisako
Forgive me
Forgive her
You can go home with her
Hisako
Someone is outside
A man?
I have no idea
He is hiding
Oume
Good evening
Come in
Don't worry
Did they make up?
Please let these girls go home.
Oume came
She hopes you girls go home
Let's go home
You should go to bed
Yes
I'll take a bath
Did you forgive me?
Please say something
Your apologies will not undo it.
You're good but I'm not
Do you want me to give up?
Do you tell me to leave this house because I can't cook?
You think too much
You planned for it.
You stole my fiancée
You took my guy
You broke us
You are so mean
Are you Akibo?
Let's go to Tokyo
They are stupid
Hisako, You go to Tokusima's uncle place
We can't work without her.
How about me?
You go home
No
I'd like to take you in, but
You are useless.
You go home and do farm job
No
What can I do?
I want to be your finance
What?
What did you say?
If I become your finance,
I'll take care of this restaurant
I don't want to leave here
OK show me your butt
OK.
I'll take care of you too
Sensei
What
I want to tell you something
Kiyo eloped with AKibo
I made a haiku.
Butterflies longing for spring
Will the war really last 100 years?
I don't think so
The war will be over in 10 years and the world will
change.
Welcome
Yuki sensei has come
You are very welcome
Thanks for your work
Osima-san
You have his followers
I'm Yuki's wife
I didn't know that
I'm Yuki's wife too
Oh you too
I'm sorry I didn't know
It's been a long time
How're you?
Let the jokes be over.
I am glad he got the literary award
I know how you feel
You cared for him in Kyoto during the war.
I hear there is a party in Tokyo, so I've come
I am so happy to get his bouquet
I want to take care his bouquet
Please be relax
Give us Brandy
Excuse me
Sensei
I'll introduce you our new worker
I'm sorry don't introduce me
I can't meet him
Why?
Come with me
Sensei
Kiyoko!
Long time no see
Oshima!
What?
Kiyoko works here
OKiyo
Long time no see
Do you know her?
We are very close
Are there any other seats available?
Can I talk with her?
Go ahead
When I come to Tokyo
I was dumped by him
He didn't like me from the beginning
He didn't want to marry with Hisako, so He used me
I was stupid
He is so bad
Then I worked at my friend's inn
Then there was an air raid.
I lost my home
I worked several jobs
Why you don't go back?
It's hard
Really
I was afraid to see you
How's Akibo?
He got a woman and have 2 kids
He's working hard and doing a great job with his ceramics.
Hisako has backed to Tokushima
I hear something about her
She opened a restaurant in Yasui
She use Name of Totoki?
No.
Totoichi brother is managing the name of Totoki
He is waiting for you to return
You should go back in Kyoto
Let's go back in Kyoto together
But Hisako won't forgive me
We'll talk to her
I'll do my best
So let's go back
You work at TOTOKi restaurant again
I'll support you
Thank you
It's embarrassing to enter this room
I feel very guilty
Don't say that
Please have a bath
I'm ok.
What should we do?
Let's talk about her
I'm thinking of seeing Hisako tomorrow
Really?
I didn't think it was a good idea to go with her out of the blue.
I'll meet totoichi's brother and
talk about her
Then I'll go to see Hisako
Can you do that?
I'll go
It's not good if you go
Why?
I think if Sensei goes,totoichi's brother is willing to listen
And Hisako is happy to come
It's troublesome if she comes
totoichi's brother is ok
Hisako is not good if she only listens to Sensei
If you go back, they won't feel better.
I will talk first and Sensei will take you home
You look very confident
Leave it to me
It's up to Hisako to give the shop sign
Hisako forgive her first
I want to make sure their sisters get along well
How does Hisako feel now?
She?
She is very worried about her sister
But I don't know if she forgives her or not
Can you talk to Hisako?
Please
I'm sorry I can't
I can't tell what kind of condition Kiyoko is in from what you have told me.
I have no reason to ask her
Kiyoko apologize first
Then Hisako forgives her.
This is better
I get it
I'll go to see her
Whereabouts Yasui?
Nishiura in Yasui
I'll ask if she is there or not
Hello?
It's me
Well, Kiyoko has back in Kyoto
Wait wait
Mom will visit you to talk about it
You should talk with her seriously
Talk to you later
So please take care of her.
Get better, Hisako
She made you suffer.
She bankrupted the restaurant
I can't forgive her when she comes back
That's what she deserves.
I feel sorry for her
She's stupid.
She wouldn't have a hard time if she didn't come to Kyoto
That's right.
I didn't have to be fiancé
Are you his fiancé?
Because I wanted to have a relationship with the Totoki restaurant
Totoichi's brother is taking care of me
Of course I think it's her responsibility
You are suffering but she is suffering too
She is very regretful
Do you still hate her?
I don't hate her.
We are sisters
That's right
Hisako
Be strong
Don't interrupt us
What the hell who you are?
Stop it
Let me talk with her
She has had a lot of trouble
I'm sorry
Please understand how I feel
I also want Kiyoko to come back
I also want her to work in Totoki restaurant
But I'm thinking of Hisako
I'm sorry
I also want to cry with you
I feel the same as her
I also understand your kindness
I can't understand why she used you
That's my problem
Why didn't she come alone?
Why didn't she write to me?
Why didn't she talk to TOTOICHI brother
We are sisters
That's right
But She thinks you don't forgive
I want her to come back
Really
I can't say
I can't say that from myself
Please understand her feelings
I get it
So what should we do?
Can you go to see her?
I can't
I hope she comes back alone
Just come back and apologize to her
But
I don't think she will come back alone
Tell her to come back alone
What do you think?
Can you go home?
Yes
You sure?
Apologize to her
Please apologize to Oume too
Yes
Excuse me
Can you send us a cab?
You sure to go home?
Call me if you get home safe
I don't care if it's late
Turn the corner
Here's fine
She has not called me yet
After Kiyo got forgiveness from Hisako
Next is Totoichi's brother
Sisters should go to apologize to him
I'm worried if Kiyo can cook like she used to
If she can't cook, they won't use that name again
If she makes up for it, it won't matter if she can't use the TOTOICHI name again
That's right
So I have an idea
The day after tomorrow will have your celebration
Then bring the guests home.
No problem
Please have TOTOICHI's brother among the guests
Then?
Ask Kiyo to cook
I see
It depends on KIYO's cooking that you can use the name of TOTOKI.
I'm going to bet on it
That's a good idea
First of all, it is important for them to make up
I want her to call me soon
It's already 2 am
She hasn't come back yet
I will complain if she comes back
You don't have to say anything
I see
I will complain
Sister
welcome back
Here's Oden restaurant?
Do not serve dishes with such ingredients
Stop it!
Watch out
Stay strong, please.
Help me to bring her upstairs
Watch out
Stay strong
You drunk too much
How You could take my guy
Please curse me
I don't sleep yet
Let's take a walk
Come on
We're sisters
We're only sisters
Hisako
We're sisters
Totoichi's boss has arrived
Welcome
How are you?
I need to talk to you.
Have a seat
Thanks for the other day
I was worried, but my sisters were able to make up.
That's good
I would like to apologize to you for the three of us.
I have a request for you about that
What's that?
Kiyo cooks tonight's food
Hisako and Ume are cooking it together in the kitchen now.
It may bother you
I wish the happiness of the three
Please forgive her
But
She hasn't cooked for a long time
Try eating her food and make a decision
If she cooks well, please forgive her
Please
Don't forgive me
Thanks for telling me
Thanks
I am very happy to be asked by you
But
I want to see her ability
That's for them too
I will judge her strictly.
Could you serve the food soon?
We are ready if they wants
Are you ready?
Totoichi's brother is here
Really?
Our mom would have thought of you
So please
I'm cooking now.
don't disturb
The food tastes the same with or without him.
Let me know when sense's speech is done
Timing is important for this celebration soup
Is this fine?
Good
Let me greet you
Thanks for coming tonight
I won a literary award.
It is because of your support
I want to thank you guys for what you did for me today.
Thank you very much.
Please enjoy your time
His speech has just finished
Let's go
Hi Madam
What dish is this?
It tastes good
I don't know what dish is this
I tell you
This is TOTOKI's business trip cooking
Female sisters cooked.
We,Totoki grantee this
Please enjoy your meal
Oh, Totoki's
I know them
Kiyo,Hisako
Our guest asked us what dish was it
And Totoki's brother answered him this was Totoki's dish
Sister!
I'm glad
Thank you very much
I cooked hard not to embarrass you.
I'm tired of cooking for the first time.
Keep going cooking, you girls
I know
Brother
Don't say anything
You didn't forget how to cook
Thank you very much
Restaurant to be remodeled tomorrow.
We'll set the sign of Totoki
Sure
Thank you very much
I want to ask you something
Tell me
I didn't know Oume is your fiancee
She thinks fiancé is the one who gets paid and does
nothing.
How dare you
She is cute
She'll be nice woman later
Don't be glad
You pervert.
I hate you!
I'm glad
Kiyo,Hisako
Please use me when you'll be busy
Let's drink together
Sure
Oume came to me to pick the Miso
Did you cook with it?
I need the miso to cook it
Thank you very much
Let's drink
Good job
I'm glad you used our Miso
Was it hard for you to prepare the food?
I spent the morning shopping at various stores.
Totoki's miso is our dead father's favorite
dish.
How did you cook it with the Miso?
I can't tell you the secret
You have quite a way with words.
Never mind
I'll know
Yes if you can
What?
I'll try
You have quite a way with words.
Sorry
Sensei
I can't beat someone with skill
No matter how stupid you are, people with skills come alive.
Like sister and mother
You too
THE END