Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
(New Year's Love)
Bash!Bash!
What?You're not gonna resist?
You dress in outlandish clothes
I can't stand the sight of you!
Uniformed schools have school rules
Why you don't have your hat?
I have
Wear it if you have
Take your hat off
Bash!Bash!
Fuck you! You stupid!
You bustard!
Stand up!
Fuck you!
Fuck off!  Eat Shit and die!
I can't get on a train with this face
I'm taking a hired car home.
I'll take you to the station
Well, I'll find a hired car
Long time no see!
What's the matter?
You never call me at all.
I called you last night
I feel blue recently
So do I
Why don't we go for playing golf next Sunday?
By the way
I hear Tonko had a fight with Kacchan
She likes you better now
She calls you, right?
She does
When?
Yesterday?
Everyday
That's what I thought
So you are into her?
You are too noisy!
Mind your own business
You will get off at next stop, right?
I will go with you until Yokohama
You are too noisy!
I've told you I feel blue
See you.
I will call you tonight
Local Train is coming for Shibuya
Train is coming for Shibuya on platform 10
There is no waiting for the express train.
Please use this train
You look good
I have no money for train ticket
I'm sorry but could you lend me some money?
I don’t have enough money
I don't think so, You look rich
I borrowed this cloth
I only have 100 yen
You are no use. then bye
Good luck
I also feel blue
Because
Koike-san calls you,doesn't she?
I know all
But it's up to you
I know that
I hear Tonko had a fight with Kacchan
You know that?
You know what
You're the cause of that
She calls you
Close your mouth
Phew
Hahahahaha
Welcome back
Hey handsome guy!
Handsome guy!
Hey!
Don't ignore us
or We're not on your mind, are we?
Fuck you!
Damn it
I'm coming!
Welcome back home
Open the door whenever I come back home
Where is my brother?
He has not come back yet
He didn’t come back home last night too
He said he will back home late tonight too
This house is haunted
There's no one here but spirits
I'm here
You are the ghost
You're in a bad mood
Yes I am
Your girlfriend is calling you
Be in good mood
Hello?
Will you have dinner right away?
Of course
From Koike-san
What the heck!
Hello?
You are too noisy
We just met short time ago
I won't go!
I feel blue anyway
Bye
Eat steak and Cure the blues
This is Matsuzaka beef
You cook nothing but beef steaks because it is easy to cock
Wash your hands
I know.
You are too noisy
Ringing is making a lot of noise
Say her I'm not here
Hello? Yes
I see. He has not come back home yet
Yes, then see you
Who was it?
From Aikawa-san
You stupid, you should say him I'm here
Hello? This is Yamada speaking
Oh you are on this phone
Yes I was here
Because my old lady is mean
That's a false accusation
Shut up!
Hum? I was not taking about you
Well...It's not been a good day
I was planing to call you
I'm back
Welcome back.
It's good timing
Yes
We got Matsuzaka beef
You are too noisy
You're well as always
He said he is blue
You are too noisy!
Therefore
Those senior are cocky
They still have four months before graduation
I'll train for that
I will have my revenge on them
What a scary
So you should quit playing basketball, a feminine sport
I will also quit playing golf
I can't say it now
Let's see you at school
Then see you
Have a good evening
You've been making suspicious phone calls
Why do you think so?
I will train myself from tomorrow
I will beat them
What would you say goodbye to a friend you see all the time?
Of course I say that
We are good friend
What are you going to do tomorrow?
Both of you are going to study together?
We will  study too
Are you sure?
Shut up!
Hit the jab!
One two
Speed up!
Use your body!
Hit the jab!
Pull down your chin
Straight!
One two
Speed up!
Use your body!
What are you going to do, join the boxing club?
You're training yourself to get back at us?
That's stupid
Say something
You bastard!
Wait
If it's five against two, we're bound to lose
If you're a senior, you should be fighting one-on-one
You people are a pain in the ass
Well, I will fight with you
You will fight with him
You bastard!
Help me,Yamada!
Are you Ichiro?
I'm back
Where is Ichiro?
He has not come back home yet
Why you are lying?
She is so rude
Oh
What's happened? your face...
Let me see
I'm OK
What if your eyes go bad?
You are injured.
Did you have a fighting with someone?
Mind your own business
Wash your face at bathroom right away
Did he hit you in the boxing ring?
I hit him if he hits me
You are stupid
You should play basket ball
Boxing doesn't suit you.
I'm going to put a potion on you
Oh, Mercurochrome medicine is missing
What's the matter?
It seems Ichiro has fight with someone.
so He got injured
Mercurochrome medicine is missing
What's wrong with your legs
I used it for my legs
You'd better apply some other medicine
It's all red and disgusting
Buy a Mercurochrome medicine
We do have other ointment
That medicine will hurt
That medicine will do the trick
Don't be silly!
Go to buy it
Ok I get it
I'd like to try that potion
What happened with her?
She has been crazy
I will be crazy too
By the way your friendships are bad
I hear he is called Yamada who is fag
Don't be friends with that rich man
There are better friends than him
Your class has 40 to 50 students so
There is no good one other than him
He is the best one
You are kidding
There is no good man who plays boxing
That sport is for punks
Students should play other sports
The home of boxing is England
So what?
The home of the pirates is also England
I'm not surprised
You look bad
There is no good man of your friends
You get beaten up for looking so cocky
I think so
Shut up
I asked him to play boxing
Aikawa is the son of a restaurateur in Ginza?
Yes, he said like he gets his revenge or something
Shut up!
I worry about you
It hurts!
You should be patient
Why you begin to play boxing?
You don't know the world
You have no idea what's going on in the world
Boxing is popular in the Soviet Union and the United States
An eye for an eye, and a tooth for a tooth
Don't scare me
Our father is busy with his work,
I am also busy with my study
You are talking right
You had good grades until college
Do not say "until college"
Your grades have dropped since you went to graduate school
That’s not true!
Your grades have dropped tremendously
Students have to study
Your father is a corporate executive
I am the maid of this house
Do your best to do your jobs
Who's on this phone?
Yes
Yes we are
Yes he is here
Please wait a min
From him
Not you,
Your girlfriend is on the phone
When I was younger, I didn't make as many calls
There was no phone at the time
When?
You're very brazen or something
I'm very positive
In that case You can't study calmly
You are too noisy.
Shut up
I can't stay silent. I'm responsible for what happened
I'm your mother's replacement
I've been raising you since you were babies
Do you understand?
Welcome
There is a seat upstairs
Here is fine
You know a stylish place
This is my first visit
Can I take your order?
What do you want?
Well, anything you like
Well, we’ll leave it up to you
Sake?
Beer
Certainly
Welcome
Welcome,Welcome
Shall we go upstairs?
Here is better
I don't really like to sit on the floor
You are not kind
I don't know. What should I do?
Do whatever you want
So,If I turn down a marriage proposal
what you will do?
I don't like the way you say
Then I should say like what?
I don't know why you take it so seriously
This is serious for me
so I don't like to go upstairs
Is the food ready upstairs?
Yes it's ready
Are you a sister of her?
No she is a daughter
She is beautiful, isn't she?
So the man in the kitchen is your father?
She is your mother
Yes she is
Why you ask her a lot?
I have reason to ask her
Here it is
So Please bring beers upstairs
Yes
How many beers did you deliver upstairs?
8 beers
If they drank that much, they wouldn't be able to taste the food
There are a lot of vulgar customers these days.
The owner of this restaurant complains a lot.
Let's go upstairs
You said you don't like
The owner of this place scares me and I don't want to drink here
Excuse me, We are going to upstairs
Yes, please go
Welcome
You came upstairs because you wanted to see that woman's face, didn't you?
I'm surprised
For what?
She is so beautiful
Are you making fun of me?
I'm having trouble
But I can't do anything for you
You should say you marry me
Why I have to say that?
Because I like you
You are kidding
Excuse me
You don't have to sit back
Shall I pour beer?
Please
yes
We had a call from Ichiro,
he said he will stay at his friend's house tonight
At who's place?
He said in Yokohama or something...
He does nothing but play
He's playing with such bad friends
There are many bad kids in Yokohama region
Is that right?
You are kidding
There are more bad kids in Tokyo
A lot of high school kids are bad these days
He's quiet at home,
but he has a lot of bad friends
This guy is bad too
What?
Please make yourself at home.
Shall I bring beers?
Please bring a lot.
We don't care the taste of your foods
Certainly
You are so rude
You take an immediate interest in beautiful women
Refill!
Let's make a toast to say goodbye
what the hell you doing!
You're awful
You know what?
I'm just friend of you
I didn't do anything wrong with you
You held my hands at the night
You said it's a lovely moon
You held me my hands
And then I got burned by a cigarette
Not at the time
In the woods of Karuizawa
You asked me out that time
We held hands and sang
That's ridiculous
You deny us our memories
Excuse me
Oh..What's wrong with you?
I'm wetting
We just moved to upstairs but..
You wanted to see her face, so we moved to upstairs
I don't care about you anymore
We are leaving so check please
I'm leaving
Please share time with him
I will take care of your outfit
Thank you
You are Yamada-san
Yes boring name
My brother's bad friend is also called Yamada.
I'm really in trouble
Please wait a min
I'm  in trouble too
There's a phone call for you
Thank you
I'm tired
You are busy, aren't you?
You think a lot, you know
I feel distressed when it's quiet
It's normal to study in a quiet place
It's weird to study in a noisy place
This house is haunted
I am the ghost
I'm ok.
I'm not playing
We are studying together
It's true!
Ask my friend
You should study seriously
I don't want to be invited to a parents' meeting
I know that.
See you
He said see you
No use complaining to him
Mom's never been called to be a teacher before
If he flunks out, we can make him a cook
He's not going to learn how to cook
He's at an age now where he wants to play
I have never studied in my life
Of course.
You didn't graduate even junior high school
I didn't think anything of it at the time
My parents also told me that if I didn't like school, I could just quit
That was the time
But you played a lot
You got into the habit of it
Whenever you see a girl,
You ask her out
Finally I got you
We're just like each other
You couldn't even write a love letter because you never learned
I am astounded by his attitude
Welcome
Welcome!
Sorry
Oh here is nice place
Thank you
The food and the women are wonderful here
Yes
I am not
Don't be shy,
you're amazing
Do you like my back?
If I choose anything
I'm just the draw
welcome
He's the executive director of Yokohama Commercial
Nice to meet you
In my business, I'm picky about taste
It’s pleasure to meet you
Please
I'm Yamada
I will come here often
Oh you are Yamada-san?
Yes
You know him?
No No,
The customer who just left was also Mr. Yamata
Oh, that's incident
Which Yamada do you like?
That customer looked so young
I'm also young
He was in a lot of trouble
He was here with a woman
The woman splashed beer in his face
Oh that's too bad
Then Do you want to splash beer on my face?
I don't trust Yamada-san in Yokohama.
There are many bad people
That's a nice greeting
She knows all of me
You are too bad
He is my older brother
Shall I say hi to him?
Be polite
I will
I'm polite
Welcome back
Can you cook something for me?
Do you want to eat something?
I couldn't eat at the restaurant
I will ready it soon
Welcome back
Oh you
It's good to meet you
Take your seats
What do you want to drink?
Water
Don't be formal
Don't be hesitate
Thank you
Do you have any siblings?
I have one older sister
So you feel lonely
But Yamada-kun has also one sibling
It's hard enough to have several brothers like him
I have to be hard on you
My sister also has to be hard on me
She is very beautiful woman
She's famous at school
I've heard that
Your brother is famous at school too
Oh really?
He is handsome and tall
Don't flatter him.
He'll be wrong
That's what the girls in my class said
Who is the woman?
My soul mate
You stupid.
I told you not to say anything funny to him
So Enjoy your drink
Do you want to eat beef steak?
Yes I want
You always cook steak
You will be smarter if you eat steaks
Please study much harder
She is always complaining
You will have an exam soon?
We studied together
I'm tired
You study while listening to Jazz
Shut up!
She is always complaining
Let's go back room
We will study hard
Anyway his sister is wonderful
Why are you laughing?
Anyway Regardless of his study...
Totally...
He is not bad student but..
How can I say... he is mysterious
I think he needs to study more
Moreover he starts to play boxing
He's too tired to study when he gets home
No matter which club he joined...
It's same
I'm sorry I had a cold
But He doesn't have to play the fisticuffs sport.
And I think he has bad friends
How was the result of Yamada?
He was not good so much
I asked his brother,
but he has not come here yet
He doesn't feel like coming
birds of a feather flock together
Why doesn't he have any smart friends?
That's what I thought too
They are matched
Both has very nice personality
They wants to be bad or
They're old enough to be interested in women
If you, we can do anything for them
But it's not
I have no idea what I'm supposed to do to them
Do not misunderstand that I give up with them
I'm in trouble as a teacher
I've got a cold and I feel terrible
I'm sorry I'm late
Oh
You are here too
You are the Yamada's brother
I'm older brother of Hikaru
Why you didn't say that before
You told bad about him so
I had no time to say it
And you were with that woman
She had nothing to do with it
Teacher,I understand what kind of his friend is Yamada
Can I go home?
Yes go ahead
Thank you very much
Excuse me
Please wait a min
What do you mean you understand how my brother is?
Because he is your younger brother
I'm sorry for that
Don't worry about that
Please take your seats
It seems I had a cold
You feel pain?
Take your seats
She is very beautiful, isn't she?
Let me see...
You need to consider if I am wrong or you are wrong
Every semester the teacher calls me out and I'm in trouble
I will do it from now
You're all talk.
Do you really want to go to university?
I don't care
I don't care too
Be quiet
I don't mean for you to be brilliant
I don't care if you're in last place,
I want you to do well
Don't you think you're lucky that so many people want to go to college but can't?
I know that
You should appreciate for it
She says right
I think so
Hey you
I'm thankful.
But happiness is another thing
What do you mean by another?
You are cheeky
We're lucky we're not now
There's no one like you, not even in the past
You think so?
Yes, true
Anyway, you should stop boxing
I will stop if you want me
I think it's a good manly sport
Be quiet
And you should stop to be friend with Yamada
What responsibility does he have for my academic performance?
Both of you are doing poorly in school because you spend all your time playing
A man should not only study, but also play.
All you did was play
Please be quiet
You know what
You can play as long as you study
You see?
Both of you go back to restaurant
I get it, by the way
Fujii's son wants to take you as his wife
No way.
He just eloped the other night
You should consider yourself too
I don't need you to tell me what to think
Wear nice Kimono, bring beers, get nice guy, makes you happy, right?
You stupid, you are still a kid
You don't have to study a lot.
Just study some more
A little study won't get you into college
Yes
What do you want to be in the future?
You work for yourself,
you live for yourself
It'll be fine
You won't be fine
What are you going to do after you finish graduate school?
I will work for a company
Then what you will do?
I will work there
He'll be president or an executive
Yes
What do you mean by that?
What are you saying?
That's a good job
That's pointless
You are right.
It might be pointless
What did you say?
Meaning exists or it doesn't
It's about how you lived
How can meaning exist in our lives?
In this world
You don't understand if I explain
I found that out the hard way myself
Hello?
Sorry, he is out now
I don't understand the family history of these women
Anyway you should stop to be friend with Aikawa
Why do you say that?
That's good for you
Whatever!
Too noisy
Hello?
Oh master
I wonder what so many people are thinking when they come here.
They are not human being
They are man and woman
What is the Christmas?
With the ashes of the atomic bomb flying in the air
What kind of idiot looks at his hands and prays?
I hope the atomic bomb kills them all
Oh my god!
Brother!
Let me sleep with you?
What's wrong?
I'm afraid of the ghosts!
You are idiot
I could hear the rain, I was so scared I was shaking
Oh my god!
What are you doing at mid night?
Sorry for keeping you wait
She is beautiful,isn't she?
Yes true, she is really beautiful
Thank you very much
Are you from Kyoto?
Yes I am
She's the daughter of one of my regular inns
Do not say daughter, I am too old
Anyway it's good to meet you
it's good to meet you too
I am also a live-in woman
It's a lot of work when your family is in the hospitality business
They use me a lot
In return, business will flourish
Thank you
I will pour your tea
Just a cup of tea
Excuse me
Mikako-san
Yes
Yamada-san is here to see you
Yamada-san is downstars?
I invited him to take a seat
He needs to tell you something
I'm going
It's a curious connection
Whenever I come here sometime, that Yamada-san will appear
Then please make yourself at home
Sorry for the other day
I was rude, sorry
Well...
Where is the rest room?
This way please
It's at the end of the hallway
Thank you
This is for women
Excuse me
My brother has been taking care of you
You're being sarcastic?
My brother is strange
My brother is strange too
But I want to talk to you to avoid misunderstandings
My brother is still a kid.
He's not as bad as you think
I'm here to honor my brother
I know that
Unlike my brother, you and your father have good education
I didn't mean that
You also have a great restaurant in your house
We can't educate our children in this water business of ours.
Right back at you
But
The first time I met you, I made a blunder
It made you look bad to us
Anyway my brother is only one son
He is very important to us
My brother is important too
It's the same for one or two people
I don't want him asking my brother to play boxing.
I worry his nose gets broken
I told him that too
It didn't work
If he's a good friend, I'd suggest he stop boxing and start studying
Not just for fun, he also gives good advice
So I'm here to talk about that
While bringing your girlfriend and fighting?
You talk bad
You came here to check how we are, right?
You came here to check how my brother's home
That's not true
Don't get too comfortable with me
Sorry
You are his older sister
I'm his god-sister
I was flabbergasted
Anyway call your sister and serve me some beers
Certainly.
If you are a customer, you can say anything you want. Beer, right?
Beers..
This is where I was dumped
I will serve it
Bring beers to Tsuki room
Certainly
Don't worry
I'm not trying to be difficult
I am happy now
Excuse me
How is that Yamada-san?
According to Kiku, he is handsome man
I don't care his looks,  I am upset with him
That's very suspicious
He is a brother of my friend
So That's more suspicious
That's not suspicious
His family is suspicious
The other day I was called into school again
You're in a lot of trouble
What would you like?
Anything OK
Oh..and
Can you call my home and tell I will be stay at Tokyo tonight?
This is the phone number
Yes
Hmm...This phone number...
What? do you know?
That's what I thought
I will tell you clearly
I don't want my brother to be friends with your brother
I see, I understand what you think
I will tell my brother so
I'm disgust with it
You think only your brother is wonderful
You think only my brother is bad
I don't know whether your brother is bad or not
But
You ask me too much
I'm disgust with you and your father
You said what?
There's a beautiful woman and this man in the room over there
Oh!
Oh you
You are here as I thought
Well, sit down
I will introduce her
This is more than a strange fate
You are here too
I'm embarrassing
Why you are embarrassing?
She said you had a woman pour beer in your face
Hahahaha
He is our elder brother
Well, It's very nice to see you
Welcome back
Where is Ichiro?
I don't know
He is here or not?
There's no point asking
I'm disgust with you
He is not here
I wonder if he is with him
Hello? this is Yamada residence
No, he is not here
No, Hikaru is out now too
Excuse me, and your master will stay at Tokyo tonight
Yes, see you
I'm sure They are playing together
Right attack! Right attack!
Right attack!
Hey Shige-Chan
I'm hungry, can you make rice with tea poured on it for me?
Yes
can you make rice with tea poured on it for me?
Do you want to eat at this mid night?
I'm hungry
It's bad to eat at this mid night
I want to eat
There's a tangerine in there
I want to eat rice with tea poured on it
I didn't want to wake up
I will go to cook
You doze off in your spare time
If a thief breaks into your house, you won't know it
I'm afraid to think so too
What did you say?
What does Ichiro do when he is alone?
I don't know at all
He watches TV or something?
No, he said watching TV is boring
You should watch with him
I don't want to look at it because it makes my eyes worse
Let's see if there are any interesting TV shows
Being alone is boring
if you feel being alone is boring, you should marry someone
It's not easy
You think so?
Oh it was close
You said you don't watch
I want to watch boxing
Man's sports is nice
You're disgusting
oh.. no way, I know you are too
What do you mean?
I know you want husband
You don't have any good people coming to your store,
do you?
You are so rude
My husband is very nice
The other day I had a cough and he gave me some cold medicine
So you bought the wrong medicine the other day
I've got better now, see?
I'm disgust with you
You should find good man to marry
Mind your own business
You cry sour grapes
I thought you were going to stay at Tokyo,
because Aikawa-san called us
I heard that a guest wants to stay in Atami
I had a client go alone
I'm in trouble with him
Shall we find home tutor?
If he's not motivated, there's nothing you can do
Hello? this is Yamada residence
Oh Please wait a min
From your brother
I will take it
Hello? Are you Hikaru?
Oh Dad
Where are you playing at?
Come back home soon
It's late.
Can I stay at friend's house?
Who's house?
At Aikawa's
What? Aikawa's house?
I will talk with him
Wait a min
Hello? You shouldn't stay at his house
Why I can't
You can't any way, go home right now
Hello? Hikaru! Hello!
I have no choice...
Can you tell me Aikawa's phone number?
Wait
Hello? This is Aikawa residence
Please wait a min
Hello? oh, you
What can I do for you?
No, Ichiro has also not come home yet
So He was calling me outside
My brother said on the phone he will stay there tonight
You can kick him out if he visit you
I thought he has come back home
It's too late
Ask her when he left there
But it's mid night
The trouble is mutual.
I will call them
Um
I think I go to bed now
No smart people will come from this man
You are kidding
Boys take after their mothers
Yes I see
No, he has not come here
Hun, My brother came home alone, and he is sleeping now
Then I will wake him up and ask him
I'm sorry to disturb you
What they said?
Ichiro is on the phone
Hello?
Are you Ichiro-kun?
Yes, you are brother,aren't you?
Did Hikaru say anything when you are separate?
He was very angry after calling you
He said my brother is too bad
Right
Your sister is bad
My sister scold me too
Why do you have to say that
So you separated each other
He said he return home right away, and asked me to borrow some money
I feel strange but I owed him money.
How much did you owe?
It's 300 yen
Do you know where he went to stay?
Well... I have no idea besides our house
I will talk with him
Hello?It's me
What did you say to my brother?
It's my business
I've gotten a lot of complaints from you
You destroyed the friendship between my brother and your brother
If anything happens to my brother,
I'll have your parents take the blame
If anything happens to his brother...
Because of what you said to Yamada's brother
Because you don't study much
I told you I will stop boxing next year
You should have acted sooner
I can't study calmly in this house
There's no one to talk to in this house, no one to support me
I think Yamada feels same with me.
He's gonna die
He's gonna die..You're exaggerating
He doesn't need to ask my parents.
He and his brother are not good people
His father's not a good man either
Hello? Yes , this is Yamada residence
Yes, please wait a min
He is sleeping as he went back home late last night
I will wake him up
There is a phone call from Atami
I see
Hello? Are you Kiyo-Chan?
It was terrible last night
Please come in, wait a min
Yes
Aikawa-kun is here with his sister
I see
I'm awake completely
Hikaru is with her in Atami?
Anyway Please ring him up
He is in
What are you doing?
Why you didn't call us if you stay at Atami last night?
I couldn't sleep well as I worried about you
I couldn't sleep either because I was afraid to sleep alone in my room
This person woke me up just before
I was angry with my brother
I thought she took care of me even though I have no money
Yes...yes
Welcome, oh Ichiro-kun
My brother is on the phone, so don't worry
Oh he is!
Where was he?
Anyway take your seats
Where he is calling from?
From Atami
Atami?
He was relaxing in the spa
Your brother's a real rock
He's got a good point
My head hurts from lack of sleep because of it
You worried for us?
Of course, Because you threatened me
You're overreacting
Of course,I worried about you
It's not funny
My father will pick me up by car so you can come with him
I'm waiting for you
I'm sorry I can't send you until Tokyo,
It's faster if you take train from Yokohama
I hate to say this after you sent me home, but...
I didn't really want Ichiro to go to Atami
Why is that?
A person from Kyoto will come
I couldn't say he doesn't have to go
You should say it
Oh, where are you going?
I'm upset so I have no idea where to go
You are kidding
I'm not kidding
I don't sleep well
I don't know what happened if I speed up
I'm disgust with you,
Where are you going?
Stop here
The car will be stop if I crash
Ah!
You are too bad!
You're a thief!
I am brother of Hikaru
Why you stopped here?
I don't need a pretty landscape to talk to you
I don't want to talk with you
You are too selfish!
You insulted me
Let go of me, please,
Otherwise I will shout
Help!
Please help me!
Please come in
You are shameless!
You are so clumsy
You can complain a lot
It kept me awake
I don't want to talk with you
Please take a nap
It will take a long time
You don't have to drive to Tokyo
I won't drive to Tokyo but Atami
Oh you!
If you worry about your brother, you should go to pick him up
Yes I worry about him
Your father was upstairs in our restaurant holding the hand of a woman
How can people let their child see such a scene?
That's OK they love each other
I'm disgusted with you
I don't want my brother involved in your household
No problem, so I should bring him back, right?
Then you tied up him
Mind your own business
He is pity
My brother and Ichiro are both loved by their siblings
Our love will mean nothing
I'm in trouble
I'm the one in trouble
It's me
Here is good place, shall we take a rest?
You can if you are tired
Then I will smoke
I want to smoke
Here is it
I rarely smoke
Women smoke when they're in a bad mood
You think so?
No,I'm not in bad mood
But you are bored I think, because you need to take care of drunker for your work
Drunks are innocent
You think so?
People like me and my father are bad?
It's our business
That would be fine
But sometime you should take a rest
Views like this are rare
How do you think?
It's very nice, isn't it?
I don't need beautiful scenery
I think You need it
If you look closely, the view is nice
Me or Mt.Fuji?
The moon is in the east, the sun is in the west
What a beautiful
You are like bad guy
You make everything but yourself look bad
So let's hurry up
What a nice sea, isn't it!
It's lovely color
Please stop here
Ah....
Please
No thank you
Then...
As Atami approaches, I don't want to go
What?
Let's go home
Atami is there, It's soon
They are having fun, I don't want to bother them
I can't take him out to play when he's out of school
That's bad
That's bad, but I will let him play today
Ah.. I also want to let him play today
You are sleepy, right?
I've been worried about my brother until now
I wasn't looking at you
You were not looking at me too?
I was not at all
You don't get it, do you?
What do you mean?
You don't know how beautiful are you
I've heard a lot of compliments in my store
That made you your bad character
You can't understand real words
So What do you want to say?
Well.. I am...in short...
Anyway Please get in the car
Let's go home friendly
Please
Back seat would be fine with me
Oh There is a castle over there
That's Odawara castle.
Shall we go to see it?
Don't worry.
This is not sightseeing
Mt.Fuji or a castle
Oh, yeah!
Odawara's eel is delicious. Shall we eat?
I'd rather not to eat eel...
So we can't go.
Eels have a habit of cheating on their parents
You are funny guy more than I thought
Yes I am
Don't look behind you. It's dangerous
Nice drive, thanks to my brother
(singing)
Costumers here
Please come in
(singing)
Who is it?
You must be tired
You too
I'm hungry
I will order something
Make yourself at home
Oh you
Welcome
Thank you for having me
Thank you always for taking care of my brother
Who is the brother?
Ichiro's friend,Yamada
Oh..that's bad friend
I'm the brother
Anyway welcome
Thank you for always coming
Please make a tea for him right away
OKOK
Please make yourself at home
What would you like to eat?
Anything OK with me
How about eel?
No.. more sexy one
Who is it?
Good man
He can be her husband?
No good, no good
That bad guy...
Ichiro's friend who got into trouble last night
He is the brother
It's good if he is the brother
He can't.
Mikako is so upset
You stupid
You don't know a woman's mind
I will go to see him
Bring that tea
Take me some plates
Please come this way
Give him a hand towel
I get it
Give me a salt
Oh..Thank you for having me
Yo
Keep relaxing
Thank you for coming
Thank you for always coming
Not at all.
Sorry that my brother makes you trouble
Never mind.
Our daughter is strong-minded
I'm afraid my brother has a bad reputation
My daughter has a good reputation but
No man wants to marry her
She looks like a sellout
Her bad character is like her mother's.
Her good character is like me
What are you saying?
Anyway please be relaxing
Young men and women are good.
He's doing well.
Little crazy
Please take it
(singing)
How was it?
It's love at first sight.
I'm glad
Not you
Do you think Mikako likes him?
I don't know it now
I have a lot of trouble with that
I'm my brother's educator
I also like my brother
I was a freshman in high school when my mother died
He was still in elementary school and I felt so bad for him
Luckily,That maid has come back
I know how you feel.
He's going through a difficult time right now
I took the opportunity to come here today so
Be patient with your brother
My father and I too
I may have said too much
So do I
From now on, let's cooperate with each other and talk about our brother
Yes true
Let's shake hands
Mikako
There was a call from Atami
What he said?
He said he'll go to Kyoto from Arami directly
To Kyoto?
No way, he can't
Did you hang up the phone?
Yes
Please call him right away
He didn't ask me the permission?
He said he will study from next year, so I will go to Kyoto
Then what did you say?
I told him Kyoto is nice place, you can go
No wonder he hung up
Did he say he goes with everyone?
Maybe
This is why I don't like him. He's a softy
Our father is same too
I don't like it
Your father staying with that woman and flirting with her is disgusting
He holds her hands
We just held hands
I forget it
I see, then I will go to call him
Where is the phone?
There
It's nice to be in Kyoto at end of year
You idiot
She is crazy
Hello?
Are you Minamijien?
I'm Yamada speaking, can you call my father?
He said they will return?
I'm going to Kyoto from now
They have left already?
He probably called right before he left because he thought he'd get scolded
I hear they have just left
I hate that about your father
Your father took my brother to Kyoto without permission
That's my father's strength
He doesn't bother to call for permission when the kids are happy
Of course, I love that father of mine
I'm going to play in Kyoto too.
Thanks to my father
Hello? Can you send there if you go home by car?
Sure, I will send you to Ginza
Dad!
Ouch!
You hit my face...
You're too stingy with the cab fare.
You are stupid
I feel regret
Ichiro can write good
Of course, he goes to school
If he can write like this, he's better than me
He's better than your father, but there's always a better way
Is there anything lower than me?
There is no
He's a wonderful son, we can tell
I'm the worst, but I'm still running this business
If he ran this place, it would be much bigger
I supported you so your business was a success
Ha, If you hadn't interfered, this place would have been a building
Then would you work in the basement cafeteria?
You're a toilet cleaner.
Both of you talk so much.
Could you keep your voice down?
I'm busy on December 31st.
I can't shut up
I have to work with my mouth and my hands
You're quietly thinking of Kyoto
If you want to go, you can go.
No one will complain
I haven't say I want to go
so I don't have to worry about men playing with you, though
I get a lot of marriage offers for you
Playboy, yakuza, son of a gangster
Thanks to you, this store has a good reputation
Don't you think so?
Ok, shall we go back work?
I will ready
Hello? Yes yes
Yes right, Could you wait a min?
Someone is calling you from Kyoto
Hello?
Are you Ichiro?
What are you doing?
What? a Picture card?
I received as it was express mail
Yes
Then Yamada's dad has returned home
I see
So when are you going home?
What?
Will you go home on New Year's Day after hearing the New Year's bell?
Yes
That's good hearing the New Year's bell in Kyoto
Are you Yamada-san?
See?
Yes
Her voice is different
Thank you for taking care of my brother
Eh? Ah..Lighter
Yes There is
Eh?
Ah, I see
I thought that lighter was a gift from a girlfriend
Yes, I will keep it
Well..I will be busy tonight...
You don't have to worry about us
Yes yes, then see you
You are too simple
In thoughts, sexiness is outside
He said this lighter was a memento of his mother
You can go to Kyoto,Mikako
I can't go at the new year's eve
You don't need to be upset
I would be angry
Too busy and frustrated
I don't know why I'm getting old
So you go to Kyoto to think about your life
Gong Gong
Ichiro makes me worry all the time
It'll take your mind off your problems
Gong
You are too noisy
If you'd rather I wasn't here, I'll go
I don't care both Ichito and this restaurant
Ok I will go to Kyoto
If I'm in the way, I'll go.
See you
Ha, I'm disgusted with her
She said she will go for us even though she goes to a guy who she loves
It seems no one is here..Door has not been locked
Welcome back
You should lock the door
I will go to Kyoto from now, so Please prepare my stuff
What's wrong?
I'm over
It's strange that you cry,
You are a strong-minded woman
You misunderstand me.
I'm weak-minded
Some tea cakes are here.
Did you have a visitor?
He has left
Who?
That man came
That man?
The man in the drugstore you like
So Please listen to my story
I don't want to listen
That's too bad.
I feel sad
I will go to Kyoto.
I have no time
Go ahead.
Everyone is cold
Talk to me now
I will say directly
I'm broken heart
You were serious with me?
Excuse me
People like you have no idea how I feel
You are excuse.
So What happen?
Actually he said he wants to talk with me something
That man is called Yoshio, Good name isn't it?
Then The Yoshio did what?
Please listen to me
I'm listening
My heart was beating
It's the first time in my life
You'll have to guess
I will
So he came here
There was just no one here
I served him tea and sweets
He left without eating anything
Please eat if you like
You've been lied to, haven't you?
No, No way!
He was serious and proposed me
That's good for you
It is not good at all
Yoshio's father has no wife now
so Yoshio asked me to marry his father
With his father
How old is Yoshio?
Still 20
I'm a sissy wife type
That's ridiculous
Don't cry and help me
Today is last day in this year
You can find better man next year
Well, I have no time
I want to go somewhere too
You liked Yoshio so much
It's more than I like
But I will forget him
Tomorrow, a new year
I'll start over with a fresh mind
You are saying right.
I'll start over with a fresh mind too
Is anyone nice in Kyoto?
Yes there is anyone nice in Kyoto
Get the toiletries ready
Please introduce me to someone.
Because it's a new year
My brother's gone somewhere
He's going to talk to someone, isn't he?
He is young so
Are they not here?
They want to be alone
Let's go to the bell tower.
I'm sure they'll be there
I don't think you'll like my father's relationship with Kyoko
I think it's OK
After my mother died, my father didn't allow any women in the house for us
It would be nice for my father to have a girlfriend out there
Just as there is love for us,
there can be love for our lonely father
Just as there is freedom for us,
there can be freedom for your lonely father
I'm glad you understand that
Let's shake hands
The bells are starting to ring
It's finally a new year
This is the year I'm going to take on the seniors
Knock them out!