Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
I was asking you if you did or not!
Soldiers risk their lives fighting for their country.
You know?
You committed an offense without permission.
Kubi (1968)
You really like it.
Paper relies on donations from readers.
If I get the paper without permission,the police will arrest me.
It could be.
The criticism of the Cabinet that you wrote last year was pretty good.
I had to write it.
People are too quiet these days.
You have a good reputation with the judge.
They don't like soldiers, so they like you.
You have a very high reputation as a lawyer, so I think it's best not to push yourself too hard.
Don't worry.
Are you sure?
I'm 48 years old and have been through a lot of hardships.
Mr.Masaki.
There's a phone call for you.
Yes that's right.
He is a foreman at a coal mine in Ibaraki Prefecture....
He's a very fit man.
He died of a cerebral hemorrhage three days after being detained by the police.
I doubt it...
He was killed?
There is such a suspicion.
Takita-san and Kishimoto-san, who are involved in the project, are asking about me.
Mrs. Takita lives in Tokyo and is close to me.
I know you are busy, but could you meet with them once?
I get it.
Instead of taking them to the office, we take them to the bar hall.
This is Aokura Village, Nalahara District, Ibaraki Prefecture, where Takita Coal Mine, which is run by my dog, is located.
This is a very small coal mine.
We used to have about 80 employees, but now we have very few employees.
We currently have 34 employees including us.
Have you been running this place for a long time?
No.
My late husband owned a mountain in Sendai.
But it was far away, so we sold it and bought this mountain.
This is the only coal mine in this village?
There is another mountain called Katayama Coal Mine.
I'd like to hear about the man who was killed.
He is called our worker,Sakiyama.
Sakiyama?
He was a mine guide.
He's the one who investigated and decided where the mineral deposits would be..
He was an important figure in the management of the mine.
We needed him.
Is he from this village?
He was from Fukushima Prefecture and worked for Tokiwa Coal.
He returned to Fukushima on January 15th to attend a relative's wedding.
Today is 24th..
He came back on January 20th, 4 days ago from today.
Are you Noboru Umura from Sakiyama?
Yes I am.
I have something to ask you, so please come to the police station.
Why you ask me?
Anyway come with me.
He is Yasui, police here.
Is he from the police station?
He was arrested for gambling on Hanafuda cards.
It was the evening of January 20th.
Two days later, Officer YASUI came to the mine.
Have a seat.
I would like to tell you about Okumura in police custody on the 20th.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
He suddenly died of a cerebral hemorrhage this morning.
We want you to come and retrieve his body.
His cause of death was a cerebral hemorrhage?
Yes.
Anyway we went out to the police station in Osaki.
I'm upset just remembering it.
It was just Hanafuda gambling.
He was in jail for 3 days and he was kicked and hit.
Police asked me something.
Police asked he's not just gambling, he's doing the dark stuff, too.
He was targeted.
I think so.
Takita Coal Mine will be bankrupt soon.
I know you know about this.
I'll stop by Kawashima Transport before going to the police.
Kawashima Transport is the transportation company that handles all of our employees and brings them to Gozenyama Station.
The president of this company, Kawashima, is in and out of the police station all the time.
I was concerned about Okumura.
So I went there on the evening of the 20th when he was taken to the police station to ask for help.
I'd say it's a game of hanafuda, but the other guys just got punched and came home.
Anyway, they should be released as soon as possible without being interrogated too badly.
Kawashima clearly knew that, didn't he?
I heard he switched his hanafuda gambling to the dark side right away.
They were buying up white rice and making rice cakes and sending them to the Tokyo area.
So I asked Director Shiozawa to let him go home early.
Are you sure about that, Mr. Kawashima?
What do you mean?
Actually, Mr. Kawashima, I'm told that Okumura died suddenly this morning at the police station.
What?
He was dead?
I'm sure police used violence.
Damn it. I asked them...
used violence?
We can't take his body right away.
But We can't leave the corpse at the police station forever.
That's absurd.
He's from Fukushima Prefecture. I sent a telegram this morning, but no one's come yet.
Anyway, until the bereaved family arrives, please keep his body here.
We're in trouble.
The autopsy is already done and the death certificate is in order.
I firmly and strongly insisted that We couldn't take his carcass home with us.
They insisted on taking it back.
The police hired a car for us.
Take it home with you no matter what!
Right now we're at war and we're both busy.
Take care of it quickly and efficiently.
He said, "Isn't it your duty to do the work in the mines for the soldiers.
It can't be helped.
By the way.
I thought you had to have a death certificate to be allowed to bury a body.
Actually, this is...
Cerebral hemorrhage...but It's a presumption.
Yes, it is.
Today is January 24th.
You buried his body on the 22nd.
It's only been two days.
Oh, Justice Minister?
I'll take to Mr. Iwasaki, Minister of Justice, or Mr. Komori, Director of the Criminal Affairs Bureau.
This is our attorney, Masaki Masaki of Masaki Law Offices.
Yes that is me.
I'll visit you now.
Tell Komori that I'll visit him.
Yes, thanks.
Will you handle the AOKURA Village case?
Oh no, that's not necessary.
But the cause of death is a bit odd.
The point is, once the authorities do a proper autopsy, they'll know for sure.
You know, I don't believe what police do.
But I believe D.A.'s office.
They're all well educated and well mannered.
I'll see what they take care of it.
I'm too busy, I can't handle this case.
Matsuda, Chief of the Criminal Division, welcomed Masaki at the Justice Department.
The head of the Criminal Investigation Bureau, Mr. Komori, was not present at the meeting because he was with Minister Iwasaki, who was giving a speech to the Diet.
I understand the situation and the circumstances very well.
I will consult with the Criminal Investigation Bureau Chief immediately.
What I'd like to ask for is an autopsy.
I understand perfectly.
I'll call you right back about that.
Thanks.
But the next day, the 25th, I still hadn't heard anything from them.
I'm a little concerned because I haven't heard back from them yet.
If they don't do an autopsy soon, the body will rot.
I want them to be clear.
If it's a brain hemorrhage, I can tell it to their family.
So please.
I'm preparing the indictment now.
A indictment ?
I mean, I don't have the right to demand an autopsy any sooner.
For now,I am just at the stage of informing the authorities of the strange rumors.
So the interrogation of the previous four candidates for playing Hanafuda.
This is clearly an assault.
I would like to add to this the accusation that Okumura's death is strongly suspected to have been caused by an assault by a police officer.
I don't know anything about it, but I'd appreciate your cooperation.
When will you go there?
No, that won't be necessary.
All we need is an accurate autopsy.
If you file a complaint, the authorities will take care of it.
It might be easier to do it this way.
Hello? Masaki law office.
Oh Matsuda?
Sorry for the late reply.
I've been trying to reach you by phone, but I'm too far away.
We have been assigned to the case.
He is Prosecutor Tashiro of the Tokyo Appellate Court.
He is Prosecutor Tashiro of the Tokyo Appellate Court?
I'd like you to meet with him I'd like you to meet with him and discuss the situation in detail.
Well, thank you very much for your time.
I'll go to the D.A.'s office as soon as I can.
I understand perfectly.
Are you lawyer Masaki?
I've been expecting you.
We need the autopsy as soon as possible.
You can't do anything if his body collapses.
Hold on.
He could show the complaint to his boss and discuss it with him.
I don't think so.
It's not big deal.
He'd just returned from Manchuria.
He doesn't fit in here yet.
He's a little tense, isn't he?
Then I had to wait 10 or 15 minutes.
All right, I'll explain the case.
Well, before you do that, I'd like to ask you a few questions.
How was this case brought to Masaki Law Office?
That's none of your business.
I have a responsibility as the prosecutor in charge.
But that's easy for me to say.
Shizue Takita, who worked at the mine where the victim worked, knew Mr. Nomura of the Nomura Printing Studio and came to him for advice.
Mr. Nomura remembered me and consult with her because he was printing my magazine.
That's all.
He continues to ask as many questions as he needs to about the path he took on the case.
Finally, it was over.
I understand the pathway of the case very well.
Now, one more thing... about Masaki's relationship with the Justice Department.
Minister Iwasaki, Chief Komori, Chief Matsuda.
Regarding your relationship with these people, are any of them relatives of yours?
What does that have to do with the case?
I'm in charge of the case. I have a responsibility to hear everything.
He goes on and on about the relationship between Masaki and the Justice Department.
He acted as if he were a prosecutor investigating a suspect.
I was starting to lose my patience.
Finally, that interrogation is over.
You're an idiot, aren't you?
I don't think it's necessary to ask something that has nothing to do with the case, no matter how many prosecutors are in charge of the case.
When are you going to be there?
I would like to go tomorrow.
If possible.
I'm a busy man, and this case is only about the autopsy.
If possible, I'd like you to bring the body to Tokyo.
That's all I ask.
I don't know if we'll do an autopsy or not.
Even if they were to do that, I can't tell you where they would do it.
He's smart.
They definitely only do dissections.
I don't mean that.
Apparently, something I shouldn't trust, but have trusted too much so far.
I'm going to the Ibaraki site tomorrow.
I never think everything is as it seems.
But why do the people in the D.A.'s office behave like that?
Are they the same people who, like the police, wield insidious power within the Japanese bureaucracy and taunt the people?
If so, I was too stupid not to have noticed it before.
No, it's not.
Because of the war.
This war is swamping all human good will and sense of justice.
Lawyer.
(Kishimoto: We are on dissecting a corpse)
Isn't this telegram dated yesterday?
The time was 6pm.
It came to me late last night.
Why you didn't tell me before we got on train?
I'm sure we'll be there today, and they've already done his autopsy yesterday.
If I showed it to you,I thought you wouldn't go to Aokura.
But.
Sir, in this case, I hate the man who had Okumura killed more than the police economist who killed him.
As I told you the other day...
There's another coal mine in that village.
The manager there is good friends with the Yasui police officer stationed in the village who arrested Okumura.
YASUI gets rice, miso rolls, coal mines, lung liquor, and even clothing from Katayama.
They are very close now.
That's why he's harassing us.
And Okumura's arrest is really an attempt to destroy the Takita Coal Mine.
If an officer colludes with a contractor to do such a thing If an officer colludes with a contractor and goes to such lengths,
there would be no more laws and the world would be a mess.
Anyway, the autopsy was done yesterday.
AOKURA will have to wait.
Anyway, when we get to Mito, let's stop by the Mito Public Prosecutor's Office.
They destroyed evidence....
I'm fight with them to the end.
Are you Masaki lawyer?
The autopsy was completed yesterday evening.
He died of Brain hemorrhage.
Brain hemorrhage, as I thought.
I just heard the report myself.
He died of illness.
The autopsy results show that he died of a brain hemorrhage.
Thank you for everything, but this is a great relief for me.
Now I can explain to their family.
Let's go to Aokura now.
We can see the river, and We climb along the river?
Yes, this is the upper reaches of the river, but it is still about 8km from here.
Are there any inns in Aokura?
Yes, but only one.
I sent a telegram last night.
I'm sure they're all waiting for you there.
The workers complained about the torture and assault of the policemen against them.
It was almost an outpouring of sad indignation at something irresistible.
And they spoke about the Okumura case.
He died of an assault, not a cerebral hemorrhage.
He was killed.
They are awful.
Who among you was present at the autopsy yesterday?
He's Susumu Okumura, Okumura's younger brother.
He came from Fukushima.
You were present at the autopsy?
I was the only one allowed in the tent.
Don't enter!
Were there any wounds anywhere on his body?
I wasn't sure.
But the autopsy surgeon showed me the inside of his head, where there was a lot of blood.
He said this was blood from a cerebral hemorrhage.
So it was full of blood?
Yes, it was full of red and black blood.
What else?
He had several red lines on his back that looked like he had been hit with a stick from the shoulder.
Red line?
People can often do this line when people have a cerebral hemorrhage.
These red bruises running from his shoulders to his back.
OK.
What else?
Before the autopsy, I was going through his pants, which he had been stripped of, and I found a sarumata pants.
You found a sarumata pants in his pants?
I had a similar experience with the police.
They made me sit in a cold cell for three hours.
And then?
Now that the result has been decided, please ask the prosecutor.
His cause of death was cerebral hemorrhage.
Please bury the body as soon as possible.
Yes.
I'd like to be alone for a minute, please.
I need to think.
I'd like to be alone.
I stayed overnight in Aokura and went to the Osaki Police Station the next day, January 27.
Anyone here?
What can we do for you?
I'm Hiroshi Masaki, a lawyer in Tokyo who is investigating the case with the family of Noboru Okumura who died here in the detention center the other day.
I'd like to meet the warden or the chief judicial officer.
The warden and the chief justice are both out of the office right now, but they're not.
Then when will they be back?
I have no idea...
I'll see Dr. Horimoto who wrote Okumura's death certificate first, please tell them so.
I get it.
What was the position of his hands and feet during the autopsy?
the position of the hands, the position of the feet...
I don't remember about that.
So in any case, he was given very little in the way of anything resembling care for his injuries.
By the time I got there, there was nothing traumatic, but the pulse had already stopped and the trends had opened up, so there was no way to patch him up.
What about his body temperature?
His body temperature?
You said he was already cold.
But I think his temperature was still somewhat warm.
Then the time of death isn't so clear.
The night of the 20th, the night you arrived.
I immediately went to see Shiozawa, and asked him to let him go as soon as possible without any fuss.
We met at a banquet that was convenient for us.
And the next night, the 21st, I told him once more
There was a farewell party for a sergeant named Morikawa at Suzumuraya later that night, and we were together again, you know.
Please tell me about him.
Takita coal's Okumura?
How could I have asked you to do that yesterday?
What's going on?
I've been in a bad mood all day.
I had a little too much to drink last night.
But he's a real hard-ass.
I investigated him from morning to night, but he won't tell me anything honestly.
This is different from what Mr. Yasui at the station said.
Yasui reported something completely different to us.
So?
He didn't approve, so I assaulted him.
I wonder if Officer Yasui made up the story of Noboru Okumura's dark activities, as Takita Shizuku says.
In any case, Okumura stubbornly continued to deny everything during the interrogation on the following day, the 21st.
Shiozawa, who was in a bad mood with a hangover, punched him.
This provoked the fatal blow, and Okumura died at dawn on the 22nd.
There was no other way to prove this than to let the corpse, which had closed its mouth, speak again.
Masaki and his team headed for Mito City after a preliminary survey of the area.
They were looking for Dr. Murota, who had performed the autopsy at the Seiryuji cemetery.
Is the hemorrhage from inside the brain or outside?
Well, it's close to the outside.
There was a lot of bleeding, and it was full of coagulation.
I'm asking you again, the hemorrhage wasn't internal to the brain, was it?
No, the hemorrhage was near the exterior.
Did you take any autopsy photos?
No, I didn't.
He was in no condition to have an apoplexy.
The fact that it happened so suddenly... You don't think there was a trigger?
For example, cold or whatever.
As far as I can tell, the arteries are a little stiffened, but that's all.
I'm busy, so I'll just leave it at that.
Then I had no idea that the man I had autopsied was a police officer who had died a strange death.
In the car on the way home I didn't know that until I asked Mr. Hashioka of the Mito District Public Prosecutors Office about it on the way home.
I assume you know the results of the autopsy.
I know exactly what happened.
But I'm afraid I can't tell you what it says.
Why not?
What right do you have to tell me that?
Right?
As far as the authorities are concerned, we found an odd body, so we just did an autopsy in accordance with Article 182 of the Code of Criminal Procedure.
No, this needs to be reunited.
No way.
There should be no connection between you and me.
If you're going to make such demands, why don't you just file a complaint?
I took a look at it the other day, if I recall.
Please, feel free to file an accusation or a complaint.
It'll clear the air between you and me.
If I file a complaint, he'll assume that the formal autopsy of this case is over, and he'll cut all ties with himself with a simple paperwork.
What am I supposed to do then?
I interviewed Professor Fukuhata, an authority in forensic science, through an introduction by my old friend, Professor Akiya.
But the details of the case, the death by torture of a police officer, were not made clear.
Your first question, general symptoms of death due to cerebral hemorrhage.
I'm not sure if the clause you're asking about applies to this, but it does not.
And your second question, in the case of a cerebral hemorrhage, whether or not there is massive bleeding on the underside of the brain, again, clearly there is no such accident.
Then, can you appraise this corpse?
No, the University of Tokyo cannot accept such a request from a private party.
But the idea of taking these issues as far as they'll go as an individual is a thought.
Times like this, you're putting yourself in a lot of danger.
I mean...
I'm not saying you should give up on anything.
There are limits to what an individual can do.
You should borrow the help of a group.
Borrow the help of a group?
This is a major human rights issue.
Saburo Miyazaki of the Grand Master's Tokyo Bar Association is the most passionate about human rights.
I'm sure he'll be eager to take up the issue, so why don't you meet with Mr. Miyazaki.
Why don't you ask the Imperial Lawyers Association to take up the issue?
I don't see any other way.
How can an individual be so proactive?
I understand very well.
But, you see, the Imperial Bar Association is not supposed to take up non-members' proposals.
But since the matter is so important, I'll make every effort to have it taken up at the meeting and I'll make sure it gets taken up.
I see.
Thanks very much.
However, it is not enough for you to tell me what you have told me.
I would like you to write a petition detailing the circumstances to date.
Please do so as soon as possible, even if it takes a day or an hour.
I started writing the petition on the morning of January 30th.
Tea is ready.
As I continued to write with a vigor that seemed to be possessed by something, I occasionally felt a huff of resistance to something that tugged at the bottom of my heart..
Is it okay to be doing this?
I just kept writing.
But I still felt a kind of uneasiness deep down inside me.
I wonder if I'm doing the right thing
I worked on the petition for 24 hours straight, finally finishing it in the morning of the 31st.
But as soon as I finished that last sentence, I realized for the first time exactly what it was that was so strangely stuck in the bottom of my heart that I could not get rid of it.
As of January 30, 1944, Okumura's body was buried in Okura Village, Nakahara County, Ibaraki Prefecture, but due to the cold weather in the area, it is expected to withstand autopsy for several more days.
I wonder if the corpse will survive the autopsy for a few days without corroding.
I mean, it's a cold place, but...
That's fine.
Please typewrite about 25 right away.
The next regular board meeting is February 5, so I'll talk to the board members and make sure we take it up.
February 5th?
As you know, we are short-staffed.
And we can't get the forms.
It will not be completed by February 4th.
But I will try my best to make it possible.
You seem to be in a great hurry.
I will try my best to make it possible.
February 4th is too late.
Once his corpse rots, it's all over.
I need police permission to exhume and dissect the body.
But there's no need to do another autopsy.
I just need to see what's already been dissected.
He is currently undergoing temporary burial.
I'm here to see Professor Fukuhata. Todai can't accept a request from a private party. I'll ask him to introduce us to a private forensic scientist with authority.
And together we'll go to the cemetery in Aokura Village.
Professor Fukuhata had already gone home and was no longer at the university.
I had no choice but to grasp at straws and pay a visit to Professor Minami, the world's leading authority on anatomy.
The doctor in the country says it's a cerebral hemorrhage.
A cerebral hemorrhage?
This doctor is in cahoots with the other party, that's for sure.
Is there any leading private forensic scientist who can give us a thorough evaluation?
Fukuhata here is the best.
But Professor Fukuhata has gone home, and he's on a business trip tomorrow.
You're in a great hurry.
I need it done an hour early, or that corpse will rot.
Well, then... Why don't you just bring me the head?
Just his head?
Article 189 of the Penal Code
Exhumation of a corpse is punishable by imprisonment for up to two years
Article 191. Committing the crime of exhuming a corpse
Those who destroy or steal the hair of a corpse or the remains of a corpse, or any other objects placed in the museum, shall be punished with imprisonment for a term not exceeding five years.
That's too much.
Even if you succeed in getting what they owe, the local police will surely pay back Takita Mine even more than before.
Sensei, the local Kishimoto wants to keep this incident to this level.
I have to think about everyone's life too.
You don't have to do that.
Masaki, you may already have someone following you.
If you're discovered in the middle of your work, you'll be arrested on the spot.
Even if the work is successful, if it is discovered on the way to Tokyo, you will be arrested on the spot and the evidence will be taken away.
And this is the most important point.
And if all of that were to work out, if the cause of death were a true cerebral hemorrhage, then what the hell would you do?
You're wrong, obviously.
You may be convinced that it's the right thing to do.
Justice is an action that's originally based on the most rational of minds.
What you're trying to do is a gamble.
If you fail, everything you've built will be destroyed.
Your whole life will be ruined.
The body's rotting.
I have to get the head soon.
The corpse says I'm rotting.
The corpse is telling me to cut off my head quickly.
It's not Okumura's body that's rotting away.
It's my body, my mind, my heart that's rotting away.
I'll get three tickets by 8:00 tomorrow morning and go to Ueno Station.
As you wish,
You can do whatever you want up there.
I don't care if I lose the Aokura mountains to do it.
I knew that under no circumstances should I bother this Nakahara person.
This man is a trainee in the Department of Anatomy at the University of Tokyo.
Yesterday, Professor Minami introduced me as an enemy appointee for the decapitation operation.
Then this person doesn't know what the case is about.
He doesn't even know if this is a university job.
He just was told to help me.
If he knew the contents, he'd be an accomplice.
I can't tell him anything.
You may already have someone following you.
If you're discovered in the middle of your work, you'll be arrested on the spot.
I just received Mr. Okumura's letter of approval.
We will now re-examine his body.
But this is an absolute secret.
We should be careful.
Ok?
So you and you will go to the cemetery first.
But you can't go through the village streets, because you'll be seen.
You'll have to go into the mountains behind the cemetery.
Ok?
We'll leave half an hour after you leave here.
Then you will go ahead of us, and we will remove the soil from the cemetery and open the lid of the coffin so that we can do our work more easily.
Good luck.
I knew it was you.
Looks like you had a visitor.
A client of mine is on his way to our mountain.
Oh he went there.
I'm busy to prepare for cooking.
Excuse me.
Get out from there.
Now we're going to reexamine the body.
To do that, we are going to cut off the head of the corpse.
And then we'll bring the head back to Tokyo.
OK?
That's why We can't be seen by someone.
Stand guard.
You stand guard there!
You should be careful.
Come on.
Open the bucket.
Have a drink.
Apparently, Officer Yasui from the police station noticed you're here.
He must be coming here soon.
Don't be in a hurry.
Yeah.
He must be Masaki, who came here the other day to do some field work.
He seems to be here.
He seemed he went to the mine for it.
I checked, he never went to the mountains.
Yeah.
He just passed by the station house, heading toward Mito.
Robbers feel fear only when they make off with the goods rather than when they enter
It was some strange realization.
we'll make it to Ueno Station for this 4:37 departure?
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Please make sure we catch that train.
Even if the work is successful, if it is discovered on the way to Tokyo, you will be arrested on the spot and the evidence will be taken away.
Hurry up!
Please make sure we catch that train.
Looks like we will barely make it on time.
So there's no shortcut?
There's no shortcut.
Then the way to the next station after Mito is...
Yes, we can skip to Akatsuka, maybe we can make it in time.
Please.
Hurry up!
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Please.
Your ID?
The police are searching our belongings.
What's this.
Lawyer.
Who’s this?
It's mine.
What's in here?
It's not a black market item.
I didn't ask you this.
Let's see what's in here.
Open it.
Hold on.
This isn't what we bought at the store.
What's in here?
The human head
The human head?
Don't make fun of me!
You can smell it in the warmth of this place... and it's kind of disgusting.
I couldn't stop smelling something.
It's the smell of fish... rotting fish bellies.
Don't bring in those disgusting stuff.
Where are you going?
Ueno.
Get out from here.
Don't you have any idea how much trouble you're causing the passengers?
I was thinking of using it to fertilize my garden.
Go.
And if all of that were to work out, if the cause of death were a true cerebral hemorrhage, then what the hell would you do?
Soon we'll be at Nippori.
I'm closer to home if I get off here.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
You must be Hiroshi Masaki, the lawyer.
Yes.
We are police.
Let us examine your belongings.
You have no right to examine my stuff.
You're only carrying that briefcase of yours, right?
You'll know it when you see it.
Nothing else?
You guys are useless.
Oh Masaki.
You are here more than I thought.
I made it hurry.
How did it turn out?
Good morning.
It's been a long time since I've had dinner.
That mizutaki was very good.
Fukuhata professor please.
The lawyer, Hiroshi Masaki is here.
He's brought one of his heads with him.
I'll send it over to you now, so please take a look at it.
Please.
I heard Professor Fukuhata doesn't take requests from the private sector.
Don't worry.
Take that to the forensic science department.
Please.
Hanai.
Take a look at this.
Professor Fukuhata is still trying to avoid this stinking private appraisal.
Professor Fukuhata won't examine this.
After all that washing, there's no more evidence.
There is a large subcutaneous hemorrhage 4 cm behind the base of the left strong root.
There is also a large subcutaneous hemorrhage on the right frontal surface of the brain with significant red blood vessel hemorrhaging.
There's an almost identical hemorrhage on the left temporal surface.
This is traumatic.
This is not a brain hemorrhage.
This is clearly a beating.
It worked well.
Now I'm afraid I may have put the brakes on you a bit too much.
Justice is not so much about rational thought as it is about doing what is necessary, when it is necessary, and to the best of one's ability.
This may be it.
But Masaki...
But I'm afraid I'm still thinking...
I understand that when we think only rationally, we tend to become selfish and even righteousness gets lost in the process.
But I still have something to say about what you've done.
What exactly am I trying to say to you?
I'm talking about your future.
I have a feeling that what you've done might change who you are.
Everything is at war.
It's because we're at war that we're seeing these terrible violations of human rights.
I don't know in what way.
As long as the war is over, there will never be another incident like this again.
I don't think I need to worry about it.
The head of this unfortunate victim was in the Department of Forensic Medicine at the University of Tokyo for about a month afterwards.
At the request of the court officials, it was moved to the Keio University School of Medicine's Department of Forensic Medicine.
Professor Nakazato of Keio University's opinion was completely the same as that of Professor Fukuhata of Tokyo University.
What happened next was a long, long story.
In the end, the head was determined to be a murder by assault by a police officer, and the case was closed.
This is commonly referred to as the "Headless Case.
However, in an air raid on May 25, 1945, the head was burned in flames, signaling the end of the war.
Ten years later.
Masaki has remained strangely unchanged.
He's exactly the same as he was ten years ago.
In contrast, the war may be over, but the mechanisms and workings of the world may not have changed all that much.
They say the murder weapon was an axe used to chop wood. The victim, Soichi Hayakawa, bled to death.
Something that big couldn't have done more damage than this.
The murder weapon in this case was not a wood chipper, but a single-edged knife.
The first hit is like this, and the victim reflexively does this.
THE END