Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hey you!
I will definitely give birth to a baby
Darling...
Black challenger
Thank you very much tonight
Anniversary of the founding of Nango Law Office
Thank you to everyone who has taken care of us on a daily basis.
We are very happy to have a party with you
I think it is time to close our party
Thank you very much
Thank you very much everyone
It's still early
Everyone, I'm dissatisfied
Nango-kun.
It is wonderful tonight
Wine,music
And there are beautiful girls too
We are in good mood
I have a long relationship with you, having been your legal counsel since your father's time.
Mr.Kotaro Minami, Doctor of Law
He was a good lawyer
I was very disappointed when he died
But his son has become a lawyer as great as his dad
In a sense,He is a lawyer who is more modern than his father
His brains, his energy.
He is more handsome than dad
Well...The problem is from here
This is my complaint
Nango-kun,
Why are you still single?
That's right
I represent a bar owner in Ginza.
I strongly agree with that opinion
Mr.Nango
Do you have someone you love?
Say it!
We are the Metropolitan Police Department Investigation Division 1
I have known him for 8 years
I did his investigation
Unfortunately there is no such woman at this time
Damn it!
How dare of you
There is also information that he has a love for his assistant, Kyoko Kanamaru.
There is also information that Kyoko also loves him
Hey you!
That’s enough!
Thank you all for late
Congratulations
Thanks
I'm leaving now
You can stay
I will see you at office again.
Good night
I forgot to say
This is tonight's reward
Here it is
Can I open it?
Sure
Wow! wonderful!
I'm glad!
Just let me have one more drink, please.
Hello?
Is Mr.Nango in?
It's me
Can you help me please?
Can you come right away?
I will ask for the case tomorrow at the Ginza office
It must be tonight.
Right now...
If so, can you come here?
I can't move
Can you help me please?
It ’s a murder case.
I am not the murder
Did you report the police?
Not yet
Because I was...
I get it. so what's your name?
Fumie Tono
Can you come here soon?
I am scared
Hello?
Can you come here soon?
I can't stand anymore
I can't breathe
I will go there soon
Where are you now?
What?
Ochanomizu?
I see
OK
I got it
Hey you!
What's wrong?
Hey!
Are you Ok?
Hey you!
Nango-san,
Can you come soon?
That's too bad
She was 5 months pregnant and it was too late
She had terrible internal bleeding
Was she pregnant?
The placenta usually comes off after the child is born
Peeling before birth is called premature peeling.
This is very dangerous
What is the reason?
She hit her hips hard
She was kicked by someone?
I think it's her fault
It's snowing so she may have slipped and fell
So..She's not a suspicious death
Well..kind of
I'm sorry to ask you but What kind of relationship do you have with her?
I am the client of the case
I see
Then
Thank you
I feel sorry for her.
I should have come little earlier
Ah,Ita-cho,I want to ask you something
Listen to me
Now a young woman died in the hospital
Her name is Fumie Tono
Will you investigate the hotel in Ochanomizu?
I think it's a murder case
Then I'm counting on you
Good morning
Thank you for your hard work last night
Did the Ita-cho contact me?
He said he want you call him back
I see
Hello, this is Nango Law Office
Is Itatsu-department chief in?
Yes
I see, I get it, Thank you
He is absent?
Yes
He's on site.
Where?
Here it is
Eiraku?
You know what.
It's the hotel's responsibility if the car is destroyed in the hotel parking lot, isn't it?
I know that,
but your car's doors and antennas are not broken
The roof of the car is just dented
You know what.
My car is cheap but the roof doesn't dent due to the snow last night
Someone dropped the flowerpot from the hotel
Flowerpots are not on the balcony
Please reimburse anyway
What? There is No dead body?
Yeah
This is definitely human blood
The dead person went to heaven alone
Hey,Don't joke
This is the first time
Someone killed and carried out the corpse
It ’s a person who does troublesome things.
It ’s easier to kill elsewhere from the beginning
Where is this person's belongings?
Well..there
Hey
Your turn is later
This is a police job
I will work first
Hmm?
I was asked to defend by Fumie Tono
Dead people don't pay defense fees
We just give you an incense
You take pride in your work, so you do this meaningless work.
Fumie who died was here with a man last night
That Fumie killed a man and ran away
She jumped from here and committed suicide and dented the car
Do you really think so?
What do you mean?
Do not pretend you don't know
If you're telling the truth, the man's body should be here.
Another person was here
But no one from the hotel witnessed it.
But who would bother to call me if She was going to commit suicide?
I see..hmmm...
So What are you going to do?
That's not fair
What?
You pretend that you don't know.
You are trying to get a clue
I don't want to get in the way of your work. See you
Call room service if you need
Thanks
Excuse me
What?
Wait wait
Your eyes are beautiful.
You are my taste
Here it is
Never mind
Just take this
Thank you
By the way,What does this invitation mean?
You know,right?
You can ask other person
I want to ask you
I only talk to beautiful women
You are good at kidding.
Did you come here for the first time?
Yes
This invitation says that you must bring your companion
You? Can you come with me?
No way, I can't
It is a rule for women to bring men
I see.
I think I know how it works.
That's not good for me...
Madam
Oh it's you
Oh
I met you in a rare place
I was also surprised
Did you do it alone?
I'm sorry not
You?
I'm alone
He suddenly became appendicitis
That's too bad
You are lonely alone
But I found a good man instead
There's an interesting party.
Can you come with me?
There's an interesting party?
It ’s called the Gozenjin meeting.
Actually I am also invited to the party
Really?
Don't be surprised
I'm surprised
If you were interested in that party, I would have invited you.
I didn't know that
To be honest
I don't have good taste
Who invited you?
Never mind
She has a boyfriend
You don't have to worry about me
I'm curious about that woman.
It's a warm pool but it's getting a little cold
Shall we have a coup of tea?
Um
Hey, who is the woman?
A woman I know?
Are you jealous?
Who?
Actually I'm really jealous
Thanks
So I will tell you
Who?
Fumie Tono
Fumie -san
I see I see
You should be careful
She is a little dangerous
Are you jealous again?
Really
I know her lover
Who?
Oh,Are you jealous ?
I'm sorry it's wrong
I'm just boring man.
I just felt sorry for her
Really?
I've heard he have a promising future as a government official.
A government official? What is his name?
It can't be helped to look up her lover
You don't need to worry
I want to be with you
Why are you grinning?
Well...
I think the party where you and Fumie Tono are invited is interesting
Yes it must be interesting
How does the party work?
What?
I can't tell you here
Is it a serious secret?
I will tell you when we are two
Excuse me
Hey you
I want 2-6 for 10 and 3-5 for 10
Can you buy a betting ticket without looking at the horse
Your age and my age
Can you pay for us?
How much?
200,000yen
That's too expensive!
How much have you got?
1/4
Ok I can pay for it
I'll replace the money.
It seems interesting
The only guys here are suspicious people
Yes true, because A lot of money moves here overnight
That ’s why there are many rich people.
By the way, there is also fumie's lover in this, right?
Who?
We don't care about other people's lovers.
Stop talking about it
Look! A man is there
He is an executive of a trading company
He often comes here
The person who passed in front of us now
He is a major shareholder in Kansai
I see
There are many other officials
Everyone, the racehorses of the first race will enter the gate
What is that horse's food?
It ’s not a carrot, right?
It's a Pay
Pay?
Horses and jockeys want it, so they run hard
Ready
Go for it
Fast!
2-6, run fast!
Run fast!
Faster! Faster!
Go for it!
What a shame
Embarrassing play between men and women
Some drug patients
This weird play is not the only purpose
There is some secret
I have to find out more
Hello, Mr.
Can I have the fire, please?
She is nice
She must be elite
I wonder who is she
She knows me
I didn't know you are here
I didn't know you have this hobby
I don't know your name
You also have a good hobby
Who invited you?
Wouldn't it be better if I wasn't here?
Not at all,I'm happy to meet you
I'll invite you to an even better party next time.
Thanks
Looking at your way of speaking, the organizer of tonight's party must be you
So...
Oh you are here, looks this, I got win!
Shall we go back room?
I will lose if I play any more
I will go there soon, wait for me
OK I will, give me the key
Um
Here it is
Come soon
Yes
You want to know the name of Fumie's lover, right?
I will tell you
Thanks
The second race will start soon
Please buy a betting ticket
Is that Ok?
Yes
Then see you tomorrow
Certainly
Wait
What?
Who is the woman who went up the stairs now?
That woman?
Hey you, The manager is calling you
It seems urgent
Hey,When you interrupt, say hello
I was sorry
Hello?
Um
Do not turn the light
Front please
Please contact the police immediately
Here's the case. And don't let the guests out tonight.
Does it make sense"?
Please don't gawk at the woman.
Who is the woman?
She is the female president of Sanurou
I see
Please come in
So What is Madame's cause of death?
Eh?
As a result of dissection, half chocolate came out of her stomach
It contained potassium cyanide.
Um
Of course it's a murder
She kissed someone
Then he pushed chocolate into her mouth with a kiss
It's a romantic murder
What are you talking about?
If I hadn't come along, you'd be the killer.
Thank you for that
Thanks
How about the human race?
There is no evidence there
I saw with my eyes
There were a lot of people. There was no way he could have escaped in the half hour I found them.
It was happened mid-night
In addition, there are cordon lines in the mountains
No one has run away .
Everyone is complaining
Isn't anyone talking about that human race?
You are the only one who told me
Ita-cho,Why don't you check out the men and women who were racing that horse?
They are a little suspicious
There is no criminal there
If there's a murderer out there,he'd get out of there.
If only you had come back to the room with Madam
She didn't have to die
I have a grim reaper
But,Ita-cho
I feel sorry for Madam but
The problem is the other side
Why she was killed
Do you have any idea?
I have
In short
She wanted me to tell her the name of Tono fumie's lover.
Also, I figured out how the party was set up last night.
How the party was set up last night?
Yes, That weird party
He doesn't want her to talk about the party
He killed her to keep her quiet about it.
I really doubt it
Ita-cho!
Can you check on that boss lady from earlier, please?
Ryuko Hojoji, right?
The target is big
Fumie and Madam are the member of the party at least
Fumie Tono...
Thank you for taking care of my daughter
Thank you very much
Please make yourself at home
Thank you
I wasn't expecting this.
She told me in her letter that she was studying a foreign language because of the Olympics this year.
I'm sorry to ask this but do you know her lover?
I heard he is an official
Nango-san,Didn't my daughter die of illness?
The police told us so
It doesn't mean that, but I would like to hear about it because of my work.
I was there when she died, and I'd like to hear about it.
Do you know the official's man
I would appreciate it if you could tell me
You...
I didn't tell anyone because I didn't want my daughter to get in trouble.
Actually she was planning to marry a man named Ihoriya
Ihoriya?
Do you write it as Ihori no Tani?
Yes
His first name is?
My daughter taught only the surname in a letter
She said she would talk about the details after meeting
I see
I don't know if that person is that official
Can you show me her letter and diary?
I don't think there was such a thing
Do you have her notebook or photo album?
There is no,right
No
I don't know what happened but
The night she died, her room was a huge mess.
I see
Please
Can I see the match?
Club 3B
Is this hers?
Yes,I think it's her part-time job
Never mind
I believe she works here, but do you know her?
This person does not work in here
Is she a regular customer?
It's difficult to remember the customer's face
Do you know this person?
She's the one from the other night, the couple.
What do you think?
Yes
Yes She was
You sure?
Yes
Hi
What's wrong?
This is a souvenir I bought in Hakone
You're giving it to the wrong person.
Are you jealous?
You are playing with a strange woman
She wants to play with me
Please quarrel after I left
She is strong
How about the Hakone's case?
The possibility of drugs is low
I searched a lot, but I couldn't find anything.
Really? Certainly drugs were used for human horse racing
If you have a new intuition, the organization is very big
How about the Ryuko Hojoji?
She is a businesswoman
She is nice and trusted by banks
But...
She offered a hotel for a weird party
And Madam was killed there
With that Ryuko Hojoji...
Welcome
Thank you for the other day
Hi
What Can I do for you?
I just happened to be in the neighborhood, so I stopped by.
I see
Hey
Ita-cho is here too
I just could relax.
You are a comfortable person
By the way, you met a strange incident in Hakone.
Yes
Please don't make a big deal out of it.
You say that like it's someone else's problem.
You had something to do with the dead Madam, right?
That's true, but I'm busy
I can't handle this work
It is true that Fumie was killed as a result
That's a problem
It's going to be hard to get involved with that woman
In my opinion...
That is the point
That's why lawyers like the police and Nango are investigating.
It's not just your problem
What if they find out us?
Our boss will get angry too
What do you do about Hakone?
Nango got a clue
It's not my fault
Don't worry about that
Boss and we have an idea
I don't know his fast name but his surname is not common, so easy to find
He is an official, Please check immediately
Yes
Leave it to you
A woman
Gambling
Drug
There must be something
What's behind?
Hojoji Ryuko...She is suspicious
This is Nango speaking
Well...I don't know
Oh..that's you! How are you?
I'd appreciate you called me
3B? I know it very much
Certainly, I will visit you for sure
1 am tonight
Then
3B...
Finally you will appear
Thank you for waiting
It is time to have a party
Today's party is called Wall Invitation
What kind of wall to invite men to
First of all, please draw a lottery to decide the order
Please
Your turn
Please draw lots one by one
Did you draw lots?
Please
This is last one
No.1 Please
Who is the no.1?
It's me
Oh!
We will invite you to the wall in numerical order
No.1 Please
Please
Take off your favorite high heels
Take your time and Choose high heels
Then No.2 please
Take your time
I see.
Tonight's party is the best
We have a connection, don't we?
Maybe it's bad connection.
Oh wait
I'm sorry for the women if I die in the middle of a kiss
What do you mean?
Push chocolate with potassium cyanide into the other person's mouth during a kiss
I have read it in a detective novel
A woman I know was killed by that
I'm relieved.
You are rude
Do not pretend you don't know
We are alone.
Why don't you take off your mask
What's wrong?
I was thinking about this wonderful night
What kind?
It ’s a story of a murderer.
It ’s a story of a murderer?
You
You know Fumie Tono,right?
She died strangely
Did she eat the chocolate?
Do not pretend you don't know
It was Madame Hatsuko of Bar Grandprix who was killed
The place was a hotel in Hakone that you run
Yes, But we are in trouble
It will affect our business.
I met the deaths of these two women twice
The deaths of these two have something to do with each other
It's becoming more like a detective novel
I'm sure you know
What?
Why they were killed
That's the job of the police
I hear you are a good lawyer
They were your member,right?
member?
Yes
I am also the member
I invited you because I thought you were a good partner
But all the women who have something to do with me have been killed
Next is my turn?
Or my turn, maybe
If I die, I won't be able to play this kind of fun
I feel same
I wonder where that murderer is.
You doubt me after all
Doubt me as a woman
No no.. You are best as woman
I'm glad you named me a partner
Your name,Ryuko Hojoji is unusual
Were you a noble in the old days?
I was dumped in front of a temple called Hojoji.
It was the year of the dragon at that time, so the name is Ryuko.
Mr. Osho gave me the name
And
When I was 16 years old
He fucked me
I have many experience
But I have never loved
All men are enemies to me
When I first met you
What's wrong?
I'm leaving now
I'm a coward
Then see you
Wait!
Oh..You finally revealed your true identity
You become more and more suspicious
I can't die yet. For two friends
Don't get me wrong
You have not slept with me yet
I want to sleep with you but you have pistol
See you next chance
Hey, Ita-cho
Were you sleeping?
You said what?
I am not like you
By the way
Investigate a club called 3 B in Roppongi
Yes
There may be some clues
Then
Hello?
Oh you
Good morning
Were you safe last night?
Yes
You have a strange voice
I'm just hungry
I don't care about it
I want to eat rice balls
You can ask someone to cook it
Wow! that is wonderful!
Delicious!
You can be nice wife
I don't want to hear flattery
I hate people who cheat.
Oh you think too much
I was just about to be killed
You
What?
You are a lawyer not a detective
I shouldn't have told you about the case
I can imagine it without asking you
If so, please understand my feeling
It ’s difficult to change my personality from now on
If so,let me help you
You're slowing me down.
I want to help you
I will try not to meet women.
What the fuck
I will leave this office
Wait,I will go out of business if you quit
So let me help you
You
I got the name and office of a person named Ioriya
You did good job!
You are my good assistant
I don't want to hear flattery
I wanted to let you know right away but you weren't there
I'm sorry for that
So
Kiichi Ioriya,He is an official of the 4th Division of the Ministry of International Trade and Industry
Hello? this is Ioriya speaking
What?
I'm sorry to call you suddenly
I'm Fumie Tono's classmate who died the other day
Actually, I have some serious news from her
I want to meet you and talk to you, Do you have time?
Yes
I see, so You were her classmate. right?
Yes since I was in high school
So You are from Nagano
What? Yes yes...
She is strange
Fumie's high school is in Yamanashi
Hello? What about your availability?
I see, I will meet you then
Well.. 6pm tonight
Call me 2881-2123 for sure
I will wait your call there
I will tell you where we meet
Yes, Yes
See you
He told me to call here at 6 o'clock tonight
OK,Look up this phone number
I'm going to go there now. Can I make a reservation for a perm hair set?
You called wrong number, we are not beauty salon
But you are 281-2123,right?
The number is correct but we are small restaurant in Kyobashi
I'm sorry
You can be good actress
OK I see
Who is the manager here?
Are you police?
Or Are you a detective?
I am an insurance business
You are insurance sells man
Life insurance
So I'm in trouble if many people die
I'm leaving, check please
Ok, can you check please
I called you just before too
Did you call me?
Yes
Could you do me a favor?
Can you tell him to withdraw from this case?
Oh do you worry him?
He is lucky man
But I can't
Why?
Because he's so stubborn
Where is he?
Please bring sake and food to the 3rd table
Thank you very much
Welcome
Thank you every time
Oh you are here
Mr. Endo, it's rare to meet here
This is a nice place
I will tell you the truth
Here is my restaurant
I didn't know that
Tell your lawyer everything
Anyway I'm glad to see you
You are playing a lot, right?
I look forward to working with you
I know
Then take your time
Thanks
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting
Hey boss,Will tomorrow's deal be on schedule?
Why? We can't change our schedule
How much does the police know since the Hakone incident?
And The Nango...
Hey, Nango is here as we thought
He has an assistant named Kyoko look it up
They'll know who I am.
I think it's good that the Iroriya gave Nango the phone number here.
I mean
We understand the movement of Nango
We could bring him here
Do you think so?
That's a naive thing to think.
He is a tough person
I know him very much
He is stubborn
We have to decide what our endgame is.
Kazu..OK?
It's time, I'm counting on you
OK
Hello?
Thank you very much
Check please
Oh you
You're going to Isogaya tomorrow
What?
What did you say?
You haven't heard anything?
Ioriya told me to buy a ticket for Isogaya at Ueno station tomorrow at 1:00 pm
I get it. Leave it to me after that
He told me that
Don't worry, That's enough for you
I also want to take a relaxing bath in the hot springs once in a while
Thank you for your hard work, please wait at the office
Who are you?
We don't want you to investigate
I see, I get it
I need to go
Wait!
We will beat you!
Oh You learned karate
That's interesting
Damn it!
Hey! Stop it!
Hey you
Oh
I worried about you
They were going to kill you
Please leave the rest to the police
You know my personality
By the way, I have a request
what is it?
Get a mug shot of Ioriya, Trade Division 4, MITI.
Um
I looked up him and he's an ordinary official
You knew him, didn't you? I was wasting my time.
But
But why he is a member of that party
It's a problem
How about him?
This was the man?
I think so
He was
You sure?
Yes
I guided him, so I remember well
OK thank you
Thank you for your good work
He is Ioriya for sure
I'm convinced by this
But Fumie's partner was killed here
There was no corpse of him
I have an idea
He got blood from some hospital
He pretend to be killed
Then Fumie was surprised, and ran away
There was a car down there
She tried to fall down from the balcony
And the Ioriya appeared and pushed her down
I doubt it
There was no reason he killed her
She was 5 months pregnant
Get in the way of his career
Does he murder for that reason?
If he is found, he will be arrested
I see
He was going to kill the child on her stomach
Anyway it was murder
I get it
I understand your reasoning
As I told you last night,Please withdraw from this case
Ita-cho
You're a lawyer. I'm a cop.
Each has a position
It is too late to say it
You understand it,right?
But, Ita-cho
I saw at a hotel in Hakone
They were using drugs and women
I saw their badness
I can't forgive them as humans
So it's a police job
And you're in mortal danger.
You may be killed
So I'm motivated
Criminal investigation is not play
I understand
It's time to go
Where are you doing?
It ’s my personal thing.
See you then
Your car is ready
It's time to go
I understand
As I said earlier...
About Ioriya?
He is no longer useful
There is already a substitute for him
So do you want to kill him?
You're not thinking clearly.
Why didn't you kill Nango at that time
Do you fall in love with him?
You know I'm a woman who doesn't do that
Let's go, it's time
He's going to isogaya. We have to be careful.
I know that
Oh, Are you Kyoko Kanamaru?
Yes I am
Please come early
Nango's in trouble.
He's in trouble?
I'm Inoue from the Metropolitan Police Department
I was contacted by the Ueno police station
He was in a car accident
Oh my god
He is at Ueno Hospital Mr. Ita went there too
You should go
I will get ready soon
Ioriya won't come
or He must come,
There is only one train left
What happened to him?
Or I wonder if there is any trap...
Hello? I want to ask you something
What?
Where did you bring the foreigners?
To Ishinochiya
Is there something over there? I went back and forth many times today
There is a party there, I have been invited too, Wait a min
Yes
Where were you hiding
Am I hiding?
Well.. Here is good place to relax
By the way, about Ioriya
Oh,He went missing
I think you are looking for him
I intended to do that, but I can't find him easily
Don't be so carefree. Where are you?
You are with Kyoko, right?
What? With Kyoko?
She is not at office?
I've been calling many times since daytime or She can't answer the phone
That's strange
So where are you now?
I am at Isogawa Onsen
I'm going to Ishinochiya now
Then
Tanabe
Yes
Call the ISOGAYA police office
And Get the car
Are there any Japanese women?
Yes There are many. I will show you now
This work will be discontinued for a while at the direction of the chairman
What's wrong?
What?
Hey, I'm counting on you
Too noisy!
Be quiet!
How old are you?
I'm 20
How about you?
How old are you?
Stop it, calm down
I can't
It's your fault.
What?
It's too late!
Stop it!
That lawyer will be here. It's a problem.
We have to think about killing him
Boss
What's wrong?
We have caught Nango
Good job
Ok you can kill him
I got it
Wait
Bring him to my room
OK
Boss,We'll be fine next time?
And, Tendo-san
OK?
We can't trust her
I wonder if we will cut off with her
Hey!
Damn it
Oh
We meet in the strangest places, don't we?
Don't pretend you don't know
You have planed to meet me
I haven't invited you tonight
No way, My Assistant Kyoko has been invited
I came on her behalf
By the way,Show me the continuation of the show
Show?
I was disturbed in the middle of the show
I see, Do you want to see?
But tonight's show is boring
Come in
I see, next show is peeping
this is not my taste but no choice
Are you sure?
Kyoko!
You!
Let's talk calmly
Let's deal now
A deal?
Please bring Kyoko and another women here before that
We can deal after that
Don't bullshit
We can deal it later
What the fuck
Drug,smuggling
I know you do illegal business
You are trading those women
I saw it with my eye, and you are the boss
I hate people who take advantage of the weak.
You're a lawyer, so you're good at talking
Thank you for complimenting me but
What are you going to do?
I want you to give up
You want me to give up?
Or
You want me to work with you?
Don't say bullshit
You are my enemy
But I need you
What do you mean?
Please be clear
We love each other or kill each other
There is only one way
What?
What if I say I love you?
I see...Do you want to play a trick on me?
I'm serious..trust me
I'm honored to be liked by bad people
OK
then I will kill Kyoko Kanamaru
I will not make any unprofitable deals.
You are a poor woman.
Do you think you can get real love in a deal?
Boss!
Kyoko!
Kiichi Ioriya
You killed Fumie Tono and Madam
And you tried to kill me at 3B
I don't know!
You don't know?
Don't pretend you don't know
You know how Fumie Tono felt when she called me on that snowy day?
I didn't intend to kill her
As a result, it ’s a murder.
I loved her
So.. I...
You wanted money and drugs
She said she would reveal your secret if she couldn't marry you
Then you killed her
Is that right?
I am a lawyer
In some cases you may defend
But I feel like killing you now
Stay down!
I'm revealing your secret!
Listen to me!
Article 36 of the Penal Code
Attacking others for self-defense is not a punishment
In short, If I kill you, there is no punishment
Shit!
Hey you
Tendo
You are bad lawyer
You disturb me without my defense
Your father was better
His son is in trouble with a strange sense of justice
I will beat you
Awww!
Wait!
Tendo!
Where is Kyoko and others?
I don't know
Tendo!
You profited from drugs and sold a woman
And you hosted a secret party
Tendo!
I'm sorry I was your lawyer
You!
I can't breath!
I'm not bad
Nango-kun
I'm sorry
It's too late!
You are bad!
Nango-kun!
Hello?
Where is Kyoko?
I can't breath!
Where is she now?
She is with Ryuko...
You sure?
Hi
Ita-cho!
I'm in trouble if you strangle the serious suspect
How are women?
We rescued them
Ok I'll leave the rest to you
Kyoko!
After all you came
Why do you do this?
Because I hate it
You hate what?
Don't worry.
She will wake up after an hour
You are a stubborn woman.
Ichimiya has been arrested
You should turn yourself in.
Will you defend me?
Depend on the case
I don't need to go to the police
There's a membership list in this room with all the information on the organization.
I'll give it to you as a souvenir.
Where is it?
Inside the small door under the French doll
Hello!
Wait
I will take it
Hello!
Check inside the box
Call an ambulance!
Oh
There was a pistol on the door
Hey, Are you OK?
Wake up!
Hey!
I...
What?
I loved you
The only one
Come on!
Nango-san...
Where are you?
Come on!
Hey!
Great information is written here
The business relationship is also written in detail
This is so great
It would be a big fuss if we announced this
It looks like her last work
I feel sorry for her
That's too bad
It's not like you to sympathize with the bad woman
Well...There are many types of villains
She was born unhappy
I think if she was born happily, she was a good wife
I don't want you to be deeply involved in my work
You are good at making rice balls
You should find a marriage partner
You mean
I don't like you
I will be careful about women from now
I'd like to be on your short list of potential marriage partners.
You!
Kyoko
There's something going on every day under this sky.
I'm always needed
If I wish so, Do you laugh at me?
I don't
Finish