Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Black bundles of money
Managing Director's Office
Even for me
To you, General Affairs Manager.
I don't ask about the business status of our Asia Processing Company
The president, we are
We came on board to fundamentally improve the situation of the business, which is losing money the more you sell
We will do whatever it takes
We must thoroughly improve this company's structure
For the time being,Externally,
we do not pay dividends on our stock
We do things like shelve our bank debt
Internally, we are trying to streamline management
We're going to restructure some of your section chiefs
Chief's been talking to him for a long time
Yes
How many Chiefs have been called?
Three heads of sales management
Looks like there are 16 Chiefs in our division
So 19 people in total?
The restructuring has begun
Will we ordinary employees also be restructured?
I think so
Those who want to get ahead through the power of academic cliques should be careful
It seems that all the department heads that were called in graduate from S university
It means These are the former president's henchmen
Speaking of S university,our Chief also graduated from S university,right?
Yes he is
so After five years with the company, he surpassed Mr. Ishida, who was two years his senior, to become a section chief
See you
Good night
Welcome to our store
I'm sorry I'm late
Can you pass me the hand towel?
Yes
I'm starving
Oh, You're just drinking?
Shall we eat something?
May I help you?
One serving of pork cutlet, please
Yes
One beer
You don't drink anything but beers
Did you have a bad day at the office?
What happen if I resign from the company ?
I have never thought about that
I don't want to be a husband with no economic power
What are you talking about?
Oh I just remembered, Excuse me
I'll have a pork cutlet sandwich to go, please
You have not eaten the pork cutlet sandwich yet
You can eat it
You have not had a dinner yet,right?
What's wrong with you?
It's bad you drink a lot
Here it is.
This is Yummy
I don't feel like eating
I think you has something wrong at company
Please tell me
Nothing wrong
You just told me you resign from the company or something..
You are too noisy.
I've told you nothing wrong!
I'm sorry
I won't ask you anything
But We promised not to hide things from each other
Please keep the promise
Sorry... I'm something wrong today
Oh..It's too late so I have to leave now
There's still the last train
Yes
You should take a rest too
Um
Be careful of having a cold
I know
A total of 84 people at the head office and plants are being restructured
84 people is 40% of the total factory.
Next, it's the employees' turn
If so, our union will complain
It's just an employment union.
It won't work
By the way,What will happen to chief’s company housing?
They said they'd sell it to him for 70% of the market value.
He can't afford to double his severance pay
That's too bad
They told him if he didn't like it, he should get out of his house.
That's ridiculous
This is the fate of businessmen
Today you, tomorrow me
Chief,There is a visitor
Thank you
Shinpei Miyagawa
Please take one
Thank you
You are the section chief
So I should have given you jobs because we are old friend
It was too late to see me
I might be fired soon
You are kidding
You remind me of something
How about Sumie Higuchi, who used to be in the secretarial section?
She is fine
She does bar business in Tsukishima
Oh I see
I thought she got married
It's a beautiful bar in that area
I see
She must have found a good patron
It might be so
You have good memory
About her
I won't forget her
Shortly after joining the company I made a printing mistake.
She helped me out
Oh yeah, I remember that
By the way,Hiyama-san
I know it's been a while since we've seen each other, but it's hard to say...
Can I borrow 1000 or 2000 yen from you?
Well...I lost a bet on a horse race
I'm running out of money as opposed to earning an allowance
Have you always liked horse racing?
I like it
Here it is
Thank you very much
I'll return you soon
Where do you live?
Don't worry.
You can see me whenever you are free
I see
Thank you very much
Yes
Oh you
No work today?
I was supposed to work but I have overtime every day so..
I'm so tired, got headache
Are you OK?
Yes
You should take a rest
Thank you
There is a blanket in closet
Thanks
Take care
I'm going out
Take care of yourself
Yes
There are some bread there.
You can eat if you are hungry
Um
Can you come over here,Hiyama?
It's awful that you transferred me without even asking me what I wanted
If you don't like it, it's company policy to let you leave the company
You mean you want me to leave this company?
If you refuse the transfer, there is no way to ask you leave this company
You idiot!
Stop it!
Let me go!
I will leave this company!
Mmmmm...
Kashiwagi-san?
Mmmm
Yes
Hi!
Are you kashiwagi-san?
Yes
Well..This resident list lists only one person, Eiko Kashiwagi
What kind of relationship do you have with her?
Your name?
Kenji Hiyama
Address?
The police won't check your family register now.
You ask me my name and address.
What you will do then?
This is not checking your family register
Information network in the jurisdiction...
I am not shady
I'm not a thief
No No do not misunderstand me
Then I understand.
Excuse me
How dare you
Ah...
Awww
Do not disturb me
Who's there?
I'm Miyagawa
Miyagawa?
Oh you
How did you know here?
Mr.Yoshida of your company told me you probably stay here
Yoshida said that?
Yes
Can I come in?
Please
Please take your seat
What a nice room it is!
Is this the home of your future wife?
Yoshida also said that?
Ha?
Please make yourself at home
Why you have visited me?
Thank you for the other day
I'm sorry I don't have a envelop for the money
You didn't have to come all this way
Thanks
Ah wait!
You don't have to check the bill?
What?
There are just two bills so I don't need to check
Have you noticed anything different?
I have not noticed anything different
Can you compare with other 1000yen bill?
What?
You haven't noticed yet?
There is a difference from the other 1000yen bill
There is no number!
What the hell is this?
A printing error at the mint?
No way!
A bill without numbers won't make it to the world
I'm sorry to have to say this but Nowadays, bills are made by the Printing Bureau, not the Mint.
You are right
so Are these counterfeit bills?
Yes that's right
There's a watermark on the bill.
It's easy to make it
For example,If you put a half sheet of paper on top of the tempura
The oil soaks into it, making it look translucent
That's it
So..You made this
How is this?
It's hard to notice,isn't it?
Making counterfeit money is a serious crime.
Making counterfeit money for use is punishable by life imprisonment or more than three years
Even if it's not intended for use, people don't think so
What happen if someone report you a police?
Don't worry
You are the only person I showed this
Only me?
What the hell is this?
Actually,I need your wisdom
My wisdom?
I have a favor of you
Can you?
So you made this for use?
I'll get back to you on that after you've consulted with me.
How many bill have you made?
I will tell you later
But..it's hard to consult with you
I think I'm stuck.…
I didn't know you'd come to me for help with something like this
I've given it some thought, and I've told you
Call me when you've made up your mind
Please
Actually,I need your wisdom
This is a consultation
Call me when you've made up your mind
Oh you forgot something
Your cigarette
Thank you
This guy
I first met him at the race track.
He came to see me after a few days,then asked me for a drink
I like drinking
I drunk with him 6 or 7 times since then
But He told me one night that he had a lucrative job for me
That job was making counterfeit paper money?
Yes, he asked me to Print 10,000 bills with 1000 yen bill
It means 10 million yen?
Of course I refused it
I take pride in my printing work
It's easy to make counterfeit money
I've always heard that making counterfeit money is not a worthwhile crime
But he said it's a crime if you make it yourself and use it yourself.
He said you just make it
He said He will buy them at real 4 million yen if I make the fake 10 million yen bills
Then we cut off our ties
He has nothing to do with the one who uses it
He said you can get real 4 million yen
He did not use the counterfeit bills in Japan, but exchanged them for dollars in Hong Kong
I heard that it is easy to exchange money from any country in Hong Kong!
I'll give up 4 million yen, but is there anyone who can take it back for 1 million yen?
I spent 700,000 yen to make this
You're talking to the wrong person
I don't even have 1 million yen
In the first place, No one with a million dollars would do something so dangerous.
That's right, if you succeed, it'll be 10 million yen.
You'll make ten times as much money.
This is a crappy theory
It's a crime to use counterfeit money but
No one else will be affected
If you steal or murder, there will always be victims
But even if you use counterfeit money, no one is personally harmed
If I had to choose,The governor of the Bank of Japan or the Japanese government.
That makes you feel better about the same crime.
Did you really make this only by yourself?
Yes..why you ask me that?
I don't know the specifics, but can you make something that elaborate by yourself?
To be honest, there is another guy
Who is he?
I promised him to not tell his name
I gave him a lot of money and let him make it.
Once it was finished, I cut ties.
Isn't he an ex-convict?
Don't worry about that
What do you think,Hiyama-san?
Do you have any good business ideas?
Even if you use counterfeit money, no one is personally harmed
If I had to choose,The governor of the Bank of Japan or the Japanese government.
Right?
if you succeed, it'll be 10 million yen.
You'll make ten times as much money.
10 million yen..
Only 2.5 million yen in retirement benefits from a company I worked for 25 years.
I have 25 years until retirement.
Even if I'm lucky and don't get laid off, I'll make 3 million at most
If I had 10 million, the interest would be 700,000.
Interest of more than 50,000 yen per month
Eiko's dream comes true by opening a beauty salon with half of the 5 million yen.
I can loan the remaining 5 million yen to the business.
Oh, what are you doing without turning on the light?
Don't you feel cold?
You know what,Kenji?
You told me just before you resign from your company
I think it's better to resign
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
I talked to a lady at the store today who was obsessed with stocks.
She said your company's stock kept going down
Your company's prospects are bleak
You are right
I'm not so sure about my prospects at company either.
So you should resign from your company
I want to say that to you but
There is not a better job
There is
Really?
So there would be no problem
I don't like salary man much
But I need a money for the business
Of course you need
About how much?
It is about 1 million yen
Just 1 million yen?
I think 1 million yen is big money.
Do you have?
Of course I don't have
I've only got 200,000 saved up to open a beauty salon
so you shouldn't say just 1 million yen
I thought you need 5 million yen at least for doing business
So What kind of business?
Mmmm.. someone told me..
I can make ten times as much in a couple of months if I'm successful
Ten times ? so 10 million?
That 's a lot
Yes true
I may never get another chance like this
500000 yen is not enough?
No.... I need 1 million yen at least
So you can start the business if you have 1 million yen
Forget about this talking
Oh..Why?
It's just a dream anyway
You sure?
You really think so?
I can't help but think so
Never mind!
Thank you
I hear you have a lot of problems at work
I'm making a last futile effort
You talk about it like you are someone else
By the way What about that thing I asked you to do on the phone earlier?
Are you going to Hong Kong?
I don't mean that.
I need to write a report
In that case,Let's go get someone who knows what we're talking about
Don't worry.
This is just small task
I see
By the way
Is the Japanese yen accepted in Hong Kong?
Accepted?
Well..for example
You pay with Japanese yen when you take a taxi
It does not mean they accept Japanese yen
But It is ok if you pay with Japanese yen at Hotels or Famous Jewelry Stores
And moreover there are many money changers and banks in Hong Kong.
You can exchange money there easily
In a way, the Japanese yen does work in Hong Kong.
How much Japanese yen is currently in circulation in Hong Kong?
There is no reliable way to spend Japanese yen in Hong Kong.
But estimates are that it's between 100 and 150 million yen
I see...between 100 and 150 million yen...
Well...Thank you very much
What the hell with you?
You said it was urgent and to come here right away
Stop it.
I feel embarrassing
No no
Look into my eyes
Don't look away
Do you really love me?
Tell me you like me or not
You like me ?
I like you
So You won't leave me
Of course
Why are you telling me this now?
Please take this
What?
What's this?
Well...I've borrowed money
If I remember correctly..This drawer's Kimie tokito...
Yes, our teacher
So Did she lend you a million yen?
Yes. for 3 months
for 3 months?
Yes, because You've been told that the money will grow tenfold in a few months
Any condition?
Nothing at all
We just need to pay back 1 million yen in the third month and we'll be fine.
Is it interest free?
Unbelievable.
This is not lie
You said you need 1 million yen, so I have borrowed
We will be fine
I've never imagined this
Please do not upset
I have a hard time seeing you these days.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
I think a woman is happiest when she is an ordinary wife.
I really think so
Thank you
I want to marry with you as soon as possible
I feel bad about letting you live halfway around the world.
When I had a bad experience with Yoshida
You told me a new life
If you hadn't gotten involved with me at that time,
you married the daughter of an executive...
I'm the one who ruined your life
So Don't say anything and
Please take this money
That's a cool thing to say but I bet on you
What?
Bet on me?
Yes
I believe in you
I'm sure you will win!
So good luck
Eiko!
I'm sorry for keeping you wait
In my house, I don't want to be seen
This restaurant is owned by Sumie Higuchi, right?
Yes
So her patron is...
I wasn't trying to hide it
I failed to mention that you imagined it
Sumie knows about that?
Yes
In fact, it was here that we first talked about this
As you may know,Sumie is a solid woman
No one knows this story except for you and five other people.
so Sumie told you to borrow 2,000 yen from me.
She said You have good wisdom and help us
I was fooled
I'm sorry
I can't have you saying no to me here
I wouldn't say no either
So Can you help me?
I don't help you
I want to deal with you
Once the deal is done, I'll cut you loose.
Any conditions?
Two conditions
Handing over 1,000 counterfeit bills and the equipment necessary to print the numbers for 900,000 yen
900,000 yen?
If any of the three of us, including Sumie, were to be arrested
Don't mention other people's names
I agree with you on the second one
But 900,000 yen...
The only money I have available is one million yen
I need at least 100,000 yen for expenses to convert to 10 million yen.
It might be so but
I've actually spent 700,000 yen for it
So Can I borrow 100,000yen?
I will return it half year later.
Is that fine with you?
It's been a long time,Hiyama-san
You look great, Higuchi-san
I'm too old
You are beautiful
You flatter me!
Did he agree with us?
Not yet
He found out about the plot where I went to borrow 2,000 yen.
I shouldn't have invited him here
No problem.
He'll figure it out later anyway
Is that right,Hiyama-san?
You said there were five people who know this, but there were four, right?
Oh..well...
There is no person who called Junzo Kochi
That's what I thought
You're the one who came up with the idea for Koch-san, aren't you?
You've been completely exposed.
I have no choice but to accept your conditions.
Do you have the money with you?
I've prepared
I will give you the exactly amount
This is the printer
2000 days using 5 bills per day each.
It takes 5 years and half if I spend all
About 3 years half days using 10 bills per day each.
No...Eiko's debt is only due in three months.
Redeeming counterfeit money in a short period of time is the first requirement for safety
I'll need a partner to do this work.
I'll need a partner I can trust to do this work.
Here is your tea
Thank you
Here it is
I'll take care of it
There's a lot of dust.
It's hard to come in windy day
You seem to be busy
Make yourself at home
Thanks
Let's celebrate with Mr. Ishiwatari!
Sorry Sorry
I worked until 6pm
What? Are you salary man now?
The world has changed
Your seat is here
Ah
It's been a long time
Anyway have a drink
I'm glad everyone is here
Everyone was waiting for you
So How are you?
No bad
I hear you work at a company.
where is it?
It's not big company.
It's Ekidanjo(fortuneteller)
Ekidanjo(fortuneteller)?
What is that?
This
No way!
I'm not kidding
You'll know if you come.
It's easy to find if you check the address
Are you the fortuneteller?
I'm still learning it
I can't believe it!
What kind of fortune teller is a man who was in the student movement?
It's not big deal
Anyway listen to me
I've always rebelled against authority.
I've been fighting it since I graduated from college.
After all, every world is a bureaucracy.
I felt it was pointless to fight the powers that be head on.
I began to miss innocent humans
I just happened to walk by there and decided to take this job.
My feeling was right
The people who come there are innocent.
At least They're more human than people in here
You talk too bad
What do you do there?
If you go to a university hospital, they'll give you a psychiatric diagnosis.
That's it
Ask the customer their name, date of birth, and what they want to have read
Make a dater to a fortune teller
To be honest,It's not a job I would recommend
That's so you
Let's have a drink
You are smart as it is
Don't flatter me.
I'll read your fortune later
You can be an executive or you can be fired.
Hey Saito
Maybe I should see a fortune teller
I understand
The first visit fee is 3000 yen
You can't see me today?
He will be available 5 days later
Please visit us 3pm on Friday
If you will be late, you should wait 5 days later again
Yes, Thank you very much
Thank you very much too
Oh, You are here as I thought
You're doing better than I thought
Fortune telling is like a new religion
False stage sets and god-awful speech.
High fees make it a popular business.
By the way why you visited me?
You're here to tell your fortune?
Something like that
What do you mean?
Actually I'm thinking a business.
I met you last night...
Yeah
So you want to see my fortune-telling skills?
Kind of
Is the business difficult?
Ah?..Kind of
I'll be out of work in an hour, so just wait for me at my house.
OK
My house is a small apartment.
I'm drawing a map now.
Who are you?
I am a classmate of Ishiwatari
He told me to wait here
I see. He should have called me
Please come in
Please take your seat
This is Yamaguchi of Moreno cosmetic company
He just showed me the cosmetic
Pleased to meet you
Please enjoy!
See you
Bye
Please take your seat
Thank you
I'm sorry for the mess
Excuse me for a moment.
Wait!
I have to leave now.
He has picked up me, I can save taxi fee
Please look after our house
There is a hot water in the pot
It"s good to go to Izu
It's quiet, it's glamorous, and you can have a beer at night
I like sea side.
Let's go together
But your husband will know
Do not care about him
This is well done
I have 10,000 bills
10,000 bills
10 million yen?
Yes
But Counterfeit money is not profitable.
Because it is not reasonable to create and use.
You will succeed if you use this counterfeit money well.
This is the history of counterfeit money since the Meiji era and its newspaper articles
Where did you search this?
At library
I see.
You're the kind of person who takes things slowly and carefully.
What is this table?
I've sorted the bills into denominations, years of issue, and number of issues.
I've ordered the bills by security, efficiency, and Fineness of work
efficiency?
I will explain it
The problem is, What amount of bills can be effectively counterfeited
If you use a 100 yen bill, it's only worth 1,000 yen when you spend it.
A 1000 yen bill is worth 1000 yen if you use one.
In short,A 10,000 yen bill is the most efficient
Safety is the degree to which you are least likely to be discovered.
Based on the number of bills in circulation and the amount of money, 100 yen bills are the safest.
Fineness of work?
The newer the year of publication, the better.so 10000yen bill
But in a sense
In general,The older the year of issue, the easier it is to disguise.
In short,It can be made with a simple printing process.
This is the principle of Fineness of work
Therefore, 1,2,3,4,5.
Here's how it works
So if we calculate the rankings of these three, we get the answer
This is the answer
10000yen is 10
5000yen is 11
1000yen is 6
500yen is 9
100yen is 9
so 1000 yen is the best
In short The best way to make counterfeit bills is to use 1,000 yen bills.
Moreover There are already 10,000 of those 1,000 yen bills
What do you think about this plan?
Hmm
I haven't seen a new bill in 12 years.
This is the negligence of the Bank of Japan.
It also makes sense to issue a warning to the Bank of Japan
so you can be my partner?
Did you really think I'd say no?
Well..We're dealing with a nation, and it has no more power than we do.
This is worth fighting for
You think so?
so Let' have a toast
By the way So there's five of us, including me.
Yes
Is the one million yen your money?
No
But don't worry
The woman I'm marrying borrowed it
From who?
From the Madam of the shop she works for.
Is that OK?
Don't worry, she is just a woman
A woman? A woman lends a woman a million yen?
What?
Hiyama
I'm sorry to have to say this but you should check where the money comes from
I do
What do you want to talk with me?
Yes...just a little
Welcome.
What would you like？
Don't worry, we will leave soon
Yes
I'm too busy now
Did you really borrow that money from your Madam?
Yes
You're not lying?
What are you talking about?
You seem strange
Oh
Hi
Thank you very much
There's nothing else to talk about, is there?
I need to go
How long does it take?
It took 50 sec
The more numbers we have, the better.
If it's one by one, it'll take 50 seconds per bill.
10,000 bills will take 500,000 seconds.
so 138 hours...
It would take us five days and eighteen hours of work without sleep.
This would be hard work
If there is a printing error, it will be meaningless.
Therefore,Decide how we want to use it and then print the number
There are 2 ways how to use
Short term and long term
Of course, it's better to use it in the short term.
From every point of view
But If we want to use it in large quantities in a short period of time, we need to test it first.
Test?
First, we'll use 10 to 20 bills to find out how long it takes to be discovered.
Counterfeit bills will be discovered and their numbers will be made public.
Use counterfeit bills with different numbers all at once when the public's attention is focused on that number.
This is a test, but we can earn too
OK
Then the simpler the number, the better.
Yes,for example, AB123456C
That's too simple
Anyway,let's try
How is this?
CB654321A
Hmm? Number 4 has little error
Let me see
I see
But This is a better way to think about it.
The counterfeit bills would feature an error in the number four.
That's true
Good. let's do this way
For the first test, we use 10 bills each
Keep the rest of bills
Why?
My house is not suitable
not suitable?
Piece
Yes
Can I pay by 1000yen bill?
Here it is
Here is your change
IS that OK?
What?
That 1,000 yen bill could be a fake.
Maybe
Thank you very much
Sorry for keeping you wait
Here it is
Thank you very much
Sorry for keeping you wait.
It's 100 yen
Thank you very much
Ah, you forgot something
Here it is
Thanks
This is new bill
It's been a long time to receive new one
That's good luck
I can give you a discount
No thanks.
400yen is ok
I see.
Thank you very much
You don't have small coins?
NO
Thank you very much
Sorry for keeping you wait
That’s 800 yen
Could you wait a min?
Thank you very much
What a good smelling.
I will eat
This is very delicious
How is your business going?
Good
I'm glad to hear that
I'll tell you about my work in a little while
Don't worry.
I'd be happy if you like the job
What's wrong?
Why you don't eat?
I spent all that money on the business.
That money is for that
Eiko
Tell me the truth.
Where did that money come from?
From where?
You've hidden something
Who?
Tell me
From which guy?
A Guy?
Who?
Tell me
Um.
I knew I wouldn't tell you under any circumstances.
If you are so jealous..
jealous?
Yes
It was my madam who gave me a million yen for sure
But what happen if we can't return it in 3 months....
What happen?
The owner of an appliance store near the store will pay on our behalf.
Remember?
We met him at coffee shop other day
44 or 45 years old man
Why he will pay your debit ?
Eh?
Why? Why he pays?
He said to me he can support me to open a store
I see.
So you freaked out and went out.
You and he are already!
Stop talking!
Stop doing imagination
You don't know how I feel
You are too bad! terrible!
Eiko does not know.
She know nothing
She does no know I use the fake money
What happen if she knows it
Wait..I wonder Ishiwatari is ok
I can trust him.
But That woman seems to talk too much.
Hey! What are you doing?
Give me your hands!
I will put this down
That is summer cloth
Yes,There's a model competition tomorrow for summer clothes that pay me 5,000 yen.
Stop it.
You can do it tomorrow
I need to go early tomorrow.
I need to prepare it today
Stop! Stop it!
You idiot!
Ah...
What did you see?
I saw great things
You're in trouble if I talk.
I will be in trouble?
When did you see it?
last night.
I wonder what time was it...
Really?
Did you really see it?
Yes.I saw it through a crack in the wall.
I was like this
Please do not tell this to anyone
Depends on the terms you give me.
Please. I can go to Izu with you
Are you sure?
I promise I can go with you
OK then I won't tell anyone else
To be honest,Those are all fake money
fake money?
You really saw that?
Yes... I saw it
Of course I saw it
Hiyama
I'm responsible for what happened.
Now that they've found us, we have no choice.
We have no choice?
That's it
If it bothers you, I'll back off.
The two of you actually used counterfeit money
I'm the person who just know of it
Hiyama
He knows so We should ask him to join us
And Your goal is to cash in as quickly as possible.
Is that right?
OK I accept him
But Promise me you won't add more than these four.
Of course I promise that
How about you?
I don't need to tell you.
The more people you have, the less you get for your share.
Even baby know this
If there are four of us, how much is our share?
Let me see
Hiyama gets 4500000
Our couple gets 3500000
Yamaguchi gets 1000000
So Just us, a million less?
Yes
Ishiwatari is two people
so 3500000 ok, Hiyama too
and I get 2000000
I think this is fair.
No...This was Hiyama's idea.
Originally, it was just the two of us.
You're not the ones who matter.
You may be right
OK then We'll compromise
1000000 yen is big money for me now
What do you think?
SO let's get move on!
I have a car so we can go wherever we want
Stop! you talk too much
Mind your mouth
It's not like selling cosmetics
I don't like it when you say that.
but I will be careful
By the way I've been using 20 bills for 9 days now.
There is no news for that.
What's wrong?
Counterfeit bills must be circulating, and one should be discovered.
In reality, some of them must have been found.
The police have yet to make an announcement.
The police may be investigating
The police investigation may have gotten to us.
But when I think about it..
In a counterfeit money investigation, unlike corruption or election fraud,
the finder can't be the culprit or accomplice.
It was an accident.
The police don't have to hide it.
It was an accident. The police don't have to hide it.
It might be so
If one of them is found, some newspaper will report it.
Some newspaper will report it.
Ah, Please wait
Is it Trump fortune telling?
Yes,I'll show you I'm a professional fortune teller.
Let me see
Don't worry.
The reason they can't find it is because the counterfeit money is so well made.
Yes I think so
Hiyama-san
oh!
It's been a long time
Where are you going?
I'm going home
I see.
I will send you
Please get in car
Thanks
Please
Hi
Oh you! come in
How is your business going?
Yes, no bad
How about you?
Everything has been changed
Oh yeah, Did you know Mr. Yoshida was promoted to section chief?
Oh..Congratulation
Because you left from our company.
This guy Watanabe is placed for your former position
Good for you
Thank you very much
By the way, Are you still with the woman, kashiwagi?
Why you ask me that?
I ran into her the other day in a strange place.
Did you meet her?
She was in front of a hotel in Sendagaya
Sendagaya?
I averted my face because it wasn't convenient for me either.
Wait
Are you Mr.Hiyama,aren't you?
Yes
This is a letter for you
Thank you
I'm going to Ito for the town's consolation trip.
I wasn't going to go, but I couldn't say no, so I will.
I will be back tomorrow.
Eiko
I can't tell the difference between this one and the real one.
The number 4 has a slight error.
This is the characterize
And The numbers are easy to remember.
Um
Light
Yes
It's so well done, I think They printed a lot of them.
The watermark is clear.
It's slipperier than the real thing.
The ink on the numbers is a little off.
This is Section 3. Hun? At where?
Here
Wait a min, Chief.
Another bill was found again
Hello. It's me
What? CB654321, yes
and at where?
Chuo Bank, Kyobashi Branch
I get it.
Thank you
As I thought They widely used.
Right
The hard part about counterfeit money cases is that it's a crime until the criminal uses it for the first time.
It is not a crime for others to use counterfeit money.
There's no relationship between the killer and the user.
I know it's a hassle, but let's go through all the printing houses.
Publicize and get the private sector to cooperate.
Let's do this two ways.
Welcome home
It's cold outside,isn't it?
You know what, Kenji
There is news about counterfeit money.
They say it's well done.
This is a souvenir for you
I enjoyed at Ito
The fish is very good.
I'll prepare some tea now.
I don't want
Oh What's wrong?
Oh you are upset that I went to Ito
You saw the letter I wrote, right?
I didn't want to go, but I had to.
Oh What's wrong?
I met Yoshida yesterday
I see
You went to a hotel in Sendagaya with a guy,Tokorohara,right?
I went to a Hotel with Tokorohara?
Yoshida said he saw it
Are you sure?
Do you really think so?
Please reply me clearly
You're a miserable man.
I can't believe you trust Yoshida more than me.
If you underestimate me, you'll underestimate yourself.
If you think so, I will leave here
Eiko!
I'm bad.
I'm a miserable man as you told me
I don't understand myself
The only thing I know is
I will be mess if you leave from me
You're not doing so well at work?
I only have a month left to pay back the money.
What happen if If I fail...
Why do you think about failing?
Please go ahead your work
I believe you will be success
So I borrowed the money.
If you have time to doubt me, please do your job.
So Please go for it
I don't care if you try and fail.
Everything will be OK in the end.
So Please do not worry
The CB bill has the following five features
1.The arrangement of the numbers is a little uneven.
3.The texture looks like it was painted with wax.
4.The watermark is blurred.
All number is CB654321A
All five are in line with our calculations.
Operation One is a success.
All the counterfeit money was discovered by financial institutions. The public doesn't understand.
So far there is no problem
we can print the number on the bill
We should wait another 15 bills are discovered
We don't need to wait
Hiyama-san
3 people of us thinks we don't need to wait
Ok, then what kind of number shall we print?
Why don't we make 10 sets of 1,000 copies each of the same number?
I have a good idea
Let's do this
This is what I use in these situations.
Here we go
6..here are they
What's the code?
There is an alphabet on the card.
There are 52 sheets, so you can make two sets of alphabets.
Put them in a row, three at a time.
What do you think?
Let's do this way now
Please choose the first number,Yamaguchi
Leave it to me
How is it going?
At this rate, it will take about 80 hours.
We'll get used to it, go a little faster, and be done in three days.
We can start using it in four days.
The problem is how to spend
How about this idea?
Four of us scattered all over Tokyo to shop.
One shop at a time, every half hour.
No way. 20 bills per 10 hours
We have an hour to move around.
We'll be tired.
How about the station?
Buy the next ticket at the first station, then buy another one at the next station.
We can spend 1 bill in 10 min
That's a good idea
How many stations are there?
Four people moving.
If we use it enough times, they'll remember our face.
That's bad too
How many bills can we spend in a day?
Let me see...
1 bill per 30 min
We work 8 hour a day, so 1 hour 16 bills
We work 25 days a month so 400bills
so 400000yen
Not that easy. We buy something, not exchange money
I see..so...
Expenses are 10% per person, so 360,000 yen per person.
for 4 people, It will be 1440000yen
Only?
So if we spend million...
No
It takes 7 months
The police will find us.
So What should we do then?
Be quiet!
Because
I have a good idea!
We can go to Hong Kong then exchange them
Hong Kong?
I know someone who concern about Hong Kong
He often goes to Hong Kong
So?
We can ask him to exchange money without saying that is counterfeit.
We'll give him 10% commission and ask him to exchange them for dollars.
I think He can exchange these for dollars.
In Hong Kong, they'd never know they were counterfeit money.
I agree.
Let's do it
It's dangerous to get involved with such a smuggling ring.
If we can exchange money in Hong Kong, that's the best way.
Leave it to me.
I will study for it
Director
The printing companies were fine.
Researching private companies can be time consuming.
We don't keep that data on file with the police.
Don't be weak.
You can do it.
lately I'm tired
The owner of the butcher shop in Asakusa who deposited the counterfeit bills found at the Oriental Bank yesterday is here.
We have just done half
I wonder this will finish by tomorrow morning
Can you help me?
No No. you should do 250 bills
My arms were really tired.
Let me see
It was in the evening, the busiest time of the day.
If I recall, it's 1,000 yen for a customer who bought ground beef
Do you remember his face?
Let me see
It was so busy so
Let me see...
Wait a min
The man is 42.3 years old.
dark skin and wear glass
Until now, 17 CB bills have been found
They've announced they're offering 10,000 yen to anyone who finds counterfeit bills.
That's all for the news
10,000 yen?
No bad
Ha if we brought them all, they will be 100 million yen
You should take a rest,Hiyama-san
We have to finish it by tomorrow morning.
We have no time
There are 900 bills left
I will take a rest for it
Hey, Finished all!
Done?
We did it!
Hey
This is
Is last night's news on it?
I saw the criminal
Look this photo!
I will see the person after I had a breakfast
I will go with you
Yes please
Take care
Leave it to me.
Don't worry
That man lives a long way
Tama liver is there soon
He lives there
Oh my god
Stop
How much have you talked to that person?
How much?
Didn't you tell him it was counterfeit money?
Of course not
I asked him to exchange them into dollar
But What if he tells someone?
Do not look down him
People who work in that world don't talk about it to others.
Either way, We need to cash out soon.
The police are investigating the printing house.
We don't have enough time
Let's go back now
Yamaguchi
What?
Is today Saturday?
Yes
Let's go
I went to the bicycle race track in Korakuen on my way home to check it out.
The exchange window is the same as for horse racing.
What was the number of visitors to the bicycle race yesterday?
33237people
Ticket sales are 1599798400yen
Japanese yen circulating in Hong Kong is being used in bicycle races in just four or five hours.
So you plan to exchange money at race
Yes
If you're exchanging money, you'll get 1,000 yen, unlike if you're buying merchandise.
If we exchange 10,000 yen each at one time, that's 400,000 yen for four people.
There are 10 races a day
so 400000 yen?
No,
Last race is at 4:00.
It took an hour for the window to close after that dividend was decided.
5 hours in total
Each exchange takes five minutes.
One person can exchange 60 times
We can do 50 carefully.
So each one spend 500000 yen so million yen a day
But If We exchange money 50 times per person,We're in danger of having our faces remembered.
The window is so crowded they can't afford to look at our face.
But In some places, They can see our faces.
So Exchange money during crowded times.
However in case of the race in Korakuen last night
We were 4 people in 340000 people
They can't remember 1/8000
Or The percentage of that happening would be even lower if the four of us went to separate racetracks.
That's what the face reveal is for.
The worry things is..exchange is the process of making 10,000 yen or 1,000 yen into smaller amounts.
This is common sense
But We will try to turning 1,000 yen into 10,000 yen.
moreover we will try this many times
You don't worry about it?
Of course, I've already researched it
In reality,I have been turned 1,000 yen into 10,000 yen.
It's not unnatural.
That's what I'm trying to do
Our 1,000 yen bill will be used soon.
The money changers will be happy , because they want 1,000 yen bills.
Mmmm.. I see
But the bills are problem
Even if Our 1,000 yen bill will be used soon
They'll be suspicious when they get new bills again.
Yes, It might be so
So..here is my Retirement Payment 200000 yen
We can mix and match these bills.
So we need to make our counterfeit bills look like the old ones.
You are very smart, Hiyama-san
I worry another one
After the bicycle race is over, the bills are taken to the bank.
The bank will know for sure.
This is the weak point
But there is a way
What kind?
We can do on Saturday and Sunday
I see.
Bank close on Sunday and work till noon on Saturday
Yes.
When the money is brought in on a Saturday night, there's no banker.
The counterfeit bills won't be discovered until Monday morning at the earliest.
What day of the week today?
It's Friday
Oh..and 13th
As I told you before,
We have to use counterfeit money in a short period of time.
So this Saturday and Sunday, We should divide into 2 group and exchange money at Chiba and Hiratsuka
Then We can gather in Ito Sunday night.
And we can exchange money at racetrack in Ito
In case the police are called, we'll be in Ito.
The police are slow to arrive because of the different jurisdictions.
By your calculations, We can only exchange 6 million dollars in three days.
Anyway let's do this. The rest of money, We can consider later
How is it?
Um.. and
It's a local bicycle race track, so there may not be many visitors.
Pay attention to the situation at the counter.
You can change the number of times you exchange money.
Then let's camouflage that bill.
Let's do
I bought 10000yen ticket too!
My prediction is correct for the Hiratsuka bicycle race.
Statistically speaking,The date of the event last year's September/October/1112
We should wait until first race is finished
Hello,You have dropped this
What name of inn in Ito?
Let's decide when we meet at the station
I want to go to hot spring,and have a drink
We will miss the train.
Let's get ready
What's wrong?
There is something on the newspaper?
Club Sumi's madam Sumie Higuchi found a new 1,000 yen bill on the street in Tsukishima 3-chome last evening
and delivered it to the police station, where it turned out to be a counterfeit bill.
This bill is the same as the CB bill, but the number is KE836475M
Club sumi is Miyagawa's?
Yes
We didn't print this number
The same kind of bills can't have fallen in Tokyo
I'm going to Tokyo
Tokyo?
This could be calling me
Who?
Sumie Higuchi
Look this KIMONO.
K.E.N..Its KEN
She calls me as KEN
Maybe something happen
OK, Let's see you tomorrow 30 minutes before departure at gate
The location the bill was is here
Oh! Here!
Here?
She can get 10000yen for the prize money
We missed getting 10,000 yen.
I'm really unlucky
Because you're walking around looking up
I wouldn't expect to find it down there.
Did you pass by here too?
I passed over that woman
So Did you pass right in front of that woman?
Yes, I wonder why I didn't notice it
I'm really unlucky
You've called be as I thought
It was too late
It was too late?
Who is it?
Who is this guy?
The printer I made work.
He's here to beg for money
He suddenly went berserk
so that man did...
What should I do?
It has nothing to do with me or you guys.
You promised me.
Please, Hiyama-san
Please help us again
I will return you 100000yen
This has nothing to do with you people.
I return you!
Hiyama-san
If police find this, you're finished, too.
What can I do for you?
So we need a way to get rid of this dead body.
Oh yeah
You took the sheets of the futon from the storage room.
What you will do?
I'm going to weigh down this dead body and sink it.
What the hell...
Do it right now
Ken-Chan
Miyagawa said to me your girlfriend is beautiful
Did you meet with Yuko?
That's why she told me you weren't coming home for a couple of days. And then I made a play where I picked up counterfeit money.
That's strange.
You are kidding
Eiko was out for her work
What are you talking about?
She'd been dressed fancy since noon.
A guy visited her
Director
That madam's patrons are Shinpei Miyagawa and a printer.
A printer?
Yes
Who is it?
It's me
I'll be there soon
What brings you here at this hour?
What are you doing!
You Still Doubt Me?
I got a headache at the store.
I left work early and went to bed.
You're gone for a few days.
And The strange man,Miyagawa comes
I feel weird, so I locked the door and slept all day
You are too bad!
We should return 1 million yen
We still have money.
You return it tomorrow morning
Hello
Is Miyagawa here?
Miyagawa?
Shinpei Miyagawa
Your husband
We visited your house, but no one there
He has not come here
Oh I see
Light up
Did anyone get hurt?
A customer
You are closed today?
Chief
Sumida,Telephone
Senda is there?
I need a forensic scientist here ASAP.
Yes, the place is 3-25 Tsukijima
Oh
There is no
There is no 1 million yen
No million yen in counterfeit bills.
Eiko took it by mistake.
What madam will do?
If she bring it to bank, They will find us
I should stop her somehow
Hello?
Are you Kenji Hiyama,right?
Is Ms.Kashiwagi not here?
No
Are you off today?
I'm about  to go
so excuse me
I'm Hiyama. Is Kashiwagi in?
She has just left
Where is Madam?
She's just gone to the bank
Which bank?
The Sogo bank in front of station
Thank you
Welcome
Can I have this and this?
Yes
I wonder she has already left
Or I arrived a little too late
Or she has not come yet
What's wrong,Hiyama-san?
Thank you for taking care of Eiko
I guess she returned the money this morning
Yes she returned me for sure
Actually about the money...
I have new bills today in hopes of making a deal.
I'm sorry but can you change with his bills?
I understand
OK here they are
Thank you very much
I didn't intent to kill him.
Trust me
He got drunk and attacked me first.
I just pushed him then he fell down
I'm not lying to you.
I didn't intent to kill him.
You are stubborn
Elsewhere, you profited from counterfeit money.
No!
I didn't use the counterfeit money
Cut it out!
Sumie Higuchi said you made it
No! I made it but I didn't use it!
Who used?
Who?
Tell us who?
Where have you been?
I went to buy a cigarette
I see.
Are you hungry?
Wait a min
I won't eat
Why?
I need to go to Ito for a important deal
To Ito? but you can eat some
No time.
See you
Hello
What?
Does that important transaction take a long time?
I can finish it within today
The client is a bicycle racing executive.
I need to go to see him at racetrack in Ito
See you
Wait Kenji
Please bring me.
I want to go there
I can take a break from work at the store.
I went to Ito the other day.
I loved it.
I wish I could go there with you
So Please bring me
Is that OK?
That's impossible.
Not today,sorry
Maybe next time
Yes.
You don't want me to say this all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
Take care
See you
Wait
I will be success in Ito
After that,I'd rather disappear from Tokyo.
She wants to go.
It would be good opportunity to travel with Eiko
OK
Eiko
Did you forget something?
No..
Let's travel
What?
I'll be free when my work in Ito is done.
Let's go where you want to go.
Really?
I'm not lying
I'm very happy.
I have never seen the bicycle race
I will get ready soon
But We can't go together
So let's meet at Ito station 5 pm
Ok. 5 pm
Yes
What the hell?
Let go!
You are Kenji Hiyama
This is an arrest warrant.
Finally it’s last race
Let's make a lot of money.
Five and three are not the real deal.
I recommend this driver.
He is capable.
Thank you very much.
Here it is
I won!
Hey, Who?
That man
Kenichi Ishiwatari.
Stay down!
Oh damn it!
Do not touch me!
What are you doing!
Stay down!
We are police!
Get after him!
Get him!
Damn it!
They say he's a counterfeiter.
That CD bill's?
It seems so
They are terrible
Do not push,Do not push
Come this way
He is the counterfeiter.
Oh he is
Show us your face!
He is the counterfeiter.
He is terrible man
Kenji-san!
Get in the car
Wait!
Kenji-san!
Eiko!
Wait!
Ahhh...
Finish