Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
I live alone in this apartment room 31.
But until recently, I was with my sister.
She worked for a magazine.
I went to a dressmaking school.
I was happy even in such an ordinary life.
BUt, it was one Sunday morning about three months ago.
On no sis.
I bought this because you said you were going to see your uncle in Sendai.
Sorry.
I was totally careless
I'll put it in your bag.
I'm sure your uncle will be very pleased.
I don't know.
He's going to tell me to get married already.
It's cold so you should bring a sweater.
I don't want to increase my luggage.
And I'm traveling alone anyway, so why try to dress up?
You never know, something good might happen.
You meet a great guy at the hotel.
No way.
I'm going.
Oh yeah.
This is your employee handbook
Thank you
Why don't you bring this?
A Mascot?
It's a good luck charm.
It's all right.
You're going out?
Oh, it's gonna rain.
Not bad.
Traveling alone in the rain.
Thank you for staying at home.
Please buy some Sendai miso.
Take care.
My sister looked so happy that day.
I thought it was because she was free from her busy work and could take a relaxing trip to Tohoku.
And yet, that very next night...
Excuse me.
Hello?
You've got a big problem.
I just got a call from the police.
Actually, your sister has been killed in a punishing accident!
Accident? Where?
Just outside of Hamamatsu.
She was on a trip to Tohoku, and now she's dead in Hamamatsu.
I couldn't believe it.
She never lied to me before.
Please come in.
She passed away yesterday at 19:23.
Sis..
What are you doing?
It's an interview.
I'm from weekly times.
That's rude.
I can't believe you took this part.
I don't think so.
The bus company is clearly responsible for this accident.
That's what journalism is all about, isn't it?
Anyway, I'd appreciate it if you'd refrain from doing so.
You don't have to push.
I'm terribly sorry to hear that.
It was raining so hard at the time of the accident that there was no visibility.
A temporary freight train was approaching the crossing.
The driver also said that he had no choice but to get out of the way.
Another second or two. another second or two, the whole bus would have escaped.
I'm very sorry for the passengers in the back seat.
At first, we couldn't identify your sister.
We were very concerned.
And we know it's rude, but...
We went through her suitcase and handbag.
but there was not a single piece of clothing that gave us any clues.
Finally, we found the name of the tailor on her clothes,
I was able to find out where she lived.
I believe I found an employee handbook in here.
Oh..
But if she had something like that, We would have identified her right away.
So it's gone..
No, I don't think so.
The handbag came out from under the seat in front of the bus, still in the suitcase.
he seat in front of the bus?
Wasn't she sitting in the back?
As a matter of fact, someone told us...
She had a companion.
Companion?
She was sitting in the front with her companion until just before the train departed.
We tried to find the passenger.
It was just a man of good looks.
Who said such a thing?
Tsuneko Saito, a waitress at the Marufuji Restaurant.
I didn't think it was possible that my sister had a boyfriend.
The next day I went to see her.
But Tsuneko Saito had left the restaurant yesterday.
Naked Island, Yamanashi Prefecture
After hearing only the address of Tsuneko-san's parents' house
I decided to go back to Tokyo
After that, I was contacted by a magazine company.
I had to work in place of my sister.
At the time, I thought I had made the decision to join the company because I just missed the smell of my sister's scent.
But the truth is that I didn't know about my sister's life
In the shadow of my sister whom I loved I think I wanted to find out who that man was. Maybe I wanted to find him
In that black, black sea of trees
Kuroi Jukai / Black Sea of Trees (1960)
I've done it.
Editor!
Kasahara,Please bring me the manuscript.
Yes.
You graduate from trainees hip, right?
Which one?
modern woman magazine,Seno Ikuo
Ask Machida for the address.
Come in.
Welcome,
I'm Seno.
I'm Sachiko Kasahara, the newest member of our team.
Thank you very much.
Kasahara...
I'm the sister of Nobuko Kasahara, who passed away.
I knew it.
I'm so steeped in the foreign way of life.
She was so nice.
I'm sorry.
A car accident, I think.
Did you know her well?
She used to come to me to pick up my manuscripts.
So just I know.
Kasahara.
Did you hug with him?
He said it was a custom when he went abroad.
I doubt he's ever been abroad.
He told like If you don't understand a word in the manuscript, just ask.
Did he ever touch your hand?
Kind of.
Does he do that to anyone?
How did you feel?
He's dirty.
He's play boy.
I hear Nobuko was into him.
I'm the only one who knows.
What do you mean by that?
Why you don't know?
I don't know anything.
It could be.
She didn't think she could tell her sister that.
Let's go out!
Now?
Machida.
I'd like you to tell me more.
About your sister?
Tomorrow's fine.
You won't go?
We're hosting the Christmas party tonight.
It's a good chance to show your face.
But I don't feel like it.
Let's go out!
What's this?
A gift for my brother.
You are a good sister.
How dare you.
I hear Nobuko was into him.
I'm the only one who knows.
Why you don't know?
It could be.
She didn't think she could tell her sister that.
About your sister?
Tomorrow's fine
Good morning.
Are you hangover?
Our Christmas parties have become a bit of a tradition.
There were bunch of cultural people
But ending at 8:00 is a little too early.
Ending at 8:00 is just fine.
Everyone is busy on Christmas.
Good morning.
Yes, Editor office.
Machida has not come yet.
Who?
Police?
What?
Machida was killed?
I see.
His Identification.
But Machida would've had his employee handbook.
He would've figured it out right away.
He didn't have it?
The autopsy results place the murder around midnight last night.
The investigation team estimates...
Ms. Machida was with the murderer.
They walked around Ginza on Christmas Eve,
Between 10:00 and 11:00 p.m., she was taken to the Tama River by car.
The suspect is believed to be a close friend of Ms. Machida's.
The task force is investigating a cab heading toward the crime scene from the Ginza and Shibuya areas at that time.
Looks like the crime scene is here.
Stop here.
Are you alright?
Oh you ...
I saw you at the hospital in Hamamatsu.
What are you doing?
Just little..
Just little..?
I wanted to see the crime scene.
Crime scene?
As I recall, your sister also worked in the women's magazine.
But why did you want to see it?
I was just curious about something.
Curious?
I'm the brother of the murdered Tomoe Machida.
You?
I was surprised.
You know what they say.
The killer always arrives at the scene of the crime once.
So.
Well, I was thinking the same thing.
You said you were just curious about something.What's that?
Maybe I'm imagining things.
It's like what happened to my sister.
For what?
My sister's employee handbook was also missing.
Employee handbook?
I just don't think it was a coincidence.
So you're saying your sister was killed too?
No. My sister's death was an accident.
But according to the bus company...
She was with a man.
So you think he and my sister's killer My sister's murderer could be the same person.
Yes.
I see.
Well, that would mean that the man is a mutual acquaintance.
If your sister were to travel with you. What would he be like?
I think it was just a business associate.
Then it would be the writer who was in charge.
Wait a minute. If it was a writer, that narrows it down to a few mystery people.
Really?
Your sister, my sister, and the writer that they both worked for, and pick out the one that they both had in common.
This would definitely mean they knew each other in common.
Well, it's true.
What?
He's hangover?
Did you come back to work because of it?
He says he's been drunk since Christmas night.
He is the most popular writer at the magazine company here.
Ask him.
You are in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
He used to be your sister's agent.
With Machida,right?
I'm sure he'll put you in charge.
Why?
You met him at the tailoring exhibition, didn't you?
When you went to buy fabric for my dress?
He said.
You have a nice figure, so I'd like to model for you.
You should go to wake him up.
Help me.
Hey,Ando.
I'm counting on you.
There is one better than me.
Hello, this is Kasahara from the Women's Club. Is there Uno?
Oh you are.
I'm in a bit of a panic over Tsurumaki Sensei.
I don't know that guy.
After the Eve party , he left me in Ginza...
I knew you were with him.
I know.
Why?
Tsurumaki's in love with your sister too!
How was it?
I couldn’t.
You'd better catch him at the party tonight.
I'm the editor.
It's me.
Mr. Machida?
Thank you for the evening.
Have you done your research yet?
What about the mystery people?
Four?
That's not so many.
Shall we go to the Journalist Club's New Year's Eve party tonight?
I'm sure all four of them will be there.
I'll see you there.
We are in the middle of a party, and Mr. SAJIKI is here.
He's got a thousand or so chapters all over the country, hundreds of thousands of students. He's a modern-day monster, a kind of religious guru.
He's doing other things besides teaching ikebana.
Reiko Sajiji is the one dancing with SENO.
That's Sajiki hakuun's only daughter.
Is that Dr. Santaro Nishiwaki of Cosmetic Surgery?
He's the Sajiki family's doctor and very trusted by the ladies.
Rumor has it that his hospital is much capitalized by the ladies.
Women are cute.
No matter how much they say bad things to me, I can't hate them.
Sajiki Nishiwaki SENO TSURUMAKI
Can we narrow down the suspects to these four after all?
If it was those four guys, it would have been in the employee handbooks of two of them.
They are people of high social status who care about their appearance.
Well, then, I'll start looking into alibis tonight.
Aren't you going to go to your sister's funeral?
Funerals don't mean a thing unless the killer's up there.
I'll check Tsurumaki at the beginning.
I'll give it a try.
I'm jealous of you.
You're funny.
Where did you go after the Christmas party?
Why?
I'm annoyed.
Seno thought I was with you.
There's no problem with that either.
Where did you go after the Christmas party?
I'll tell you if you stay with me tonight.
What do you think?
Oh, you're here.
Come dance with me
I've been asked to go back to France next year as a cultural envoy.
But even if I go there, I can't do any business.
I don't actually want to go to France.
Have a nice day
It was a nice timing.
Why don't you guys come in?
Please come in.
Hello, may I ask you a few questions?
You'll be in Kyoto and Osaka next month for a workshop.
You've been busy since the beginning of the New Year
How have you spent Christmas?
After the party, ONO, Sakurako-san and I went to a bar.
Then?
I think I was just walking around Ginza.
Alone?
Yes.
I was just trying to relax.
It's like secret.
What time you back home?
I thought it was just gravure photos?
That's not what was promised.
I guess it's up to the reporter to make the most of the photogravure.
I'm interested in you, so I'd like to ask you a lot of questions.
Sekiya.
Hey!
I'm sorry to bother you.
Hello?
But I'm sick of office girls these days.
They want you to have a nose like Elizabeth Taylor.
Have a seat.
The manuscript is ready.
I know my schedule's a little crowded and I'm a little weak, but I feel bad for your sister that I'm bothering you.
I'm sorry. That's very kind of you.
I'm going to Yokohama now.
Wanna go?
I have to deliver this to the company.
Tomorrow will be fine.
Wanna go to night club?
I'm a gentleman.
You don't have to worry.
But I don't go such a place.
Well, that's too bad.
Your sister used to come here all the time.
Did my sister spend a lot of nights out with you?
She was a friendly person.
She would come wherever I invited her.
Where?
What kind of places?
Don't be so sure.
I'll light the cigarette.
You can dance.
Your step is nice.
I bet you had a lot to drink and dance about on Christmas Eve.
I was at your office party.
You weren't there.
Out with your girlfriend?
I'll leave that to your imagination.
I heard that the party ended around 8:00 p.m. What did you do afterwards?
I'll leave that to your imagination too.
Then I'll decide that you went somewhere with a beautiful woman.
Don't make fun of me.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry you couldn't make it tonight.
Well, that's why my plans have changed.
Can I get you something to drink?
I hear something about you.
Don't get me wrong.
It's up to you.
I hope you haven't forgotten that you're a major shareholder in your hospital.
Madam.
I hate women.
I hate everyone you fall for.
Don't bully me.
I was just playing around her.
Trust me.
Women these days are so mean.
Dr. Nishiwaki asked you out, didn't he?
Yes.
Don't get too close.
He's dangerous.
Oh Madam.
Good day to you.
This way, please.
I have an appointment. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
SENO is here often?
You know him?
Then I could have met him if I had come here on Christmas Eve, too.
He drank till dawn that day and passed out.
I was tried.
Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
I wanted to talk to you more last night, but...
I was about to leave.
But when I found the doctor and you, I got curious.
I think Dr. Nishiaki is a good person.
What's so dangerous about him?
Yeah.
He'll make you feel familiar and secure, and then he'll go for that opening.
I know you think I'm lying.
Dr. Nishiaki's relationships with women are wildly unpredictable.
He's definitely secretive, right?
He's a champion of sex medicine.
If a scandal broke, he'd be dead on his feet.
So.
No way.
He's so afraid that Mrs. Sajiki will find out about it.
He is trying so hard to please her, He looks like a man-maid.
You're so mean.
I don't want to slander people, but...
Do you know the Asahi Hotel in Shinjuku?
That's where they meet every night.
I wonder if Dr. Sajiki knows about this.
He knows.
He likes Sekiya, the secretary.
That makes two of us.
Why are you telling me all this?
Well..
Because I don't want Nishiaki to take someone like you
I like you.
Sachiko-san, Sachiko-san...
You say that because I'm like my sister.
Sachiko-san
Hello!
Good morning.
How's it?
Well, I'm getting there.
You think we're close to finding out who did it?
You'll just have to wait and see.
The word "impossible" is not in my dictionary.
Yes, sir. Weekly Times.
Yes, yes, he's here.
Machida, call for you.
3rd times.
Hello. Oh, Sachiko.
I've just come here.
Yes, yes, I'll be right there.
Husband and Wife do affair?
Sajiki and Sekiya Shizuko.
Mrs. Sajiki and Nishiaki.
I'm flabbergasted.
That's how it is with people, even people of culture
I don't know if it's like that.
Anyway, I'll take care of the alibi checks for these two couples.
You'll sure about Seno?
That's what he clearly said at the club.
Then TSURUMAKI is the only one who doesn't know who's accompanying him on Christmas Eve.
He was not with his lover, Yuriko Uno.
I wasn't with him.
The most suspicious one is Tsurumaki.
Welcome
Is he here?
He'll be back soon.
The fabric for the clothes will arrive from Paris, so I want a good design.
I will do this work hard for you.
Please make it as soon as possible
We will.
Thank you very much.
What can I do for you?
I'd like to clear up a misunderstanding.
I'd like to take a moment of your time.
I didn't even go to the party on Christmas Eve. I went straight back to my apartment.
So... I'd like to find out who Tsurumaki's girlfriend is.
I'm pissed off.
He's so playboy.
Tsurumaki was with who  ?
I'd bite him if I knew that.
I think it's because you can't control him.
On Christmas Eve. I heard you were with Sajiki and his secretary Sekiya.
After Tsurumaki escaped, they were caught, so I had no choice.
So you were with him all night?
We split up... after 10 o'clock
What's wrong with that?
Because you two seem to be getting along so well.
I thought you might have been disturbed.
Yeah.
Two people with a rented room at a tourist hotel in Oku-Nikko.
How was the hotel?
I knew it! Sajiki came and stayed with his secretary, Shizuko Sekiya, on Christmas Eve!
What time?
The time around midnight, almost the same time as the murder of the sister.
Nishiaki and Mrs. Sajiki have an alibi at a hotel in Shinjuku.
SENO was at a nightclub in Yokohama
Now all that's left is Kanzo Tsurumaki.
I'll look into Tsurumaki.
I doubt you'll find any clues that easily.
I'll find out.
For my sis..
But it's not like your sister was murdered.
I mean... if he really was with my sister... On the bus in Hamamatsu...
I want to ask him why he left her injured and ran away by himself.
I'll give you back your New Year's break and we'll work together.
Thank you.
Do you know Sachiko Kasahara's room?
If it's Kasahara-san, she's in room 31. but she left this morning.
To where?
To Naked island in Yamanashi.
To Naked island
Yes she was.
My sister was in the front seat of the bus once.
I thought she was beautiful.
She was about third from the front.
She was across the aisle from me.
She was with a man?
Yes, I thought it was a companion, but the woman moved to the back before I knew it.
She was in a lot of pain when the accident happened.
I asked the guy if he was her boyfriend.
But he said, "No, no, no...
You don't remember what he looked like?
Is he in here?
I'm sure he is.
I don't know.
Take a good look at him.
I've forgotten.
Maybe you'd recognize him if you saw him in front of you.
I'm sure you'll understand when you see him.
Then why don't you go to Tokyo?
I'm glad to go to Tokyo.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You've been twice.
Maybe he'll stay today.
No. He's going for a day trip, that's for sure.
Oh Sachiko.
I'm back.
Oh machida.
Oh, thank God.
I was just about to leave.
I'm sorry.
I heard you went all the way to Yamanashi.
I met her.
I've asked her to come to Tokyo on the Hakuba train the day after tomorrow.
She's not here.
Go to ticket gate.
Tsuneko Saito of Naked Island, if you are here
Please come to the office.
Tsuneko-san, what time did you catch the train?
I hope that's all right.
Please describe Tsuneko Saito.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to investigate.
What do you mean?
Hi, Editorial Department
Kasahara?
Call for you.
I'm sorry
Hello, this is Kasahara
Hello?
Sachiko Kasahara?
You'd rather not do a boring investigation.
You'll lose your life.
See?
Ok?
Hi, Editorial Department
Call for you.
Hello, this is Kasahara
Machida?
Did you get a reply telegram?
Tsuneko-san is sure she took the Hakuba train.
Tsuneko-san was dead...?
She's Tsuneko-san for sure.
Then Tsuneko Saito, the victim...
Tsuneko Saito was going straight to Shinjuku?
But she got off at Tachikawa Station.
The crime scene is near Yanoguchi Station on the Nambu Line.
Maybe the victim knew someone there.
But Tsuneko knew I was coming to Shinjuku Station to pick her up.
I didn't think she got off at Tachikawa Station.
I see.
Someone must have gotten her off at Tachikawa Station.
And is it not conceivable that the Nanbu Line took him from Tachikawa Station to Yannoguchi Station, which is even closer to the site?
No, the victim never got off at Yanokuchi Station.
No one at the station claims to have seen her.
He's been making strange phone calls to you.
That means the killer knows we're on to him.
That's right.
Ms. Tsuneko was killed because I called her.
He's so bad.
Maybe you should be careful for a few days.
I'll do whatever it takes to find out who did it.
If I don't, I'll feel bad for Ms. Tsuneko.
But if anything should happen to you...
Don't worry.
I have a mascot for good luck.
Mascot for good luck?
It's really supposed to protect me.
Funny?
No.
Don't laugh?
I'm not laughing.
I'll give you one.
You have to be careful too.
Thank you.
Train is coming.
Hi.
What a incident.
Same here.
Where have you been?
Martial Arts Garden
I haven't sketched in a while.
Is the seat free?
Someone was sitting here.
Maybe he went to the bathroom.
I'm here again.
Who's that woman now?
She's a girl for Uno.
Her name is Machiko.
So Tsurumaki wasn't traveling alone.
Why?
Tsurumaki is like Uno's boss.
Of course he knows.
How can he be sitting in the same car with that woman, sitting so far away from her?
How about this theory?
He was sitting side by side with her until Tachikawa.
But when he saw us, he said, "This is a bad idea.
She was the only one who moved to the back.
It must be so.
I bet they're sitting side by side right now.
What's wrong?
I was thinking that Machida-san's reasoning earlier applies to my sister.
I see.
That's why your sister moved to the back of the bus in Hamamatsu.
But if that's the case.
Your sister, her companion, and someone who knew them both boarded the bus.
A bit too coincidental, don't you think?
But the coincidence is real right now.
Let's get that woman and find out what his alibi is.
Tell me.
It's Christmas.
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
If MADAM gets to know, I won't be able to stay in here.
I won't be able to do my sewing.
We won't tell anyone.
Just answer if you were with Tsurumaki on Christmas Eve.
I went to Atami.
With him.
You sure?
Where were you at 12?
Take a bath at the inn in Atami
I'll check with the inn and see if you're lying.
Trust me.
Go home.
I won't tell Madam, so please don't tell Tsurumaki about today.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll take this.
Here you go.
All clean.
How is this possible?
Wait a minute.
You, me and Tsuneko Saito's family were the only ones who knew she was coming to Tokyo on the Hakuba train yesterday.
There's someone else.
Who?
The woman in the apartment.
Did something happen?
The caretaker's aunt was killed in a car accident.
Hello?
She got pulled over right out front.
It was around 5:00.
I was just passing by and I got the license plate number right.
But the police found that the car with the license plate number was driving somewhere else.
It was a fake license plate number.
Police said same.
Do you remember what the car looked like?
Polices asked me same things.
It was dark, and I only focused the number.
But I'm pretty sure it was a mid-size car.
It was a mid-size car.
Are you sure?
Everyone else who saw it said so, too.
Are you newspaper reporter?
Yes.
Wanna take a rest?
Find someone who can drive a mid-size car.
Saito Tsuneko and my sis must have been taken there in that car.
The hit-and-run on the woman in the apartment must have been planned by that guy.
Why would he do that?
He used her as a spy to protect himself.
But he already killed TSUNEKO.
When there was nothing she could do, he killed her to keep her quiet.
Yoshii
Ah, seniority.
Do you have something to be guilty about?
No, I don't.
The Weekly Times circulation seems to be up quite a bit.
Well, thanks to you.
You've got a reputation for being the top story there.
Machida,Sorry I'm late.
I found out.
Nishiaki is the only one of the four who has a medium size car.
How about Seno?
He doesn't have one.
He's got a license, though.
So Dr. Nishiaki is the one who pulled you over yesterday?
That's the thing...
Strange thing is...
Nishiaki took a cab to and from the hospital yesterday.
He left the hospital in a cab around 4:00.
The woman was attracted to a mid-size car with a fake license plate around 5:00.
So somewhere along the way, he got out of the cab and into his own car.
It all fits together.
I'll see what I can find out about his behavior yesterday.
I didn't expect you to ask me out.
I was frustrated about my job.
I'm sure with someone like you, I'll be able to find some relief and distraction.
You've changed.
No way.
I kind of want to be a punk.
No, no, no. I'm saying you're becoming more and more attractive.
Hello?
Fake culturist.
You have to be careful with that guy.
He's play boy.
No way.
No, it's true.
There was a woman who came to me, asking me to take care of his children.
The one who was close to you.
You mean she was my sister?
No way.
He just loved your sis.
Machida didn't think much of your sister.
Sachiko, I want you to dance with you.
Kasahara,.
Go home.
I'll send you.
Nice car, isn't it?
First time?
It's a domestic car.
If I had the money, I'd trade it in for a foreign car.
You drove this car to the hospital every day?
Yeah.
Yesterday you took a cab.
Yesterday my car broke down and I had to take it to the shop.
He's my family repairman.
If I leave it there for half a day, they'll take care of it.
Is it in your neighborhood?
Damn it.
What's wrong?
It's broken.
It's fixed.
I've been having a little trouble with the engine lately.
Well..
It's still early. Let's go have a drink somewhere.
I know good restaurant.
But..
Let's go.
Let go of me!
Stop it!
I'd hate for you to get the wrong idea.
I think I was joking too much.
You think I'm the kind of person who would seriously do something like this?
Good night.
Who?
It's me.
Oh right.
It's late.
Where did you go?
At a nightclub.
Yokohama.
That's it?
Yes, that's it.
Nishiaki was so scary.
What's wrong with Nishiaki?
Tell me.
I didn't tell you.
No matter what happens, I have a mascot.
Damn it..Nishiaki.
Did you find out anything about the car?
He said his car broke down yesterday and he had to take it to the shop.
where?
I heard it's his family's shop.
Wanna come in?
Anyway, I'm gonna check out this factory.
Now?
The sooner the better.
No repairs.
I hope you didn't take it to another factory.
Not at all.
We've been repairing Dr. Nishiaki's car for a long time.
One phone call and we're on the road.
We've been taking care of him for a long time.
I see.
Seno loved your sister.
Machida didn't think much of your sister.
Who?
The door was open.
I'm the caretaker now, coming on behalf of my sister.
That car.
You said it looked like Nishiaki's car?
It was too dark to make out but..
Then I guess Nishiaki is the culprit after all.
It was a complete lie that he went to his family's repair shop.
But your sister was murdered on Christmas Eve.
Dr. Nishiaki has an alibi, right?
That's the thing. I spent all night last night trying to figure it out.
The final conclusion I came to was that he had an accomplice.
Who's an accomplice?
Someone who can drive.
I mean, Seno.
Well, they don't seem to get along.
They're always bad-mouthing each other.
That's what's suspicious.
They could be making it look that way, but behind the scenes, they could be holding hands.
But then again, maybe Seno has an alibi for Eve.
At a nightclub in Yokohama.
That's very suspicious.
Nightclubs are very crowded on Christmas Eve.
If he leaves in the middle of the night and comes back after the crime, he won't even know what he's doing.
I see
I think I need to go to the hostess and check it out.
Anyway, I'll see you soon.
I'm trying to set a trap for Nishiaki.
What kind?
I'll tell you at the Lunar.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
300,000yen.
Machida's severance pay
She can't get it if she's killed.
It's big money.
If you quit tomorrow, I'll pay you a severance package.
Oh.
Send here.
Her mom?
Kotani Village, Tsuru District, Yamanashi Prefecture
If it's okay, I'll deliver it.
I'll see her son.
Where?
Right there.
That's funny.
for what?
Machida's brother isn't in Tokyo.
Yes, he is.
He's in the Times Weekly.
What?
He's still in high school.
Eh?
High school student?
You saw him yesterday, too.
Where?
At Tsukihashi Park.
Masami Yoshii, my junior in college.
Oh.
Why not?
I won't.
Even the case isn't closed yet.
It's just the weekly one.
I'm having a hard time finding a top story.
Write the article.
You pretended to be Ms. Machida's brother for our work.
Yeah,but.
But now I regret it.
Hey, you love her?
That's not so you.
Write the article.
Is this fine?
You made it.
I'm going out for a minute.
Yoshii
He really love her.
This is a picture of the trap I'm going to set for Nishiaki.
I asked the photo department to get one that looks as much like Nishiaki's car as possible.
Seno and Sajiki's daughter is getting married tonight.
After that, they're going on their honeymoon to France!
I'm going to finish this today, whatever it takes.
What's wrong?
Yoshii
You are terrible.
You impersonated Ms. Machida's brother to reassure me.
You were trying to get material for the top story.
I was so stupid.
I can't believe I was fooled by you.
No, it's not.
What do you mean by that?
I love you.
Don't say that.
I'm here to tell you that I won't be indebted to you.
I'm sorry I deceived you.
But what I just said is true.
That's enough.
Wait a minute.
Don't worry.
I have this.
Bring this.
Sorry I'm late
I was busy preparing to go to the wedding.
For seno's wedding?
Yes
I thought you wouldn't go
Why?
Because you don't like him,Seno
But It can't be helped.
What do you want?
Yes.
Tell me.
Actually, sir, there's something I'd like to show you.
It's a picture of a car.
It's a car that got pulled over.
The photographer in my apartment took it by accident.
But why did you come to me to show me these pictures?
I thought it looked a lot like your car.
The photographer says he's going to report it to the police.
He's very funny.
I get it.
By the way, what time did you leave Seno on Christmas Eve?
Oh, I don't know... a little after 10:00, maybe 1:00.
10:00 to 1:00.
I was wondering if he'd gone home, and then I found him passed out on the couch.
He told me I thought you were gone, I was sad.
He pretested to be cool.
I even went to a hotel with him, but that was stupid.
You left here together?
Yes.
Well, didn't SENO have a car at that time?
Yes he had.
Nishiaki's car.
Nishiaki's car?
You sure?
I would like to propose a toast to the prosperity of the bride and groom and their families.
Congratulation!
Mr. Nishiaki is on the phone.
Again?
He's kind of rude.
Still no end to the party?
I need you.
No way.
I'm a doctor.
Hello, please... I made your marriage happen, just like we promised.
I'm about to give her another dose of anesthesia.
Oh you're still here.
I have to work.
Hello?
Sachiko Kasahara?
From Yoshii
She's not here
She hasn't visited us.
See you.
I'm about to leave, so you guys should go, too.
You look so nice.
Oh Dr.Nishiaki
Seno
I'm so glad you took the time to come.
You're in danger.
Congratulations.
Anesthesia is working?
Anyway, please come right away
Just wait until this party's over.
Another an hour.
We don't have time.
Please think about the location.
This is a big wedding for me.
You know as well as I do.
You've already forgotten how much I helped you with that wedding.
Are you saying I didn't return the favor?
When NOBUKO died in a bus accident in Hamamatsu
And now you're just cringing.
What do you think would have happened if I hadn't happened to get on that bus and help you?
It would have been best if you hadn't gotten on that bus.
It would have been best if you hadn't stolen Madam Sajiki's eye and gone on that trip with that woman.
I killed three women because of you.
No.
You killed Tomoe Machida for your convenience.
That's true.
But to get Sajiki's daughter and his fortune, I had no choice.
She was going to tell Reiko about our relationship.
And in the middle of a Christmas party too!
But tomorrow I'm flying to Paris with Reiko.
So everything's fine with me.
Then what about me?
Up to you.
By my calculations, we don't owe each other anything.
What if you solve the problem alone?
If I could do it on my own, I wouldn't have asked for your help in the first place.
Yes, you can. Make the best of what you do.
You know, you could do her face and dig in the ocean.
So you want me to kill people too?
In today's society, people are victims unless they're perpetrators.
You're a coward.
Crime is an intellectual sport.
If you're cool, you're on your feet, and you're seemingly careless, you won't get caught.
You're a lunatic.
You're crazy.
That's right.
But it's the only way to survive.
Dr.
Why don't you get these white hands dirty once in a while?
Hey, do me a favor, please.
Please, please, come with me.
I don't know what to do.
You're in trouble, aren't you?
Where's Seno?
I think he went out.
Went where?
I heard he went to see Dr. Nishiaki.
Nishiaki?
This is the police, please say your location.
Hello?
She's not here.
please say your location.
This is the police
She's calling the police.
This is the police, please say your location.
You think these pictures are proof?
She tricked you.
She doesn't need any more plastic surgery.
She had a severe nervous breakdown and crashed accidentally.
We tried to save her, but we couldn't get to her in time.
You're good at making people die in accidents, aren't you?
Go around there now.
But..
I'm leaving my wedding to come here.
I can go back now.
Seno.
Okay, so you're just gonna get out of here?
You ambush her at that window over there and push her down.
Hurry up.
Speed up.
Where's Sachiko?
Sachiko!
Yoshii!
Sachiko! Sachiko!
Sachiko!
Sister. I finally found the person who abandoned her sister and ran away from the scene of the bus accident in Hamamatsu.
Dr. Nishiaki
I think I hate Dr. Nishiaki
But I hate Seno even more
Seno, who happened to be on the bus, got Dr. Nishiaki to arrange a meeting with Sajiki's daughter on the condition that Dr. Nishiaki,
who was in a panic after the accident, would abandon my sister and not tell anyone, and killed Tomoe Machida, who got in the way of the meeting.
On the other hand, he used the woman in the apartment as a spy.
Tsuneko Saito was the only witness who knew that my sister and Dr. Nishiaki were on the bus together.
When he found out Tsuneko Saito was coming to Tokyo, he killed her.
He also killed the woman who maintain in the apartment
But then Seno died too.
He left his bride on their honeymoon in Europe.
I'm here to apology you.
I cheated on you, and I'm really sorry.
That's why I didn't write about this case.
Then see you.
THE END