Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Black Trump Card (1964)
I have to go.
Don't leave me alone.
Oh..It's past midnight.
You're meeting with the usual.
Someone strange.
What are you going to talk about with him?
It's none of your business.
I know.
You're up to something.
Maybe you're trying to avenge your father's death.
It could be.
I can't get the image of my dad sitting in the fire and dying out of my head.
I just can't get that fire out of my head either.
When I got there, the building was about to come crashing down on him.
Ironic, isn't it?
Until then, I was a typist and the president's boy.
If the company goes under and the CEO commits suicide...
The son will be the one to feel responsible.
Don't say that.
You'll meet what kind of person?
What are you going to do?
I have no idea.
It's not friendship or anything.
Friends with the same goal of revenge.
See you.
They are Nanbada
they're very famous around here.
You can't control them alone.
You don't have to concern about them.
Should I bow to them like Mr. Yoshino?
You should stay away from the Yakuza world like me.
Think about it.
When my boss was killed, he was trying to say something to me before he died.
He was like. I feel shame,Ken.
I can't forget.
2 beers.
The Chikamatsu group has lost territory and members.
That leaves you and a man.
We'll beat Nanbada.
I'm no longer Yakuza.
Not you.
Who?
I don't know.
He's just so smart.
Welcome.
You're doing great.
Oh Ken.
How's your business?
I'm different from you guys.
Would you like to meet our boss?
I'll go with you.
I don't want to be indebted to that person.
He is a very selfish scam.
You guys hit me.
You guys know exactly what's going to happen?
You know how hard I punch.
I got a job to do. I'll pay you back later.
How's it?
Police patrol is over.
Where's him?
1 am.
He's coming soon.
He?
Both of you are punctual and wonderful.
Let's go.
So the midnight patrol found nothing out of the ordinary.
So the safe was ok.
Good morning.
Damn it.
Are you Ueda?
Well, they won't touch any of the cash, and the safe is intact.
Was something stolen?
Nothing can be stolen other than money.
Well, as I recall, your house was burglarized last week.
The thief never touched any of your valuables or money.
Yeah.
And this week, your company was targeted, and They did the same way.Is there anything you're not aware of?
Nothing.
Ube is calling for you.
Hello, this is Kazue.
The Master is still on a trip.
Oh,that bookkeeping?
Yeah it was stolen.
I need Chairman Fukazawa to return ASAP.
I'll make the necessary arrangements.
Please be careful.
See you.
I'm back.
Thank you for your work.
I'm trying to get some info on what happened at the UBE house.
Again, the money was not stolen.
Apparently something important was taken to replace it.
What do you mean by that?
UBE doesn't say it.
I think he's afraid of us investigating.
I see.
So he lied about being a thief to blind us.
It could be.
He was very scared.
If so, he was too good at acting.
Come in.
I was asked to deliver this to you.
Who?
he didn't say his name.
He said if you look inside, you'll know right away.
Thank you for your work.
This is Kyokuto Shinkin Bank back book keeping.
Please find out who delivered this.
Welcome.
Are you alone?
I wanna be relaxed.
The bar has been renovated and many customers are now coming in.
He's the bandmaster, NEGORO.
He gives me lots of ideas.
He can be used, so please take care of him.
Welcome.
Come with me.
Serve him.
I heard you brought that Band back that night.
You have nice eyes.
I happened to find them in a small bar.
Did you have fun with them?
please don't cheat on me
Are the guys here?
I need to see them.
Oh here.
Hold on.
Who are you?
We are Nanbada.
You destroyed our gang.
I'm KENICHI TADA.
You asked someone to kill our boss.
We are here to kill you.
Ready?
Stop it....
Who are you?
we are open for business.
Get out from here.
If you get in my way, you'll get hurt.
The police are coming, so if you don't get arrested, go home right away.
Damn it.
We'll pay you back.
I'm sorry for bothering you all.
you are very strong.
Let's have drink.
Customers are waiting.
He's great.
What's his name?
Kyohei Negoro.
I think he should stop playing music.
Please bring him here when he performs.
I hear Tada came.
Don't worry.
Everything is fine.
I get it.
Tell him you won't forget tonight.
This is the reward for him.
Well, what's happened can't be helped
Mr. Nambada will be coming soon, so let's think about it after that.
But I'd like you to do something about it as soon as possible.
If the truth comes out, it'll be a problem.
I'm well aware of that.
No matter what happens, we will help you
Have a tea.
Here please.
Mr. Nambada is here.
Sorry I'm late.
I've just backed too.
Have you heard about it from Kazue?
Yes almost.
Actually, I got this in the mail yesterday.
Is this you?
This is well done.
This is handcuffs.
Please look into it immediately.
I'll find out soon.
But police is the problem.
Why don't you go to our vacation home for a while?
vacation home? You mean boss's hakuun mountain's?
Not there but Hong kong.
There's a call for boss.
Hello? Yes he is here. who are you?
He doesn't say his name.
Hello, this is Fukazawa.
Who is this?
Hello,Hello.
What's this?
It's a funeral march
Who is this?
It could be Mischief.
Fuck you.
Welcome home.
We made them to listen to the tape.
You were right. Fukazawa was in Katsura.
they were surprised.
Now, finally, the declaration of war is over.
I met with NANBADA, just like we planned.
Now we just have to see how the D.A. handles that bookkeeping.
Do you know the Osaki D.A. ?
College is an interesting place.
Ex-convicts help prosecutors.
We are like that.
Negoro.Nanbada attacked me and you helped to take me to the hospital.
I've been at your beck and call ever since.
I was drinking alone at the bar counter when you tapped me on the shoulder.
And we don't know much about you.
Why don't you tell us why you're helping us?
I'm as well.
I want revenge.
But for me not Nanbada but their boss.
Tell me the detail.
What's wrong?
Are you ok?
It's ok.
You're that frustrated?
You can tell me when you're feeling better.
Take it easy.
What the hell are we, friends?
Comrade.
We're here to defeat the beasts of our time, who abuse the law to destroy good people one after another.
I'm excited.
I feel great.
It's not just about getting back at the yakuza.
This was what we thought.
I didn't know he left Japan.
Damn it.
They are great.
I don't know what to do.
I'll get closer to Nambada and find out.
You are the another option.
What?
I'll have Ube's whereabouts thoroughly pursued.
The problem is the backstory of the Far East bank.
In addition to the regular credit union route, there is a black team route centered on the UBE.
In other words, it's a stranger to private finance.
Even financial, business, and political figures have invested in the company as individuals while concealing their names.
They use the money to pay higher interest than legally required.
This is an abuse of the law
They have deep connections with the business world and the Securities and Exchange Commission.
For example, Konosuke Mitamura.
Hideo Takizawa of TOYO Finance or Yoshinori Fukasawa of Asian Development.
Ube must be one of the subordinate.
I agree with you, it's better to stop at the last minute economic violation.
If it becomes a political issue...
I'm sure they'll get a lot of help.
I would suggest looking for the main culprit.
This is what I do.
It's good to have ideals.
After all,  You only catch the gangs and you don't catch the main culprit.
We should be careful.
OK.
Find out who the victims of the black market have been.
I'm sure one of them sent the bookkeeping.
I agree with you.
We are working on it.
We'll find out.
Osaki,there's a call for you.
Thanks.
Hi' I'm Osaki D.A.
Oh Togo.
When did you back?
Just now.
I had a friend take over for me and I got home a flight early.
Because today is my birthday.
Did you forget?
I remember.
Let's go for dinner.
Come to Silk Road night club.
Even the D.A. goes there.
8PM.
I'll book the table.
Sorry.
From your fiancee?
But that call was not private use.
Why?
Nanbada gang team is very clever.
They did start a real estate and construction company.
They are related to UBE and have a connection with Yoshinori Fukasawa.
Actually, the Silk Road CLUB is a private store in Nambada.
I'm going to check it out by posing as a customer.
OK.
I'd really like you to pay for it.
But I'll pay on my own.
What would you like?
My friend will come, then we'll order.
I see.
Long time no see.
I play saxophone here.
Happy Birthday.
You have a nice memory.
Who you will meet?
I'll take a guess.
Osaki?
Yes.
He's always worried about you.
Welcome.
You're not still married to Osaki?
He's busy with work.
You haven't changed.
You are always quiet, and beautiful.
I wanted to date with you, but Osaki was won.
I've never lost to him in the study or in music.
In life, he's the winner.
Are you married?
I'm always alone.
I'm not getting married.
Why?
I know you like someone.
Yes I can't forget about her.
So I'm always alone.
Am I interrupting something?
Excuse me.
Mr. President is here.
Where?
Manager's Office
What's wrong?
I'm sorry to say this.
Negoro asked me to tell you that.
Come.
When did you become his girl?
Don't get me wrong.
I worry about you.
I can only love one girl.
But you always talk about Negoro.
So What's wrong?
The old Chikamatsu gang's henchmen got together and beat up the president's office.
You seemed really cheerful and happy.
You suddenly changed your mind.
And then one day you moved away from me.
You're right.
I left from you.
I dreamed of having a happy family with you.
I heard your parents got something wrong.
My Mom committed suicide.
Why? What happened?
I have a right to know.
I was your fiancee before.
Tomoko.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh Negoro.
It's not good to keep your fiancée waiting.
I happened to meet him.
He play saxophone here.
Oh that's good.
Today is TOMO's birthday.
Let's celebrate together.
Brandy
Sure.
Do you play piano?
Yes When I'm frustrated.
You can be pianist if you are good.
Yes you are right.
I was a bad student, like a failed student.
You're no good as a prosecutor.
I saw something in the paper about the Far East Credit Union.
I can't believe the chairman of the board let you get away with it... just like your piano.
Why you know?
I had a law degree, too.
And I was getting better grades than you.
Here it is.
Cheers again.
Happy birthday.
When did you start to work here?
A half month ago.
Do you know the manager here?
I think Nanbada.
Something to do with Nanbada and the Chairman of the Board of the Far East Credit Union bank.
I didn't know.
Apparently there is a connection between Nanbada and Fukazawa, the man who collapsed your house.
Did you check out my house?
When I was going through Fukazawa's background.
I found out about your parents' misfortune.
You've been away from us.
How's your father?
He's dead?
He's in a vegetative state.
You have a grudge against Fukasawa.
But you work at NANBADA. Is that by chance?
What if I'm not?
I need your help.
Forget hate with the power of law.
Are you a good prosecutor now?
I'm not but Japanese law is great.
If that were the case, there would be no bad guys in this world.
Gero, Fukazawa,Nanbada,Ube
They're all breaking the law and prospering.
You want to avenge them alone.
I would do it at any cost.
But I too once wanted to study law and become a prosecutor or a lawyer
For the sake of the Japanese legal establishment, I wish you all the best.
Excuse me.
The boss wants to see you
Make Tomoko happy.
If you don't, I won't forgive you.
I was sure he sent us the bookkeeping.
Come in.
Thanks for your help the other day.
Thanks too.
Wanna drink?
I'm still working.
I heard from Miki.
How did you get the information?
I was gang before.
My mates was gathered by money
Reach.
Hello?
Who's there?
Say your name.
Oh..boss..
From Boss.
Stupid.
I'm sorry, stupid answered your phone.
What?
Chikamatsu team is coming here?
Here's so peace.
I think that's wrong information.
Someone came to tell me about it.
He said there was nothing wrong.
It's good if so.
Hey.
Here.
That doesn't make sense.
Hey look at this!
You are lucky.
Bet.
Here you go.
I'll bet more.
What’s that?
I'm too busy to play.
Look around there.
Oh damn it.
Oh my god.
Here you go.
Be careful, hurry up.
Hello, President.
Oh damn it.
President.
Still no idea who did it?
I'm thinking it's the TADA case.
Did you find him?
I looked for him, but I don't know where he went.
It was bad of you to let your guard down.
I’m sorry.
Be careful.
Negoro,get in the car.
I have to go somewhere.
You were right.
I'll give you the profit.
It's your responsibility.
You missed him.
Damn it.
In order to realize the above 2nd development plan
we need a location north of Hakuunsan.
But some of this land is state-owned.
Currently applying to the Ministry of Finance.
We'd like to ask for Chairman Fukazawa's help.
Leave it to me.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I have to interrupt the meeting due to an urgent matter.
It's better if we don't meet here.
What's wrong?
I received a call from Hong Kong saying that Mr. Ube is coming to Japan.
Ube?
Why?
They say his child is unwell.
what should we do?
Up to you.
Are you sure about this information?
He remembers the news, and even though the name is different, he contacted UBE as there is no doubt in his mind that it is UBE.
You have a nice friend.
Please.
Mr. Ueki?
this is an arrest warrant.
come with us.
I'd like to keep him quiet.
It's none of your business.
I always say that.
We have a problem with Ube.
I'll leave it to you.
Show him that.
I'll give you something you've always wanted.
I'm bothering you about Ube.
Here it is.
What's this?
Oh this.
It belongs to Mr. SHAKO's wife.
Leave it to me.
I'll make sure you won't be inconvenienced.
I'm not worried about that either, since you're in charge.
New Asia Development is working on the issue of disposing of Hakuunsan.
I forgot the name of the head of the Department of Management at the Ministry of Finance.
Koyama?
Are you in good contact with him?
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
By the way, they sent this doll to my place.
They sent this doll to my place too.
Does this mean I'm going to be hanged?
This is ours.
You find who did this?
He must be TADA of Chikamatsu-gumi.
No.
This is not a gangster's job.
There's always someone else who did this.
Hello, it's me.
Who called my husband?
What?
Apparently he won't give his name.
Connect here.
Hello?
Again.
Don't worry.
He is very smart.
Other than gang..oh you know him?
We have Hayashi, who took away the property as collateral because we were unable to repay it.
I think he is.
He's not.
He targets me.
You?
And he's got it all planned out.
please investigate him.
I worry my life.
You worked for Hayashi Shoji for three years until it went bankrupt.
I heard that you were good friends with the son of the deceased company president.
We would like to hear from Tetsuya about the incident at the Far Eastern Credit Bank.
Do you know where he lives now?
Until recently, he lived in an apartment in Sakuradai.
But he moved away half a month ago, and I don't know where he is now.
How do you communicate with him?
He just call me.
He seems to be planning a personal vendetta.
It could be.
Because his father died so tragically
Would you like to tell me what happened?
He borrowed money at a high interest rate.
The terms were terrible. There were rumors that the entire company's fortune had been transferred.
The company was on fire, so I flew down.
It was big fire.
Testuya.
Dad.
Well, since then, the TETSUYA have changed.
But you're not alone.
He's got company.
He's got friends in the Yakuza.
And there's another strange person. He's taking advantage of Tetsuya.
He must be Negoro.
I have no idea
Thank you very much.
I'm getting figure out.
Negoro was at Haneda Airport.
Negoro do something with them.
I'll win.
Once UBE is caught, the law will take care of the rest.
I make him confess.
I'll take care of it then.
Because I'm a client of the boss.
Don't forget to tell him that.
I know.
why don't you knock?
Why do you come to my dressing room?
I'd love to play with you.
I'm glad.
I've got nice body.
How about tonight?
I can't tonight.
I have a prior engagement.
Is he the president's customer?
I hear he's an official.
Which?
I have no idea.
But the boss said he'd give me tips.
How about tomorrow?
I can't wait, I'm a man.
I think the officials will go home soon after playing.
Come see me as soon as you're done.
OK.
Don't lock the door.
How was last night?
You are much better than him
Chief of the Administration Department works on land disposals
Yes that's right.
The official seems very bossy.
He said it all depends on how you fill out the paperwork.
So Mt.Hakuun.
He's meeting with the boss early next week to get it done.
He wants me to meet with him again then.
Next week?
That's right.
I want to get a lot of money from the president and go to a hot spring with you.
Good.
My friend.
Who are you?
You came too early
Get out.
Hold on.
I need to wear.
Get out.
You are always naked.
By the way, he says he'd much rather have my body than yours.
If you're so disappointed, why don't you try it with your body?
I'll pay you back later.
You sleep with women to use them.
You wanted to know who my client was last night, so you dragged her into it.
What the hell are you?
Did you approach me in a seductive way to take advantage of me?
I wanted to change my job to another more upscale bar.
No.
You want to do something with Nanbada.
You're using me to get the president to trust you and find out what's going on.
Don't make fun of me.
I'll tell him you are spy.
What are you going to do with me?
Destroy me?
I can't.
I loved it.
Ube.
You can tell me everything now.
You are not capable of doing anything wrong.
We have a certain person marked as the mastermind behind your appointment to the board of directors.
We believe that you were merely taken advantage of in the recent UKIYOSHI case.
Tell me,Ube.
Hello, Osaki room.
Who are you?
I'll ask him.
Your son is Ichiro?
Is something wrong with Ichiro?
The hospital informed me that he's dying.
Really?
I want to meet him.
Please.
Are you alright?
Wait.
That was stupid of him to get called out on a fake phone call.
I'm sorry.
Ube was murdered.
The Far East Credit Union case is over.
I'll find who did it.
Osaki,The murderer has turned himself in.
Really?
How many times have I told you?
My brother works for the company that went under.
They don't even get a severance package.
That's when I started going after him.
Bullshit.
Someone asked you to kill him.
I did it alone, for the world.
Because you guys don't work.
Don't say bullshit.
Don't make excuses like that.
Can I have a cigarette?
Damn it.
I wanted to kill UBE.
My feelings were half-hearted.
Leave it to OSAKI from now on.
If you're happy with the UBE being killed, then you can leave now.
Before I decide that, why do you hate FUKAZAWA so much?
Tell me.
Yeah,It's time you had a talk.
It was shortly after the war ended.
My father took care of Fukazawa, who called himself a Manchurian Ronin
I used my father in Fukasawa to do all kinds of business.
Smugglers, black market finance...
He learned to make money by breaking the law.
It may have been his inborn talent.
And he seduced my mother.
My foolish mother..
She left me and went into Fukazawa.
My father never complained.
My father had borrowed a lot of money from Fukazawa.
Then Fukazawa abandoned my mother.
My mom killed herself.
I'm sorry.
Moreover.
After my mother and I died, he used my house as collateral for a loan.
I was a junior in college.
I was studying law, and I hated him.
But people who violate the law have many lawyers.
Court notices, foreclosures, and forced evictions before I know anything about it.
The law that was supposed to protect us persecuted us.
I was disappointed in the law and quit university.
6 years later.
Fukasawa became the back world and boss of the economic world.
He did it in violation of the law.
When I decided to take my revenge on him personally.
Your father killed himself.
Your master was murdered.
How's your father?
Is he dead?
He killed himself.
If so, I've already given up.
Don't ask me.
What can I do for you?
We're brothers.
I follow you.
What can I do for you?
Thank you.
Here we go.
Here it is.
I can't accept this.
You don't have to hesitate.
But for future reference, please accept this in cash.
But...
Please.
Hurry up.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Why don't you take a bath?
Please take him.
Enjoy your bath.
Minmin.
Don't rush.
Go to bath first.
My important things are in this jacket.
I'll take care of it.
Go to bath.
Why don't we take a bath together again?
I'll be there soon.
You go first.
Why do you want to know Negoro's address?
Wanna see him?
I haven't been able to sleep since you told me about his misfortune.
I don't know what to say. I want to comfort you.
Because you still love him.
But I can't stop my feeling.
He left me without telling me why.
I hated him with every fiber of my being.
I made big mistake too.
I want to meet him, but I think he'll give me a challenge.
Here..
If you see him, I'd like you to tell him like this.
I'm working hard to make up for my mistakes.
So please be patient a little longer
Are you going yet?
This year, in order to get engaged to you, I have to solve this problem.
Tenkaidai National Land...
Hello,it's me.
Is this Mr. Ishii from an industry magazine?
I'm not good enough for it.
We definitely need you for this roundtable discussion.
A young reporter will pick you up at 5:30.
Please.
Get up.
Koyama-san.
I'm glad you finally woke up.
I'll get right to it.
You got the money from New Asia Development.
Say the truth.
During the day today, you cashed a check for 3 million yen at Sanba Bank
This is the photo.
Then you put 1 million yen of it in a fixed term deposit at Sanba Bank
and another 100 to the Dairokujuroku Bank.
And you put the remaining 100 into a loan trust at a large investment trust bank.
This is the photo.
You admit the fact of corruption?
Say Yes or no.
Say.
We want you to talk everything what you've done.
Please.
Don't you know where that is?
That's what they did to me on the way there and on the way back. They put me under anesthesia.
Were they 3 people?
Yes.
What kind of men?
There was a guy who looked like YAKUZA, and another guy who looked like a businessman, And one other guy.
That other guy is suspicious.
He wore dark glasses.
You at least remember what he's like...
His moles, his hair.
I remember nothing.
What did you tell them?
Everything.
Everything?
Mr. Fukazawa of New Asia Development
You're calling from Tokyo.
Who?
Hello, Fukazawa-san, is it?
I have something I'd like you to listen to instead of music today
I just did what NANBADA told me to do.
Of course, they knew if they accepted the money, they would have to obey him.
I was wrong.
I was something wrong.
What do you think?
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
My dad is calling me from the hell.
Your dad?
My ex family.
You forget?
A mother who cared for you died,
A family was taken from you.
So you are...
Some of the gems you're collecting for your antennae. There must be some diamonds that hold a grudge.
I'll pay you back.
See you then.
Oh the person was he...
Now he knows about me.
We don't have time.
Let's get started now.
I'm looking forward to it.
Hey,Koyama was dead.
I just heard it on the radio in the car.
He was found dead in a ditch in the river.
They killed him.
I didn't think they would kill him in a small mountain.
I'll use my last trump card.
See them in person.
He wasn't in the car.
No?
Hello?
Oh you.
I came in on the early shift and the boss rushed out with Sasaki and Yoshino.
They'll go far.
Far?
Where'd he go?
He had them carry pistols.
Besides, yesterday he was showing off this amazing diamond to the manager.
He said it used to belong to his ex family.
What?
I see.
Thanks for telling me.
Do you come tonight?
You don't know?
Don't do anything dangerous.
I'm worried about you.
Say something.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Oh ken. what?
He doesn't get off?
I've been looking for you a long time, I'm sure of it.
He's got to be a stopover.
Go to Mt.Hakuun.
Mt.Hakuun?
There's his Villa at the peak of there.
I'm sure he goes there and he called Nanbada.
Nanbada too?
I'm sure he's got everyone there working on a plan to deal with me.
We'll break into there.
Come back now.
Who?
What can I do for you?
I was confused but I wanted to see you.
May I?
Come in.
I am a man who has no use for your old sweet memories.
I heard from Osaki about you.
That was a dramatic story worthy of the collapse of a former family, wasn't it?
Don't say that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But I want to comfort you.
It's too late.
The one who stole my youth, stole you, stole my future.
I can't stop about my frustration.
Please leave.
We live in a different world now.
Outside of law and inside.
I know this much.
What you're doing is wrong.
Please leave everything to OSAKI.
I do things my way.
I may look like a crazy person.
I have something to show you.
Can you follow me?
Here.
Mental hospital.
Mentally ill patients, abandoned by their families, are being admitted to the hospital in a similar fashion to incarceration.
Hey get out!
This way, please.
Give me my XXXXXX!
This is my last secret that I never told anyone.
Money.
You see?
He's almost crazy.
I'm determined to get revenge in my own way.
I'm going into the enemy's main camp.
Lose or win, Osaki will have to handle it.
Please give this to him.
Nurse.
Give that patient something good to eat with it.
I beg you.
I'll see you there.
Here's here.
Sorry I'm late.
I finally find who he is.
Who?
He is my ex family.
He is  my son in law.
He's Negoro.
He was a nice young man who loved music when he was a student
Negoro...
I just followed to Nanbada.
Of course, they knew if they accepted the money, they would have to obey him.
I was wrong.
Then stopped.
This is enough.
He told you to go to The mountain?
We have to find where Nanbada and Fukazawa are.
Please find it.
He has not come to the club?
Go to his apartment.
Bring him to here.
He is spy.
That's why he knew about us.
To where?
No operation at night.
We are New Asia Development.
We have an urgent matter for Chairman Fukazawa.
Here.
This is Nanbata's car.
Let's go!
Freeze!
Damn it!
He's fake.
Drop the pistol.
Stay away.
I'll kill him.
We knew you'd come.
Our customer was told to contact us.
I've lost so far, but we'll win in the end.
Long time no see,Kyohei.
You grew up.
You grew up on bad things.
You seem to know too much about us that we don't want you to know.
I know about Ube and Koyama.
I sent my notes and the tape recording to the police before I came here.
Don't worry about it.
As long as this man is not alive, none of that stuff will works.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll go home by your car.
Are you Osaki?
I think you have been contacted by the police.
It will take you there in 1hour.
Unfortunately, sir, flying at night is forbidden.
Connect the line.
The dynamite will explode in half an hour.
See you.
Anyone who has a grudge against the chairman will dynamite himself along with the house.
I will make the announcement.
I feel good.
They are trembling now.
It's been 15 minutes.
There's a lighter in my pocket.
Look at me.
OK let's go.
I have contacted Shizuoka Police.
I get it.
Hurry up.
Fire my lope.
Hot!
Hurry up.
Little above.
Okay.
Hot!
Come in.
Three minutes left.
We can at least hear the sounds.
Let’s see.
We have no time!
Not yet?
Hurry up.
Untie!
Forty minutes now.
That's strange.
Damn it.
They escaped?
We have next choice.
Give me dynamite.
Connect this dynamite to the fuse.
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
They could be waiting down there.
In the case, I use this dynamite.
It works.
Damn it.
They did it.
Ok let's do it.
Fukazawa!
Just above him soon.
We are gonna set the dynamite on fire.
Shit!
Try the next corner.
Now!
What's the hell?
We made it!
I hear something strange.
What's that?
Stop the cable.
What's wrong?
Negoro?
That's nice you escaped.
Wherever you go, We'll beat you.
Fukazawa's car fell off a cliff.
It's his grave.
What?
If that's true, I'm grateful.
I will inherit all his work.
You won't.
What's the hell?
I put dynamite on the bottom cable.
What?
There's a fuse underneath.
Go to hell.
Set the fire.
It's ready.
We will win.
Go to hell.
Nanbada.
Mr. Nambada, right?
What?
I have a warrant for your arrest, please come with us.
If they die, we have nothing to fear.
It's all Fukazawa's fault.
Let's go.
Look at that.
The fuse is burning.
Shit.
what is this sound?
It's a helicopter.
Help us!
they are waving the flag.
The cable car is stopped, so it might be an SOS signal.
Oh he's Osaki.
It's me.
Oh Negoro.
What's happened?
I'll get closer to them.
Osaki.
Help us.
They need our help.
Please.
Please give me a rope.
Hurry up.
Little right.
Come on.
You go first.
Thanks, bros.
Hurry up.
Negoro!
That cable car will explode.
I took him.
Thank you very much.
Uncuff him.
Can you leave from here?
You need to talk with me again?
I've helped you enough.
I have nothing more to say.
I'll be the one to tell you what happened today.
Nambada just confessed to the UBE and Oyama's murder.
Your Note worked.
The power of the law has finally come to light.
If you'd been a little quicker, those two men wouldn't have been killed.
So you're saying you won?
You decide that.
I look forward to seeing how you decide.
Don't get me wrong.
The law is not perfect.
But the important thing is not to take the back roads, but to create a society that respects the law with an open mind.
Good people respect that.
I will judge you harshly.
Please do that.
That's how I can be saved.
Cigarettes are so good when I get them from someone else.
I didn't have any friends for a long time.
How's Tomoko?
She's getting on a plane to Hong Kong today.
Please have a wedding soon.
It seems that she will go to Hong Kong for a change of scenery and come back.
That's good.
THE END