Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Black Speeding (1964)
Three Motorcycles Ahead.
Stop by left.
Oh it's a problem!
Mom!
Where's her mom?
Do you know who it is?
35 house's Yamazaki's?
Please get his mother in here right away.
Someone call 119 and ask for an ambulance.
Thank you very much.
Is there a police box near here?
Does anyone have a handkerchief?
It's a hit and run incident.
That Motorcycle?
Where he has gone?
He went to No.2 Keihin.
I'm Tsuda from the Mobile Police Force.
I'll chase them.
You'll be fine.
2m...18
It's terrible.
We can't let our kids play outside.
A big bike ran into him.
It's terrible.
Did you catch him?
I missed him.
So, ambulance?
I took him right away, but I don't know if that's gonna work.
He was unconscious.
My husband isn't here yet?
I don't know.
Surgery is about to begin. Please come in.
How's the condition of the child who's about to undergo surgery?
He has a compound fracture of the femur.
He'll be better?
He has severe internal bleeding and may not survive.
I'm Yamazaki,Where's my son.
Please enter the first operating room.
The photos has done yet?
I have to bring the photo by today.
Don't be so hasty.
But it's unusual for you.
I can't believe he got away.
He's a vicious bastard.
He should've been caught.
It's your fault for running off like that.
Don't worry.
He'll be back.
Our boss is upset.
Did you escape?
Yeah.
Where's boss?
He's waiting.
He said thank you.
Police chased you?
Just little.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I've made my job.
Your money.
This is unclear.
My bad.
You remember the number?
I couldn't check because of the mud on the plate.
If only you could take a clear photo
Which type?
Did you check it?
I think it's Skyliners.
I'm sure
I think it's year 63 type.
I think so.
No confirmed accidents photographed for the two motorcycles that fled earlier.
So, if that's the case...
I guess we'll just have to find this hit-and-run guy.
Anyway, let's find all the owners of the '63 Skyliners.
Let's do it.
Please work harder for us.
Please let me use your phone.
The only clue we have is the TYPE of this bike.
If he dismantle the bike, this lead will disappear.
So We don't have time.
I get it.
Is this the Central Public Hospital?
I'm from the Metropolitan Police Department's riot police.
Are these the results of Yamazaki Tamio's surgery?
He's saved?
That's good.
Thank you very much.
Sorry.
What's wrong?
There was a traffic accident.
Welcome.
I'm looking for this.
What time do you think it is?
They said if you weren't here by six they would turn the room over to someone else.
Then why didn't you at least go and see?
I can't do that.
We should go together.
We can't get married without a room.
I know.
Don't be upset.
Can you go out?
I'm supposed to be out by 6:00.
Let's go see a movie.
But it's too late.
Don't worry, we'll make it.
Let's go see a movie.
Maybe we shouldn't have gone to see the room today.
Why?
It looks like another room will become available next month.
He says it's a nice room.
Why didn't you just say so?
I'm leaving.
Tsuda!
There's an article about you in the paper.
Look at this.
Perpetrator ran into an amusement park to evade an unnecessary police chase.
and caused the unfortunate accident.
Therefore, some people are directing their anger at the cops, saying that the cops are responsible for going after the criminals too deep.
What's the hell?
That was necessary.
So this was you?
That's what I thought.
Why?
Because that's what you'd do.
Don't say bullshit.
If your name is written in the newspaper, you become famous.
I definitely don't remember chasing anything.
Well, that's all right.
If that's the case...
I can't just sit back and let them write this nonsense.
I'm going.
Strictly enforce the center line in the vicinity of Daini-Keihin Nakahara-kaido Road.
But Captain...
I did what I had to do at that time.
You're making a mistake too.
What?
You didn't help the child and followed him.
Don't get me wrong.
I asked the police officer at the police box to do the job, and then I followed him.
Listen to everything I say.
In that case, you need to get the kid to the hospital as soon as possible.
But I also had to call an ambulance right away.
With today's traffic, the ambulance may be late.
What do you do in that case?
You're in charge
Saving lives comes before apprehending criminals.
That's the motorcycle officer's code of conduct.
Driver's license
Is something wrong?
OK?
He's getting better.
But the doctor says he needs to see the results of the X-ray again.
I see.
This is the fastest propeller shipboard plane.
This is how it would be put together.
I bought it because it's fun.
This is the propeller that you put on an aircraft carrier.
The wings are supposed to fold like this.
It's a propeller.
It really turns!
This one fought with the Japanese Zero fighter.
Do you know which one won?
Doctor will come.
How's it?
Get better soon.
See you.
Oh here it is.
Yeah.
The Limits of Self-Defense in Criminal Investigation
He still writes difficult things.
He's very confident.
He said he was praised by everyone for being useful in investigations.
I wonder if he thinks I have potential.
His fiancée seems to like him very much.
Who's the bride?
She is the younger sister of the Division 2 manager.
Her
She's nice.
She's pretty and smart.
She'll make a great wife.
Takuya.
Don't get too interested in her.
Don't say bullshit.
So he's gonna marry her?
He looks so scared when I tell him about this.
Welcome back.
Takuya is here.
How are you?
She looks nice.
You guys should get married soon too.
He's mean.
He's just shy.
Serve him a beer.
I know.
I saw you in the newspaper.
I'm upset.
I know how you feel.
Is it likely that the culprit will be caught?
It's been a long time since the accident, but I don't have any clues.
This will be cold case.
The hit-and-run investigation team is very lazy.
But it's not that easy to investigate.
What would you do if you were the head of a task force?
It's none of my business.
I'm in charge of murder.
It's same.
It's murder.
Guys like that do it all the time.
You're not going to catch the killer yourself, are you?
Maybe you should leave it to a hit-and-run investigation.
You may think I'm deviating from my mission.
I just can't help myself if I don't catch him.
you might cause problems.
You might use forceful means.
I wouldn't do that.
There were three of them.
I'm thinking maybe he's part of a motorcycle gang.
So I'm thinking of casting a net around where they congregate.
But I'm not too impressed.
It's like a kamikaze investigation or something.
Kamikaze or not.
I'll go all the way.
You're always like this.
You're always so stingy with everything.
Don't get me wrong.
He's wrong.
I’m not.
I'm just asking for advice.
If you're not helping, I'm happy to help.
You?
I know it's not much, but it's better than nothing.
Sunday, December 6th
They're a group of guys working at a lumberyard in Koto-ku.
The man with the most brilliant steering wheel
Masahiro Takano.
The car he's driving
It's a skyliner, but he's small.
But I checked.
Wait here.
They are members of the Tokyo Auto Club.
Company employee Koichi Kihara and Southeast University ITO SHU
I don't think these members would be involved in a hit-and-run.
Shibuya HARUO seems a little too young
He looks like criminal.
You're pretty good, aren't you?
I'm surprised it's a woman.
Excuse me, can I borrow your fire?
Nice bike.
It's a trial, isn't it?
Yeah.
Take a drive.
They were young men working at a U.S. military camp in Yokosuka, Japan.
They look like the team.
But they have alibi.
I've been looking for him for a long time.
I wonder if any of these people are the killer.
Seems kind of pointless.
I don't think there is a killer.
I think he'll show up soon.
I'd like to go somewhere else for a change.
I'm bored.
We're not here for fun.
It costs money to rent a car and come here.
The room will be available.
What?
The apartment we're renting.
Oh yeah.
We really have to go there this Sunday.
OK.
You guys come here every Sunday.?
You guy's are bike crazy.
You too.
Yeah.
You wanna drive long?
To where?
Hamamatsu
It's this coming Saturday.
There's a club called Tsubame Auto Club.
They're hosting this event.
The membership fee is 3,000 yen, they take the car home, and they pay for the gas.
Wanna join?
Sounds like fun. Anyone can join?
Yeah.
You wanna come too?
Maybe we can find some clue.
I'll give it a shot.
They want to come.
Hello.
I'm Yazawa from Tsubame Auto Club.
Hirai and Tajima.
I'm Machida.
She's my girlfriend,Ito.
Are you a confident driver?
A little bit.
It's okay, I'm the one who recruited him.
It's a long day for recreation.
I'm looking for someone who's good at it. I don't want him to fall off halfway through.
Here.
What's your job?
Factory in Izasuko.
Where did you learn to drive?
Use Factory car.
You're good.
Wanna dance?
Why would you meet someone like that?
It's ok.
Do you think they are suspicious?
I don't know.
I don't like them.
i need some clue.
I don't think it's worth it.
By the way, did your brother say something?
He's really mad at me for being your assistant.
He said you're both crazy.
I know.. I mean some clue..
Does he talk like that?
Oh yeah.
But here's what he said.
He thought he was a pro.
pro?
A professional hit-and-run driver.
Yes, a professional rider.
Oh yeah
He was very good at that.
I'm back.
Would you be willing to provide security support for members of the Diet at Haneda Airport?
Today?
I'm sorry.
I have plans today..
Please.
I've got relatives coming out of the country.
I have to pick them up at 2:00.
Well, there's nothing I can do.
What's wrong?
We can't go.
Why?
our plans have changed.
Hamamatsu is in trouble.
Listen up everyone!
I'm very sorry about what happened.
our plans have changed.
We couldn't rent bikes today.
Of course, I complained, but there's no more bikes left.
I'm sorry, but we're going to have to postpone today's ride.
That's strange.
He's making fun of us.
Don't you think they are strange?
It's a bit sloppy.
but i don't think they are the culprits.
Why?
It's not a threesome.
That woman is always attached to them.
I can't help it.
I'll go back to the tech and look for it.
You're not going to find him there.
Hit-and-run drivers don't always go there.
What's wrong with you?
Hold on.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I was looking forward to it.
Next chance.
Why don't you come out and play somewhere?
There's Oi Auto race.
Shall we go there?
I won!
I won too.
What should I drink?
I want coke.
Oh, that's unusual, isn't it?
I can't believe we're meeting like this.
How's your gambling?
That's bad.
There are no good racers like you in the races, so I can't make any money.
What do you think?
You hate me.
This and this.
Buy it.
OK.
What did you buy?
2-4
I think it's good.
The woman you are always with is your lover?
Why you ask for that?
By the way, was Mr. Yazawa a motorcyclist?
He used to be famous.
I know you work .
Yes
Where?
At a record store.
Interesting place.
I like mono-jazz, too.
I'll go buy some next time.
You have a nice figure.
Wanna hang around with me too?
You don't like it?
She's pure.
Where the hell have you been?
I'm leaving.
Wait.
welcome!
Thanks for the other day.
Water?
Yes
One Water
You look not good.
I lost last time in Oi.
You'd better drive bike for a change.
I thought auto racers were good at it, but it's not that big of a deal.
What?
I watched the race and got mad at their driving skills.
It's not easy.
Really?
I don't trust you.
They are not professional but just rider.
You have a big mouth.
I'm, you know, I'm not good at everything else, but I'm pretty good at driving.
I saw his skill.
He's very good.
Why you are his side?
I'm the one who scouted him.
You're going pro, you're going to be popular.
because you're cool
That’s funny.
Stop badmouthing them.
Why?
He used to be Pro.
Sorry I didn't know.
I know you are much better.
Let me show you what a pro looks like.
I'm afraid.
Come on.
I'll show you.
What kind of game are we playing?
If we run into them from here on out, we'll hit a boat and definitely crash.
We'll start out all the way over there.
From there, we're going to hit us at a hundred kilometers an hour.
Remember?
100km excactly.
This is when you do the spin turn and stop.
We'll see who can go as far as they can, and we'll compare them.
It's a thrill.
I'll show you how the pros do it.
Are you coward?
Don't be afraid.
It's ok if you run away.
I will do it.
You got some balls.
Remember?
100km excactly.
Let's start.
I'm lost.
You are great.
You got some balls.
You made it.
He's play boy.
We can use him.
You want him to join us?
No way.
I doubt him.
For what?
He acts strange.
You think he's police?
Yeah.
He's too good for us.
You think he's police?
I think so.
Boss is too kind.
I'll go out with him and see how he is.
I'll find out if he's police or not.
By the way...your outfit was so nice.
I rent the outfit.
See you.
I'll send you home.
No thanks.
Don't be hesitate.
I feel sorry.
You can go with him.
Where do you live?
Meguro.
See you.
Here's fine.
Don't be hesitate.
It's far from your home.
Never mind.
Here's fine.
I'll send you home.
Hold on.
What?
Stop here
Why?
I'm hungry.
I'll treat you
Noodle.
You told me you worked at factory.
Where?
Akebono print in Sinagawa
How long are you working there?
About 5 years.
Good paid?
It's not a lot.
What kind printing?
It's just a pamphlet.
We are small factory.
Manager told me there were a lot of Labor costs.
How much?
I'll pay.
Don't worry.
That'll be 100 yen.
Thank you very much.
I'll drive this time.
You drive too fast.
Hold me tight.
This is good though
It's a speeding violation
Don't worry.
Are you ok?
That's what I told you.
Speed over 100km.
My bad
License.
No license?
It's at my house.
Why don't you get off?
Don't you think you're in violation?
I told you I was sorry.
Stop it.
Never mind.
Come.
Wait!
Come to the police.
Police 36 team here
Ok what's wrong?
I'm taking the speeder to the police.
we get it.
Actually I'm police.
We received a report from the Head Police this morning that what you did was clearly overzealous.
But given the circumstances of the hit-and-run, I couldn't resist.
You don't trust the task force?
But, boss..
I saw the man who did it.
I couldn't see his face, but...
I still have a distinct impression of the man.
I don't mean that it is not your business.
I'm just saying... you can't go around breaking traffic laws...
I mean, even if it was an act, it's still... it's still overkill.
It's a deviation from the call of duty.
Don't you think?
I've never seen a man behave as recklessly as you have.
You have to manage him.
Listen.
Now, this would normally be a matter of your resignation, of course.
If this gets out...
This becomes a problem for the whole department.
I'll stop you right where you are.
Don't do this again,ok?
You too.
Write here.
What's this?
Pledge of Allegiance
I will henceforth perform my duties under the command of my company commander and squad leader.
I will henceforth perform my duties
I will never deviate from my duties.
I need you to write this down so I can stop you.
But I don't think I pulled that kind of bullshit.
Your actions alone are destroying the discipline of this police force.
But
Write it.
write down the date of your signature.
If the section chief said that much to me.
I'd lose all respect for our department.
Can't you at least be a little bit aware of that?
addressed to me.
Just in case you need this pledge for your own good.
All right.
Go.
He got angry with you?
He's stubborn.
Hey,Mizuno?
Hey, let's reconfigure the team today.
You'll be working with Yamashita.
Tsuda's needed with me for the time being.
I'll take 800 yen.
You look upset.
Nothing.
You are not in good mood.
Thank you very much.
Do you have Latin chorus?
You must be tired.
Forget about those weirdos.
Why don't you take it easy this Sunday?
I can't.
Why?
The captain told me I had to work a special shift next Sunday too.
He's stopping you.
It's not funny.
Thank you very much.
Can you do me a favor?
Can you get close to YAZAWA for me?
No I don't want.
I worry what he will do to me.
Just call him ok.
The phone number of the BAR the other day.
If he ask for me, you'll try to be nice about it.
Welcome.
My fake name is Machida.
I know and you are  printer.
Job for me?
We'll go to Osaka but not Hamamatsu.
Osaka?
It's far.
You know there's a clunker shop in Nishinari called Sudo Introductions?
I've already contacted the president.
The total price is 170000 yen.
Fifteen cars?
Yes, 5 foreign cars included.
Isn't that cheap?
Don't say anything you don't have to.
You couriers can shut your mouths and carry on.
Be careful with the crowd.
Leave it to me!
Only 3 available.
Only 3?
It was too urgent.
It can't be helped.
Use the tech to gather them up again.
How about bringing Machida?
Don't worry. I saw he was arrested. I'm sure he's not police.
How about calling his factory to check his identify?
Hello? This is Akebono print.
Is there a person called Machida?
Factory worker
Yes, he is. but he went home today.
He went home today.
Can you tell me his address?
It's urgent business.
He's good at riding.
Especially spin turn.
What's that?
To come barreling in and brake suddenly and at the same time dig a hole and go around.
This is very high skill.
Beer.
I bet Yazawa is the killer.
You told me the killer was pros but Yazawa was pro-rider.
What do you want to ask me?
That's why YAZAWA has no decisive power to arrest you even if he knows you're suspicious.
What should I do in a case like this?
How would I know?
You're the expert.
There's got to be something you can do.
Don't do that. That's a job for the task force.Don't do that. That's a job for the task force.
YAZAWA was a professional. The task force didn't know that.
But it's not your territory.
You act like my boss.
I don't think it's right that the police have jurisdiction.
That's why there are so many hit-and-runs.
Anyway have a drink.
Look, you and me, we're gonna be brothers one of these days.
you are unreliable as a brother.
I don't want to have an angry younger brother like you.
I'll never ask for help again.
Oh you are here.
What's wrong?
I'm hungry.
i will introduce her to you.
She's Keiko.
You saw her photo some day.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tsuda.
You should leave
Please have a seat.
Don't worry.
We'll sit there.
Let's have a meal.
My bros will pay for it.
One Geso.
I want Toro.
Is Mr. Machida here?
Who are you?
I'm Kajima.
You have a visitor.
Kajima.
Kajima?
Auto bike club's
I don't know him.
I guess Tsuda's visitor.
What can I do for you?
I wanna see Machida.
Did you talk him about me?
It can't be helped.
Treat me.
You're bad.You're a cop and you use my name.
You didn't tell me that up front.
i thank you.
I'll use your name next time.
I see.
Why he came here?
He told me to go to Osaka next Sunday.
Osaka?
Last time I was here, there was a checkpoint.
Turn right from Shizuoka.
Take this road to the north.
To The mountain?
There's a path that takes you upstream of the creek here and out of the valley once here.
Have you passed there before?
Yes from Nagoya.
I once came back from Nagoya to Shizuoka in three hours.
It's a little tough, but it's the safest.
You have a visitor.
I see.
What's wrong?
I wonder if you have a tea.
I have many. thanks.
Welcome back.
What's wrong?
Are you going to Osaka tomorrow?
I got holiday.
Take me there.
You shouldn't go.
Why?
I think you're going to be dangerous.
I had a fight with my brother.
It was for your sake.
He doesn't want you to go to Osaka.
I see.
He wanted me to go stop you, but I didn't want to.
I didn't want to, so we fought.
My brother says there's no medicine for stupidity.
Take me there.
I can't.
I have a feeling we're going to catch the killer this time.
So it's really dangerous for me to take you with me.
Okay, then.
But I'm not going home tonight.
I'm gonna give my brother a little trouble.
Where are you going to stay?
I'm staying here.
What's the hell?
You should go home.
No
I'll send you.
I'm never leaving.
If you don't let me stay here.
I'm going away.
Hi
Hello?
What's wrong?
The other day, the important one...
What are you talking about?
Please hit the accelerator.
He's stupid.
you are very stubborn.
You are like your bros.
It's so annoying that I'm staying here?
I don't mean that.
Don't worry, I'll go home.
I'm kind of worried about me tomorrow.
I'll be fine.
Because if the real killer shows up.
If the real killer shows up, you'll be in deep trouble.
And you don't even know how you're going to get to Osaka.
Are you sure you're okay?
Suddenly you're talking about something that worries me.
I don't want you to take any danger.
I wonder how that boy's surgery is going.
I'd feel bad if he got a bad leg or something.
I've never said this before.
I have a feeling I'm partly to blame for what happened.
Why?
I chased him too much.
You were so angry when it was written in the paper.
Opinions from a third party can be more accurate than you think.
You were right then, weren't you?
Of course I was.
Be confidence.
That's not so you.
I feel responsible for that boy.
Responsible ?
I'm sorry for what I did to him.
That's why I'm gonna do what I have to do.
Are you serious about solving this case?
Good luck.
Be careful.
I knew you'd go for it.
Is he really suspicious?
I think I'm onto something today.
Okay.
But if you're so sure, why don't you report it to the hit-and-run unit?
That's the only way they'll understand your enthusiasm.
After the other night's debacle.Try any more of your deviant behavior.
You'll lose all credibility as a human being, not to mention a cop.
You came here to stop me?
Then leave.
You want to take credit?
Don't say bullshit.
You're gonna get hurt.
What are you going to do?
You don't know that because you've never cracked a killer.
A killer is like a wounded beast.
When they get cracked, they'll bite down on you like a rabid dog.
It's a more dangerous job than you think.
I get it.
Come with me to the police and file a report.
Leave it here
I know.
I'm going to police, so don't worry.
You go there first.
I know you'll go to Osaka.
You don't know what I'm talking about?
Let me go.
I want to catch the guy who did this to the kid who got hurt.
I may be trying to do more than I can.
But I'm going to do this one thing, and I don't care if it gets me fired.
I understand.
But I'm warning you.If I find out they're guilty...
Don't try to arrest them on the spot.
Why?
They have mates.
That's the most dangerous.
If you're in a hurry at the critical moment, you'll lose everything.
Never take your police book or handcuffs with you.
If they find you, all your hard work will be for nothing.
I get it.
Take care
It's a foreign bike.
New bike cost close to a million yen each.
BSA,BMW,Harley-Davidson
It's strange that such a high-end bike is available at a rental bike shop.
Attention.
We are about to leave, but...
As I've asked you many times before, please do not drive erratically.
I've outlined the course, but we'll be leading the way.
There will be many ups and downs, but we will lead the way.
So please hang in there.
So Let's go.
Safe drive.
You are a woman, please avoid traffic violations.
I’m sorry.
License.
You do have a driver's license, right?
Please drive according to traffic rules
What's wrong?
My motorcycle is acting up.
What's wrong with it?
The carburetor here, it's just not right.
This is strange.
The body and engine have been reassembled.
This one uses a different year, doesn't it?
Mine is same.
It's been repainted so I won't notice.
Have you ever participated this event before?
No, this is my first time.
It's a beautiful day.
Have you ever participated this event before?
That's the third time.
Where did you go last time?
Nagoya.
and before that?
Osaka.
What kind of hotel did you stay at?
It's a hotel that costs about the same as the membership fee.
But... of the 3,000 yen membership fee...
1,000 yen for lodging.
The other 2,000 yen is for gas, lunch and car rental.
That's a little low, isn't it?
Some people object to the price.
When We went to Nagoya, We just drove straight on the national highway.
It was nice, but the return trip was not.
Did you take a different road on the way back?
The motorcycle I used on the way home was very old.
Do you use a different motorcycle when you go home?
On the way back, I used a rental bike in Nagoya.
Nagoya's?
What will happen to the motorcycle I rode here?
I wonder if they should do some maintenance or something.
Maintenance?
The license plate number on the way back was from Aichi Prefecture.
That's strange... a different motorcycle on the way there and back.
I'm sure it's something...
Are you ready for gas?
Let's go!
Hey, you okay?
Help him.
You okay?
You have to ride carefully.
This is rental bike.
Looks like he hurt his leg.
I can't help it.
You guys go first.
Don't go too fast.
Don't worry.
I can drive.
Don't push yourself too hard.
motorcycle broke.
You stupid.
There's no point in getting angry.
We have to take him to the hospital.
Take him to your bike.
what to do with his bike?
Do it.
You know how to go?
You okay?
There was something wrong with the plug, but it has been fixed.
Let's have lunch here.
Departure is at 1:00 p.m.
There is a village six kilometers from here.
From there, we will be on a bus road.
Then it's straight to Nagoya.
We'll take a short break in Nagoya.
Then we'll drive the Meishin bypass and be on our way.
We should be in Osaka by 5:00.
Understood?
You're free to go until 5:00. But don't be late for the departure time.
It's a hell of a road, isn't it?
But it's a nice place, though, isn't it?
Nice weather.
When was the last time you were in Nagoya?
I wonder when.
Was it Saturday?
No, it was a weekday.
That's why there weren't many people.
As I recall, that was the day after the 26th of Nov holiday, right?
Oh yeah.
26th?
Then what time did you arrive in Tokyo on the 27th?
It was rather early.
We left Nagoya at 7:00 a.m., so it was around 3:00 a.m.
On November 27th, at 3:30, that accident happened.
That's for sure.
There's no way to know for sure.
How do I get them to confess?
It's time to depart.
Lend me the fire.
Hold on.
You're police.
I saw you push that motorcycle off the cliff.
Why should you abandon your car?
Tell me!
It's a stolen car, isn't it?
I just helped him.
Yeah
What are you doing with it in Osaka?
Sell them?
November 27th, last time you guys were on your way back from Nagoya.
You were speeding in Yamashita-cho on Loop Route 7 on your way home from Nagoya the other day?
Who ran over the kid at the amusement park?
I don't know.
It was not me.
I knew it was Yazawa!
Wait!
Damn it!
What are you doing?
Don't be late.
Sorry I was looking around.
Where's Tajima?
He'll be back soon.
He told me to catch up with us later?
Ok let's go.
Not a phone around here?
No.
You have to go to the village.
You made good job.
Let me take your photo.
You're a motorcycle cop for the Metropolitan Police Department?
Stay away.
When did you find out that Yazawa was the hit-and-run driver?
Say something.
It's not good for cops to play individually.
How do you feel about the arrest of the perpetrators?
Are you glad?
I'm not happy about the injured child.
Wait.
Keep going.
Good for you.
You're walking again.
I'm glad?
Thank you.
I'm so relieved he got better.
You must have been worried.
Thank you very much.
I saw it in the newspaper.
He's still injured?
He doesn't walk alone because he's been resting for a long time.
Come to here,Tamio.
Can you?
Come on.
You are man.
I'll make it.
Well done.
I'm so relieved.
Damn it.
Are you going to chase again?
He went that fast on the sharp downhill curve.
That's the most dangerous thing I've ever seen.
By the end of the day we have to find an apartment.
But..
Go ahead if you want.
You won.
Get on my back.
THE END