Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
This is a complete marriage fraud
He said he would get married with her for three years, but he changed his mind
Let me explain what fraud is
Fraud is when someone cheats you out of your property or things.
Did she get the money deceived by the man?
She hasn't taken money
She lost the most precious thing in her life to that man.
In that case, you can file a civil claim against him for alimony.
Decide if you really want to sue him or settle him
Then let me know
You know what
In this case it is difficult to expect legal sanctions
Anyway
Please be careful not to do this again
Be careful that your daughter is not deceived by men in the future.
What I want to say is, You should have an eye for men.
Sorry I'm busy
What should we do after all?
Decide if you really want to sue him or settle him
Then I will take care of you
It's been a while since I've had a visitor, but it's like someone came to me for life advice.
They should be on a TV show.
Sensei
About the case
Can't I quit the office yet?
Wait for a whole
Wait until someone else joins the company
The Black Torrent
Mmm...
Ah...
Urrrr...
Calm judgment for men
Have a cognitive eye
It's like a textbook
But I got this result
But
I'm not going to end up with such a poor lawyer
You want to say like that?
I've been hearing that line from you for three years.
You want to be a first-class lawyer
And if given the chance, You'd like to take Dr. Wakamiya's daughter as your wife.
Takeshi-san
Lately I'm thinking like that
There is no future even if one woman works at a law firm
I want to have a small clothing store in Roppongi
But it's not good
It doesn't make sense to be with you
Let's go home
Today I got a call from the lawyer's association
Yes
It was a contact of the public defender
I will see them tomorrow
It'll be a boring incident anyway.
This is a troublesome problem
Yeah
Why you have come here?
I have no work
I'll be a court-appointed attorney and make some extra money.
To where?
The district court
Ah sensei
I also go to the district court
Leave it to you
See you then
Hi
Good morning
Wakamiya sensei is here
He is here?
Yes
His daughter too
Good morning
Where is Wakamiya sensei ?
He is in the back
Ah,Sensei
It's been a whole
Hi
Please come to Denenchofu once in a while
Yes
I think this case is difficult
But our lawyer association has to take charge of this case
That's right
If it is a public defender, the reward is small
It would be nice if someone handle this case...
Ms.
What is the case he just said?
This is..
This is the Abe group of companies incident that appeared in the newspaper a month ago.
Abe group of companies?
He says the case is a no-win proposition.
This is an obvious murder case
This case appeals
Robbery Murder Fujie Kaizuka
25 years old
Arraignment
The accused was around 6:00 pm on May 15, 1972.
In the mountains of Okuishi-cho, Nishitama-gun, Tokyo
She invited Tatsuhiko Abe, the head of the department, whom she happened to know.
She had sex with him and demanded money
She found out he had a lot of money.
So she wanted to rob him of money
She robbed him of money and pushed him out of the valley
She killed him with it
For the reasons
It's only fair that the defendant receive the maximum penalty.
I am not guilty
I didn't do anything
And Article 46 of the Penal Code
I was on that day...
That day was the evening of May 16th when Abe was killed?
Defendant is sentenced to death
Yes
I went to buy a camera film in front of the station for work at the inn that day
The time was just 5 o'clock
Our cook was on holiday that day and the inn didn't take any guests.
It's about 2 km to the station
I arrived in front of the station around 5:30
Two films, please.
Yes
Here are they
How much?
800 yen please
Can I have a receipt?
OK
Here it is
Thank you
Here is the change, 200yen
Are you Fujie?
Are you Shinku-inn's Fujie,right?
Yes...
You don't remember me?
You are cold
Oh..You stayed us before..
Yes, I'm Abe
Your inn is closed today?
Right,There is also road construction and Our cook is holiday today
I see
That's too bad
Where are you going?
To Sekiote. it's far?
It takes 5mins by car
I see, then I will go on foot
Really?
I'm on a diet
I need to walk
So I have come here by train
Can you show me around?
Ok no problem
Then did you go back the way you came?
Yes
I was separated from Mr. Abe in front of the suspension bridge
Wait
Good
Let's review it
This is the Shinju-inn where you have worked
You headed towards the station from here
You went to a souvenir shop in front of the station to buy a camera film
The train arrived while you were waiting
This train arrived at 5:35
You also checked the time by the store's clock
This is correct so far
You paid and got the receipt
It took 5 minutes in the meantime,so 5:20
Then you met with Abe right away
How long did you talk with him?
I think 4-5 mins at most
So let's say 5:45...
Then you went to the five-way road directly?
So It took 15,6 mins to go back to the five-way road
You arrived here around 6:00
You turned right here
You went to until the suspension bridge
There is about 200 meters from this suspension bridge to the five-way road.
Even if you walked slowly, it took 5 mins
So.. at 6:05
You were supposed to be in front of the suspension bridge
You separated with Abe here, right?
Yes
Then?
As I said at Police station
After you saw him off, you were under the bridge
You were under the bank
It's true
If you stay under this suspension bridge for half an hour, I'm sure someone was watching you.
I was sitting behind a tree
So no one noticed me
Police suspect this 30 minutes
In the last 30 minutes you invited Abe to have sex, robbed him of money and killed him
You really didn't go to this murder scene?
How many times I repeat this..
OK
You were under the suspension bridge
Thinking about various things
What you had a hard time until today
What you will do in the future
You were thinking about that
Is that right?
Then you got up and tried to go home
That's where Abe's fountain pen fell,right?
Yes
The fountain pen had an initial called TA dug.
I quickly realized that it was Mr. Abe's
Then It started raining
At 6:55 you returned to the inn in the rain
The person at the inn was checking the time because your return was late
Is that right?
My clothes were wet so I went back to my room and changed my clothes
Your colleague Sumiko Morimoto saw it,right?
Speaking of what, Sumie returned here in hurry
She was out of breath and her face was deep blue
She changed into jeans when I entered the waiting room
There was a wet kimono in the corner of the room and she had her hair fixed
She never answered whatever I asked
She has a gloomy personality
We searched this room
Abe's fountain pen was found in the accused's dressing box
We found 50,000 yen in her handbag
The accused says that this 50,000 yen is the saved money
I think it's strange to put a lot of money in a handbag
Normally, people keep money they don't use in a savings account.
Defendant during 30 minutes of crime time
She says she killed time under the bridge
But there is no proof
She says she got wet in the rain and washes all her clothes that day,
including her underwear
This is an act to eliminate semen after the accused has sex with Abe
This is clearly evidence destruction
What do you think of yesterday's prosecutor's opening statement?
Abe fell from here
Fumie Kaizuka didn't come here but
The prosecution is assuming she has come
The only evidence on the prosecution side is Abe's fountain pen in her handbag
Something is wrong with the prosecution's statement
Why did the prosecution prosecute without complete evidence?
That is the problem
Mr. Abe's company's political contribution is hundreds of millions of yen per year.
I don't think the prosecution has moved because of that
They treat the dead Abe as a completely well-meaning person
They have decided that there is no possibility of suicide or negligence
They have decided that the criminal is Fujie
Let me review it
I try to find out the mistakes on the prosecution side
Next,The accused's fountain pen is the only physical evidence
Now,Judiciary Prosecutor's Fifth Statement of Statement
And I would like you to recall the transcript of the first trial.
The accused guided him to the suspension bridge as requested by the victim
The accused explained the directions to the inn where the victim stayed here.
Victim put out a fountain pen and wrote directions in a notebook
He was focused on explaining with her
He could have accidentally dropped his fountain pen.
What I want to say is The fountain pen may not be involved in crime
And also
The accused has brought the fountain pen back to the inn
As a criminal's psychology
Psychologically proves that you brought back what you used for the crime
Even if it's expensive
The criminal expected the police to pursue
It's normal psychology not to take those things home.
Secondly, the prosecution says that the defendant is guilty of a crime
Round trip time from the inn to the station
Well...at normal speed
It takes about 1 hour for the round trip
Look at the map
According to the prosecution's claim
It took her 1 hour and 55 minutes to get to this store and back.
55 minutes is excess time
Defendant and victim arrived at the bridge at 6:03
They crossed the suspension bridge and turned right on Third Road
And they arrived at the crime scene
It takes 12 minutes at normal speed from the bridge to the crime scene
The distance from the crime scene to the inn is about 2 km
so I takes 30mins
Therefore
We have to deduct 42 minutes from that excess time of 52 minutes
It's gonna be 13 mins
During these 13 minutes, the accused must have sex with the accused and take the money.
And She had to push him into the valley
This can't be done in 13 minutes
Moreover The accused wore a kimono on the day
So She walked slower than normal speed
It's common to think that way
The 13 minutes used to commit the crime will be further reduced.
More important than that
That the defendant said he left the victim on a bridge.
Judge
Prosecutor Please
The defense attorney said the victim left the defendant at the foot of the bridge.
Attorneys claim not to hand over to the crime scene
We have witnesses on that matter
This is a floor plan near the site.
Where do you live?
I live in front of the suspension bridge
Did you meet the accused on the day of the case?
I didn't but
I saw her
That's May 15th for sure?
Yes
I returned to Gunma's parents' house on the 16th of the next day
So I remember well
What time did you see her?
It was past 6 pm
Why did you remember the time ?
Because my eldest son watches children's news on TV at 6 o'clock.
What did her look like?
After I watched the new with him
I went out to clean up the store sign
At that time, I was
I thought she was an employee of the inn
I didn't care at all
Why you lied?
You said you crossed the suspension bridge
I crossed the suspension bridge
But I parted with Abe after I crossed the suspension bridge
Give me a break
You said you didn't cross the suspension bridge, that you left him at the foot of the bridge.
After the witnesses appeared you said you crossed the bridge and then you left him
Do you approach the crime scene every time a witness appears?
I really broke up with him after I crossed the bridge.
But If I crossed the bridge, I'll be closer to the crime scene.
I thought it would be a disadvantage
Give me a break
You should have said it from the beginning
A new witness has come out
What?
No good, don't do that!
I'm Yano
What is the new testimony?
Please tell me
As the prosecutor says
The man's screams, as heard by Kiyoko Kosaka, who was arraigned by the defense, were
It cannot be determined whether it belongs to the victim Abe
But It cannot be said that it is not Abe's
Because it was the day of the incident
There is no evidence that it is not Abe
From the situation, I think it's a scream that Abe fell off the cliff.
Therefore, this defense counsel
A new witness, Kiyoko Kosaka
She went to visit her husband at a general hospital near the scene
On her return way
Just before she gets on the bus in front of the hospital at 6:50
She heard the man scream
This testimony should be emphasized
Therefore
At the crime time claimed by the prosecution
The accused was at the suspension bridge at 6:03 with the victim
The accused crossed the bridge and was at the crime scene at 6:15
It is said that she committed the crime in 13 minutes and returned to the inn.
In this case
The time when the accused pushed the victim to the bottom of the valley
It must be between 6:15 and 6:28
But the new witness hears his scream at 6:50
What does this meaning?
If the prosecutor claims it is not the victim Abe scream
Show confirmation that it is not Abe's voice
According to the record
The time when the accused returned to the inn is 6:55
The time when Abe fell into the valley is 6:50.
In doing so
The accused has to return to the inn in 5 mins
To do so
She had to run 2000 M at a speed of 15 seconds
Moreover she dressed Kimono at that day
If she ran at a speed of 100 M 15 seconds
She ran like this way
It's not funny
This is the behavior of the accused on the day of the crime claimed by the prosecutor.
Secondly
I will explain the life of Tatsuhiko Abe
I'm not going to hurt the victim
But it ’s important in this case, so I will explain it.
That is different from the facts stated by the prosecutor
His personal life was a little troubled.
Judge
Attorneys should continue to make statements
He was on May 14th, the day before his death
He stopped by his new lover
This is his new lover
He stayed overnight at her house and came to Okutama the next day
This means
The prosecutor said he only had a few thousand yen
So the prosecutor determined that the accused had robbed the rest of the money.
Also in that his underwear had a small amount of semen on it
The prosecutor has ruled that this means he had sex with the defendant.
I doubt this
He stayed at his lover's house the day before
He gave the woman money
I think he had sex with the woman
If you argue, please show the rationale
Prosecutors allege that the accused invited the victim
Prosecutors allege that the accused had sex with him and robbed him of money
There are discrepancies on these points.
That's all
By the points of the defense counsel
There was no fact that the accused, Fumie Kaizuka, killed the subject and robbed him of the money.
The victim just fell
the accused, Fumie Kaizuka is not guilty
Stand up
Sit down
Please come forward near,the accused, Fumie Kaizuka
From now on, I will hand down the murder-robbery judgment against the accused.
the accused, Fumie Kaizuka is not guilty
The reason 1.
The accused is after the first trial
She denies the crime in this case
Especially at 5 pm on May 15, 1967
She has an alibi for that time
The court made a statement about the accused's alibi
The court adopts the defense counsel's allegations
As a result, the defendant was found not guilty.
Firstly on May 15, 1967
The court considered the accused's actions
Cheers!
Thank you for this time
You did your best
Everyone is mentally unstable during normal detention
Everyone has the illusion of truth.
I was most worried about it
You did your best
I'm sure you had a hard time
Sensei
You're forgetting one other woman who had a hard time.
Sorry
Ms. Kaizuka has a patience award, and you have a special merit award.
It was hard when I went to the site of Okutama with you
That's right
The witness you found was very effective
It seems I did nothing
You worked good too
And You will move to a new company
I'll have her work in the office instead of you.
Me?
You can't work at that inn, right?
But it seems to me difficult work
I can't handle it
Don't worry, you just serve tea,clean the office, and get bored
Then you kill time near the coffee shop
You bad
Oh,You laughed!
I saw her laugh for the first time
So it was decided
She will stay near the inn tonight, but We have to find her new apartment
Please enjoy drinking
I called to book your inn just before
You forget all and take a rest
Thank you for everything
I think you should move slowly later
Yes
I don't have much luggage
Oh here it is
Good night
Sensei
What?
Oh don't worry, I have already paid the accommodation fee
It's not that
No? So what?
How much does a lawyer fee cost?
Did you worry about it?
As you may know, I don't have enough money
So
So?
There is nothing I give you
So...I...
You can sleep with me if you like
Ms.Kaizuka
I'm not drunker
I'm serious
if you like
You are stupid
I'm not thinking of getting money from you
You should take a rest, good night
But sensei...
If we quarrel in front of the inn, we look weird
Please come to our office tomorrow
We should talk about future
Yes
Have a good dream
Another one?
You came early
Yes
I didn't expect it
I thought you would stay somewhere
You've been dumped by a woman.?
I dumped her
You are cool play boy
Keep your change
Oh you are leaving now?
I have plans with another woman.
With Whom?
The person closest to me
Thank you very much.
What do you think about the prosecution's abandonment of appeal?
I was confident that I would win even if I fought in the Supreme Court
Is this the first time for you?
This is the first time for a public defender
Public defender is not profitable
You know very well
This week's issue of our magazine headlines
A gentle lawyer who takes over the former defendant
Do you think this is fine?
Leave it to you
I will make a good story and write an article
These days, all the incidents are boring.
Then see you, have a nice day
You are like big star
I should have take a charge of it
Excuse me
Yes
Please copy this
When you copied it, Put it on the cutting machine.
Yes
Please write as carefully as possible
Be careful about mis-writing
Yes
I didn't notice but She is beautiful
You think so?
Your attitude is not so good
But it's good she is here
Do not make a fool of me
I just hired her because she doesn't have a job
I'm just kidding
Well...
So Can I reply to Mr.Yamakura about the case?
Yes please
I'm not sure if I am good enough
You just have to take on the corporate lawyer
You can earn a lot
Oh yeah
Wakamiya-Lawyer are interested in you after the case
Your future may be bright
Please drink
This is something small but We would like to congratulate you
Thank you
I was talking about you when I talked to Kitagawa-kun of Nitto Bank today
He really likes you
I told him that you were my trainee before
Then he also likes me
Thank you
Thank you for your work
Please
Tomoko
What?
Yano also worked hard and became a first-class lawyer.
Congratulations
Not at all
You guys overestimate me
I was just lucky at the work
I don't think it's my ability
I see
She was expecting you all the time
What?
You grew up before I knew it
You mean!
You are a first-class lawyer now, your job will be more difficult.
Please do your best from now on
I know that
Daughter and I are expecting you
Thank you
Can I eat?
No no no
No no
Can I eat?
No, like this
like this?
Can I eat?
Good evening
Oh
Do you eat ? because I got a gift
Thank you
Feel free to ask me if you need something
Don't worry about that
If you are in trouble, please feel free to tell me
See you
Thank you
Sensei
Did you get used to it a little?
Yes
Everyone is very kind
That's good to hear
I'm sorry there is nothing here
I will bring some beers from next door
Don't worry about that
But I feel sorry
Please wait
I got some snacks too
Please drink
Thank you
You used to work at an inn so you're used to it
Sensei
Please do not talk about the inn
I didn't mean that
I'll have this
What?
I'm sorry
I was very worried
I thought you were angry
I was angry?
For what?
Because
I told you a dirty thing when you saw me off at the inn...
A dirty thing?
Did you tell me anything?
I wanted to thank you
I was stupid
I couldn't tell anything but a dirty thing
Please forgive me
You don't have to worry about it
At that time, we both had the feelings of a defense counsel and a defendant.
After the trial we are a man and woman
Don't you feel that way anymore?
I still feel
I'm stupid so
I can't say it well
Kaizuka-kun
Sensei
I want you
I want you too
I...
I expected this to happen
Kaizuka-kun
I'm on the side of a weak person like you
I feel happy
I'm not thinking about the future
It's Ok if I'm happy now
I'm happy now...
Sensei
But now we're the focus.
So we have to be careful
Ok?
I know
But I want to cook and wash your underwear as a woman
That's what I hope
Don't think stupid
You want to be an Idol?
No
I won't be selfish so Don't leave me
I want to support you from the shadows.
so Don't leave me
I'm okay with being a secret woman.
I'm okay
I think of that statutory time
I am very happy compared to that time
You know what,Sensei
Will I never be called to court again?
Don't worry
Professionally called non-bis in idem
Once acquittal is determined, they can never be tried again
Really?
You don't trust me?
It is written in Article 39 of the Constitution
I feel at ease
Originally you were not the culprit
You should be proud
Kaizuka-kun
Sensei
Oh thank you
I'm going to the bank
OK
You need cigarettes?
Can you buy?
I'll get the money later.
Short-Hope, right?
You are strange
You should tell me
Please say by name
Takeshi-san
You don't sleep with me these days
Don't say weird things
So Where should I talk?
Recently you are crazy about her
Takahashi-kun
I know
You're concerned about the media, but you're a little bold.
I don't think you mean it
She's a cheap woman, you know. we don't even know where she's from.
You should be careful
What about Wakamiya-sensei's daughter?
I'm sure she will know about it
You think too much
I'm sorry
I found You have a hotel match
Of course he is not bad man
But he has a wonderful future
If I say it clearly
He just plays around you
This is not a joke
I used to be just like you
What?
I don't want you to be like me
If you're not careful, he'll just play you
As you told be before,
What is his future path?
You don't know?
Wakamiya sensei's
I know
It ’s his teacher.
The teacher's daughter graduated from college this year.
He's a rich daughter
She is different from us
Don't get me wrong.
I don't want you guys to break up
I'm just giving you advice
I hear when you were in college, all you did was work.
But Your grade was excellent
I heard a lot about you from my Dad or others
Oh my god, but thank you
But I wasn't the good student you think I am.
No way
You seem to have been working alone at any time
That's good
I'm bossy.
Can I follow you?
Kaizuka-kun
Why you are here?
Anyone saw you?
That's the way it is
Come in
Good customers haven't come these days
They only talk about marriage or divorce
Why you keep standing, come in
There is something you want to do, right?
I've heard from Okahashi
What did you hear?
Sensei
You have something to do with her
What are you taking about?
I've heard about Wakamiya's daughter too
Do you trust what I say?
Or Do you trust what she says?
Which one?
Why you didn't tell me?
It's needless to say
It's important to me
Is that true?
What if it is true?
Please do not look for various things
It's weird
You said you wanted to be a shadow woman.
That's not your business
You said you were on the side of the weak
Yes
It doesn't mean an enemy
You wanted to be a shadow woman.
I just support you
I'll decide whether I marry with Tomoko or not
You also can decide whether you will be a shadow woman or leave me
The two have nothing to do with each other
Does it make sense?
I'm sorry I'm late
I will answer the phone
Hello?
This is Yano speaking
Yes,This is Yano speaking
Yes
Yes I know.
I will go to the lobby of Togo Kaikan at 13:00
Yes
Ah...
Really?
I apologize for interrupting your busy schedule.
As I told you other day
Mr. Kitagawa, the president of Nitto Bank, wants to meet you.
I am honored
He's always been a picky man.
He wants to be a matchmaker between you and Tomoko
He decided it on his own
Let's decide the schedule while eating meal
Oh, he is coming
How are you?
I apologize for interrupting your busy schedule.
I introduce him.
He is the Yano Takeshi I talk you before
He is a bad friend since my school days
He is Kitagawa,just old man
I'm Yano.
Thank you for the good reputation
You were good
I also studied law at university
Anyway let's have a meal
Yes. let's go up stairs
You dress nice,Tomoko
What are you up to?
I'm doing Okay
How did it go the other day?
You forget?
Please
Take your seats
Be relax
You seem to have more work
Yes
Anyway Let's toast
Please take care of our daughter
Let's toast
Kanpai!
I'm home
Good timing.
I have a call for you.
Phone call for me?
Yes from Kaizuka-san
Kaizuka-san?
Kaizuka?
A person who works in my office
Ah
She calls for me, I will answer
Thanks
Here it is
Hello? are you Kaizuka?
It's me,Yano
Hello?
Why you don't say anything?
Where are you now?
Hello?
What's wrong with you?
Tell me
Say something!
I told you I want to be a shadow woman
I withdraw it
What?
I need a father for my coming baby
Please marry me
Are you insane?
Is there evidence that the baby is mine?
What?
You are easy.
You slept with Abe
Right?
That's too bad
I tell you clearly
I've just been playing you
Why do you threaten me?
Shame on you!
You were kind before but..
You have changed yourself
I don't care about it!
You know what,You and I are out of balance.
You just stupid!
I tell you.
Do not dream that you want to be lawyer’s wife
You are just shadow woman
You are so cheeky today
You should think
You were originally a murderer
You were supposed to be in jail
But you can now live a normal life
You should thank me
Wait!
You can't leave me
Why?
I tell you
The true criminal who killed Abe
I am
What?
You stupid
Don't be crazy
That's true
At that day... I was...
I crossed the suspension bridge with him for sure
I found out later
He told his friend he was going to rape me next time
Of course I didn't know that
I was brought close to the cliff by him
I was told to guide him because He wants azalea flowers
Then...
I was raped
He forced to rape me
Abe-san, you are bad
What do you mean?
I can't go home anymore today
I see.
You want money,right?
I don't mean that
I was disappointed
I pay for it and it means not rape.
I bet with a friend.
I lost
Shit
I will give you money if you want
If I pay, you are the same as prostitution
Take it
Oh my god
Poor people really want money
50000yen is not enough?
You are greedy
Leave me!
I was panicking
I ran away
You are lying
Do you think you can fool me?
Did you fly back to your inn?
Just then A car passed by
A car?
Give me a break
The road was under construction at that time
It ’s a car that a foreigner was driving.
So he couldn't read the Japanese sign
It's nonsense
Where was his notebook?
I didn't want to tell the truth
I didn't want to say it even if it killed me.
This is my last word in my life
But you tried to leave me so....
I had no way to keep you
I know I am not qualified as layer's wife
The feeling I want to be with you
It does not matter if I am poor or rich or no educated
I don't want to let anyone marry you
If you dump me, I will visit Wakamiya
I will ask Tomoko and tell the truth
But if you really don't like me
I go to court and sue you
I say you're an accomplice.
Is that all you want to say?
Help me, Sensei
You stupid
Who can trust you, crazy woman
That case is already complete
You will only be laughed at.
Do it whatever you want!
I don't know what happened
Shit!
That crazy woman threatened me
I don't want to let anyone marry you
If you dump me, I will visit Wakamiya
I will ask Tomoko and tell the truth.
I go to court and sue you
I say you're an accomplice.
You're an accomplice.
Stop!
Get after the car
Are you police?
Whatever, Keep eyes on that car!
OK
Please turn right at the next corner
They are heading to Denenchofu
Denenchofu?
Damn it
What shall I do?
Excuse me
Wait for me
Wait here
OK
Our staff Kaizuka came here?
You didn't meet her?
She visited us just before
What she said?
She said you come here for urgent business soon
Unfortunately There is no one today
I have to go
Kaizuka-kun
You are really...
All I wan to say is as I told you last night
I get it
You surely sue me
Yes
Ok I see
Good morning
We've received the documents from Yamamura Sangyo for you
Thank you
I envy you becoming a popular lawyer.
Kaizuka-kun
Stay away
I'll come here again
I'll go home today
I'm sorry but let me take a holiday
Excuse me
You told her bad things
I didn't mean that
You are about to get married.
I thought it was better to organize your relationships
I don't want you to grudge
But you're going to be a pain in the ass.
There may be no legal problem but
But it will affect your work
The media may say you are a bad lawyer
I'm in trouble
And also
Kaizuka is completely different from Ms. Tomoko
Tomoko may have a fever and sleep all day
What should I do, Yukiko
You are an egoist but You're small-minded.
I need your wisdom.
Sensei
I hate this kind of life
I told you, right?
I want to open a clothing store in Roppongi
I found the shop in Yotsuya
It costs 5 million yen for an unoccupied property.
You will marry a rich daughter
Furthermore, the president of the bank is a matchmaker.
How about instead of money for my retirement?
What the hell you talk about?
What are you saying?
Now I'm in so much trouble
I'm not telling you to do it for free
I'm the only person who knows your secret
In short
It is an exchange condition
It is an exchange condition?
You don't get it?
You kill her
kill her?
I kill who?
Of course Fumie Kaizuka
You kill her pretending to be an accidental death
And I testify that it was an accidental death
Dear Judge
I swear to God now and tell the truth
Travel...
If someone suspects us, I will say the three of us were planning to go together.
I testify that I got sick on the day and couldn't go
This is the important point
Whether to die by negligence or accident
In any case, there's only one way I told you.
From whom?
Hello?
What?
Kaizuka-san?
Wait a min
Phone call for you
Thanks
Hello?
This is Kaizuka speaking
Yes
Come in
Thank you for coming at mid-night
You might laugh if I say this
I called you because I want you to live in this house
Trust me
What I mean is.. I want to apologize you
Come in
I'm not doing this because I don't want to be sued by you
I remember supporting you in the court
I remembered that moment.
I was thinking of using Mr. Wakamiya's daughter to get ahead.
But I realized my true self now
Fujie
I'm breaking off my marriage to Tomoko.
I don't care if you're a murderer.
I want to start with you again from the beginning
Fujie, Let's get marry for our coming baby
Sensei
I was sorry
I was about to send a letter to the court
Fujie
I'm the only person who understand you
I'm asking you to marry me.
I was sorry
I will be your slave for the rest of my life
Please forgive me
Let us forget about last night.
Would you like to go on a trip for a few days?
Go on a trip ?
Let's go to a place where the air is clean
Then let's forget what we have done
Let us make a new start
Sensei
Let's drive early tomorrow morning
I'm happy
Sensei
Don't leave me
I won't
I won't leave you  for the rest of my life
Your tea
Thank you
It's very quiet here
This season is a quiet season
Your wife is the first time to come here?
We will go for fish tomorrow so  Please lend us a boat
Yes
There may be fog tomorrow
fog?
Yes
That's too bad
But we want to go because we came here
Sure
I will go too?
I'm scared to get on the boat
Don't worry.
Our boat is solid.
But I can't swim
You stupid.
The boat will not capsize
And I will be with you
That's right
Please enjoy
Then please make yourself at home
Thanks
Is something wrong?
Well...nothing
You are strange, tell me
Because she said I'm your wife
Everyone thinks so
I've never been called that way
You are late
I'm sorry,I forgot the sandwich we ordered
Please
Let's go
Yes
I think you got fish
Hmm
It's strange
It looks like the fish are in a bad mood today
Let's go to the shore.
Here is bad place to fish
We don't need to move
I feel cold
Let's go back
Sensei
Can I guess what you are thinking now?
You are trying to kill me
I found out it when I looked into your eyes last night.
But I wanted to beside you whatever you do to me
So I came with you
I see
What will you do if it's true?
Right,I'm thinking of killing you
And I will be with Tomoko
You will sink with this boat
No one can see in the fog
You fell into the water trying to catch a fish
I tried to save you but there was something wrong on the boat
I tried to save you but couldn't see in the fog
This is unavoidable
You understand?
The act that was unavoidably committed for the life of oneself or others
If the other person is sacrificed, it is not a crime under the criminal law.
Sensei
Don't go anywhere,Sensei
I will not give you to anyone
Sensei
You are mine
You are mine!
Dear Judge
I'm going to get on the boat so I write a letter fast
I can't leave Mr. Yano
We choose death
And
I am also the true criminal who killed Abe
I threw the proof Boston bag into the river
Abe's notebook is in Mr. Yano's apartment
Wakamiya-sensei
Tomoko-san,Yukiko-san
Please forgive me
Good bye
I didn't know
I didn't know they'd gone to the lake.
He is stupid
That woman ruined his life.
I should have known it
I could stop them
Good morning
Hi,Machida
hi
It's bee a whole
I have nothing to do
I'll be a court-appointed attorney and make some extra money.
Is there any interesting incident?
Finish