Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Black Weapon
At that time, each electric machine manufacturer was
mass-producing TVs.
They produced 60,000 TVs a month
2500 units per day on average
One TV was produced every 12 seconds
To win the competition in this business
Manufacturers have made their TVs bigger and smaller.
Or aimed at popularizing color TV
Anyway
They needed a new idea
Hey, there is something inside
What? I have some one
Me too
Bar angel
It's strange
I wonder who put this in
What's the matter?
We can drink a glass of highball for free with this ticket
Hmm...I think you will be billed elsewhere
Recently, there are many bars that overcharge
I give you this
I can't drink
You sure?
Then I will take this
I appreciate it
So we can drink tonight
This one service ticket made my life go crazy
The bar was a cheesy bar like everywhere
Hostess came to service
After we drank highball there
We felt good so we ordered another cup
It was good drinking
I got drunk comfortably
Then, all of a sudden
A woman appeared in front of me
She was so beautiful that I couldn't see her face
Hey, Shall we dance?
I'm bad dancer
It's Ok
You are doing great
Keep going
Good
Good couple!
I want you to come here again
Only you
Please keep it secret
The next day
I came to see Reiko alone
Welcome
She treated me like a different person from last night
I was like her regular customer
But
I'm just a worker, why she treat me well
Why was she so familiar?
Let's dance
You know what?
What time do you finish work on Saturday
5 pm as usual
Can you leave the company early?
Are we going somewhere?
I want to go for a drive
You want to go for a drive?
I was surprised but
I can go for a drive with her
I was excited to think about it
Is that good? Promise me
1PM on Saturday
How is this car?
Hmm
That's good
Is it bad that bar hostess has car?
I don't mean it
I think you make a lot of money
All the salary from the shop is used for clothes
Then why you have a lot of money?
I'm investing in stocks
You are investing in stocks
Investing in stocks is lucrative.
Stock research and courage are needed
I'm not into that
Why?
Because I don't have the current funds
It's okay if you borrow money
I can loan you the money
You should buy the stock of your company
Dainippon Electric's stock is an excellent stock
Are you assigned to the inspection department?
Yes
How long have you been working there?
It's been exactly three and a half years
I'm currently attending a night school at a university.
After graduating from school, you will become an engineer
Of course I will be promoted to a full-time employee
So You shouldn't go to the bar
I have time to go to your bar on the way home from work
But I don't have enough money
However, if I become a full-time employee, my monthly salary will more than double.
It ’s your dream to be an engineer
Yes
You know what
What?
Shall we stay one night here?
What? We won't go back to Osaka?
I think it's ok just one night
Your mother will worry about you?
Hum
You know what
I was crazy about her
Regarding the stock of Dainippon Electric
There is information on the stock price increases
Why don't you buy it seriously?
What is the information on stock price increases?
RV-17 mission
It ’s a new product that your company is making right now.
If the product is revolutionary, the stock price will rise.
But We don't know well what is RV-17 like
It seems that something is being prototyped at the laboratory
Can you research what is it for me?
Once I get that information, I will buy a lot of stock
I think the stock price will go up to the 300 yen level for sure
If I sell the stock there, I will get a profit of 1.7 million yen.
I was crazy about Reiko
I investigated Operation RV 17 to please her
What are you doing?
Well..nothing
What do you mean?
Actually, I accidentally dumped something in the trash
It's not big deal but it's a baseball ticket
This incinerator is for the Central Research Laboratory only.
We don't burn such waste paper
Is that so?
I'm so sorry, sir.
I don't know for sure yet but
Look this
What is this?
This is probably a cathode ray tube glass
This was in the incinerator of the laboratory
Let me see
Is this related to the new product?
I think so, I need to survey more
Anyway this is not made by our company
The thickness is different
Can I get this?
What? You want to survey this?
I will ask someone to survey this
I was disgusted before
There was news that color TVs will be released by towa Electric
I didn't do my research at the time and spent all my money to buy stocks.
That was fake
Yes true, I lost all money
Oh yeah, I will survey more for you
I'm counting on you.
If I make a profit, I'll share it with you.
I'm back
Welcome home
You're home late.
Um
What's wrong with you?
I met my friend.
You should have slept earlier
Do you eat inari?
Yes I want to eat
The water has become lukewarm.
I don't care
By the way, Mom
What?
I have something very important to tell you.
What is that?
You know what
What?
Shall I massage your shoulders?
Don't worry, Please eat it
I'm sure you are hungry
I think I'm getting marry with someone
What? Really?
Are you sure?
She is so modern
She is beautiful and has a very bright personality
I think you will like her too
I see, so you are home late recently
You know what, Mom
Do you approve of us?
If you want to, of course I'll support you.
I want you to be an engineer soon
And find good wife
That's all I hope
Thank you, Mom
This is what the glass looks like when restored from its thickness and curvature.
This is a about 6 inch cathode ray tube
6 inch
So this is Dainippon Electric's RV 17.
Yes.
This is a groundbreaking micro TV
Did you call me, Chief?
katayanagi-kun,
I'm going to have to ask you to leave the company.
What?
You know the reason
The union also approved your dismissal
I don't think there is any reason to be fired
You didn't know?
We have been monitoring your behavior all the time
The woman at your friend's bar was a Taiyo Electric spy
Are you sure?
Don't pretend you don't know
I didn't know that
I was just asked about stocks by her
Chief! Trust me!
I didn't know she was spy
I didn't mean that...
I didn't feel like betraying our company
But As a result you betrayed our company
Get a severance pay at the accounting department
Damn it!
What happened?
Is Reiko-san in?
Hasn't she come yet?
Oh, she left day before yesterday
She left?
Yes suddenly
Do you know where she has gone?
Well...She is a beautiful girl, so she was invited by various men
I wonder she has gone to Minami
Is it urgent?
No...
Never mind
It ’s your dream to be an engineer
You are so sweet
Damn it
I will do it
I will do it!
I will be an industrial spy and take revenge
Taiyo Electric deceived me
Taiyo Electric broke my dreams and future
I will beat them
An eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth.
3 years later
Where we will stay tonight?
I want to stay on the Shima Peninsula
The meeting in Nagoya ends around 3 o'clock
I want to come to the Ise Peninsula
I'm glad
I've never been there
It ’s so beautiful that it ’s called the island of pearls.
It's a call.
Mr. Takasugi of Dainippon Electric
There is a phone call from Osaka, so please come to car 2.
What?
You can leave your bag here
Don't worry
Hello?
Hello? This is Takasugi speaking
I can't hear you well
Hello?
Are you Takasugi department chief?
Yes  I am
I am Tokuda of our company
It seems that a person from Taiyo Electric is on the train aiming at your bag.
Does it make sense?
Yes
So Please make sure to watch out your bag
Then Shindo of the Yokkaichi Branch will be your guard.
Shindo, right?
Yes, he is young man
He will get on train at Yokkaichi station, so Please corporate with him
I get it
What happened?
It's not big deal
That's good to hear
Look, what is that?
Would you like Snacks, beers, and Tobacco?
Yokkkaichi,Yokkkaichi,Yokkkaichi,Yokkkaichi
Are you Takasugi department chief?
Yes
I'm a shindo from Yokkaichi branch
Nice to meet you
Thank you for your work
Did you get a call from our department chief?
Yes
There is something I want to talk with you
According to the director, the Taiyo electric spy on the train is aiming at your bag.
So Do not be alone
I'll take care of your bag when you go to toilet
And who is the woman with you?
She is just my friend
I'm sorry to ask you but can you trust her?
Do you think she is the spy?
No no..just.. I hear there is a woman on the train
Woman?
Yes
I'm hungry,Shall we go for eat?
Let's go
Oh, Do you carry your bag again?
Yes
I'm sure there are important things in your bag
Kind of
I will go to buffet
Can you take care of this?
Sure
Leave it to you
Yes, Enjoy your meal
We are arriving at Uwana in 3 mins
The exit is on the front door
Uwana
It won't come that easy.
Can you give me it?
Or We can go to police together
You will be arrested for theft
Which way you prefer?
Who are you?
I'm not from Daiinippon Electric
Mr. Kuronuma, Managing Director of Taiyo Electric, scolded me a lot.
Please give my regard to Mr.Kuronuma
Hey you
Do you want to help my work?
I'll pay twice your current salary
What work is it?
A man has posted a house maid job opening in the newspaper.
You work as house maid at his house
And you report me his behavior, custom,habit,secret, something like that
I will be a spy's partner?
It seems little interesting to me
I think it's fun to be thrilled and make money
so you want to try?
Let me see
I think I am about to quit this work
Are you sure you will pay me twice my current salary?
Depends on the job, I will pay 3 times or 4 times
Who is the man?
He is Kuronuma, managing director of Taiyo Electric.
You did stupid, Shindo
You shouldn't have missed the chance
Sorry
And you didn't see his face
What the hell you did?
I'm sorry
You are no use
He said he was scold by me?
Yes he said that
But I have no idea who is he
Yes
There is a call for you.
He never say who is he
He said he has something urgent business with you. What can I do?
It seems he is that man
Connect me
Hello?
Are you Kuronuma, managing director?
I wanted to call you
You want to know my name?
I don't need to tell you
Kuronuma-san
You missed to steel the secret of Dainippon electric
I did something trick
You
How much you need?
Don't say stupid things
I have a grudge against you
I'll tell you the detail later
But you don't have any idea hearing his voice?
What the hell you did
I didn't think it was a fake phone call on the train
That's an excuse!
It ’s a huge loss to our company.
I know..but...
I have already applied for the patent
That is no use
They apply for a patent in a similar way
Hello?  this is president office
Wait, do not hang the phone
He wants to talk to you about that document he has stolen
What?
Record it
Sure
Hello?
I am the Naomune
Who is it?
I'm busy so please talk briefly
Then what do you want?
It ’s the matter you ’re talking about right now.
Don't pretend you don't know
I know you are in president office at 5 floor
See?
Mr. Tomura, the secretary chief, stands in front of you with anxiety.
Don't make a joke
What do you want?
Please calm down, President
I recovered the stolen documents from a Taiyo electric spy
Don't be panicking
If you get excited, your blood pressure will rise.
You made a good idea..electronic thermos
It is good that the water in the pot gets hot or cold with one semiconductor thermoelement.
I will buy it when it is completed
Then, what do you want?
Don't hurry
I'm going to return the document
It's ok if you don't need it
There are many companies that wants the document
Who are you anyway?
Anyway let's meet
That's fine
But just you and me
That's not good
I can't meet strangers alone
Of course, it's ok if you bring Tomura cheif
Ok then let me know the place and time
How about 10
I don't care where it is
I'll meet you at Ashiya at 10:00.
Ashiya? Where about Ashiya?
I will visit your secret lover's place
What?
Is that Ok with you?
I get it
I'll wait for you
And I know you record this
You should erase the last part I said
President This is obviously a threat
Shall I contact the police?
Not yet, I will meet him
But I wonder who is he.. he know about Ashiya's...
You should erase the last part I said
He makes fun of us
President
We are looked down on
Papa
What would you like to give to your customers?
Don't worry about him
Please go away
He is coming
Thanks for talking with me just before
Take your seat
Thanks
Oh you!
Did you remember? Tomura cheif
You are Katayanagi,right?
Yes I am
I was fired from my job three years ago.
hear you've risen to the rank of section chief. Congratulations.
Were you our employee?
Yes, The man in that micro TV spy case
I fired him at that time
President, I had a grudge against the company at that time
I wasn't going to spy
I know it's too late to say it
But Thankfully I became an industrial spy
So What do you want?
Madam, Can you serve me a cold drink?
I can give you this at 3 million yen
3 million yen
You do some weird things.
We had that document stolen by the people at Solar Electric on purpose
Everything was as planned but You broke our plan
You don't know because you're not an engineer so You don't understand what written in the document
We pretend we are the worst
It doesn't help if you get it back
You misunderstood that you became an industrial spy
You are not good enough
This document is the same as garbage.
You are lucky
Because If this document is true you will be arrested
But Why you wanted to meet me?
I wanted to see your face
Are you going home?
Madam
I will come here again
Then I'm leaving
Were you OK?
Don't worry
But I hate violence
He is a sneaky person
We should beat him
Good evening
Oh you!
Why you came back?
I didn't know you asked Yakuza to beat me
Yakuza?
What do you mean?
Don't pretend you don't know.
That's the way you use
You really wanted this document,right?
I give it to you
I have a lot of copies of that document
There are convenient machines these days
Please buy the documents anyway
Wait wait!
So 3 million yen is enough?
I was violent
How about plus 500000 yen?
Ok I give you 3500000 yen
In return,Give me all the documents you copied.
OK?
What did you say?
You should apologize to me.
You used Yakuza
You just want money, right?
You are too selfish
You guys still think I'm an employee of the Dainippon Electric.
I was fired 3 years ago
Ok OK Katayanagi-kun
You won, there were many misunderstanding
We should forget everything
Don't be familiar and say my name
You should call me Katayanagi-san
Do you think so?
I don't force to sell this.
You want this, so I sell
You should beg me to get this
You are right, We are sorry
Please fix your mood.
Please give me it
I'm not going to be mean
Madam
Please give me a piece of paper and a pen
What are you going to do?
I need you to write a note for me.
Please write that you are not threatened by this transaction
Because Mr. Tomura may tell the police
Thank you
Please write it
Please
What should I write?
Let me see...
written oath
About our important documents
Thanks to you, I've recovered it.
I will give you 3.5 million yen as a reward
( Singing)
Lalalalalala
Oh
You have nice figure
I'm shy
Would you like to go to see a movies next Sunday?
Your wife will scold me if I go with you
She won't know
But...
So Let's go
I'm shy
It's ok
I will be in trouble
Well.. I don't know
He's very secretive.
Did you ask his driver?
He's very tight-lipped.
By the way
Does the husband like you?
Well.. I don't know
Try to seduce him
I don't like such a old man
He is still active
But there are stains on his face
His son is more interested in me than The husband
Is that college student?
Yes, he is very nice
He is not smart but
It's like his father's opposition
Anyway Did you take a picture of the visitor?
Yes
It was hard to take the pic
It's a little out of focus
Who is this woman?
I think she is an employee of the company
Does she sometime come?
She has just come once
She came for company's business last time
Do you know her?
Let me know when she comes next time
Um
This is reward for you
Do you know the other party's information?
We are trying to do but...
Currently, Taiyo, Kowa,and We are the top maker
We have to sell a cheap refrigerator to win this competition
You,What is our laboratory doing so far?
Yes
Who are you?
Why you enter without permission/
President, you can use me
Mr. Tomura does not know the information of Taiyo Electric
I can get it for sure
It costs a lot but good shopping
We can't trust you
You can't trust me?
Why?
I got the electronic thermos documents back
3 years ago
You sold our secret
You don't know why I became an industrial Spy
President
I was fooled by Taiyo electric and this company got fired
Taiyo electric broke my future and dream
I wanted money
To take revenge on them
I trained industrial spy for 3 years
I am aiming for Managing Director Kuronuma of Taiyo Electric
I want to beat him
I want revenge on him, and I want him to regret it.
President
I hope you understand
What do you think?
Will you leave it to me?
I'll leave it to you
President
How much you want for this job?
Well.. I want 5 million yen
I want to see Mr.Kuronuma
What can I do for you?
I want to talk to him about some important news about your company's labor union.
Please wait a min
He will meet you
Please take your seat
I'm the Kuronuma.
What can I do for you?
Actually I'm from CIC
CIC?
As you may know,Related to the U.S. military
My mission is to work in the Far East, especially in Japan
And information activities in the Middle East and the Soviet Union.
I got information about your company so I thought I'd let you know
I see.
Thank you for it
Excuse me
Don't worry
So what is it?
Well..last year October
3 people from your company went to Europe,right?
Yes they went for 2 month
Do you know who they met in Berlin then?
in Berlin?
Yes
It ’s a place in West Berlin.
We know they met a key Communist Party executive
I see
As you may know
The activities of the Communist Party's industrial spies are conducted in secret.
I think it will be a big problem for the union
I see
Around the end of this year
We also pay attention to the fact that there are some delicate movements.
Hum
Good
I did good job
Hello?
Oh,Mari
Well, you know what
The woman in the photo you showed me came here
I see
Ok I will go there soon
I was not going to slap you
But I couldn't help but slap you
These are the rewards you received from Mr. Kuronuma.
A number of achievements as your industrial spy
That's good
But
Have you ever wondered how many people were sacrificed because of you?
I'm one of them
But
I finally found out
I found someone who deceived me
It can't be helped if you resent me
But please listen to me
What?
I was just ordered by Kuronuma
I'm like a toy that is controlled by a remote control
Do you think you are not responsible?
I think you are responsible
I didn't meat that I deceived you
I was fired from the company because of you.
I broke my dream of becoming an engineer
I was going to marry my favorite person and have a happy family
Do you think you are not responsible?
I feel sorry for that
Do you think that's enough?
Then what do you want?
I will make you pay for what you've done.
I'm currently working on checking the electronic rate of Taiyo electric
I'm in the same business as you.
I want you to support my business
You want me to work as spy?
Yes
Please betray Kuronuma
That is your reimbursement.
Can you do that?
Immediately after I got fired from the company
My mother got sick and died
I think she was shocked
It was worthwhile for my mother to be an engineer
I feel sorry for her
Did you sleep with guys to do spy?
I don't want to hear about it
Do you have anyone you love?
Kuronuma?
not him
Why you follow him?
Why you ask me that?
You are still young
You still have nice figure
You shouldn't play with that old man
Did you really love me at that time?
Why not
I really mean it
What if I ask you love me?
I can't love you even if I trust you
I will help your business
You can try to trust me
Ok, then I will tell you
I set up a small recorder under the table in the managing room of Taiyo Electric
Your job is to change the tape daily
You trust me if I do that?
Then love me?
I need real love
Because I haven't got loved
I want to quit my spy job
What:"?
Why?
Because..I'll tell you the truth
I fall in love with Mitsuo now
His son?
Yes
Because he is so passionate
But I think carefully
He is only son, right?
If his husband dies, he will inherit all his fortune.
That attract me
He is little crazy but
very nice
I wonder if you can marry him.
He won't approve it, I think
Then we'll elope.
He follows what I say
Are you leaving now?
Yes, I have something to do
Call me sometime
Okay
Did you call me?
Can you call our manager?
Yes
You recorded good
Did you replace it with a new tape?
Yes
Thank you
The manager went to the Hirakata factory
I see
There is a board of directors from 3 o'clock
You have 20 min left
I know
Call Sakuma-kun
Yes
Sakuma is the technical manager,right?
You
What's going on with that patent?
Tell me briefly
Why don't you apply for a patent early?
I'm making some changes now.
changes ?
I thought it would be better to apply individually but collectively
We are narrowing down the scope of patent applications
Hmm..I think it's better
I will apply for a patent after showing it to the managing director tomorrow
Please do it
The documents will be in the vault tomorrow.
Once it gets in there, it ’s impossible to take it anymore.
It's still in the tech department tonight
Yes
Located in the locker of the tech department
That locker is easy to open
But the door is so tight that I can't enter the room
What floor is the tech department
7F
Just above the managing room
Right away
Why you helped me?
Suddenly I wanted to help you
That recording was a trap to lure you
But I couldn't fool you till the end.
What do you mean?
You trapped me
Why you suddenly changed attitude?
I'm a spy so
I'm a spy so I'm not treated as a human
We are so miserable
You sympathized with me
I'm not
Then why?
I don't even know
I couldn't help but doing it
I love you
But
I don't know how much I can trust you
I don't like the thought
I can't help but..
I can't trust you even if I want to
I can't love you?
Reiko
Proof me
I want real love too
What is this proof?
We can't trust each other
Why?
We'll suspect each other.
We have become weird humans
You deserve it
It might be so
I wish if you trust me...
I always worry if you don't trust me for ever
I'm in a stupid situation
Do you think that's okay?
Please don't blame me anymore
What would you like?
Mmm....yes
Brandy
Please prepare
Yes
We met in an unusual place,Mr.Kuronuma
There is something I want to talk with you
You are overconfident in yourself
The world isn't so easy.
What are you talking about?
Katayanagi-kun
You don't have to hide
I know what you work
I hear You have a grudge against me about that incident three years ago
You got what you deserved in that case
I think you are right
But...
I wanted to teach you the hard work of an industrial Spy
Give up your idle hopes.
Think better because you are young
Am I still young?
Don't make me laugh
It's not right for you to speak so nicely.
You treated a serious young man like garbage
You are overconfident
You won't win
Why?
You have no organization
You need money and organization to win as an industrial spy
I can or not
I just want to try it
You shouldn't go against me
In return, I'll buy your grudge with my money.
How much you want?
Don't forget that I will not be bought off and Not affected by intimidation
Excuse me
Oh!
Mistubo was scolded for our relationship
I was so mad that I talked to him about running away from home.
But we don't have money
Do you want to borrow money from me?
Yes if I say in short
You know what
Please, 50000yen is enough
Wonderful
You are so cool
It's ok if I talk to the husband
About us?
You want to be with him,right?
You are so good
In exchange, you'll stay hidden until I can talk to him.
You can go to around Shiharama
That's good. I take this
You should leave tomorrow morning
Is is not good if I leave tonight?
tomorrow morning
Do you have any plans?
I will tell you the details just before departure
Hi, Hello?
Hello?
Are you managing director Kuronuma?
Yes I am
Who are you?
I kidnapped your son
What?
Your company is applying for a patent for an electronic refrigerator, right?
Please tell me the contents
Your son may die if you contact the police or you refused
Don't make fool of me
I'm serious
I'll call you again
I'll visit you next time
Hello?
Oh you...
What? Mitsuo?
He hasn't returned from school yet
I see
Call me as soon as he got home
What? well..nothing
Is the house okay?
I'm in trouble
House maid Mari is missing from morning
What? Is she missing?
Anyway I'll go home and talk with you
Hello?
Please call the technical manager
Hi
Did you call me?
What time does the Patent Office close?
Today is Saturday so it's until noon
Ok
Do you have anything to do?
I'm sorry but
Please write this data with random numbers and make another document
What?
another document...
You can't release that document?
Mitsuo's life is important
Don't be panicking
May be just a threat
We don't know if he was really kidnapped
If we hurry, it will be as he planned
I don't how important is the document but
We have to save Mitsuo's life
Everyone thinks so,right?
You are just panicking
You'd better calm down
I'm serious for it
He could be back home as if nothing had happened.
He's a person who is familiar with the inside of the company
I should have applied for a patent sooner.
So there was no problem
Why we were delay for apply?
It was this afternoon when I received the document.
An express mail?
This is hard
This is a car key
Postmark is Nishinari station
You should take some rest there
Let's go
I think we should contact the police confidentially
This is obviously a commercial kidnapping
But Mitsuo's life is dangerous if it is reported in the media every day.
We can't handle this
I know who does it.
Katayanagi?
Yes
Why don't you accuse him of the police?
He's a man like a wounded beast
He is a very dangerous man
Are you managing director Kuronuma?
Yes I am
I will teach you how to publish the documents
There is a TV transmitter in the company's laboratory.
So please show the documents and broadcast
Does it make sense?
You
Don't make fun of us
Please listen carefully without saying anything extra
Broadcast at exactly 7 o'clock tonight
The frequency is 190
Is that ok with you?
Please make sure it
Will my son be released if we broadcast it?
Yes sure
If you refuse, the newspaper will tell you that your son died in a car accident
You are Katayanagi,right?
I don't know such a name
Hello?
I understand.
Katayanagi is relates to Dainippon Electric
Target to Tomura
If we follow him, we will know something
I'm against for it
Even if we broadcast false documents, they have engineers who can see right through them.
I think Mitsuo's life is the most important
I feel same with him
But it ’s a problem if they get our patent.
It's me
Did you get ready?
Did you adjust the video frequency as instructed?
We are ready for it
Did you prepare fake documents?
Forget stupid idea.
I am an engineer
I can see the distinction between fake and genuine
I won't say it many times, but please do as I say
Or I'll kill Mitsuo-kun
Ok, I promise you
But there is a problem
Cannot transmit at frequency 190
What?
Our laboratory is UHF Broadcasting
UHF?
It's 770 megacycles
There is only that way
It's too late to say it
But
This is the only method currently available for broadcasting
Please accept this
Hello?
This is our last request
Ok, then broadcast at 770 megacycles
Why did you choose UHF broadcasting?
There are many obstacles around here
It can't be helped because of the reception area
Attract him
And catch him
There is only that way
Hello? Tomura has just left home
Good
Follow him without him noticing.
Katayanagi got in the car
He's also got a receiver.
I understand
Where are they going?
Heading to National Highway No. 1
The car model is gray Gloria
I'm sure they go near the patent office
The antenna came out from Tomura's car
I'm sure they are the culprit
Ok, I get it
They have to go through a cement factory to get there
I think they'll pass there around 7 o'clock
Listen to me,Catch the evidence there
The car model is gray Gloria
This is Shindo speaking
They deviated from National Highway No. 1
Yes
They haven't noticed us yet
What?
I think they pass the cement factory at just 7 o'clock
Yes I got it
It's 3 min ago,Director
I know
It's 1 min ago
What shall we do?
Do you want to report real documents?
They are staying in a cement factory
We are ready to catch them
Good,Break their receiver
We are ready
Good,Broadcast
Damn it!
Oh!
(Boxing commentary)
Director
This is Shindo
What happened?
It didn't work
What?
They haven't received yet
What the hell!
Hey
What?
Oh that's it! It's there!
Oh my god, shit!
Obviously a commercial kidnapping
This is valuable research that our company has been conducting in secret.
That's true,This is valuable research
I can't forgive that man
Our company's plan was useless for him alone
Be sure to catch him
And who is the culprit you think?
It's Katayanagi
Shichiro Katayanagi
But there is no proof of that, right?
There is
His voice
Bring the tape
Yes
Are you ready?
Excuse me
Is Togawa out now?
Mr. Togawa has returned to the Ise countryside
Ise?
He got on the limited express at 11:10
Thank you
Why are you going home?
I'm going to think quietly alone
I see
You said to me before that
Your heart won't heal.
Don't leave it alone
Let's make an effort to get happiness together
Will you follow me?
We will be happy for sure
It's too late to say it
You've become stronger than I ever thought possible.
What do you mean?
Even if you say that you do not choose the means
It's not good to threaten with kidnapping
I swear I didn't kidnap him.
I don't mean that
It's not good to take advantage of a parent's love for their child.
It's too despicable, even for an industrial spy.
You are misunderstand me
We are victims
They treat us like animals while they make a profit.
Even if so,It ’s not good to hurt people
You are the one who will eventually hurt
Do you still want to keep fighting?
Yes...well...
I'll try
I see
So I should say good bye
The voice of your threatening phone is recorded here
I replaced it
I thought I'd send this tape to you when I got back to the countryside and felt calm
It's better if I give it to you now
See you
I won't see off you
Good bye
Finish