Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kuro no Chushajo / Black Parking Lot (1963)
I am Mitsugi Tsunonuma, the new president of Maruki Pharmaceutical Co.
Maruki Pharmaceutical has not performed well over the past few years.
This is not only due to the passive and negligent policies of the previous president.
It is because you have lost the will to fight for your respective jobs.
I intend to rebuild Maruki Pharmaceutical into a completely new company.
The personnel changes announced today are targeted at the senior management level.
We intend to continue to move all employees to new workplaces and fundamentally improve the company's structure.
Congratulations, Matsuzaki.
I hear you're the only one staying on.
I don't know if I can glad..
The new president have good eyes.
I'm so relieved.
What can I do for you?
The president wants to see you.
Why would he call me?
Even the former president didn't talk to me.
You'll see if you meet him.
This is Mr. Izumi Izumida of Izumi Chemicals.
I'm Izumida.
Oh you.
Matsuzaki told me all about you.
Have a seat.
I hear you're quite hard worker, Izumida-kun.
No, I owe everything to Mr. Matsuzaki.
I learned a lot about drugs from him, even about starting the factory I'm in now.
I'm the same.
I know nothing about drugs.
I'm calling a special meeting of the stockholders soon.
You'll probably be promoted to the board of directors there.
But I'm not good enough for the position.
The people I brought in only know about the stock market.
So please support me.
By the way, Mr. Izumida.
I'm going to tell you straight out, I think you and our company should merge.
I promise you a considerable post.
I'm sure there's no mistaking your ability that Mr. Matsuzaki sees in you.
I don't want a relationship between a subcontractor and a parent company.
I want you to cooperate with me.
What do you think?
I'm sorry to hear you say that so suddenly.
It's a tiny factory, but it took me five years to get it going.
But the big pharmaceutical companies do so at the expense of their many subcontractors.
I want to clean up the situation and correct the state of the pharmaceutical industry.
What do you think?
Let's merge and live together in harmony.
Mr. President, we'll talk about it later.
Thank you.
What's the matter? Anemia again?
You need to rest.
You get anemia a lot.
Their perform is getting better.
I like the bright performance.
Let's put the dark past behind us.
What happened to the merger after that?
I left it to Matsuzaki.
He is my benefactor.
I wanna stay here.
I don't wanna work in big company.
A big company will dump you at retirement after 36 years of work.
I will do my best.
Hello.
I'm going to be featuring IZUMIYA's new drug in an upcoming feature.
I know it's a secret, but I'm going to ask you specifically today.
I need to see Mr. Hattori.
Okay, but...
I wonder what he'll say.
Hattori
Did you call on me?
I would like you to explain your research on soil fungi
Since your last discovery, emerging organisms have been the subject of worldwide research.
They work great, but they're hard to cultivate.
And there's also the problem of the commercial base.
How do you plan to resolve those issues?
We can't reach a conclusion until we've done clinical trials.
Is there production?
It's no use researching something that has no production.
Can't you be more specific?
You'll note it?
The new president of MARUKI asked me to do some publicity.
I'm not working for Maruki but here.
But Parent company Maruki is the distributor, right?
The world is very picky.
I wish you'd leave me alone before you finish it.
Wait.
I stopped some advance publicity for your new drug.
You have to take good care of that.
Stopped?
I see.
Hattori will be relieved
Please judge the recent merger from MATSUZAKI's point of view.
Don't worry about me.
I worry about Matsuzaki's position.
You are as loyal as ever, aren't you?
I need his support.
I'm not capable of running a factory in the first place.
You've raised a golden egg
You finally got your hands on a new drug.
You are good business man.
If Mr. Matsuzaki hadn't picked me up, I would have been nothing.
But to merge with Maruki is ridiculous.
Maruki has something wrong?
No, not really.
Did you apply for a partial patent on the manufacturing process?
I did as you asked, but no one else can do what we did.
You should be too careful.
You're familiar with the woes of subcontractors.
How's Noriko?
She's female writer.
She works well.
She was also very capable when she was my secretary.
She's the kind of girl who can handle anything.
I think you and her are good match.
It is better for you to remarry.
I know your relationship.
Marriage is troublesome.
Welcome.
Excuse me.
Well...I have to leave now.
Please stay for a while.
I'm going on a business trip tomorrow.
To where?
Osaka sales office.
I have to leave now.
I'm sorry.
See you soon.
Please see him off.
You can leave.
Wait here.
Take your time.
You don't have to worry about anything, do you?
She know how he feels.
Thank you very much.
You stay here.
I don't want to be kicked by a horse.
What do you mean by that?
Anyone who interferes with my factory should be kicked to death by a horse.
I'm leaving.
I'll call you as soon as I get home.
There's someone I'd really like you to meet.
See you soon.
Who?
Hey, old man, let me help you with something.
you don't have to take care of this old car.
Do not touch.
I bought this car with my retirement money after 36 years of work.
I have a little left over to pay for my family's future and to pay off my debts.
It's always been a dream of mine to own a car.
What a waste.
He worked his whole life and this is all he had left.
Your retirement allowance was very small.
Damn it.
He worked seriously unlike you guys.
When it's money you've worked so hard for, no matter how little it costs, it's worth it.
I'm off to college.
Take care of your bag.
Don't worry.
I wouldn't let it go if I was dead.
Come on.
Mr. President, phone call for you.
From Police.
Police?
One of you guys did something.
Hello,I'm Izumuda.
What?
Matsuzaki's dead?
He jumped from a cliff?
He committed suicide?
I can't believe it.
He committed suicide.
But the police were very clear about that.
But why here?
He told me There's someone he'd really like me to meet.
I wonder who is it.
I have no idea.
Mr. Matsuzaki was acting strange that night.
His wife had died.
Matsuzaki, you were all alone, weren't you?
He took care of you and me like we were his own children.
I told him I wanted to become a reporter for a trade newspaper.
He introduced me to The Pharmaceutical Times.
He must have been alone.
I shouldn't have quit my job as secretary.
Forget it.
He won't come back to life.
I feel sorry.
He was an important card for Maruki.
I will take care of you in his place.
See you.
He has just been appointed president and will immediately control the funeral.
That's strange.
What?
The most important person hasn't arrived yet.
Who?
His Mistress.
She works at the bar. They were like married.
I didn't know there was such a person.
Who's her?
Yoshino Natsuko, the president of Yoshino Pharmaceutical.
She's very famous in the industry.
Maruki Company and Yoshino Company are rival companies.
There is something wrong.
I feel sorry for matsuzaki.
Hisako-san's not working?
That's right... she didn't return my calls.
Mr. Matsuzaki is gone.
Women today don't have any sense of duty.
Maybe she was kidnapped?
No way.
She's changed the bar I guess.
Where's her apartment?
Oh I haven't seen her these days.
From when?
She works at night so I didn't really understand.
the phone is ringing.
Please do not enter the room.
You can tell by the number of newspapers how long she's been gone.
She hasn't been home for four days.
It's been 10 days,
She hasn't been back since she dropped Mr. Matsuzaki off at the campsite on the night of the 9th.
That's odd.
I'm sure it has something to do with Mr. Matsuzaki.
Is she Hisako?
I came here today to ask you something.
What is it?
What was the purpose of Matsuzaki-san's business trip to Kansai?
I wouldn't send him on a business trip.
It was a vacation.
Mr. Matsuzaki told me he was going on a business trip.
He must have been in a hurry to lie even to you.
What do you mean by that?
It's hard for you to say.
Matsuzaki-kun was betraying our company.
What?
What the hell did he do?
It's a diversion from the P-strike.
I investigated the collapse of the market price as a guide.
A lot of it was going to a cash-and-carry store in Nihonbashi.
Have a seat.
There's been a mistake.
I trust him.
I wish I could say the same. But it's the truth.
He may have done it in a moment of inattention.
But it could also be that he chose to die because it was about to come to light.
That's absurd.
I trust him.
The president covered up MATSUZAKI's breach of trust.
It should've been public knowledge.
Who are you?
Excuse me.
This is Tsugawa, our new sales manager.
He's MATSUZAKI's successor, a man who worked for me a long time ago.
Please take care of him.
I didn't think he would do something like that.
I really can't believe what he did.
I trust him.
There must be some mistake.
Mr. Matsuzaki himself came to negotiate.
He offered a 40% discount on the sale price, so I jumped at it.
but I was beaten up by my friends for breaking the price.
And Mr. Maruki gave me the stink-eye.
I see.
We are always happy to take care of your company's chemicals.
And you called me here to drink with you?
Stop drinking so much.
it's not good for your health.
Who's her?
She's my Idol.
Let's toast.
I'm leaving.
Bill please.
30000yen.
OK 30000yen.
It's not enough.
Keep the change.
Hey, asshole, don't underestimate me!
Wait.
This is how it was when I got to know Mr. Matsuzaki.
I was the good face of the yakuza.
I was running a violent bar with my ill-gotten gains.
30000yen. not 5000yen.
Understand?
5000 yen is enough for 3 cocktails and 1 beer.
You bastard!
Damn it.
That's enough
Our cocktails, you see, are a specialty.
You'd better pay.
I'm a pharmaceutical guy.
I want to take this red cocktail home and analyze it.
You're a stubborn one, aren't you?
This is not a normal bar.
Do you know the value of your hard-earned money?
why do you go to a bar like this?
Shouldn't you just go straight home every day?
My wife is dead.
But how I spend the money I worked for is none of your business.
Do you know how much worse it is to take the money of those who work without working yourself?
Is that all you wanna say?
Anyone who doesn't understand isn't human.
Damn it.
Stop it.
You're a strange one, aren't you?
I'm not.
Your view of the world is distorted, that's all.
Go to a cheaper bar.
I'll pay you.
I'm sorry for being violent towards you.This is the fee.
Come back when you're ready.
I'll charge you as much as a strip bar.
Mr. Matsuzaki came the next day, too.
He told me in order like he would tell his own son.He always told me to live right.
He changed my life.
I didn't know you were YAKUZA.
I'm not trying to make excuses.
When I was ten years old, there was a terrible air raid.
I lost my parents and my brothers and sisters all at once.
From the next day I had to fend for myself.
The only thing you can do for a kid is match him for shoes or sell newspapers.
Of course. There was no way I could make a living doing that.
Before I knew it, I was on the wrong path.
Matsuzaki-san... It's as if he was your god.
Yes, Mr. Matsuzaki is a god to me.
He's guilty of betrayal.
He didn't commit suicide.
Mr. Matsuzaki must have been killed.
But who killed him and why?
I don't know.
But I'll find out.
By any means necessary.
The person Mr. Matsuzaki wanted you to meet... I wonder who.
Probably someone connected to our business.
I'm sure they'll get back to us.
Are you Mr. Hattori of IZUMI Chemicals?
We'd like to take that bag.
Think about it.
Your bag is important, but your body is more important.
Don't act like that.
We don't ask for free money.
We will pay you what's in it and the equivalent amount.
Boss, we haven't received any orders from Maruki recently.
They've been so busy that they haven't decided on a new company policy.
I wanna a tea.
Maybe the terms of the deal went bad after Mr. Matsuzaki's death.
let's say that's not the case
There's a new drug for HATTORI.
I'm looking forward to it.
All the big companies will be coming to buy it.
As long as we have a sales network, we can be promoted from a subcontractor too.
It's a new drug that's sure to revolutionize the medical community.
If we could invent something like this in other industries, we could become a major manufacturer in a single change.
we shouldn't be greedy.
Sell the new drug through Maruki's sales network.
That's all right.
What if another company can offer better conditions than Maruki?
Izumi Chemical has come this far thanks to Maruki.
We mustn't forget that.
It's thanks to Mr. Matsuzaki.
And now Mr. Matsuzaki is gone.
Yoshino Pharmaceutical Company is Maruki's rival company.
Yoshino.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with the bag?
I was just leaving the college gate when Someone took my bag.
Someone took?
Bag?
What are you gonna do?
We'll be fine.
Everything we need is in here.
Don't be afraid... you're shortening my life span.
Take a cab next time!
Here is a table of analysis of new drug data from each company
I want results from the institute.
I get it.
I haven't heard anything on Maruki since then.
There doesn't seem to be any significant activity, so I have no idea what's going on.
You should be more careful.
How are sales of new drugs?
Sales have increased by more than 10% due to the effect of TV commercials.
You have a visitor from Izumi pharmaceutical.
Ok get him here.
You guys leave.
You're finally here.
I've been waiting for you to come.
I'm Izumida.
Nice to meet you.
Please, have a seat.
We met at the funeral.
How did you know Mr. Matsuzaki?
Is it so strange that I went to his funeral?
You said you were expecting me.
How did you know I was coming?
I just had a hunch.
Don't make fun of me.
By the way, it's unthinkable that Mr. Matsuzaki would kill himself.
That's what I thought too, that's why I came here.
You sound as if you think I killed Mr. Matsuzaki.
Before Mr. Matsuzaki died, he said he had someone he wanted me to meet.
By any chance..
Me?
I can't say but If you know something, I'd like to hear it.
When you ask someone for something, you have to create a little more of a mood before you ask.
I'm not in the mood for that.
I'm a poor man with no spare time.
You make it sound like I'm the one with all the free time in the world.
I know you are busy too.
Anyway, I'm sure you know more about Mr. Matsuzaki than I do.
I see.
Then there's nothing more I can tell you.
Wait.
You have a short temper.
I forgot to ask you one more thing.
Do you have any idea who targeted our HATTORI bags?
Who's Hattori?
Sorry to bother you.
I've decided to withdraw the merger proposal.
Matsuzaki said he wanted to take care of IZUMI PHARMACEUTICALS as an independent subcontractor.
I can't go against the will of Buddha.
I'm relieved to hear that.
It hurts worse than being dumped by the woman I fell in love with.
Izumida.
I want you and your new drug in production right away.
That's not possible yet.
We've barely finished animal testing and we're about to start clinical trials.
It's just a matter of getting the data together and applying for government approval.
I'll handle the backstabbing.
Anyway, I'd like you to start production.
I'll give you all the money you need.
Mr. President, back channels have no place in the manufacture and sale of a new drug.
New drugs are a matter of life and death.
You don't have to know anything about drugs.
You know that at least.
You're rude.
I know.
I'm saying that because of the production.
That's impossible.
Izumida, I heard you met Yoshino's female president.
Don't be so surprised.
I won't bring a new drug to Yoshino.
I'm indebted to Mr. Maruki.
I'm sorry for your loss, Mr. Matsuzaki.
I believe you.
If you feel that strongly about it...
I suggest you take me up on my offer.
Why you are so in hurry?
In order to rebuild MARUKI, we must first gain public attention and trust.
The only way to do that is with a new antibiotic drug.
Our boss is asking you to do it.
Say yes.
No, sir.
If I'm not careful, I could jeopardize the new drug.
I think we should treat each other with more respect.
Bring the booze.
We, the subcontractors, are controlled by the parent company.
I hope they don't anything bad on us.
But it's impossible to make.
Don't get so excited.
I've already said no.
Hi,IZUMI Pharmaceuticals
Yes he's here.
It's from the Maruki sales manager.
This is Izumida. Thank you for your help last night.
Add 100,000 dozen capsules of vitamins?
But you're told sales of those are flat?
Ok We'll manage it.
As you listened,Get us the materials.
I'm afraid we're overproducing capsules.
I just turned down President's request.
I can't turn down this order.
Who's the boss?
Me.
I'm here to pick you up.
Me?
Come in.
I know you want to hear something from me.
We can talk here.
You said you don't think Matsuzaki-san committed suicide.
Yes.
Why do you think so?
I had guided him to the cliff where Mr. Matsuzaki died.
What?
It was long ago.
We went there together a couple of times.
What for?
I showed him the mountains.
He can get soil fungus like a roar.
So soil fungus is my company's new drug's?
Yes, I discovered it and bought the rights to the mountain.
And I don't even have to cultivate it.
It's worth it on a commercial basis.
There were the prospect of mass production.
If you're willing to let me sell the new drug to you.
I'd be happy to supply you with the soil fungus.
And now that Matsuzaki-san is gone.
You don't have to be obliging to Maruki, do you?
Mr. Matsuzaki had half a mind to do it.
Mr. Matsuzaki has not told me anything.
He worked for Maruki so.
But he had finally made up your mind.
Can you prove it?
Mr. Matsuzaki called me the day before he left.
He said We'll discuss it together when I get back.
You are the one who Matsuzaki said.
Yeah, we should work together.
Mr. Matsuzaki had a mind to do it too.
I have a good opinion of you.
I'm willing to help in any way I can.
I don't like to accept help from women.
Women are only for marriage or fun.
I'm willing to be your plaything, but only for tonight.
We'll talk about the new drug after we find out who killed Mr. Matsuzaki.
There's still some trick up.
Where is the item?
I gave you.
P-strike.
Matsuzaki of MARUKI brought this to my attention.
What the hell is your connection to Mr. Matsuzaki?
I saved his life.
But now Matsuzaki is dead and I can't get my share.
I already paid.
Don't be lying.
Matsuzaki didn't get paid.
Are you here to blackmail me?
I'm here to get paid.
Don't be lying.
Matsuzaki didn't bring P-strike.
If you don't leave quickly, I'll call the police.
Tell me who brought?
Are you involved in the murder of Mr. Matsuzaki?
Dad, what did you buy?
Electric Car for you.
What's mine?
Let's open at house.
I can't wait.
What's mine?
You are heavy.
I can't wait.
I need to talk to you.
You guys go home first.
I need to talk to him.
Let's go.
You were the one who diverted the P-strike, weren't you?
What?
I can't believe you're saying this.
The wholesaler's owner spoke out.
So it was you who framed Mr. Matsuzaki?
Don't make false accusations.
You set it up so that Mr. Matsuzaki would commit suicide after he was found out to be P-strike.
You'd better tell me the truth or things will get worse.
Did the boss ask you to do it?
No, that's not true.
I did it on my own.
I know You can't do it.
I don't need to hear it directly from you.
I think I'm starting to get the general idea.
Tsugawa
I'm leaving quietly for the sake of your beautiful children.
There was a house breaker?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I'm the one who encouraged you to stay up late drinking.
I said we could have a drink in my office.
I got really drunk and fell asleep, I don't remember.
I don't think we'll have to worry about that.
Get back work.
Stolen data is no big deal.
Why?
Real data is here.
Here it is.
We'll be fine.
You're great.
Sir, there's a phone call for you.
Please answer for me.
It's a woman. She needs to talk to you.
Hello. This is Mr. Izumida.
who?
Hisako?
Where have you been?
Mr. Matsuzaki told me to hide myself if anything should happen to him.
I'm being targeted right now.
I don't know who it is, but I'm sure.
Please come help me.
I'm hiding in a car in the Nitto parking lot.
It's a Crown, black, parked in G-21, basement level 2.
Black Crown, license plate 1676.
Ok I'll get there soon.
I'm going.
Your head was stony, the doctor said.
The doctor said if you'd had a normal head, you'd have had a skull cavity or something.
Somebody didn't want me around, so they did it.
The police checked the license plate, and it turned out to be a forgery.
As expected, Maruki, the company's manager Tsugawa is the suspect?
He's nothing but just a slave for Kakunuma.
I need to investigate him just in case.
There's something I can do?
I'll have you check around Tsugawa and Kakunuma.
And shoes.
Shoes?
They're an odd pair of black and white shoes.
When I got hit and fell down, I caught a glimpse of it.
The voice on the phone was really HISAKO's.
I'm pretty sure that voice is HISAKO's.
Anyway, she's the key.
But she could have been killed by now.
It's been ages.
Where's Director Tsugawa?
He's not here.
I'd like to see him.
He suddenly went on a business trip.
He left without telling me where he was going.
Why don't you have a seat?
He's on the run because of an article he put in our paper.
But thanks to you, I'll be able to relax.
Why don't you go ahead and take your time?
You must miss your old workplace.
Yeah.
Let me ask you, TSUGAWA have unusual black and white shoes?
He always seems to wear black shoes.
What's wrong?
Where's Kakunuma?
He just left.
Sorry I made you wait.
The first step for a new drug is a success.
But what do you think Izumi Pharmaceutical Company will do?
I will force them to cooperate.
We’re already ready.
How about yours?
In any case, we are making an effort because there are great interests involved.
We are the reseller.
When will the decision be made?
I can't keep it up for much longer. Well, a few more weeks is the best I can do.
If we don't have the money by then, we'll fall behind.
Ok let's do it.
You take care of the legal issues.
I'm hungry. Let's order some food.
The man in the president's seat at Maruki's... is that Mr. Kato?
No.
They are Mr. Akazawa and Mr. Inoue.
Oh I see.
Thank you very much.
Inoue-san's his secretary.
Raitaro Inuzuka.
Inuzuka, that political mastermind?
I showed him the CEO's office once at work.
Coffee.
Did you check out what I was talking about?
I felt like I was spying on him.
Is it true that Mr. Matsuzaki's death had something to do with the company's internal affairs?
Yeah.
So tell me.
I'm not sure but
He's been holding back on his shipments and collecting a lot of cash.
He's de-stocked his warehouse, and he's got a bank loan.
He's supposed to be investing in equipment and beefing up sales.
He hasn't touched anything.
That's strange.
But thank you.
Do you want something to eat?
No, thank you.
Let's split the bill.
I feel like I'm being bought out.
I'm retracting this article.
If you don't cut ties with Maruki while you still can, you won't be able to retract it.
Or are you confident you can get it out in time for next week's launch?
I don't think I have to answer to you.
There's no way they'll get it out in time.
And the new drug is losing all credibility.
Even Izumi Pharmaceutical may go bankrupt.
I can't let the company go bankrupt.
The people who work at our company are the kind of people the world doesn't accept.
They need us.
Then why not even more so?
I'll take full responsibility for this.
I told you we'd discuss it after I've done with Mr. Matsuzaki case.
I don't care if it's too late.
Our new drug was made possible thanks to Mr. Matsuzaki.
I'm not willing to make a deal before I know who did it.
You're surprisingly stubborn.
And there's another reason.
Hattori was attacked the other day, and his lab was broken into.
It's possible you gave the order.
Don't be silly.
I'm making an honest offer.
Maruki didn't beat you up and put you in the hospital
And then he announced the launch of a new drug.
It could be.
The point is, I don't trust you people at all.
I can't take a rest.
Where the CEOs of big companies sleep for a month.
I get up and go to work in a day.
Assuming it goes on sale next week, as Maruki announced.
I'm sure you'll have the data from the clinical trials.
We're not at that stage yet.
That's weird.
You don't even have production data?
The clinical trials were done at Kanto University, right?
Why haven't you launched your groundbreaking new drug yet?
We haven't even applied for a manufacturing license yet.
I cannot take responsibility for Mr. Kakunuma's statements.
President Kakunuma's mouth was quite willing to go on.
Are you willing to offend Maruki?
Are your new drug announcements a lie?
You will lose Maruki's trust.
Stop it.
The president is in the hospital.
Welcome back.
Is everything all right,?
Are you alright?
I got out of the hospital on my own.
You guys met with newspaper reporters, right?
Did you read the newspaper?
Yoshino's boss came to the hospital and showed it to me.
She's too nice.
Are you alright?
So so.
Yoshida,give me painkillers.
They don't give a shit about my body.
How was the newspaper reporters?
They are pushy.
Maruki's president sent him.
What did you tell?
I denied everything Maruki said.
I hope it doesn't become a problem later.
I told the truth.
If I admit to making the announcement, we'll have to start production tomorrow.
That's impossible.
That's all right.
No one will blame you.
Thanks.
Welcome back.
I worry what Maruki will act.
Don't worry.
We have new drugs.
We'll win.
I strongly suspect that Maruki's boss, Kakunuma, killed Matsuzaki-san.
Why did he kill him?
I'm sure it has something to do with the new drug.
Big news!
What?
Maruki won't take back 100,000 dozen capsules.
Sales of vitamins in general have hit a plateau.
So we're going to have to cut back on production and switch to other products.
It can't be helped.
I told you.
The production value of vitamins is nothing new.
You're gonna make us make it, and don't take it back, we're gonna go bankrupt.
I wasn't optimistic enough.
Anyway, We made it to your order.
Please pay.
I can't pay for goods that are no longer needed.
The subcontractor will go bankrupt if they do.
Not this time, I don't agree.
Up to you.
We have many subcontractors.
I see.
What happened to the responsibility of dodging the P-strike diversion to Mr. Matsuzaki?
It was the wholesaler's mistake.
It's not TSUGAWA's fault either.
I'm sorry for Matsuzaki.
Is it just a matter of misunderstanding?
That won't help Mr. Matsuzaki, will it?
I'm sorry .
I've been very busy and I don't know anything about medicine.
By the way, I'm willing to pay for the damage to the capsule.
I'd like to see some sincerity on your part.
I've always been sincere with you, Mr. Maruki.
What does it mean to say that your employees denied my announcement in its entirety?
That made it difficult for me to control newspaper articles.
Because you made a rash announcement without consulting me.
While I was in the hospital for a beating.
I'm very sorry you got hurt.
It's ridiculous to think that a subcontractor is dragging its parent company down.
Back to the story before.
If Mr. Matsuzaki's diversion of P-strikes is innocent.
I've lost the reason for Mr. Matsuzaki's suicide.
It is a favor to the president to offer to bear the damage.
You'd be wise to go along with the president's policy on new drugs.
Either way, IZUMI Chemicals is a dead end
But we will survive at any cost.
Since I came all the way from Kansai, I can't go home without doing some work.
We'll pay you for the dishonored portion sooner or later, I promise.
Please leave today.
I can't.
Please do something anyway.
Terajima.
In the meantime, we'll have to arrange to unload the stock at a fraction of the cost.
But if you do that, it'll hurt our order.
No choice.
We're paying you.
You'll have to come back tomorrow.
Is it true? Then I'll come back tomorrow.
Why don't we take this opportunity to get away from MARUKI?
Wait a while.
I have an idea.
What are you going to do?
We'd like to hear.
The issue of the new drug will have to wait until we find out who killed Mr. Matsuzaki.
That's different from this.
The new drug is a bait to attract the murderer.
Bait?
Mr. Matsuzaki was murdered because of the new drug problem.
That's why we need a new drug to uncover the identity of the culprit.
Are you going to use the new drug as a tool to find the culprit?
What?
Do you really care what happens to the credibility of the new drug as long as the culprit is caught?
That's not what I'm saying.
It's the police's job to find the murderer.
Mr. Matsuzaki was worried about our new drug when he was about to be killed.
But that doesn't mean we can't do our research in this condition.
This isn't a big company lab.
I don't know how you've made it this far with such guts.
We've been through a lot, and we want to take good care of our new drug.
I know.
You don't understand.
You're more interested in stale dead people than new drugs.
Stupid.
Say that again.
Would you be okay with IZUMI PHARMACEUTICAL going out of business as long as it makes you feel better?
Don't you care about the lives of the people who work here?
Hattori.
Wait,Hattori.
He didn't mean that he hit you.
Where are you going?
University Hospital.
I'll drive you there.
Who knows who'll come after your bag again?
I just bought a new car, a little deluxe.
I'll bring the car around.
I'm gonna go call my wife.
I left her stomach pills on the dresser.
I'm sure she's looking for them.
Mr. Hattori, you're just in time.
I've been meaning to talk to you.
The university's research facilities are public property.
Your research is for profit.
The only reason we are cooperating with you when we would normally refuse is because I believe that your new drug has the potential to revolutionize the medical community.
I'm well aware of that.
So I ask you, what the hell is Maruki' announcement?
They're releasing a new drug next week, and it's insane.
We no longer corporate with you.
Wait a minute.
If the university shuts us down, all our work will be nothing.
Anyway, I can't be responsible for you anymore.
You can go home.
Excuse me.
Are you Hattori of IZUMI CHEMICALS?
Yes.
I'm the president of Yoshino Pharmaceuticals.
I have something to show you, and I won't take up too much of your time.
What do you think?
Super great.
Better than a college lab.
It's my policy to invest 3% of the company's profits in this place.
But for all that, we're wasting 100 million yen every year because we're not getting results.
Mr. Izumida, when he finds out that the university has been taken away from him, what kind of measures will he take?
He's more interested in finding the culprit than new drugs.
He's a brilliant man, but his way of thinking is a little strange.
People today should be thinking about doing good research and making as much money as possible, instead of playing dumb.
I don't know what to do anymore.
You look tired.
Don't you think you should take a rest for a while?
Why don't you do it tomorrow?
I'll have to look into tomorrow's collections.
I'm sorry.
I've put you through a lot of trouble.
I hope we can hold out until the problem with the new drug is solved.
Hattori is late.
He's always home by the evening.
I said too much during the day.
He's a small man.
Hattori is late.
I'll answer.
Hello, IZUMI Pharmaceuticals.
Hattori... What's wrong?
where are you?
I need holidays for a few days.
What?
Why don't you just tell me in person?
Hey, Hattori.
I need to cool off.
Don't ask me anything now.
I'm tired.
Let's meet up and talk.
Come back soon. where are you?
Hello,Hello.
This is 961-8611.
Where did that call come from?
Hold on.
From Tokyuu dai.
I see.
What's with him all of a sudden?
It's funny.
He's not a selfish man.
Maybe he was forced..
He's involved in a new drug.
He act strange.
Someone must have kidnapped him.
I'm sure Maruki's boss did it.
What the hell are you doing here?
You know why I'm here.
Go home.
We are at work.
Mr. Nakazawa, our legal counsel, and that's Mr. Inoue, if I'm not mistaken.
You're rude.
Who are you?
Come with me.
What can I do for you?
Please give me back Hattori.
What?
What happened to Hattori?
You are the only one who can kidnap him.
He was kidnapped?
If anything should happen to Hattori... I’ll beat you.
You think I'd do something like stomp out a new drug?
If it's true that he was abducted, then I'm the one who's not gonna shut up.
It's your fault.
What did you do?
Even if it's not a kidnapping, even if it's a disappearance, you're the cause of it.
He's collateral damage from an insane production announcement.
You still think I'm guilty?
Of course I do.
Or do you have proof that you don't?
OK.
I'll cancel the release announcement to prove my innocence.
When?
I'll get the press together at headquarters tomorrow.
If you really cancel the production announcement tomorrow. I'll believe you.
Where's Madam?
Upstairs.
I see.
Who's that?
Mr. Tachibana.
What's he doing?
YAKUZA, right?
He comes to see me sometimes at Madam.
Is this Izumi Chemicals?
Terajima?
Is Izumida there?
I promised him, but he hasn't come yet.
Mr. Hattori is missing?
I wonder what happened to him.
Tell him to come over right away.
Hold on.
They drive too fast.
Don't miss them.
Wait here.
OK.
Let me ask you something.
What is it?
What are you two doing here?
Visiting.
Who?
If you need me, you can come back tomorrow.
I need to see him.
It's important.
Don't worry.
They are ok.
You're HISAKO, right?
Why did she come here?
She was brought here by the person who just came in.
They say she's a relative.
They won't tell us what happened, so we don't know what to do.
Do you remember Mr. Matsuzaki?
She's delirious.
She must have had a terrible shock.
Will she get better?
I don't know.
She'll have to take our time to find out.
Come with me.
Driver!
What’s wrong?
I'm sorry to be leaving Maruki Pharmaceuticals.
I was prepared to devote my entire life to this business.
I also had faith.
I announced the production of a breakthrough emerging material, one that I hoped would benefit society as soon as possible.
But it was not yet the right time to announce it.
I was new to the pharmaceutical industry, and I was naive.
But now that I'm retracting the announcement, I can't make any excuses.
To those of you who have taken an interest in this matter.
I take full responsibility for betraying the shareholders' cabinet.
You're avoiding your responsibility by quitting.
Did you lie about the new drug?
If you're going to retire, you're going to have to solve the new drug problem.
I'm afraid there was insufficient communication with Izumi Pharmaceutical regarding the new drug.
Ask Mr. Izumida here for details.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Say definitely.
When is the new drug available?
Tell us the truth.
It's ready.
But it's going to take some time, so I won't announce it.
Why did you keep Maruki's announcement quiet?
I didn't.
They finally canceled it today.
You and Kakunuma have been planning this and stalling until today, haven't you?
Don't hide.
That's outrageous!
Show your data.
You are irresponsible.
Releasing the data would be like giving away the rights to a new drug.
If a big company starts production, our facilities won't be able to keep up.
The first one to release a new drug is the winner.
Kakunuma was running away.
Maruki didn't care about the new drug itself.
They used Maruki's stock price as a bargaining chip.
Kakunuma dumped all his shares at the highest price he could find.
He made hundreds of millions of yen.
That was the plan from the moment he took over Maruki.
Mr. Matsuzaki saw through their scheme and tried to sell our new drug to YOSHINO.
If another company gets the new drug, their plan will be ruined.
That's why they killed Mr. Matsuzaki.
Hattori.
You are saved
I'm sorry to be so selfish.
I wonder what happened to the new drug.
I saw KAKUNUMA's retirement announcement in the newspaper.
Where have you been?
I suddenly needed some country air.
I'm relieved.
Mr. President, what are you going to do now?
What do you mean?
We'd rather take our new drug data to YOSHINO than release it to the public.
Yoshino.
I'm sure she'll take good care of our new drug.
She'll take good care of our company.
Actually, I ran into her by chance and asked her for advice.
I didn't leak any data on the new drug.
She doesn't care about the data.
She thought she could damage her business rival Marquis by making Hattori disappear.
But Yoshino was deceived by Maruki, just like us.
But we can trust Yoshino. I hate her but
I agree.
Let's do it.
Mr. President... now's our chance.
You all feel the same way?
If that's everyone's opinion, then I have no choice.
I'm starting to think Yoshino is on our side.
But I just need a little time first.
Finding Matsuzaki's killer
How?
Hisako is the key.
I'll make a trap.
Call Yasuo,Kenji etc.
I found Hisako.
Oh you are here.
Sorry I was sleeping.
What's wrong with Hisako?
She's in a mental hospital.
She's become crazy.
I didn't know that.
But how did you find her?
By chance.
Maybe Mr. Matsuzaki pulled her in.
No way.
She's the mistress of my benefactor.
I'm gonna treat what's wrong with her.
You're so stubborn.
But That's what I love about you.
OK I can help you.
I'm so impressed with your spirit.
Thank you.
They're going to move her to a hospital with better facilities than the one she's in now, and she'll be fine.
I'll have the procedure done today.
This is great view.
Thanks to this fictitious Marquis stock run-up.
That's how I got all this land.
Dozens of times more money in the future.
I can't stop laughing.
I really appreciate you.
But you've crossed a very dangerous road.
This time, I was worried.
It can't be helped.
It's not like after the war.
It's hard to do drastic work when the world is at peace.
Urgent business?
IZUMIDA came to us after you left our apartment.
He found a place for HISAKO.
He's going to move her to another mental hospital.
Ask someone to kill Hisako.
Ask your boyfriend.
Who the hell would come to kill that patient?
Excuse me, sir. Just a few more seconds.
It's late. he might be relieved.
I'm sure they'll come.
Coming.
He came from the gate.
Be quiet.
Oh you.
Door is open.
Can you come here?
Why don't you just come in here?
Come in.
I can't afford to.
I found the rest of the money from Matsuzaki's murder.
I've brought it.
I'll give it to you, but you're gonna have to give me your hand.
Take your hands off .
Shut up.
I'm gonna strangle her.
I'll be there.
You killed Matsuzaki.
No.
How did you kill him?
Tell me.
Hisako invited her to the cliff.
Then I pushed him.
I was just asked.
Sorry.
You scam killed Matsuzaki.
You don't have to do that.
This is first day to work here so.
Here's better than Maruki'S office.
But I really admire your skill, sir.
Don't be surprised by this
There's still a long way to go.
I must do my best so that I can report well to you in the future.
Here's nice.
Why you are here?
I'm here to celebrate.
It's wonderful to see you start a new business after destroying Maruki.
I've been under house arrest with the intention of never going out in the world again.
But people around here won't leave me alone.
I'm sorry to say this but I have to stop your weird acting.
You are rude.
Get out.
This guy came here to say he's a sore loser.
Don't worry.
Well then, Mr. Tsunonuma... shall we listen to my sore loser speech?
You asked Hisako to the cliff.
You forced Hisako to mimic psychosis to protect your secret.
I'm the only one who retained Matsuzaki because of his ability.
I even recommended him for the board.
Why would I kill him?
You took over Maruki with the intention of eating it up from the start.
You wanted to bring Mr. Matsuzaki on board so that you could take advantage of our new drug and inflate your stock.
But Mr. Matsuzaki saw through your plan and approached Yoshino Seiyaku.
When you learned of this from Hisako's report, you killed Matsuzaki out of fear that your plan would be foiled.
I know who you asked.
Tachibana,right?
You're young.
I don't mean to be rude.
You were a YAKUZA, after all.
What you say is not a reasonable opinion.
YAKUZA is that bad?
It's better than being a murderer like you.
Murderer?
I'll laugh at you for the rest of my life.
You won't be laughing anymore.
I'll pull the curtain back on your play.
Get out.
What if I turn Tachibana over to the police?
There's nothing I can do.
I don't know this Tachibana guy at all.
He probably doesn't know me either.
Mr. Kakunuma, what is the name of this person?
I don't know.
I'll tell everything.
I'll betray you this time.
She's a madwoman, a lunatic.
You're the one who made me do crazy things.
You lured me out to kill Mr. Matsuzaki.
You're the one who wanted Tachibana to kill me.
Idiot.
You're giving up.
Mr.KAKUNUMA President.
Thank you very much for the other day.
Welcome.
It's rare to see you two together today.
I finally found the man who killed Mr. Matsuzaki.
I heard about it on the news earlier.
Everything's been cleared up now.
I did what I promised.
We leave the sales of new drugs to you!
We would like to be of service to you.
Mr. Izumi, you're forgetting something.
I've heard that you have a policy of avoiding business relationships with women.
I've decided not to consider you a woman.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
You can't?
You say you don't want the new medicine.
That's Izumida-san. you are quick to guess.
You said exactly what I couldn't say.
And it seems Izumi Drug's business isn't good either.
So I can't.
I see.
Never mind.
Many companies are interested in our new drug.
Let's leave.
Wait.
We've already talked about this.
I went out of my way to come and see this for you.
This is my new drug.
We developed this.
When did you make this?
This research can't be done by anyone else.
Yoshino's technical staff is very good.
You stole it!
I'll leave it to your imagination.
Damn it.
Stop it.
She's ahead of us.
We lost.
I like your attitude.
Ms. Izumi, if you accept me as a woman, I can give IZUMI Chemicals a job.
I decline.
I don't care if you come crying to me later.
That's a sore loser look on your face.
It's not so you.
There's one thing I want to make sure of.
What is it?
Did you steal all of Hattori's data on the manufacturing process for the new drug?
It does not mean I stole it.
So the soil fungus is bio-intermediated in a liquid. That's exactly the same thing.
Yes that's it.
But it's an original invention of our laboratory.
You think so?
It's up to you to make it.
But only if you know you're infringing on a patent.
What does that mean?
That we own the patents on those parts.
I'm just informing you again.
When did you take it?
A long time ago.
Mr. Matsuzaki gave me some advice.
Yoshino's new drug is against the patent law unless we change the culture equipment.
It's absolutely impossible to change it.
It's the pivotal point of my invention.
we won a come-from-behind victory.
I'm happy to discuss patent fees with you.
But 50% of the profits from the new drug.
We may want more than that.
This is thanks to Mr. Matsuzaki's advice.
It was close.
Mr. Matsuzaki saved us.
I'm sorry.
I was rude to you the other day.
I'm sorry I hit you.
Tajima!
You were the spy!
Leave him alone!
Forget that guy.
Let's go.
I guess everyone here has a life of their own.
they all live desperately.
A lot of people give up.
But you won.
Tomorrow is a new battle.
You won't lose.
But I'm starving.
I'll treat you a steak
I have never had a woman treat me to food.
But you have no money.
It can't be helped.
Thank you.
If we can establish a sales network for the new drug, there will be lots of money coming in.
Will you follow me for the rest of your life?
I will.
THE END