Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen
Good morning
Welcome
Thank you for visiting our store while you are busy.
Today is the opening special sale!
Short-sleeved T-shirts are discounted to 100 yen instead of 1500 yen
Original blouse 1500 yen will be discounted to 100 yen
Black trademark
Domestic rayon is a good idea
It's just the letter i and n are different.
Trademark design is the same as ours
Yes
This is clearly a conscious counterfeit using our credit,Boss
Um
Ide-kun
Were there many shirts with this fake trademark?
Out of the ten dozen items that that store purchased, only three have counterfeit marks.
But they're making these labels, so I think we're going to see more counterfeiting
Boss
This will be our credit problem
Eventually we may go bankrupt
Um
But to find the culprit of this counterfeit label
We have to find out the supplier
Yes
For the time being, the supplier...
I went to a cash wholesaler called Marusho near Yokoyama Town
The subcontract manufacturer of this shirt is a new company of Owari Ichinomiya
They seem to be struggling with cash flow these days
Then the manufacturer is suspicious
Or it could be a wholesaler dealing with it.
I also checked the wholesaler
The wholesaler is in Nagoya
Um
Ide-kun
I know it's a lot to ask, but can you please go to Nagoya and find out what's really going on?
Yes
You're going into detail.
You've got three days to figure it out.
Yes
I'm going now
What's the matter?
You are Mr. Ide from International Rayon, right?
Yes
Uww!
Ah, Sugino-san
It seems that the criminal who killed Mr. Ide self-confessed
I know it
Come in
What's the matter?
Yes
Actually, I just found out at the cash wholesaler, Marusho.
The fake label was depressed by a man named Kakiuchi, a broker in Osaka.
So I go to Osaka and look up the man named Kakiuchi.
So we can see the truth about the counterfeit label and the true criminal who killed Mr. Ide.
You read the newspaper,right?
The criminal who killed Mr. Ide says he was already caught and confessed to aim for his wallet.
Don't get confused
No...This confession is an excuse
His target was Ms. Ide's treasured notebook.
Our trade secret was written in the notebook
I think he was just targeted by a thief
Simply put, he was unlucky.
Then you don't think that Mr. Ichigo was a line of duty?
The business trip order I issued was to Nagoya
Not to Osaka
So you are going to treat Mr. Ide's death as an accidental death?
Sugino-kun
Boss
Mr. Ide noticed something in Nagoya and went to Osaka to investigate.
That would mean he was killed in the line of duty.
It might be so
But we have work rules
I can't understand why he didn't contact me
I'm sorry for that now
I see
Boss
Then please allow me to be absent from illness for half a month
What do you do when you are absent?
I go to Osaka
Sugino-kun
Don't say such a selfish thing
We decided to leave the fake label to the police
I can't give you permission
I want to take paid vacation
How many days?
All five days I have
Five days?
Fair enough
But I won't accept any more absences.
I know that
Sister,I hate the director's guts.
He is not motivated
He is retired in two years
He is now competing for an executive position with the promotion manager
So Ide's case
He doesn't want Mr. Ide's death to be a line of duty on a business trip
They have to pay for the line of duty
He'll be accused of sending him on a dangerous business trip.
I see
You're not dangerous?
Mr. Ide has a wife and three children
I don't think it's a good idea for those four to put up with only a small amount of processing money without getting martyrdom pay.
So I go to Osaka to find out the truth
I'm sorry, but I need to borrow some money. I'm on a payday loan.
We don't have money either because we paid the wholesaler
30,000 yen or 20,000 yen is fine
It ’s expensive to stay at an inn, right?
Don't worry about that
My friend from college, JINGO, is in Osaka, so I'll be staying there. He work for textile wholesaler
Ok..so...20000yen is fine?
Thank you
OSAKA
Excuse me, where is the president?
Oh! you!... a top employee of a top company.
I see.
Counterfeit International Rayon labels....
Looks interesting
I will lend you wisdom
I will not lend you money and accommodation
Can I get a cigarette?
Yes you can.
It's a catio
I like this cheap cigarette,Ikoi
Did you use that rayon for the shirt with this label?
What do you mean?
Actually
Fujikane Shoji, an affiliate of your company near here
Around this spring, that rayon original fabric worth 20 million yen
Was suspected of capture fraud
I see
They are in the process of investigating it with the police
My guess is that it's not fraud, but diversion.
So Fujikane Shoji made fake shirts with the original fabric?
Well..I do not understand
But you'd better do your research.
The man responsible for the distribution of the raw materials is a small man named Shoji.
He may tell the truth
Shoji is the chief,right?
But you are familiar with Fujigane Shoji
What?
Of course
That company is our competitor
I am hiring a consultant
I'm familiar with that company
I see
Oh yeah
Would you like to introduce the consultant if you want to know more details?
He is a strange person but has a lot of information
Thanks.
I may ask you later
Excuse me
Oh Yuki-san.
I was talking about your dad right now
I see
Yes this month's commission fee
Thank you
Thank you for your work
Excuse me
Sugino,Where do you start your research?
Well...First of all, I will investigate from Fujigane Shoji
Then I should check the printer of this label
Really? I appreciate it
Oh..Fujigane's Shoji chief, right?
Yes yes
See you
Chief Shoji's in that garage.
Chief ?
He is there
Thank you
Ah,I'm sorry to bother you suddenly
I'm Sugino from International Rayon
Actually, I would like to ask about a fake label T-shirt called domestic Tetron.
fake label?
Yes
I don't know what are you talking about
I need to go now
Well...Are you busy with 20 million yen and fraud?
Would you like to talk while eating somewhere tonight?
Tonight?
Yes, Where is good with you?
Well....
Then how about a nightclub called Haril near Shinsaibashi?
We can meet there around 8pm
Your friends won't come
Maybe...
Welcome
Shoji-san
What's wrong?
You look really serious
Will you come again ?
Yes
Yeah! I'm happy
My name is Akiko,
Please do not forget
Promise me
Excuse me
Oh, I was waiting for you
I just got a call from Jingo
Please come in
Please take your seat
Dad,he is here
Nice to meet you, I ’m Sugino from International Rayon.
I'm Kazunori Tago
I heard about most of it from Mr. Jingo
You went to Fujigane
However, Fujigane Shoji's chief Shoji has died.
He closed the garage, started the engine and inhaled the exhaust gas
He had a suicide note. So it ’s suicide, right?
So what do you want to ask me?
In short...With a fake label shirt
A man named Kakiuchi brought an international Tetoron shirt 30 darts to a cash wholesaler in Tokyo.
I'm wondering if you know him...
Kakiuchi...
Yes..write "within" for the fence
I don't know
I see
I only know information about product brokers in the Osaka area
I have no way to search it
There is a way
What?
Better leave it to a specialist.
How about looking for a cash market?
Cash market?
You don't know?
Never mind
Yukiko
Can you show him around?
I get a monthly allowance from Mr. Jingo
But not a lot of money
If you have half a day, you can go all around
Yes
I will get ready
Ah, thank you very much
No at all
Excuse me
Oh..Look who it is. It's Mr. Tago' daughter.
I'm looking for a person. Do you know a broker called Kakiuchi?
He bought an international Tetoron shirt half a month ago
I've never dealt with international tetron shirts.
Kakiuchi?
Yes
If that's the case, he's not the guy who came to stock the International Tetoron shirt, he's the guy who brought it here.
He's the guy who brought it here?
10,000 copies of a 500 yen item for only 360 yen.
He brought it and hit it all in 3 minutes
He made a lot of money and went home
I see. He is here now?
Well.. I don't see him lately
Do you know Mr. Kakiuchi's address?
Well...I don't know where he lives but
He often goes to Hime nightclubs
Hime?
Yes
Is it near Shinsaibashi?
You say you always come, but you don't
No way, I often come here
You are lying
You are cold
Welcome
Is a person called kakiuchi here?
Yes, he is here
He is sitting at the counter
Please
No no...I'm not very close to him
Tell me who is he
Please
Hi! welcome!
He's wearing that black suit and now drinking on-the-rock
Thank you
Would you like some beers?
Yes
He is a person with a strong eye
Do not stare at him a lot
He found us?
Don't worry.
He does not know us
I'm assuming you're investigating him under orders from the Company.
If so, I wouldn't do this kind of research.
I'm worried about money with you
Oh... I didn't know that
You can stay at my house if you like
What? well....but...
I think my dad will be convinced when he hears that story
My dad doesn't disagree with me
I'm a little sorry about that.
Never mind
Oh...
Do not look back
There's a man from International Rayon here.
What will you do?
I will tell him our house
And while I'm at it, I can tell him about the counterfeit factory.
Would you like to reveal the secret again?
You are a member of International Rayon.
Leave it to me
I have a good idea, Let's go
Let's get after him
Yes
It's a strange car
Yeah
What's in that car?
It's not ice cream, and it's not bread.
Sorry, we found wrong house
I'm not a suspicious person.
I am the Kakiuchi
If you have something to do, say it clearly
I was so surprised.
I don't think it's safe to stake it out tomorrow morning.
Don't worry, I'll make sure he doesn't find out next time.
Excuse me.
Can I ask you something?
Yes
What are they making over there with a sewing machine?
They make shirts etc
They make shirts?
Yes
They are subcontract factories
There is no nameplate, but what is their name?
Well...Before, there was a nameplate called Sakai Sales Office.
Sakai Sales Office?
Yes
It is a factory with 5 or 6 sewing machines.
It seems that Kakiuchi will come to stay at night
I think that fake sports shirt was made at that factory.
It might be so
Actually
There is a trading company called Mitsuya Shoji
They've teamed up with a Hong Kong company before to do some smuggling.
I think Fujigane Shoji gave the rayon to Mitsuya Shoji.
I think they're using that rayon to make fake sports shirts at the Sakai office.
I think the Sakai sales office has something to do with someone
So that someone might be Kakiuchi
No...He is a worse person
I know him...
They won't show any evidence.
I wish I could find the evidence...
I can dispose of them at any time
So who is him?
So That guy made that fake label
And Do you think he was the one who killed Mr. Ide?
It might be so
I think He was the one who killed Shoji-san
So Fujikane's Chief Shoji did not commit suicide.
I think he was murdered.
He cleverly pretended to be suicide
You may also be targeted for life in the future
For them, aim at me before you
I'm an obstacle to them
It was very hard to find this print shop
Did you find them?
Where?
It was a small printing shop in the back town of Kobe
Kobe?
You did good job
My wife's parents' house is doing printing related work
They looked up from the type
Hey! anyone there?
I'm here
Bring simple juice
What is simple juice?
Of course, it is water
So Did you know their ordered
So They didn't ask the name because it was a cash transaction
Please explain to me more about that printing shop.
I'll be there tomorrow.
I'll try to find clues
Well...He's very tight-lipped.
But it's worth a visit
Yes, let's try
Sorry for keeping you wait
How was it?
Well...He was a stubborn person
The man who came to pick up the label came by the Osaka number car
And there was a big box on the loading platform, He said that
After all, the person who ordered the label was...
Yes
He must be Kakiuchi
When this happens, I want to meet  Kakiuchi and talk about various things.
According to your father there is a worse person
Do you have any idea?
I think your father was unhappy because of him
My dad doesn't want to talk about those days
About those days?
That was when I was still a kid.
So I don't know well
It was about 20 years ago
My dad ran a clothing company
There was a bad person in the company
He cheated on the books
He set the company on fire to deceive it
The company has all burned
At that time,My mother and brother burned to death.
I didn't know that happened.
So He set fire for the purpose of destroying evidence
Yes
I ran away in the fire with my father
I was crying for days when my mother and brother died
I don't remember who he is.
He started a business with the bad money
He seems to have succeeded
Well...
Was there a police interrogation?
The police investigated many times
But They said it was the reason for the electric leakage from the ceiling
Since then my father's personality has changed
I see
If my investigation is successful,
you will know the man who brought you all this misfortune.
I've had my mind set on something ever since I can remember.
I want to ease my father's suffering
Where has he gone?
I think I'll be back soon.
He wrote only this
Hello?
Yes I am
What?
Telegram?
I see. Sorry, I was out
Yes please
For survey...go to Kyushu
He'll be back in a few days
Yes I get it
Where is the calling station
Osaka
I see. Thank you
He was in a hurry
It's odd that he would go so far away, to Kyushu.
Yes
But he went to Hokkaido last month
How did he get ready?
My dad always carries the same bag when he goes on a trip
He keeps everything he needs in that bag.
I'm sure he has brought the bag
I'm sure he left for what he thought would be a day trip.
He suddenly decided to go to Kyushu
Yes..it might be so
Ikue-san!
Oh, my God!
It seems Kakiuchi was dead
What? Kakiuchi was dead?
Why?
The factory burned around 1am and he died
Details are written in the newspaper
Anyway I will go there
Hello? Who are you?
Oh sorry, I am person who concern
I would like to ask about Mr. Kakiuchi who died.
Please go to the investigation section of the main office
Yes,It was terrible
It was hard to dissect
Anyway He inhaled carbon monoxide
There was no nitrogen in his belly
After he committed suicide with gas
The gas that filled the room ignited and became a fire
Well...Is there a possibility of setting fire?
Setting fire?
He died two hours before the fire broke out
Dead people don't set fire
He didn't set the fire.
I mean, someone killed him then set fire
Given the circumstances, I don't see that as a possibility.
Because it was all locked
I see.
I can't believe he commits suicide
You think so?
From what his wife told me, he wasn't doing so well at his job.
His wife?
common-law marriage
Junko Hamanaka?
Yes
She recognized his dead body as soon as she saw it.
She seems to be a dancer somewhere
Ok...Thanks for having me
See you
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
Where is Ms.Hamanaka?
Ms.Hamanaka?
Yes,She lived here with a man named Kakiuchi lately
Well... I don't know. We have just moved here
Right?
All of you?
Yes, this is our company dormitory
Your company dormitory?
Since when?
Since long time ago
Car has arrived, let's go!
Super Ace is a big department store recently opened
Is that so?
Yes
But If the house that Kakiuchi and the others were living in had been a Super Ace dormitory for a long time...
Do they have anything to do with Super Ace?
That's right.
So I asked where they were moving
But they don't know at all
Kakiuchi is dead
I have to pursue Junko Hamanaka
Now we need to investigate Super Ace
But Your paid vacation is over today
Yes
I'll call the manager and ask him to extend
Hello? this is Nagasawa speaking
Oh you?
What can I do for you?
What?
Extension of vacation?
I can't
Fake label news is gone
If you make a fuss, the world will misunderstand us.
What?
That's not good
Anyway I don't approve, so come to work tomorrow.
You understand?
I get it
Shit! He said I need to go back to work tomorrow
I'll just ignore it.
I think you'd better to back
But I can't go back to Tokyo without results.
It's frustrating to see Mr. Ide die in vain because of the Director.
I can't forgive him
I know how you feel but
I think you should go back to work once
You can come again
I'll do what I can until then.
My dad will help me if I ask
So please
Please return by night train tonight
I see
In that case, I will follow you
I'll let you know as soon as my dad comes back and finds out something
Thanks.
You take care of me a lot
Not at all
Sugino-san
According to the section chief, there are a lot of fake labels on the market.
Really?
Why you didn't tell me earlier?
If the section chief asks you to go to Osaka to investigate, it's not good for his reputation.
Hello? Yes he is here
Hello? This is Sugino
Oh Yukiko-san
What happened after that
What? In Tokyo? When?
I see. Where are you now?
At reception desk?
Take the elevator to the rooftop
Yes
Then hasn't your father contacted you since then?
It's been over half a month
My dad might have been in a car accident
If so, the police will contact you
So you said in the phone you are here for work
Yes I've started to work at Super Ace
Super Ace?
Why?
About 10 days ago, the president of Super Ace visited my father in sudden
He wanted my father to be a management consultant
I explained the situation to him
He was worried about my money and introduced me to a job
That's strange
The Super Ace is in Osaka,right?
Yes, but But recently there are many chain stores
The first branch office in Kawasaki was opened in Kanto
So yesterday I went on a business trip to Tokyo with the president
I was surprised that you worked for Super Ace
I'm sure you were surprised
This arrived a week ago
This is a copy of the family register
Yes.My dad ordered both
This is Akio Kakiuchi's, isn't it?
Yes, and moreover
Another one,Ryuichi Terazawa's is the president of Super Ace
See?
Heitaro Terasawa is the same father of Super Ace and Kakiuchi.
In doing so,Kakiuchi and President Terasawa are half-brothers.
Yes, so I have decided to work at Super Ace
I see...
Sugino-san!
What can I do for you?
Well..Actually, as you may know
Lately there are a lot of fake labels on the market.
We are in a situation that cannot be ignored
So we decided to take a closer look at it.
But The director said he would leave everything to the police
Yes
The fake labels have been found nationwide
The police seem to be out of control
Even at the board meeting, we decided that we absolutely have to find the criminal because this is related to the credit of the company.
We want you to take the lead in the operation
We understand your situation
But you are one of the our member
You can't oppose the company's decision
I get it.
I also intended to investigate the criminal
But I want to say one thing
If the real culprit is found, will you admit that Mr. Ide was killed in the line of duty?
Yes sure, of course
I see. I am going to Osaka tonight
If you need travel expenses, please tell the accounting
I'll take your word for it. I'll go home first.
Thank you for your work
Have a look around Tokyo.
I'm sorry I couldn't guide you
Not at all.
I like to go alone
Excuse me
What's wrong?
Well..I forgot something
I see
What did you forget?
I see.
You think he's Kakiuchi
Yes.But he should be dead and he shouldn't come to the store
Well...
Maybe he's not dead.
Then that corpse?
Oh it's time to go
Yes
Yukikosan,
Actually, today I did some research on President Terasawa of Super Ace.
He invests more and more in the companies he's interested in and gets the rights.
And he always controls the company from then on.
So..by any chance
I think he has the registration papers for Fujigane Shokai and Mitsuya Shoji.
Do you know that?
Yes...if I try to research
Really? Can you do that?
Well...I can't reply clearly
He always has a bag with important documents
Maybe it's in there.
If the registration book is in that bag.
I'll find who I'm looking for.
We can find out who embezzled your company's money and set your company on fire.
Then, I will try to research
If you are found, you are in trouble.
Don't worry
I worry about my father
Maybe my dad is in captivity in Super Ace
You think too much
Anyway, please research
I will contact you as soon as I get to Osaka
Do not do overdo
Yes
Well.. what is this?
This is in the possession of Akio Kakiuchi.
Kakiuchi's?
He had dentures?
It seems so.
His mother saw this and said it must be him.
I think this is not true.
He is still alive
Person who dead was...
12345678
I'm tired
Let me have a break
Are you Junko Hamanaka?
Well.. Yes...
I think I have met you before
The age of dead Kakiuchi is 32 years old
Yes
He was young, but he had dentures?
So what?
Where are the bones of kakiuchi?
I buried it.
To where?
Why do you want to know?
I need to know
Where did you bury his bones?
You insist!
Do you think I'm sleeping hugging his bones?
You!
You didn't bury his bone, right?
I can't take this anymore!
I said I burred it
To where?
His temple
Teach me again, teacher
Where is the temple?
It's a temple called Genryo-ji in Takatsuki
What's buried there are the bones of a different man.
Excuse me
Who is it?
Oh
I'm here to ask you something
Is Akio Kakiuchi's body buried here?
Yes Because there is a grave of Mr. Kakiuchi's ancestors here
Where is his grave?
Do you want to visit the grave?
Yes
Then I'll take you there
Thanks
Here
The burial was really done?
It ’s natural to bury it.
Then show me his urn
His urn?
I can't show you
Can you make a special request?
I can't
I'm murderous
It is alleged that a man was killed instead of Kakiuchi akio
We'll find out when we show the dentist his dentures in the urn.
But moving the grave is not easy
I will come again after going through legal procedures
Wait!
let me get the path
I see, so that guy tried to kill you
I think so
He might be Akio Kakiuchi
Excuse me
Mr. Tago was really killed?
I think the police will announce it later
This is a secret, but...
Jingo Shoten will soon be replaced by Kokusai Rayon Shoten.
So Let's work together
So did Fujikane get out of our company?
Yes,As a result of the discussion
Excuse me
Oh yeah, about that fake label....
I asked Fujikane
It was true
When you take shelter, make sure you go under a big tree.
Your company is very reliable
See you
What's wrong with you?
Nothing
The neon installation work is finished. Would you like to see it?
Yes
Please count
Thank you for your hard work
See you
Will you bring me a cold drink?
I will prepare it soon
Oh Yukiko-san.
It's me
I just returned from Osaka and now I'm in front of Kawasaki station
How was the matter in the president's bag?
Well... I tried to find it
Just before... it's not good
Not at all... I see.. thank you
Well.. I hope it works
I see, then you can stop work, I will manage it
What? well...
I'm going to take a chance and talk to Terasawa.
Anyway, You don't have to do that anymore
Did you make sense?
See you
Well..who is it?
My name is Sugino, Research Division, International Rayon Sales Department.
Excuse me
You're President Terasawa, right?
Mmm..Um
I want to hear about your relationship with Akio Takeuchi
I see
Take your seat
He was a very troubled person
He used to be my driver
His driving was very rough
He had a personality that likes dangerous things
He had an unusual personality
It's dangerous to free him so I shared the money and took care of him
I was relieved that he committed suicide
But Terasawa-san
He is alive
He is alive?
Do you have any evidence?
Don't pretend you don't know
I know everything
He is your half brother
You used him to kill some people
Hey! What are you talking about?
I am a manager
I do business but not murder
Don't pretend you don't know
Ok
I'm ready for this.
You can do whatever you want
I am very busy with the management plan of the company
He's leaving. he doesn't want any tea.
I will visit you again
Next time I will talk more with you
I find evidence to prevent you from escaping
You will appear in the police
He must be crazy
Oh Tago-san
I am planning to go to the villa of Lake Yamanaka today
Can you accompany with me?
What?
I want to organize my documents before I go back to Osaka
Is that bad for you?
No
I will go with you
It will help me a lot
Please come in
Thank you
Tago-kun
Can you cook something for me from the food bag?
Kitchen is there
Yes
Well, I'm sorry but can you prepare bath for me?
bathroom is there
Yes
Hey you!
Can I borrow your car?
What?
I'm in hurry
What's wrong with you?
I will tell you why
Your bath is ready now
I see.
Thank you
Well...you finally show who you are
Sugino let you do this, right?
Never mind
Sugino will be here soon
He will come?
Why?
I told him to come if I wanted to help you
I don't know what is on your mind but
I hired you intentionally
I wanted to know how much you know
I know you heard from your dad about my name
So.. that is you as I thought
You were the one my dad hated
Where is my dad
He is dead
Your father was no match for me... until the end.
There is a loser on the business
It's law of the jungle
Humanity doesn't matter to succeed in business
In that sense your father was a loser
And...
Sugino and you will be dead soon
You are a distraction.
Anyone who gets in my way will die.
We Super Ace are at the top of the industry
Our company is at the top of the industry
Because we used counterfeit international rayon labels
chocolate
caramel
canning,detergent
Something like that
If other stores lower their prices, we'll lower ours even more.
If they cut 3 yen, our store will cut 5 yen
This price competition almost destroyed other stores
Our company has made a lot of profits thanks to counterfeit labels
Super Ace now has many branches all over Japan
Our company has grown into a large company with 2 billion assets
Our company never went bankrupt soon
Does it make sense?
So you guys are in the way
I'm in trouble if a counterfeit label is found
Will I use that car again?
Sugino will come here soon
I'm worried because you always use the same method
Where to put their corpses?
If they die, bring them here
They would have been forced into a vacant house
I lost my family register instead of Tago
So you should play with Junko for a while
I don't know how serious you are
What the fuck
I will process your passport immediately
I want to go to Hong Kong.
That's cool
Junko!
Damn it!
You poisoned her whiskey
You would have killed me after I kill someone
You idiot!
What are you talking about?
Ok, then drink this?
You worked on ice
Damn it!
Can you kill me?
You don't have a family register, you can't live if you kill me
You have been crazy since you were born
Ahhh!
Now your turn
Come on!
You know us too much!
Come!
Be patient until the exhaust gas is full in this
Your father put up with Fujigane's Shoji for more than 30 minutes
Yukiko-san!
Stop!
Damn it!
Yukiko-san!
Oh..
Ah!!
Kakiuchi was dead
My car hit his car.
His car fell off a cliff
A fire ignited his car and exploded
It was so scary
But.. it's all over
Yukiko-san
I didn't tell you this
Your father was killed instead of Kakiuchi
I know it
I was wondering if maybe...
Terazawa told me yesterday at the villa
I don't know how I can comfort you
Don't worry
Father died in the fire like mother and brother
I think my father hoped so
I want to put my father's bones near my mother
Will you go with me?
Of course
And
I will be with you from now
Oh...
Finish