Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Black Death Ball
Hello
How's Sakaguchi's injury?
He has a fracture to his left arm.
How is his head?
He was pissed off behind the bench
The woman he was with was a fashion model?
Hey guys,I'm not Prince Shotoku or Buddha.
Whose question shall I answer first?
What do you think of the state of the Boobies' aces?
Don’t say things like that.
It might bring bad luck.
Sakaguchi's injury is no big deal.
It's just a fracture.
A month's rest and he'll be ready to pitch.
I don't worry about him at all
That's wishful thinking on your part.
Hey you,Do not look down our Boobies.
Besides Sakaguchi, Yoshida is also there. Kuroki, who joined the team last year, is also doing well.
You should come to see our camp one day
See you
Wait wait!
Wait,Nishio-san
Please answer more
I just need a moment of your time.
See you tomorrow
Please don't say that.
I just need a moment of your time.
Nishio-san!
There were many reporters
Suematsu, I think Sakaguchi will be hopeless
He has ligament damage, not just fractures.
So He will be unable to come back
Um
I figured I could use him for another three years.
So We don't have enough time
We need to decide on that as soon as possible.
Good morning
Where have you been?
You're not a woman. Long time to get ready.
I'm sorry
6 million in 1000 yen bills
Ok, We will go to Nagano now
If we put the money in front of him, Kikukawa's father would agree.
Moreover I raised the price a million more than they asked.
But We'll negotiate for the five million they're asking for at first.
If it doesn't work, we'll give him one million.
And We'll have a contract with him by the end of the day.
Does it make sense?
Yes
That's not a very motivating reply.
You don't look good.
Are you being hangover?
I had a bad night last night.
But it's not a good idea to indulge in alcohol.
That’s unlike you.
Listen to me.
Don't lose the next round of negotiations.
The Unions aren't the problem, the problem is the Eagles.
We've been losing to the Eagles lately.
They have a lot of pride.
Just make sure you don't lose the comeback at the last minute.
Yes, I know it
But I understand your painful situation.
Because you have to contend with Hamada, the Eagles who took care of you.
Hi
I met him last night
You wake up early today
Why you didn't come?
Hey,Why you didn't come?
I didn't want to answer you outright.
And there was a problem in the morning
What was the problem?
I don't feel like talking
I see...
I wrote this letter last night
I'm thinking of posting it now
It's a rejection letter, anyway?
I know it without looking
But I want you to read this.
I've thought about it a lot.
I've known you since you were working for my father's baseball club.
I used to think of you as a brother.
Then I can't believe you're getting marry me all of a sudden.
If I married you, it would be boring.
What did Hamada-san say?
I didn’t talk with my father
I see
Hahaha I get it
I don't think I'm cut out to be a Scout.
I couldn't scout you out.
I'm sorry
Ah...This...
I'll take care of it for now.
Are you going on business trip?
Are you traveling for a long time?
Yes
To where?
I have no idea
See you
Kashiwagi-san
My father left yesterday
To where?
This is the last time I'm gonna tell you.
To Nagano
Nagano?
Welcome
Thank you very much
Hi senior
You had a rough morning.
It serves one right
It can't be helped
But the quality of the players has changed, too.
It's a far cry from when you joined the Eagles from Towa Steel.
I'll have same with him
Sand-width and coffee?
But your leaders are also blind.
You could still be a player.
But they made you become a scout.
Evert reporters say so
I see
I think You have a hard time
Even if it's for business.
You're the one who has to scout out Kikukawa.
You know what
What's wrong?
I'll get off next stop, Ueda
Please take care of our bill
I don't care about it
You are supposed to go to Nagano, right?
The Kikukawa does not matter
I hear there is better player in Ueda
Oh really?
Hey, Who is he?
Of course no comment
Then see you
I'll play this piece.
Ah
Amamiya!
Eh?
Please connect me
Hello, this is Kawakami of Eagles speaking
Eh?
Oh..Arizawa
Kashiwagi?
What? He got off at Ueda?
So What will he do with Kikukawa?
I have no idea at all
Apart from that, How is your work?
It's bad!
Actually, The Kikukawa is missing
Eh?
I don't know where he has gone
Hey, can you come back earlier?
You’ve got quite a bit of money.
Why?
Are you going to take a hired car and take in the scenery?
I don't have the time.
Hurry up,anyway
It's better to take a train if you are in hurry
I have no choice
Can you speed up more?
How long will it take to Nagano?
He is not here?
You don't know where he has gone?
No...ok..good...
Oh my god...Anyone know where he is?
He's with the executive director.
The executive director?
Oh He is Hiroshi's uncle
I see.
He's with relatives.
That’s horrible.
He is missing
Mr. Hamada came in a while ago and was in trouble.
Did he come?
I was told It's secret
Where is Hamada?
Well...
Come...
Do you know it, right?
Yes
This is the Sakai Hotel in Okuyamada Onsen.
Okuyamada Onsen...
Sorry to keep you wait
I'm sorry to visit you in sudden
Kikukawa has been absent since yesterday
I asked it already at his shop.
Do you know where he has gone?
Is he not sick?
Hun? He reported you he is sick?
Yes, he called me he got bad cold
Isn't that so?
It seems they are having a family meeting.
Do you have any idea where they are?
Well...
That's horrible
I thought you know about it
You think I'm hiding something?
I didn't mean that
I really don't know
Actually I am...
I will be leave this work
What?
I've had some bad days as a teacher.
The PTA took issue with me over Kikukawa.
But it's all sudden
I'm sorry to ask you but
You've been bought out by another team.
No way! Kashiwagi-san
Please trust me
I've done what I promised you I would do.
I don't betray you
I made an effort with the baseball manager to get Kikukawa to join your team.
I didn't mean that I make you feel bad
But It's easy to be suspicious of people when you're doing this kind of work.
I'm sorry,I apologize
Never mind.
As long as you understand my position, I'll be fine.
I feel sorry that we become friend but...
How about having a drink together tonight?
Unfortunately, I'll be on duty.
I see. That's too bad
I'm sorry
But I worry about Kikukawa
Ah..hahaha
I'll leave my luck to the heavens.
Kashiwagi-san,Just got off
What?
Just got off the phone.
From Kikukawa
What?
He said he will call you again at 6 pm
at 6 pm
So Where is he now?
I don't know
He sounded like his father on the phone.
6 pm...
Welcome
Are you alone?
Please come in
Welcome
Don't worry.
I will show him around
Did you come from Nagano?
I'm sure you must be tired of the bus shaking because of the road construction on the way.
It doesn't shaking all the way to Sakura-dori.
Well..How do you like to eat?
I will have it late
Yes
How about drink?
Whiskey
Yes
If you get a call from Nagano, please connect me right away.
Kashiwagi-san
Do you eat mandarin oranges?
Is the clock at the station accurate?
The trains are always late.
Maybe accurate
Hello? This is Kashiwagi speaking
Massage?
He will be late?
I don't care about it.
Before sleeping, I will take it
Kashiwagi-san
You're still young and you want a massage?
My body is stiff because of my habits as an athlete.
So Shall I come here to massage you tonight?
What?
Ah....
He has come
I said before sleeping
Not The massagist but Kikukawa
What?
We've got things mixed up.
After all,I think it's best if I leave my son with your ball club.
Right?
Yes
Mr. Hamada of the Eagles and Mr. Kawakami of the Unions
We have talked with them carefully
But You guys have offered the best contract price.
But...
What's wrong?
Well...I'm sorry to have to say this but
My brother and I are co-owners of a store...
What's wrong?
Please speak clearly
Well, I'll take your word for it.
Actually, our store is on the verge of foreclosure.
We're behind on our taxes.
We borrowed money from a crook.
You may think that you should handle this contract money.
We want to keep this contract money for my son.
Please understand our situation...
How much is that?
800,000 yen, including interest.
Right?
Yes
To be accurate, it would be 813000yen
I understand
5 million for his contract
We will add 813000yen
Thank you
Is there anything else?
Nothing
Oh you
I thought you were back with your dad and the others.
What can I do for you?
I'm sorry my father said that
Never mind.
It happens
That is not your business
Hey, cheer up
What's wrong with your hand
It's nothing.
I was bitten by our dog.
It's not a big deal
By the way, I have a favor of you
What is that?
How can I say no to Mr. Hamada?
You were scouted by Mr. Hamada and joined the professional team, right?
I've been scouted by Mr. Hamada, too.
I failed Mr. Hamada.
I don't know how to apologize.
My father called Mr. Hamada clerically before he came here.
But I want to apologize to Mr. Hamada, too.
Ok, I get it, Leave it to me
I've hurt Mr. Hamada about you, too.
Anyway Let's see you in Tokyo.
so Do not think too much
Yes
Hello?
Mr.Hamada has just gone for a walk
Who's calling please
Ha?
To Mr.Kashiwagi,right?
I'll tell him when he come back
Some people like to take walks, don't they?
He takes his walks on moonless days.
He said it was to sober him up after drinking whiskey.
I think he went to the observatory in the back woods.
Oh!
Mr. Kikukawa called you at 6 o'clock.
Mr. Kashiwagi called you at 8 o'clock.
Have there been any other outside calls?
No
Did you notice anything else?
Well...He was a strange man from the start.
When I spoke to him, he had little to say.
When he was at dinner....
I will take a walk later
It will help me sober up.
Can I climb the mountain behind the house?
Yes,There's a path from the garden.
There is an observatory at the top.
There are a lot of visitors during the autumn leaves and cherry blossom season.
It's cold now, so there aren't many customers.
And it's too dark
Shall I send the watchman with you?
Never mind,
I like to go alone
He looked so sad.
Hmmm
That's everything he have left.
Thanks
These are Hamada's?
Yes
Dead?
Hamada-san?
Did you notice anything else?
Even if it's a small thing.
I can't believe he is dead
I see
I've been to Mr. Kikukawa's house, and he's told me most of what I need to know.
It's a tough business you guys are in.
But You're in the business of buying people's grudges.
You mean,Possibility of murder?
That's what I thought, given the situation on the ground.
Well,Please let me know if you have any ideas.
Hiroshi!
Don't be stupid.
Mr. Hamada has nothing to do with us.
You don't understand!
If I join to Eagles, Hamada-san weren't dead
Mr. Hamada hasn't been ruled a suicide.
The detective said Mr. Hamada may have been murdered.
Mr. Hamada committed suicide.
Mr. Hamada lost the scout battle.
It's my fault.
Hiroshi!
Hey Let's go!
Here we go!
Oh shit!
Hey! wait for me!
Hi, Are you Kikukawa?
Yes...
I want to talk with you
Do you want to join professional baseball?
I can join professional baseball?
You can be a good pitcher if you work hard.
But I am bad.
They made me switch to the outfield.
You failed at the qualifying tournament the other day.
You were a light outfielder , weren't you?
One infield hit and you weren't active.
Well...
I've looked into everything you've done.
You are 180cm tall
weight is 78kg
You look like you've lost some weight lately.
Let's shake hands
Hold my hand as hard as you can.
More more!
Ok
That's what I thought More more!
You have a power
But I can't control the ball.
High school is not the place for you to make the most of your talents.
Hey!
Come on!
You look like a raging horse right now.
A rampaging horse is hard to control.
But Your sinker is great.
High school kids can't hit that ball.
You have your own pitch.
When you learn to do that, you'll be a great pitcher.
You think so?
Yes trust me
My instincts are often right.
Sakaguchi of the Eagles, Aoshima of the Elephants I first spotted.
But our club has no money
We are always the last ones to be able to pay and other club take the players.
We're pathetic.
I don't care about money
Everyone say like you first
I'm not
Good.
I trust you
Listen to me
Don't tell your father or the baseball coach about what we talked about today.
OK?
Don't swim from today.
It's not good to cool your shoulders.
Yes
Good.
Let's shake hand again
Our test has been finished
Did Mr. Hamada really commit suicide?
According to our investigation, yes.
But I'm not comfortable with him dying so easily.
I feel the same
He's not that kind of man.
We started out investigating other deaths, too.
But there's no evidence of that.
Mr. Hamada's time of death was estimated at 7:30 p.m.
An official who knows where Mr. Hamada is staying
You are included,Kashiwagi-san
All of them stayed in the city
I also talked to a guest at the Sakai Hotel.
There were no one who went out at that time
Mr. Hamada was found in a kimono with wide sleeves.
He wasn't attacked by a street thief.
So we ruled it a suicide.
But He was drunk at that night
Can you guess that he accidentally fell off the cliff?
About that point
You will see if you go there
Like this
There are about 5 meters from the observatory to the cliff.
He can't accidentally fall.
According to my assistant
Kikukawa called him that night to refuse to join the team.
Hamada got shocked
He stood on a dark mountaintop.
He might have thought about dying suddenly.
Speaking of him, Recently he was unlucky
One more!
Yes!
Hi
How is him?
He is ok
How's his shoulder?
You'll know if you see his throwing
You always don't tell me
I'll teach you if he is a test student without a contract fee.
Hey! Kashi
Yes
You pitch from the home base
I want to see your shoulder
Yes
Hey, stop practice!
Let me throw a ball
He's the holder of the 108-meter long throw record.
108m?
You measure it with a measuring tape in your spare time.
You think so?
Are you saying that I'm the reason why the Eagles lost the championship?
I also missed out on the stolen base title.
My batting average has dropped to 230.
But everyone has their slumps.
I know you understand this
Why am I being traded?
Wait,kashi,
I understand how you feel
I think we should move on while there are still teams to pick up.
Even if you stay, next season is going to be tough.
I understand your situation, so I've asked the team to trade you.
Do not misunderstand me
I have a hard time seeing you being overtaken by the younger generation.
Can you transfer to Eagles?
Good luck in your new team
OK?
One more
Hamada-san has ended up in such a small box.
What time should I take the train home?
Well...from now....
I can catch the train at 1:30 bound for Shiga
I can arrive at Tokyo in day time
Is that OK with you,Kashiwagi?
Yes
So Please get ready
Well..I am...
What?
I'm sorry but you can go first
I have sometime to do here
To where?
We can go with you
Right,Kashiwagi?
Sure
No...Don't worry
I'll go by myself
The place where Hamada died is Okuyamada Onsen, right?
Yes
We can go with you if you want to go there
No..it's not
My father's friend is here
I didn't know that Hamada's friend is here
Yes
So We will go back to Tokyo first
OK?
I see
Then we can go back first
I've got a lot to prepare for.
Yes
I'm sorry
I'm sorry for being so selfish.
Never mind
I understand your situation
Let's get ready
Thank you very much
You know what...
What?
I will be here
I'm curious about something.
I see
You can go by yourself
I don't care
I see.
I'm curious about leaving her alone too
Then. I'll leave it to you
Sure
See you
Hello?
Oh, Kashiwagi-san
Eh?..Hmmm
Mr. Hamada's daughter just left.
Yes,She was looking for a Ichinomiya watchmaker.
Ichinomiya
Hello?
Why he hang up the phone...
Hello, Can I ask you something?
Welcome, men's watches are there
No no...Didn't a young woman come in here a little while ago now?
She had her head trimmed, and she was wearing a brown coat.
Oh,Hamada-san
Do you know her?
No, She was first visiting us
I see..but...
She's here about a watch her father bought.
I see
Are you a police?
No no, I'm just looking for her
Are you a private detective?
Yes..kind of
I see, I understand
I was also surprised to see yesterday's evening paper.
The day before he died, he bought a 65,000 yen woman watch from this store.
A woman watch?
Yes
He said it would suit a city girl
I gave him the same type as this one.
The size fits Mr. Hamada's daughter.
I see
I wanted to come here
But You are too cold
Why you didn't tell me you come here ?
You checked the watch store
You came to this lonely place alone.
What the hell?
I'm sorry I hide something
But I didn't want people to know my father's secret.
His secret?
Did he have a secret?
This was in his wallet
Um
He didn't buy it for me
I couldn't find that watch in his belongings.
The day before he died, he came to Nagano and bought that watch.
He gave the watch to the woman that evening.
I don't believe his has girlfriend
Speaking of it,I have an idea.
He hadn't been home for a month and a half since the end of summer.
He's sometime been home for work but
It was the first time he'd gone a month and a half without coming home.
And...
He's cut the living expenses he gives to the house in half.
Hmmm
I didn't know this
I scolded my father about the money.
It was the same the morning before my father died.
I'm leaving
When you will go back?
I'll go back soon
This is my salary
Not much this month, either.
What do you spend for?
I was surprised to see your savings book.
It's been cut in half.
I need money for my work
You can ask your company for the money
Our company has no money, you know?
Please be patient
When this job is done, I'll even make it easy for you.
I finally understand how my mother feel who dead before
She didn't complain.
Because she gave up about you
I'm not like my mother
It's hard to take care of you.
Hmm...
So you should go to marry
If you marry, I'll remarry too.
There is no woman who wants to marry you
You're not home for half the year.
I have potential.
Oh, you know someone?
What? I'm starting to look for her
I'm sure he has girlfriend
Then why did he kill himself?
I doubt too
I don't think he killed himself.
But I didn't tell the police because I didn't know for sure.
If I know he had girlfriend for sure...
His honor will be damaged.
Then you come here alone?
I don't want anyone to know this
Sorry
Never mind
But Shizue
You are just girl, so no choice
If anything happens to you, you're in trouble.
Can you leave it to me if you don't mind?
Mr.Hamada took care of me very well
But in opposition to returning that favor to him, the Kikukawa case...
I've put him in a difficult position.
I don't think that was the direct cause.
But I'm having a hard time if I think about it
So I want to handle about Hamada's case
If you don't mind
I feel thanks to you
But
I know what you want to say
I'm calling off my engagement to you.
Let's both pretend this never happened.
From now on, please associate with us as the bereaved family of the dead Mr. Hamada.
Cold wind
I need to go Tokyo by the end of today
Ok let's go
That's true.
Every school now has a physical fitness test at the beginning of each semester.
For boys, 100m...
Long jump, pull-ups, ball throw etc
The grades are differentiated.
So I have an idea
Why don't we go through those records and mark the best students?
What happen if he don't know baseball?
That's risky, and there are many materials
That's a lot of time to waste.
I don't think so,
Kashi's idea is good
We had a blind spot.
No matter how good you are, if they don't play baseball, they'll never catch our attention.
A person who has the makings of a baseball player and plays other sports.
People who do not play sports
I think there are many such hidden gems.
OK, let's do this!
Hey,Kashi
For starters, let's start with your area of responsibility.
Yes
It's a deal.
Have them go to each district to report.
Let's break up.
Hey,Kashi
Yes
You finally get motivated
No way
That's good
You have a dream of an athletic life in your head.
Hamada get rid of  it for you
Anyway good luck
Yes
There is a call for you
Thank you
Hello? this is Kashiwagi speaking
Oh, Mr.Kikukawa
How is it going?
What? Kiyoshi was??
What's wrong?
He didn't go back home since yesterday
What?
Hello?
Isn't Hiroshi supposed to be at the camp soon?
Please explain me in detail
Yes, he left home yesterday morning, then he is missing
Yes, I tried to look for him, but...
I couldn't find him...yes..
Ok I will contact them
Yes
He is not in Yoshida's camp
He is stupid
Don't worry, he is till young
He went for play
But
Don't get too nervous.
Well...They've already received the contract money.
Yes
Hello?
From Kikukawa?
Hello? this is Kashiwagi speaking
Oh..Shizue...
I'm busy now
X-ray photo?
Who's?
Yes
It was the end of last month.
Mr.Hamada sent this photo to me
With letter
I found it
Here it is
It says to find out more about the enclosed photos.
I can't report it because he's dead.
I don't need to have it.
So what is this photo?
Shall I explain to you?
Yes
This is the bone in his arm.
Look.
He's got a crack in his elbow joint.
This single photo does not show the detailed condition.
It appears to be a complex fracture.
It's a good picture because it was taken with an excellent x-ray machine.
Our surgeon was impressed.
Um
What?
I realized now
He has long arm
And he is tall
Do you know which arm?
Left arm
It may be difficult for the uninitiated to understand.
It depends on the individual.
But he is over 180cm
Calculated from the standard index of height for this bony part of the body.
It would be...
Sorry for making you trouble
Then see you
Hello, do you know where is Hiroshi?
Oh long time no see
I've just called to the baseball club office
We are sorry for making you trouble
How is Hiroshi doing?
Yes, He was brought back safely by the teacher.
Is he back?
Excuse me
Stand up!
Now
Do you feel pain?
What's wrong with you?
Do the pitching motion.
Do it!
Faster.
Throw as if you were on the mound.
What's wrong with you,Kashiwagi-san?
What the hell are you doing?
Once again
I thought you were out of your mind.
You did it as soon as you walked in the house.
I was sorry
Let's drink
Well...I am...
I was worried when I saw those X-rays.
Anyway I've relieved
Where did you find Kikukawa?
Yes..I happened to see him
Actually
We have recently appointed a new English teacher at our school
Today we're going to celebrate his transfer.
The man coming from the other side is Kikukawa, isn't it?
Stop here,Please
Kikukawa-kun!
teacher!
Your father worry about you, he called me many times
You are bad
I'm sorry
What's wrong with you?
I wanted to see where Hamada-san died.
I stayed a room where Hamada-san stayed
And I was thinking of him
I thought I'd give back the money the Boobies gave me and join the Eagles.
But I knew that would hurt Kashiwagi-san.
I'm not lost anymore.
I thought about it at the spa and got motivated.
I see
I'm sorry to make you worry
Never mind
By the way, you go home on foot
I spent all my money on hotel bills. So I decided to walk home.
You are stupid.
You could call your home
My father is noisy
Ok I will send you home
Wait a min
Something tells me,Kikukawa seems to me very cute
I felt bad about giving him back to home alone.
I canceled my buddy's transfer celebration and went home with him.
I see
Please take care of Kikukawa well,Kashiwagi-san
Of course
Therefore...Whose X-rays are those?
You know what
Ha
Do you know if Mr. Hamada marked anyone other than Kikukawa?
Well.....but in my school...
There is anyone other than Kikukawa
I see
Oh
Welcome
There's a scary man here to see you.
Eh?
Oh!
Ah
It's been a long time
You're starting to sound like a full-fledged Scout.
Only looking?
Everyone said that you were not yet good enough.
You should work hard
It's sad to hear Mr. Hamada say that.
Of course
Give him a high ball
How about Kikukawa's work?
Our Eagles will get him.
The game's not over yet.
You're a big talker.
You know what,Kashi
Do you still remember, 108m?
108m?
Yes
That was the first time I took you to the Eagles' field.
I was surprised too, inwardly.
You threw a ball that disappeared into the outfield.
I'm moved to remember it.
It was 108m
What happened about the 108m?
Nothing
108m?
What? 108m?
Yes,It's a record for the longest throw of a ball.
Did any of them set a record of 108m?
Well...speaking of 108m...
I should check it carefully
Have you ever had the same scout as me before?
Well...
He's a big guy with big sunglasses named Shinichi Hamada.
You are the first person
Yes
I see
the county's general affairs division.
Well
Yes
Do you want to see the result?
Yes please
So please come this way
I can show you, but it will take time to check it
Yes
Please feel free to take a look at it
Did you find?
Hmmm
You must be tired
But I won't give up
I will come here again tomorrow
Please
See you
Thank you
Kashiwagi-san
Oh you
I just watched the Blue Sox camp.
It's boring if I go home directly
I want to celebrate you
Oh thanks
Wanna have a drink?
I'm tired,Sorry
I know a good place to get rid of it.
Get in the car!
You should accompany with me sometime
You know what
One more bar
No thanks.
I need to wake up early
It' ok,
You are so cold
Come on come on
Welcome
Hatano-san
Oh you
We met in an unusual way, didn't we?
I was invited by the PTA.
It wasn't much fun, so I got out.
I see. I want to get out too
What the hell you are talking about?
Coat!
Yes
Then see you
Hey,Kashiwagi-san
Hamada-san is dead. But neither suicide nor accidental death.
You thought someone killed him,right?
So you are searching it
This is my guess
Hey,Kashiwagi-san
We all have our own networks of information.
We're both looking into Mr. Hamada's murder.
So we can exchange the information
I don't know what is your meaning
Why do you pretend not to know?
Shall I surprise you?
I wonder Mr. Hamada had girlfriend
How did you know?
Did you meet her?
You got your answer.
Hey, can you tell me the detail?
In return, I'll give you some good information.
There's a good hitter.
Oh, you can tell first
Kashiwagi-san,That's not fair
Hey, let's dance
You guys talks all the time
There is no woman here
You are bad
You invited me here
You are mean
I'm glad you hate me
Hey, bring that girl
Who?
That girl who wear Kimono
No good, she is not for you
Right
That's true.
She is calm not like me
I like it.
What's her name?
Yukari
Hey
We should go
She's a woman of clarity.
Welcome
Ah, take your seat
This is Kashiwagi-san
Good man,right?
I'm just dirty man
You are funny
Enjoy drinking
Oh Yukari is there
What?
Thanks for support me
I don't need anymore?
Um,Because if you stay too long, you'll get worse.
Ah,take your seat
What are you talking about?
That's our secret
Right?
Can I guess it?
You're talking about a pawn shop, right?
in and out of pawn
You have a nice watch
cheap one, right?
No way
It's a famous brand, right?
She was able to get it at the asking price.
Let me see
Someone gave you?
Yes
Let's dance together
He made a good move.
Never mind.
We'll be friends, too.
Have you been working here long?
Not long
Were you here around this summer?
Why you ask me?
My senior brought me here before
I see.
I can't remember
I think my senior gave you that watch
Shall I tell you his name?
Please
The deceased Mr. Hamada
I didn't mean I surprise you
I had seen that watch before.
I didn't know you are the woman...
What do you want to know?
I want to know everything about Hamada
I want to know the truth about Mr. Hamada's sudden death.
So I have been looking for the woman who concern about Hamada
Can you tell me?
Hamada and you...
Mr.Hamada was my guest for sure
He sometime visited us, and called me
That's all
He gave you a $65,000 watch as a gift.
Can you tell me the truth?
Did you really like Hamada?
Well...
We can talk about it at somewhere in the day time
Thanks.
Up to you
So please come to my apartment tomorrow
Around noon, it calls Takara apartment
You will know easily if you ask the police box at overhead bridge
Takara apartment,right,
I'm sure I will see you
There is a guest for you
Who?
I won't tell you
Oh you
Am I bad?
Welcome
Why you are here?
I stopped by on my way to deliver something to my teacher, Yamada
Who is teacher, Yamada?
You don't know anything other than baseball
He is a famous painter
A painting in my gallery was sold.
I see.
That's good
There is a good news
What?
I found the owner of that watch.
Eh?
It was happening.
At the bar in Gundo-cho
I see
So what kind of woman?
Hmmm
She has beautiful eyes.
I can say She is a beautiful woman
I will see her tomorrow and talk about Hamada
He has a girlfriend as I thought
I feel relieved
I feel disappointed
Why?
I'd always hoped my father would never have a woman.
Is that so?
You don't understand how woman feel
It might be so
I haven't read the letter you gave me
What should I do?
I won't answer the hard questions.
Is this a taboo subject?
I will cancel the question
Hi,Miss, your room is ready
Thank you
Then, I will go with you tomorrow
She has moved?
When was it?
This early morning
To where?
I didn't ask her
Well...Did she often have men in her room who were about forty-five or six years old?
Well... I didn't see her guest much
Oh yeah,The man with the sunglasses sometimes came.
Thank you very much
Not at all
Let's go
Kashiwagi-san, You were terrible last night
How did you know we are here?
My guess
You were dancing with that woman and you disappeared.
I heard about it later from a woman named Kyoko.
I see. but you are too late
What?
Well..Take your time. Take a look around the empty room.
The train is approaching for Ueno at platform 2
We'll start all over again.
Can you leave her alone?
Why?
Something tells me, That woman Yukari loved my father very much
She didn't want to be asked about my father.
So she disappeared
But She's the only lead I have.
I will try to find her
Takara apartment...
I know there
Where is it?
Kashiwagi-san is...
Hey
Oh that's you
Is Yukari in?
Yukari?
She is not here
But they sent her package.
So I am in trouble
I borrow some money from her but
Here is too small
Hey,What happen?
Nagano
Oh that's you
I came here while you were away.
Sorry
What happen?
Since you were working so hard.
That's a 108m guy
Let me see
He really is there, isn't he? I'm surprised.
Ken?
What?
There is a guest for you
What can I do for you?
I heard your longest throw is 108 meters.
I didn't know you got injured
What happen?
Can you tell me?
I got car accident
You're young and you drink.
You'll never recover from that injury.
You are too noisy
Who are you?
This is my business card
The same scout as Hamada.
Do you know him?
He stayed here too
He was very nice man
He took care of Nobuko too
Who is Nobuko?
She is a sister of him
Is she here?
She is in Nagano, she sometime go back here
I don't see her lately
Mind your own business
You talk too much
You should stop talking too
Don't be rude in front of customers.
You can't work as farmer properly
What did you say?
Calm down
I'm leaving now
I want to ask him before I leave
Did Hamada know about your arm?
Yes, I sent him my X-ray photo
Where did you get that treatment?
You said you want to ask me one thing
Please answer it
You can't?
It's a surgery called Inuzuka in Nagano.
Right,Ken?
What did you do!
He's a troubled man.
He's become a misanthrope.
I have a favor of you
Can I see the Nobuko's photo?
Nobuko's photo?
That photo is.....yes...right there
Wait
I met your sister other day
It's a bar called Silver Place in Hondocho.
I wanted to ask her about Hamada
But she has disappeared in sudden
Really?
Yes
I have no idea why she has disappeared
I think you know it
Tell me everything you know.
I don't know about her!
I've cut ties with my sister.
Why?
She betrayed my seniority.
Who is the seniority?
Mind your own business
I don't like Hamada.
He's old enough to have cheated on his sister.
You think Hamada approached your sister to recruit you?
I've heard from my sister about me
He said he takes care of me
Even though they're a poor ball club.
My sister was going to use me, too.
But you broke your arm in the accident.
So You didn't have to join the Eagles
But Hamada-san died because he was disappointed with your injuries?
What do you think?
I don't care about him
Where were you the night Hamada dead ?
At hospital.
Why you ask that?
Are you sure?
You can ask the hospital
I'm sorry
You and I have a connection.
108m, you have a strong shoulder
Actually that's the same record I have.
Hello?
Where is the doctor?
He is sleeping there
A medical examination?
Yes
So Please come in
Ah, Please turn on the heater by yourself
Yes
Doctor! your patient is here
atchoo!
What's wrong?
You look fine
atchoo!.
I got cold so I was sleeping
My elbow is a little sore.
Take off your jacket
Take your seat
It's like nothing
Is it neuralgia?
You want me to give you a shot?
Hey Tane!
What's wrong?
Get ready for the injection.
Yes
I want to ask something
What?
Health insurance?
No no
I have a friend who is a medical equipment salesman.
Can you meet him once?
Oh you have come here for that
Neuralgia's just a side thing.
You don't have to do anything right now.
You are fine
I'm sorry to ask this but your X-ray is...
Our machine is old. When we get the money, we'll buy a new one.
Hey
Stretch your arms out and hold them tight.
I saw a picture of someone who had X-rays taken here the other day.
It was taken well
That my friend said
He told me to ask you which machine maker is it.
You misunderstand something.
We don't have a patient with a broken left arm.
I see.
He told me he took X-ray here
Who said that?
I don't know
Hello?
So something is wrong?
Of course it is.
Where is the photo?
Doctor, there is a call for you
OK I will go
Hello? It's me
Inuzuka, What?
Well..I'm leaving now
Hey, wait
Can I have your business card?
My business card?
Why?
Well..I'd like to meet your friend from that medical institution someday.
If so, I can bring him here
He is called Kentaro Takemura
Hello? this is Inuzuka surgency
Our doctor is out now
What?
School right?
Because I got a call from Teacher Hatano
What? Teacher  Hatano?
He came in three days ago to hand in his resignation.
I was surprised because it was sudden
He has a chest illness
I think he shouldn't overdo it
Is he in the boarding house?
He returned to his hometown
He returned to his hometown?
Where
Around here
Do you know Okuyamada Onsen?
It ’s a village near that side.
I hope he'll get better soon
Where is the Mr. Hatano's birth area?
Let me see...
He graduated from Fujikura Agricultural High School
And entered Nagano Agricultural University
That's it
Fujikura Agricultural High School...
Yes
I'm sorry but can I see his boarding note?
I want to see beginning of last month one
Yes
That's why I was against it from the beginning, if it meant crossing a dangerous bridge.
Why did this happen
But uncle...
You always said you wanted money
No one is bad
I just wanted the money
There is a guest for you
Who?
Kashiwagi-san
Kashiwagi?
Through him
Please come in
I thought you would come
Please make yourself at home
Please serve tea
Or would you like a whiskey?
Either is fine
You knew who I was.
Then it's easy to talk
Mr. Hamada died here
No
Mr. Hamada was killed here.
I'd like to talk to you about his thoughts.
Was Mr. Hamada killed after all?
You've got a poker face.
Do you think I have something to do with Mr. Hamada's poetry?
Of course
Ok Let's talk about
You can stay here
Hatano-kun
Let's think again why Mr. Hamada came here
He was staying in Nagano whenever he negotiated with Kikukawa
Why did he come to a hot spring so far away?
He came here because he had something to do here other than the Kikukawa's negotiation
For example he had promised to meet someone here
Oh, with whom?
Anyone else
Dr. Inuzuka of Surgery?
Or Kentaro Takemura?
He had promised to meet someone here
I see
By the way,Mrs.
You knew Mr. Hamada was coming here
So you guided Mr. Hamada to a special room
Then you were with Mr. Hamada all the time
You didn't give Mr. Hamada the opportunity to talk to others
When the time comes, your testimony will be ...
It was to make Hamada-san's death a suicide.
Well...Dead men tell no tales
There was no moon that day.
No one tries to climb the back mountain
Mr.Hatano
You invited him
You've successfully deceived Hamada through her.
That's interesting
It's your own imagination
So that this person's testimony is unsubstantiated
There is no evidence that this person is lying
Isn't that right?
Listen to me
This was very carefully planned.
The mastermind is you
Why me?
Hatano-kun
You had a deep grudge against Mr. Hamada
Why you think so?
About Nobuko Takemura
Hatano-kun
You are Kentaro Takemura's high school senior
And you got to know her and loved her
You can't drink but you sometime visit the bar, why?
You wanted to persuade her
But Nobuko chose Hamada over you
That's the primary motivation.
And then You were greedy
If you make Kentaro, who holds the record for longest throw, 108 meters, a great pitcher
You know you'll get big money in the future
To that end, ask Hamada to give up
You have to sell Kentaro to some team
Luckily...
Kentaro misunderstood that his sister was being played by Mr. Hamada
His left arm fracture was a lie
You got a X-rays from the surgeon, Dr. Inuzuka.
You wanted Hamada to give up
But
The fracture will heal someday
so I don't think Mr. Hamada gave up
So you suddenly came up with an idea
You planned to kill Mr. Hamada
Kashiwagi-san
Your reasoning is pretty good
I'm very impressed
but there is no evidence
Can you give the police clear evidence that I'm the culprit?
Hatano-san
On the day Hamada-san died, you asked another teacher to take his place on your shifts.
And
She is your real mother.
My scenario is perfect
Hatano-kun
You didn't cheat school papers
Kentaro!
Let me go!
Calm down!
Stop it!
Hey you! what are you doing?
Get off me!
Kentaro-kun!
Damn it!
My arm's fine.
Everyone teases me
Stop it!
Calm down,Kentaro!
Damn it!
Calm down, Toru
It's over.
I've got everything figured out.
Before the police came I....
Ball!
Change pitcher!
Safe!
What's wrong?
Kikukawa was pitching safely up to the 9th inning
He suddenly got bad
Two outs, runners on first and third, and next up is Ogihara.
There was a turbulence in the 9th inning
The game is decided by the problem of the relief pitcher
The coach's command is important
An unknown pitcher is approaching the mound
He is Takemura from Fujikura Agricultural high school
He is called a phantom pitcher
That's true
Change the Eagles player.
Pitcher replaces Takemura
Change from Kikukawa to Takemura
Pitcher Takemura uniform number 9
Shizue-san.
He is the Takemura
He is called a phantom pitcher
I worry about him
Strike!
Strike! Out!
Game set!
The Eagles win 3 to 2
Thank you for watching the game until the end today
It was a good game
Another star was born
I found out that Mr. Hamada was a first-class scout
When we were chasing Kikukawa, Hamada-san was holding the jewel.
Mr. Hamada's life is on Takemura's left arm
He will be a big pitcher who will carry the Japanese baseball world in the future
After all my dad was great as a scout
I found out that my dad has pride in his work Meet the iPhone
But scouting is a behind-the-scenes job.
Is that Ok with you?
What?
Take baseball away from me, and there's nothing left.
Can you still follow me?
So, Can I throw this away?
Yes
Hey
Let's go to visit Mr. Hamada's grave from now on
Yes,Let's take Kikukawa and Takemura together
The end