Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kyohansha / Accomplice (1958)
Please come visit our store
Enjoy your shopping.
I am very honored to be invited to Hikosuke Uchibori and Masae Yoshizawa-san's engagement party today.
This is because we, who are involved in business, believe that the path that Mr Uchibori took to achieve his current success is a living example,
and at the same time, it will surely provide many hints for the rapid development of our company in the future.
Speaking of Maruboriya, there is no one in Kyushu who doesn't know about the name.
It's all thanks to Uchibori-san that we've made such progress in the last five years.
He got a wonderful wife, Masae
and this has enabled us to establish a complete system both domestically and internationally
I think they're going to have a wonderful life.
I would like to ask you to please attend their wedding ceremony on October 3rd.
I need to add some words on the congratulatory speech by the Chairman
of the Chamber of Commerce and Industry as my congratulations
I believe it is no exaggeration to say that Uchibori Hikosuke
is the truest example of Successful people.
This is because Uchibori started out as a salesman
and has made full use of his experience
to achieve the success he has today
I have great admiration for his noble character
This concludes my congratulatory speech
Well, that's the case this month.
Thank you for everything
Next month I will bring new cups and other things
Thank you again one more time
Well, bring me new one.
We want a new design.
I contacted the head office immediately
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
You'll be staying here tonight?
Yes.
But Uchibori-san's business is also good
You travel around the country and see a lot of things.
No way.
The schedule is so packed that there is no time to look around
Well, it's hard to be tied down like me at home.
I'm not tied you up
Please make yourself at home.
Machida-san
Good evening
We met again.
how are your business?
I forget about business when I am in the bath.
I've worked as a salesman for eight years after the war.
I think this is based on that experience.
I still don't feel like you.
Uchibori-kun seems to be too sensitive
I think you'll understand my feelings soon.
I only think about what is in front of me
When I go to work, I forget about my wife and stuff.
My wife is very strong.
Mr. Machida, do you have any cheap ways to make money?
I know.
Futakumi Shikaku...
It's almost time for the bus. Shall we get ready?
Open it
Look.
The number is not set.
There're a lot.
Get your act together, it's 5 million
This is your share.
What's wrong with you? If you keep hesitating, dawn will break
Listen, as long as I'm with you today, I'll forget your name and face
We have never met or seen each other
Ok?
You are very careful, so I don't think you will spend that money right away.
Let's do it steadily for about three years.
I'm fine.
Hang in there.
What are you thinking about?
You have such a serious look on your face.
It must be about work
It's about you.
Is it true?
I think I feel strange.
someone like you become my wife.
It's started again
I didn't think you'd accept it so readily
This is all thanks to you and
and I'm really happy about his personality
I'm not joking.
Of all the men who have appeared before me up until now,
you are the one I feel the most politically and trustworthy about
I'm trustworthy?
Because I have made up my mind.
Your love for me is only from the heart...
No, Don't accepted like that.
because I love you so much, so I accepted your propose.
But a woman can't decide to get married just because she loves a man
I guess it's only good if we can respect him.
Oh my god.
I'm quick to take things the wrong way
There is one thing I really want to ask you before we get married.
I wonder if I'll ask you about it.
I believe that there should never be any secrets between people who are getting married
Well, every person has secrets, big or small
So if there's something you haven't told me before
I want you to tell me
now that it is my right to hear you as your wife.
I have no secrets to tell you
You don't have it either?
I don't have it either.
Sorry to ask you.
I know that sounds rude, but I guess I'm being a bit too cautious
It's a beautiful shell. What does it say?
Akoya shell.
I grew up on Mountain, so I don't know anything about the sea
What A bouncy girl.
Men's are boring in many ways.
That's not true,
Uchibori-san
What's been in my head for the past few years
I just wanted to make Masae happy somehow
Dad still has work to do, right?
No, I've been letting Shizo take over.
no, that's not good.
I guess you have  to take care of it after all
I know.
Go ahead.
I'll take care of the rest.
She's like that.
So please take your time
He is a craftsman.
But he is a very gentle person.
Can I take off your clothes?
My dad likes you.
Because all kinds of people come and say
all sorts of things about you
About what?
No matter what, I don't even ask
The world is so noisy,
But I didn't say anything.
I like you currently.
Hikosuke-san, you don't feel suffocated when you're in this house
No, it's not like I'm suffocated or anything like that
That's good.
Sometimes I think about tradition or the times here
I always feel like that thing is rotting from the top of my head
I envy of you,Hikosuke.
You are traveling around.
Masae.
I'm leaving.
What happened ?
I completely forgot that I had an appointment.
Say hello to your dad.
I have one thing to tell you.
All I had in my mind for the past few years
I just wanted to make Masae happy somehow
I envy of you,Hikosuke.
You are so nice.
What's wrong with you? If you keep hesitating, dawn will break
Hey, move!
The moment I step out of Takasaki, I completely forget about my house and my wife
My wife is very strong.
Takasaki.
What's wrong?
what time are you leaving tomorrow?
I will be at the store at 8 as usual,
What else you need?
Nothing.
I will be taking a day off from work
Hello, is this the telephone exchange? I'd like to know the telephone number of Takasaki
It's in the Kanto region, and my boss's name is Takasaki
My name is Takeshi Machida.
Please.
Is Machida Succeeding or Falling?
If he was on the down low and found out about
my wealth and wisdom, he would threaten me
Hello, hello. Did you find it?
Hello, no. 6714 in Takasaki. What kind of business does he do?
Writer?
thank you very much
Work hard for about three years
Hello, are you an oriental advertisement?
I would like to advertise in a local newspaper in the Takasaki area of Gunma Prefecture
Is Ryoichi-san going out fishing again?
Here's a letter for you.
Leave that there
If you work too hard, you'll ruin your health
You went to Tokyo to find a nice husband.
I thought I was relieved.
He lost his job and you are unlucky.
Yoshie want her dress painted
Take it for me mom,
I'll have time after this.
I'm disgusted with you.
You don't sew Hiroshi's shirts but you really take care of him.
That's right,
I'm like you when you were young
Don't say that.
Etsuko
I hear Hiroshi get back to the Takasaki area.
So you're coming back here?
The wish he had asked has finally come true
So I'll talk to Takeoka and find a place to stay
Because Hiroshi is back
You don't have to leave here all of a sudden
Take this
This is a letter from someone in Fukuoka
Fukuoka?
I finally got the reply!
Did you win a lottery?
The reply has come, it has come, it has come
It comes from Fukuoka,
From Fukuoka?
Are you sure?
Your card reading was right.
I'm excited.
Dear sir/Madam
Specifically, twice a month
People in Takasaki City
Please inform us of their business status and
any special personal events that may occur
The details of the transaction must never be known to the other party
A monthly salary of 20,000 yen is paid
Oh yeah!
We made it!
I'm so glad.
I'll be new's reporter.
You have to make new business card.
It's been 2 years since I lost my job.
Now I can live like a human for the first time in a long time
Don't cry.
but humans is awful
I can't believe they inform me by a piece of paper like this
For us, it was more beneficial than the protection of Kannon
Yeah.
Let's work hard!
4340 yen 67151280 yen
4320 yen for 3000 tons at 85 yen?
that's 189,837 yen
How about you Omori-san?
it's just 300 yen
Did you drink too much last night again?
Next, Aomori Prefecture.
Please calculate.
6458 yen 2700
Hello?
Call my husband.
From your wife.
It's me.
please come back
I can't.
I am so busy with the accounting today.
What are you talking about?
This is important.
I know everything about you.
Come home.
I asked about you from her right now
Anyway, I'll do that when I get home
His wife is very strong.
You too?
That's true.
She's from Akagi,Joshu.
I am from Joshu too.
You have to look for a quiet man like me
You're mean.
Where were we..
Please calculate in Aomori Prefecture, the fee is 7,620 yen
2500 tons is 5 yen, and 7565 yen.
It is 133,500 yen
Next, let's go to Akita.
3120 yen and 5250 yen
President
Oh Taguchi,
Are you back in store?
I was wondering if you could ride me on.
Go ahead.
The president,everything goes fine.
Kokura branch is set.
Let's do it in Kumamoto City next
Can we leave it to me?
You're proud of your work.
My brother is working there.
Let's buy that place and think about it
All right.
Welcome back.
I have some research to do, so don't let anyone through
The business has been normal since then,
There's no rumor about women...
This has already been the fourth time,
so I would like to take a look at your face.
In this regard, I would like to visit and greet you
and ask for your kind instructions
That's stupid.
Come in.
Hello?
Welcome.
Sorry for bothering you
I just finished,
what do you think about going out with me tonight?
What is it?
Guess what.
I have no idea.
OK?
Ok.
It's a shame my schedule is busy today
Regarding the Kokura branch,  having dinner with bank officials
Ok I'll forget
I will invite you to Nishitetsu part for making up.
In appreciation of your continued, President Maruboriya
Don't make fun of me.
Business men must be always humble.
I'm trying my best to be a good wife to you
I'm sorry you got angry.
Don't get me wrong.
so I...
don't tell me.
I already know.
There's nothing wrong with what you did past
Masae.
Tonight, as the president of Maruboriya, treat everyone with respect
Well then I'm looking forward to Nishitetsu party.
Goodbye.
If that happens, I won't stay in Takasaki.
It's the same here,
but what you stay?
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
I'll make sure he doesn't say anything.
It's Really Possible?
I do what I decide to do.
Shut up!
Get out.
What's the hell?
Are they here to watch movie?
Welcome.
Is that a lie?
Instead, we'll have to start over again
Let's go anywhere far away
Hokkaido or Kyushu that no one knows
Kyushu?
That's right, let's go to Chiba where there are nice places
I have some good friends too
You also have a client there who is a
big fan of yours and cares about you
Sorry for the wait
We had agreed to communicate twice a month,
but the other day I went to the movies with my wife
By chance, I met one of my clients, Tsuyoshi
Machida, and witnessed a glimpse of his private life
Up until now, I have reported that he have had no relationships with women
We sincerely apologize for the mistake and insufficient investigation
He has special dealings with a worker,
which caused a dispute between wife
and the business naturally became poor
Recently, the business has not been doing well,
and it has become clear that a considerable number of loan slips are in circulation
This sentence predicts that the worst
will come to his business and family.
There are plenty of excuses here too
I don't wanna see your face.
Same here
Now the whole house is yours.
We have some debts, but you'll bear with them
Just 5,6 years ago, you left house and made me trouble
and I thought I had finally settled down
You got caught by a stupid woman.
Don't do same thing happened to both of us
this is a registry office, this is a divorce notice
Please give it your stamp and deliver it to me
Are you leaving now?
You don't wanna see my face,right?
so once I've decided on where I live , please deliver my personal belongings
See you.
Even fish make fun of me.
It can't be helped.
You were unlucky
Being Salary men is miserable...
Even so, it was too bad that I got fired after 2 months.
That's fine, We will wait for good fortune once again
But now Hiroshi is transferring.
It can't be helped.
Should I go back to Tokyo and try again with working?
No, no, it's not that bad.
Why not?
It doesn't mean I work as thief.
I don't like it.
I want to make any money
I'm tired of being poor.
What?
I can't hear.
I guess it's some kind of severance pay?
but I worked only two months.
I've been waiting for a long time.
Sorry.
How much?
30,000 yen
30,000 yen?
I have notified you that I will be terminating my investigation about Takasaki ,
but I would like to start a new investigation from a different angle
Therefore, I would like to continue to push back on the deadline
The goal of the investigation is to investigate the state of affairs of Mr Takeshi Machida as an example of the failure of a small business due to family disputes
I thought you have to investigate about Machida who has been to Chiba.
For now, I will send you the enclosed 30,000 yen as an extra expense
Machida-san is the man who met at movie theater someday, right?
That's right
I know that he left their home
and went to Chiba with that woman
I don't think it's right to pry into someone else's private life
That's what I get paid for at work, so I can't help it
He's not here.
Oh my god.
What's wrong?
Look at this.
What a nice Kokura branch.
Next, we will open a branch in Kumamoto.
You will open a branch in Kumamoto too?
Maruboriya will be  top department stores in  Kyushu.
If you are loved by the president,
He will introduce you nice man.
What's wrong with the Takeoka?
It's been about half a month since the ad stopped.
He must have already gone to Chiba
And that's not the case. Takeoka is an honest man
Judging from his letters so far,
there is no doubt that he is a serious person
I bet he can't find Machida. so Machida..
Hello, masae-san?
I'm sorry, sorry
I got busy this evening so I forgot...now? but..
I'm off now
Kiku?
Are you going out to your lady's house?
Get ready for a kimono right away
There was something burnt inside the cuffs of the kimono
This is a recent Kimono, and I think it would look great on a young lady
I don't really understand
he's coming, please wait a little longer.
Don't worry.
This is your business.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Uchibori has been busy.  you decided on the clothes
Because even after marriage, I can still get divorced, so he has to choose
We have to listen to the opinions of future husband, right?
Thank you very much.
You act like someone.
Of course it's you.
I don't remember my mother's face.
Excuse me.
I wonder if all the girls these days are so arrogant?
She's pretty nice
Because I raised her.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry for bothering you so often
Wow! I think this is wonderful.
Even though you work at department store.
We sell furniture.
I think it would be nice the third one from the other side
You have a good eye.
I didn't ask you.
Sorry.
What do you think?
I don't know.
You're cold.
Oh no.
You're forcing him your own preferences.
That's fine
Uchibori
It is difficult to take care of a woman.
I had no intention of raising a child like her.
I strongly protest. you may be a master of Hakata dolls, but
But you can't create a human being.
I can move left and right and I'm a complete human being
Please.
She's like that.
They're going to find out who I am.
Takeoka
Please let me know about Machida
Departing for Kansai International Airport South
Please hurry up and get on board
You back home early.
I waited for 2 hours but he didn't come
You don't trust him after all
We're just trading land and buildings.
None of them are available.
But what should we do?
There's no other way
I'll do it no matter what. At this point, I'm just being stubborn
It was close,Takasaki's store.
It was not close
If I told you I'd make it to the store, you wouldn't have been satisfied
So you were satisfied?
You are stupid.
As you are a member of his family,
I have no choice but to show you
Here it is.
Mr. Takeshi Machida and his wife Natsuko will be staying with us for a week from July 9th,
but do you know where they are going?
Yes, please wait a moment
Call Yoshiko.
I remember it well because they stayed for 10 nights.
I see.
She was very beautiful.
He was with her.
I'm so envious that they often go out at night
Do you know where they went?
Welcome, please come in.
Sorry, come in.
Hello, please. I'd like to ask you something
I'm sorry, but do you know anyone called Machida?
Do you know anyone called Machida?
He was in this house
He moved out the day before yesterday.
Do you know where he went?
I have no idea.
Everyone in my house is out
Where he went? He is with a woman.
It's different every time I check my fortune
It's like a recent weather forecast.
I see.
I should have taken that money and gone to Tokyo.
Stop doing anything like that.
Wait, Yeah.
Southwest.
Southwest?
So..
In the sea.
How can I go there?
I see, I can't keep doing this forever
Why don't you try contacting the manager of Omori again?
but it was a waste.
We shouldn't have come to Chiba.
Why don't we just give up on this unnecessary life like that?
What do we do?
We'll just have to work harder.
I'm sick of that story now
I gave up on the dressmaking shop.
At least we get a sewing machine
No kidding
How much do you think you can make by sewing from morning till night?
Currently, there is no salary of 20,000 yen per month.
buy some watermelon.
buy me some cigarettes too.
killed the driver and lost 2000 yen.
There are people who can kill a human being for just 2000
I have certainly received the 30,000 yen in funds addressed to a hotel in Chiba
I apologize for the lack of reporting
After that, the true end
I finally found out that Machida was living with his cousin
It seems that the opening in Chiba is not going as expected
He's been feeling a bit depressed lately, so I've been going to bicycle races and other events
However, living in a hotel would be inconvenient for research and would involve unnecessary expenses,
so I am thinking of moving into an affordable apartment
I'm sorry to say this,
but could I borrow 30,000 yen as the key money and 20,000 yen
as the security deposit in total 50,000 yen in advance?
I'll deduct 2000 yen from each of my salaries to repay you,
so please prepare 50,000 yen in cash
50,000 yen?
President, this is just arrived
What's wrong?
Isozaki manager just came.
He wants you to use this
No way.
I just started to use club, I don't need all that fine stuff
You'll probably end up to buy.
If that's the case, then
When did you become a golf club salesman?
Sorry
Hello, is this Sumiyoshi's residence?
Is your daughter there?
No worry.
Well then,
please wait a moment.
Sorry to have kept you waiting
Masae, please don't threaten me.
I won't know if it gets stolen
Where on earth were you going, still leaving it open?
I was meeting with a regular customer.
And you?
flowers?
Let me send you
Please take me to your house. I won't disturb you
It's ok.
I want to meet Kiku for the first time in a while and meet you again. I'm doing well
Is she ok?
That girl is a little strange, but she's also kind to me
She was with us for 3 years.
Mr. Machida gave up on opening store and ran out Chiba like a runner.
Natsuko left him.
He was very depressed.
He headed to the Kansai region alone
It seems like recovery is almost hopeless,
but in any case
Machida seems to have differentiated itself for some reason
Tell me whether to continue the investigation or not.
I look forward to your support.
He's going to look for me
Damn, what is he planning
on doing looking for me?
It's been a while
It's amazing, you can have a branch in Kokura. too
You did a good job
Yes, I heard you have a girlfriend and are getting married soon
What do you want?
Don't make that face.
I won't ruin your happiness. You did a good job
On the contrary, I am very miserable.
But it's amazing how much they managed to accomplish with that amount of capital
We have never met or seen each other
We promised like that.
I guess so
The more I fall, the more I miss you
You...
I'll be relaxing in Fukuoka for a while
Get out.
Are you sure?
You will lose everything.
Give me half of your money.
Can you?
Oh you.
You were drowning.
Get out.
Let's watch on Machida.
I'll keep trying until the end.
Please try to relax a little more.
When did you come?
Right now
You didn't notice me.
You were like crazy.
Because it doesn't hit very often
I get irritated easily
my skills are apparently poor.
I guess that's true,
unfortunately
It's due to psychological reasons?
Does it look like that to you?
It's definitely strange, it's completely different from your usual swing
What's wrong?
Nothing . I just can't hit it.
Lie, come on, confess me
No way.
I don't owe you.
I don't owe you too.
I already had my husband's secrets before we got married
I'm not feeling well so I'll leave.
Machida, who came to Osaka, has almost no money.
He tried to live in a succession of friends' houses.
but it seems that no one is willing to help him.
Machida, which left Osaka, arrived in Kobe a
few days later and is currently working labor.
Get out
Work hard.
Machida moved to Okayama
He lives in a construction company as a temporary worker.
He is definitely looking for me.
Hello?
No no!
He probably don't know that I am in Fukuoka.
But he's coming, he's coming
Machida came to Onomichi.
Machida seems to be looking for acquaintances.
A business man.
He was looking for a businessman for the can business.
All I did was tail him.
I didn't know who he was looking for.
I will be moving to chase Machida.
Please arrange for the payment to be sent to my wife in Chiba.
Who?
This kind of person would like to meet you.
This person came all the way from Nagoya.
From Nagoya?
What kind of person?
He says He know about you well.
Who?
I'll get you him.
Taguchi.
Are you president Uchibori?
I am Gen Okamoto, and I have just given you my business card
I put in charge of sales in Kyushu
and when I visited the area,
the president of Marubori Department Store
happened to be carrying this trunk
I knew that you were my senior, so I visited you.
Thanks in advance.
Have a seat.
It's amazing.
You made it.
What can I do for you?
Here it is. Please look at this
Why don’t you delete this?
In fact, when I received this bag from the company three months ago,
I intuitively believed that someone with this name must be successful
I'll ask you about the secret of success.
Wow, that's really surprising
I was able to meet you at the end.
This is awesome.
so I'd like to see the key to success
There is no such thing, I'm busy
However, I was able to meet you here
I'm glad.
In 5 minutes ok
I want you to learn a lesson from you.
I'm sorry, but go home.
Tell Taguchi-kun that and gave him a car.
I didn't come here for such a trivial matter.
but I'm going to do my job anyway
I will be traveling around Kyushu and then returning to your area in two weeks
Let me revisit.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Let me take this.
The world seems wide but it's a small place
I'm sorry.
Has he gone home?
Taguchi-kun?
I'll never meet a stranger again, you know
Hello?
don't do anything unnecessary
Who told me to answer the phone?
Are you Kiku?
Hikosuke is there?
Hello, hello, hello,
hello, it's me
Sorry, sorry, I was trying to sleep.
No, it's nothing big
I'm sure I'm tired. I'm going to rest for another 2,3 days
Thanks a lot
Do not enter this room while I'm out.
But...
Don't do anything unnecessary.
Masae-san has asked you about me me for something?
You're reporting some of my actions to Masae-san, right?
Oh, right?
I don't.
Are you doing it yourself?
Or Masae-san asked you?
I really feel sorry for her
Please make sure your make her happy
Get out.
I really feel sorry for her
He has about 10 days off.
We are also opening a branch in Kokura,
so we are in trouble.
What happened?
It seems like he's neurotic.
he's neurotic?
He doesn't meet anyone.
and doen not answer the phone
I see. I have some urgent business and I really wanted to see him
I asked about here at the post office.
at the post office?
please tell him that a man named Takeoka
wants to see him on urgent business
Mr. Takeoka?, I understand
But I don't know when I'll be able to tell him. So excuse me
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go home now
It's too late.
let's go, let's go, let's go!
Machida has arrived in Shimonoseki.
With no one to rely on and no money,
he lives alone in a shed used for cable construction on Mt. Volcano
He lives like a homeless person
Moreover,he's been sick for about a week now and am currently in bed
Machida seems to still be searching for someone,
and while he's here
He sent a letter to his cousin in Chiba,But I don't know what it is
Damn, he's finally here, what should I do?
Hikosuke?
I finally find you.
you're not at the office and I can't get through to you on the phone
I'm sorry,
Please wait a little longer
What am I waiting for?
Tell me.
Do you have any concerns?
No.
Let's go home.
But I'm sorry for causing your dad unnecessary worry
My father has been in Shimonoseki since yesterday for a business meeting
It seems like our family is a bit depressed without our father around
Can I think for a week?
For what?
I don't think it's going to be of much use to someone like me to ask
I want to think about you suffering in my own way
Is that bad?
But I can't say
It's fine, I won't be shaken by any new things
I grew up with only one guy
Masae...
Tell me.
No matter what you say, I can't say it
Please, wait a little longer
So I can talk about everything
If that's all, why can't you tell now?
Why?
Because I don't want to lose you
Masae-san, please wait for another week, no, three days
It may be natural for wait.
But I can't wait, I'm that kind of girl
I like Hikosuke
but you won't tell me anything
You don't like me?
No..., I don't want to lose you
That's right. I don't want to lose Hikosuke either.
Please tell me.
I'll definitely talk to you tomorrow or the night after tomorrow.
Wait, I'll ask you one more time
Can you please tell me that?
What's wrong?
I called out to Uchibori-san
but he just walked away without even turning around
Dad.
Don't get surprised by what I say.
I'm not surprising.
I've been with you 20 years
I might not marry Hikosuke.
Oh you have it.
Can you handle it?
I'll teach you.
Don't forget the important things, they're bullets.
Can I board with you again?
No!
I'm in hurry.
I'll kill him.
For me and Masae.
To Shimonoseki.
Wake up,Machida!
Machida!
Uchibori-san
You are finally here.
Who are you?
Takeoka.
I'm employed by you
communicator,Ryoichi Takeoka
Takeoka?
Yes.
I want to say nice to meet you
I went to see you but you wouldn't let me see you, so I called you.
and I showed the evidence
What kind of evidence is that?
About the murder.
Six years ago, you killed the branch manager of a bank
You stole 5 million yen in bills
You will be honest
So what is your purpose in that?
Don't rush to conclusions
When I received an order from Chiba and a special allowance
I vaguely smelled a crime
Just to be sure, if I ask you to send me money, you will have to send money easily.
I thought this was for sure thing.
My wife asked me to report it to police.
Well then, I don't want to repay the favor.
I was visiting the bank and the newspaper that I finally got to know about the murder
Thanks to this, I was able to see the back of Japan
But there was a thrill here too
The final communication
You didn't realize that the post stamp was made in Fukuoka
That actually had to be sent from Shimonoseki
I asked my wife
But she just couldn't accept it,
We ended up becoming a fighting.
I had no choice but to leave it up to fate
What happened to Machida?
that person?
He was very depressed in Chiba.
Now he's recovered and am doing great
I've never seen such a strong man. He's different from you
He completely forgot about the past
He is a total villain.
You want money?
Yes.
How much would you give me?
My wife is good at dressmaking.
I wanted to have her open a small shop in Tokyo
How much is enough?
Well...
If I had money like the one you held six years ago,
I could make a name for myself
You are total villain.
I was originally a serious businessman just like you
But Three years of unemployment ruined me.
Ok let's deal.
Now you can marry the Sugiyoshi girl with peace of mind
How you know?
I did my best.
So let's hurry up
We'll make it to the next cable car.
Let's hurry
Who?
It's better to move
Machida.
Wait.
You're Takeoka,right?
I've known about what you've done for a long time.
That clerk, Omori, is a man who is weak when it comes to money
He made a deal with you the first time you met.
I moved to Chiba and gradually began to understand your feelings
Since then, I've followed you around and made it this far
Uchibori.
If we let this guy live, we'll ruin.
Now it's your turn
Clean it up quickly.
it's my fault
Forgive me, forgive me
I apologize for that.
Shoot him,Uchibori!
Let me go!
Shoot him.
Why didn't you shoot?
You were looking for me to kill me
He was killed.
He was killed?
Takeoka?
Takeoka!
Hello?
Etsuko!
You.
Ok that's done.
It's hot and muggy. There's no wind at all
To be honest, when your wife jumps in,
I had no idea what was going on
But thanks to that, it didn't become a crime
You have to be grateful to your wife.
This brings an end to a cold case
We are celebrating,
You were just tired.
Well, luckily there were few injuries
I don't know what would have happened to you if you hadn't had a wife.
Yes, seriously.
We are glad this problem was solved.
Please take this opportunity to think seriously.
Yes.
But still, it's late.
Maybe it's time , it's coming soon.
Here we come, Let's go.
But you did come up with a plan for the detective novel.
THE END