Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Tokyo, a large city with a population of 10 million
Tokyo is the center of the Japanese economy
Tokyo dominates Japan.
People gather in Tokyo for power
Young people are on a course to excel in high school and college.
And compete and win the entrance exam.
They have to fight for a career after joining the company
They are busy with competition every day
There are many terrifying traps in this world
Midday trap
That document will be ready soon
Yes here it is
My opinion is different
In the old days, products were sold only by brand name
But it's different now
I think the quality and price of the product is important
But from the European market, you don't have to think so pessimistically
You're not thinking straight.
Your thoughts were completely useless at the last planning meeting
Especially about private railway metal companies
OK I get it
Thank you
Fuji-kun, I'm sorry but
Put together a report on the company's oil demand outlook in 10 years.
Yes
Here is the document
Mr. Tokue, the chief of staff, is no good
They both joined the company at the same time.
Mr. Furuya failed to work four years ago
Even so, Mr. Fuji is 32 years old and is the chief of staff.
Mr. Fuji will be the section chief in three years.
Then Mr. Fuji will rise faster than Mr. Miyama.
He will definitely be an executive in the future
Fuji-san told me that Salary men have to join a prestigious company.
And work hard at the company
And to marry a beautiful woman
I see
So Fuji-san is still single
Yes he is
He has a lot of plans
Thank you for your work
Thank you
Fuji-san
I need to talk with you
Sorry, I'm busy
Ready!
How many times have you done this?
Today is the 6th day
You are pretty good
Thank you
You're not very good at this.
I was doing right way
Is it Churchill?
I don't know.
This is my first time
No wonder
Why?
Because first-timers are slow to shoot, or you were very fast to shoot.
I wasn't aiming for the target.
Fuji-kun
Are you going back?
I need to go for some places
I want to be here too, but I'll leave the rest to you
I see
See you
Is he your company person?
He is my boss
He was studying abroad in England so he has a lot of orders
But your seem to be smarter
Not at all
Do you still want to continue?
Yes please
Why don't you join me?
Well...I'm not good at shooting
I apologize to you what I said
When will you come next?
Why you ask me?
I want to teach you because you are so beautiful
But I'm sure you'll be disappointed
Fuji-san is not coming yet
He either comes early and waits or comes late
I heard that shooting costs money
I think so
According to him, golf is obsolete.
Anyway he is great
He always does things as calculated
He is steadily on the career track
He is cool
Watch out for him.
To him a woman is like a cigarette
I like a pale man like him
He is the type who splits up immediately after sleeping with a woman
You still like him?
Some women can't leave him.
You seem confident
Why don't you go out with him?
I should?
I can go out with him
Hey you!
Mr. Furuya seems to be annoyed
Furuya,
How is your relationship with that beautiful female doctor?
Why you ask me?
It's not your business
It seems that there are many men who like her
Fuji-san often see her too
I'm sure he'll succeed if he makes a move.
He has come
Hi
Welcome,
you seem to be busy
We were talking about you
Talking bad about people who aren't there is a stress reliever for office workers.
It's good to think about career advancement, but be careful of women
Can I have a splash of water, please?
I offer my abilities and make money
My private life is none of your business.
Mr. Domoto will talk about the progress of sales to Southeast Asia.
He wants to meet you
Excuse me for a while
What's wrong?
Sorry I made you wait
I'll get right on it.
The draft of the expansion plan of Toyo Metal has been completed.
so I brought it to you
Oh thank you
Please tell Domoto and Miyazaki to come here
By the way
Are you hiding something from me?
Am I?
I'm not hiding anything from you
That's what I thought but
Please state clearly what you want to know
Actually, I heard strange rumors today
I heard that Ueki-kun will be removed from the board of directors in the next executive re-election.
Is that true?
No way
He will of course be reelected
I think so
You know the relationship between me and Ueki-kun.
I don't think you'll do that because you're the president
Hello?
Fuji-san,
Kasumi-san has come to see our president. why he has come?
I think it was a personnel change, so I did some digging.
But I have no idea
This is a bullshit article.
I will buy the information from you high
Hello? Ok connect to me
Hello?
I'm Fuji
Yes, that's fine
6pm?
I'm waiting in the usual place
See you then
Suzuki-kun
Yes
I'm going out.
Please tell the chief that you will be back at 5 o'clock
Yes
Fuji-san...
Please give me some information
Welcome
Is she in?
Do you want to see her?
Hi
Welcome
Please come in
Thanks
You know what.
Did you see someone from my company?
Well..I have no idea
Excuse me
Are you sure you're okay to come to work?
I have a small favor of you
What is it?
I worry
Actually, please lend me 20,000 yen by the 25th
20,000 yen?
Yes
What for?
I have to spend money suddenly tonight
It's okay if it doesn't work
Why you ask me?
It's the closest I could get.
I am very honored to be asked
Thanks
Please write a loan book for the time being
I will
For sure
Fuji!
Are you free tonight?
No, I'll have something to do
I have something to talk to you
Say it here
Actually.I want to ask you about Ms. Akatsaka
Furuya,
Tell you clearly
I'm not interested in Ms.Akatsuka at all
I'm relieved to hear that
I tell you. I'll marry to her
Don't say any more
It's none of my business
See you
What's wrong?
I feel strange,
When I first met you at the shooting range, I thought you were just a girl
Now?
I'm getting confused about you
Really?
Do you investigate my identity?
I gave up it
But You are a woman I have never met
You check time often
Because I need to go
I wonder who wait for you
Well...you said you gave up to investigate my identity
Hello? call me a cab
And bill please
Let me pay
Oh
I have money today
When can I see you next time?
I'll call you
Sorry
What's wrong?
I have something to talk with you
What?
Tell me quickly.
I'm going to have a baby.
Anyway Come home
Last time I gave you 10,000 yen to get an abortion.
I'll return this money.
Who said return this?
I tell you many times
It just happened on a company trip.
It wouldn't have happened if you weren't drunk
In other words we were just out of luck with each other
Do you want to give birth to a child to take revenge on me?
Why you are having my baby?
Because I want a baby
You want a baby?
Even so, I won't marry you
You love Ms.Akatsuka,right?
Who said that?
No one told me
So You're just saying crap
You are pregnant but  I don't know if it's my child
I heard you were playing a lot with  guys
Fuji-san
There is a call from Akatsuka
Thank you
Hello?
Why you know this phone number?
You gave me your business card
Oh I see
Can you keep it secret that you met me?
You don't have to worry about it.
I won't tell anyone.
Humans are complex creatures.
Because a woman is over 30 years old and single is strange
Not only for women
Yeah
I know Yasue Moniya is there
Why you know?
I'm thinking of moving
All the bad things happen lately
Really?
I believe you have an introduction to marriage.
Mr.Furuya?
He is a very pure man
Ah,Fuji-kun
The director is calling you
I get it
Did you go to Akasaka yesterday?
No.
I went to Ginza, why?
It was a mistake
Trends in the Asian market of West German affiliates
They are investigating sales plans for biomachines
Right?
Yes
Send a telegram to the Berlin dead right now.
Oh,Fuji-kun
It was decided at the board meeting yesterday.
I want you to go to Europe if you are not inconvenient
What? to Europe?
If you're going, you'll leave in the middle of next month, and the duration will be a year.
in the middle of next month?
Is there something wrong?
Well..no
I was surprised to hear that out of the blue.
I want you to do an export job when you return
Thank you
How old are you now?
I'm 32
Managing Director Domoto studied abroad when he was 35 and I was 37.
You are lucky
You are one of the best executive candidates
Good luck
Thank you very much
That's very sudden.
If you leave in the middle of next month, you only have about 20 days left.
Yeah
So please meet me
yeah, when?
Tomorrow, Sunday
Then I'll be waiting at the usual place
No, I'll visit your home
What?
I'm not comfortable outside
But...
IS that bad?
What's wrong with you?
Come in
Are you interested in where I live?
I don't mean that
You want to know who I am,right?
How many years are you going to Europe?
About a year
That's so long
I'll be lonely without you
I go to the shooting range alone again
I had a strange relationship with you
I don't want to leave you without knowing anything about you.
When you found out we were splitting up, you became very bossy.
I love you
What?
You know why I'm here?
I found this place to be the safest.
If you meet with me, no one will come to see you today.
Don't say that, please.
From the beginning you didn't think I was a normal female, right?
But...
Didn't you think I'm Kasumi-san's woman?
Are you scared?
He is very powerful
He's easy to fire me
You'll leave from me?
I'll take you away from him.
Good morning
I'm sorry
You don't seem to look at the newspaper
Ms. Akatsuka was killed
What?
Good morning
Was she killed by a robbery?
There was no mention of it in the papers.
I'm sorry
For you and for her
I had nothing to do with it.
You sure?
It can be dangerous to have a woman alone
You had better get married early
With the father of the child on your stomach
Fuji-san
The truth is, I'm not pregnant.
Good morning
I didn't do it because Akatsuka-san taught me to lie.
She taught you?
Yes
I got angry when I heard from Mr. Furuya about your relationship with Ms.Akatsuka
I told her about a company trip with you in addition to the results of the pregnancy test
I thought it would be good for her to get away from you.
I'm sorry but I didn't love her
Oh she said same
So she told me to lie that I was pregnant
I thought you might be willing to get married
I thought I could get a reward from you even if it didn't work
You look very troubled.
I think the police will investigate the person related to her
But don't worry,
I won't talk anything
I decided to quit the company and get married this month
Good morning
It seems that Dr. Akatsuka was killed.
Hey, cheer up
I don't know what you think but
She is not the subject of your marriage
You suspected that I and she had a relationship
I went to her hospital to get money from her
Money?
Of course there was interest
Damn it
The loan book I wrote the other day should be at her place
That's inconvenient
Let me see the news paper
No matter where you are last night, it has nothing to do with the murder
I don't think so.
I have a loan book I wrote in her house
loan book?
Actually, I borrowed 20,000 yen from her a week ago
If the police find it, the police will look into my alibi
But what time was that person killed yesterday?
It seems to be around 3 pm
3 pm?
So What will you do?
I can't tell anyone I've met you.
No one know that
Only you can prove my alibi
Just in case, If they find out about my relationship with Himako...
Mr.Kasumi will get angry
I may get rid of the company
I need alibi
Thinking too much makes my head hurt
I need a natural alibi
Oh yeah!
It's unusual for him to come to the bar alone and drink so much
He's a little crazy today
He also has that kind of thing
Oh welcome
Let's drink again
Your executive...
That dirty man
Mr.Domoto?
I'll toast for him
I'll toast for Yuzaki department chief
Cheers!
let's toast for Oike department chief
He works so hard,
Cheers!
I'll toast for Miyama department chief
Miyama?
I hate him
What's wrong?
It's non of your business
I'll toast for Fuji chief
You are so nice today
You seem to have an ulterior motive.
It's up to you
Because you are still single
What time is it?
It's 10 am
I had seven years of no tardiness, no absenteeism, and it was for nothing.
Because you drunk so much
I also have a hangover
Did you have anything with Mr. Miyama?
Well...nothing
Why you ask me?
You were in a bad mood when you talked about him yesterday
I was?
I'm drunk so I don't remember anything
You OK?
I'll take this
Are you Satoru Fuji?
Yes
We are the police.
We would like to talk to you about Ms. Akatsuka's case.
OK
You mean that loan book?
I suddenly needed money for a private matter
You are the chief of a large company, right?
You are single, right?
I don't save money
Our salary is not as good as you think
If I have a special relationship with her, I won't write a loan book
I see
By the way,Where were you between 2 pm and 4 pm when the incident happened?
That's a very unpleasant question for me
I'm sorry
Because this is my job
Ask as many people as I can, the more chances I have of finding a clue.
Please understand us
I was watching a movie at the cinema that time
Ar star cinema?
Yes
Did you meet someone in the cinema?
Well...there was nothing.
And I heard that there is a person in your company who has a special relationship with her.
I have no idea
We just refer to it.
I'll keep what you say secret
My colleague Furuya said he wanted to marry her
Mr.Furuya
And?
He sometimes went to her clinic
Please make a copy of this minutes
Ah, chief
What?
Is it true that Mr. Furuya was called by the police?
Police are investigating who was in and out of her clinic
They has asked me
They has asked you?
Yes
The section chief is calling you
Hello
I get it
I'll go there now
Welcome
Hi
How are you?
I thought it was not good to talk at the company
Is it because of the police?
I felt very unpleasant
The police are suspicious of you too
Mr. Furuya also said he's going to marry Mr. Akatsuka, so he's quite suspected by the police.
He had an alibi because he was hiking to the mountains that day with a colleague from the company
By the way The police have asked me a lot about you
You have an alibi, right?
Yes I was watching a movie
That's good
I'm sorry to worry you
Anyway, the police are very persistent when they suspect something.
I think you should prove your innocence early
I know
Let me tell you something else.
Did you hear anything from Director Yuzaki?
Well
I see.
You've been through a lot, haven't you?
I think you don't have to worry because you have an alibi
I was relieved to hear that
By the way, about your study abroad in Europe
That has been postponed
The company wants to let you go after your innocence has been proven.
So you need to wait
Do the police trust what you said?
I have no idea
What if your alibi isn't recognized?
Then I have no choice but to talk about you
It's not good.
If you tell them that, we're over
So What will you do?
I have no choice but to find the culprit myself
I absolutely have to find the culprit who is annoying us
It's the only way to save me.
I'm so scared
Don't worry. you'll be fine
I'll handle it.
Oh..She was murdered, wasn't she?
Is that true?
Yes
I'm sorry
By the way, The man she brought with her, is he a regular here?
He is not
But you know about him,right?
I can't talk about customer information
This is for keeping quiet.
I only know his name
He is a person who speaks Osaka dialect called Mr. Sonoda.
Osaka dialect?
Yes
What kind of work does he do?
He said he was in the finance business in Hibiya.
Thank you for waiting
Who lives here now?
teacher ’s aunt.
Is she a doctor after all?
No,She is a Christian grandmother
Can I work in your company's medical office?
I am qualified as a nurse
You had better ask Miyama than to me
I don't like him
Why?
Well...
Oh yeah,
I'd better to ask Yuzaki
He ’s the director, right?
Has he ever come?
Yes 4,5 times before
What kind of questions were you asked by the police?
They asked who was often coming
Then
I told them all I knew
Tokioka and Futuya from the Yachiyo company
and you
You told them about me
Is Tokioka a person in the sales department?
Did Miyama also come often?
He was here a lot, but he was quiet.
Do you know a man called Sonoda?
Sonoda?
He is a financial company who speaks Osaka dialect
I don't know.
There was no such person in the patient
Give me some water
Why do you think she was killed?
The police asked me that, but I don't know
What did she do on her days off?
She always went out late at night
She had a date?
I'm not privy to any personal secrets.
That's personal
You are educated
Here it is
What is this?
I don't want any hush money.
I don't mean that.
Go see a movie with your boyfriend next vacation
Bill please
Thank you for waiting
Please come in
So what can I do for you?
I want to ask you something
Ok
You're talking about profit?
What was your relationship with Yayoi Akatsuka?
Yayoi Akatsuka?
You were in a fight with her in Akasaka 5 days before she was killed,right?
You know very well so I can't pretend I don't know
She and I are acquaintances at the time of Osaka medical university
Osaka medical university
Yes
I met her when I was hospitalized for a stomach ulcer
She was working at a hospital in Osaka at that time
I loved her at first sight
But she didn't like me
But I realized she likes money
So I spent money on her
I introduced her to stocks and land
Made her about 50 million profits
So I could have sex with her one time
But that one was the problem
Since then I have never forgotten about her
Actually, I called her because I wanted to take about sea business with her
sea business?
It's sea
It ’s about making money on landfill rights.
I told her I would mediate if she wanted to resell in the future
However, the landfill was decided last year.
The price went up because a company in Tokyo said it would buy the right
The price has increased 12 times
So I tried to mediate that
But she turned it down
She broke her promise.
I told her to sleep with me if so
I spoke like this
But it turned out that way.
I was busy having been in Osaka for about 3 days
And I was surprised to see the newspaper
So you were in Osaka on the day of the case
Yes, I went to Arima with my wife
Come to think of it I was lucky
If I were in Tokyo I would have been suspected like you guys
Thank you for everything
You have bad taste.
You don't need me to reminder of my bad experiences.
If you don't like it, please say it clearly
You used to have something with Chief Miyama
I don't even want to hear his name
I had a relationship with him for about a year
Why do you hate him now?
He wanted to borrow 300,000 yen from me.
From you?
I was surprised.
He used to give me money
I was so angry that I told the madam of the bar about it.
Then Madame, on the contrary, got angry with me
But for some reason did you need such a lot of money today?
He seems to have had a problem with his wife
He married the daughter of an executive in order to get ahead in his career.
I didn't know that
It seems that his wife's husband's company went bankrupt and needed money.
How much?
He said 5 million yen
He made the money?
Well...I have no idea
He said he would borrow money from a financial institution at a high interest rate
Then he stopped seeing me
Humans without money are scary
To be honest,I don't want to investigate Chief Miyama with you.
But the criminal who killed her may be in front of us
I'm sure there was something happening to Miyama and her
It's none of my business
But you were thinking of marrying her, right?
Don't you want to know who killed her?
No
Why?
I loved her but
In fact, I thought I'd marry her to win you over.
Hey,win me over?
What do you mean?
I was going to use her to destroy you.
I thought I had to spend money because I wasn't talented
Hey you really mean it?
I mean it
But she was killed and the plan was ruined
But fortunately
I wasn't the only one whose plans collapsed
You also made a bad impression on your work in this case
I'll tell you what.
I don't work with you
What should I do?
Miyama is certainly suspicious
But I can't do anything alone
The police haven't asked me anything since.
Police may not even pursue my alibi
Fuji-kun
What is this?
This does not show the movement of the economy
I don't think I'm doing a subjective analysis
Don't flatter yourself.
Your work these days is useless
And you're no good at leading your subordinates.
You are the section chief
chief
Stop saying it in front of everyone
What?
It's a loss to turn me into an enemy
What do you mean?
I know the problem of your personal life
I have no secret not like you
Rewrite the report anyway
The police are here,Fuji chief
Let's talk here
about the case?
I'll contact them
Thanks
Come in
Sit down
We are ready
I see
I'm Inspector Tadokoro at the headquarters
I will ask you a little for reference
I heard that your personal life was pretty disturbed
You weren't in a normal state of mind,right?
You didn't have to kill her
Don't say bullshit
Do you suspect me for murder?
See? that man?
Is that the person who came to the cinema with you to hear the show time?
Don't worry, he can't see us
You are rude
If I'm innocent, do you take responsibility?
I will hold you all accountable by any means necessary.
Please calm down,Fuji-san
You speak like a bad guy
Your attitude is very bad
Please stop threatening me.
It will be a human rights issue
It's a favor to us that we're interviewing you here instead of at headquarters.
Do you understand?
Why did you lie,Fuji-san?
You said you watched the movie from 2 o'clock to 4 o'clock
I was not lying
I was watching
If you don't admit the lie, I'll formally get an arrest warrant.
You can do whatever you want
Then I'll do it
This mirror is a magic mirror
I had the receptionist at the movie theater look at your face
The day after the incident you went to hear the movie theater show time
When she was killed
I was with a person
Who is the person?
I can't tell the name
If you don't say it, there is no alibi.
Of course I didn't kill anyone
What's wrong with Fuji chief?
Yachiyo Metal Employee Suspected of Murder
I think the police are confident because they have reached the company
It became a big problem
Kasumi's wife was dead?
Yes
So He's going to marry you
I don't think so
You'll have to wait and see.
Please come and visit us again to take a break
Ah welcome
She was waiting for you
Please come in
You want drink?
I don't want
Make yourself at home.
I thought you won't come
Did you see the newspaper
I didn't tell the police your name
I would be perjury if I stayed this way
I wanted to see you
Do the police think you have something to do with the case?
I have no idea
I think the police will arrest me soon if they really suspect
When you call me
Kasumi was there
He knows about us
So He told our company about us
What does he think of us?
He never forgive us
He takes revenge
Let's run away with me
Let's go out of his sight
Welcome
Mr.Miyama is waiting for you
Mr.Miyama?
Yes
What's wrong?
I was worried because you were absent without notice
Sorry
In fact, I'm here to say sorry
Sorry for the other day
I had a quarrel with my wife and was in a bad mood
It's not good to feel bad at home.
I don't care at all
Please sit down
I saw the news paper
Yuzaki department chief worry about you
How is the situation?
I've had a bad experience.
I'm sorry to bother the company
The executives' feelings about that are very bad.
I'm defending you
The impression of our company got worse because it was written in the newspaper this time.
How about your alibi
My alibi was recognized by the police today
That's good to hear
You should worry about yourself
What does that mean?
You're struggling to come up with the money.
You tried to borrow money from a woman in a bar
Kana, right?
Do you trust what she says?
In addition, you went to see Dr. Akazsuka from time to time
What's that all about?
Because I was sick
Are you sure?
She seems to have had a lot of money
What does that mean?
Eh? so what?
You think too much
I will definitely find the truth
Do whatever you want
I don't care if you threaten
Oh you, I wonder who is he
How long have you been working at this hospital?
Since a week ago
How do you know I work here?
I asked that Christian aunt
Did you come to ask me about that incident again?
I fed up with it
It's not.
I don't care about her
I'm here to ask you out
Wow nice
Can you go?
I'm working until 8 o'clock tonight
So I can play with you
You are too good
I will pick you up later
Actually I saw many times
The wall in my room was broken and next door was the her room
I could see
She kicked me out every time a man came
You took a peek at the revenge
You are bad girl
Did you always see?
Not always
I saw your sex
What?
Do you afraid?
I saw Futuya and Tokioka's sex
Did you see Miyama's?
Miyama-san and her are unrelated
I don't think so
I saw him out from her house
Miyama-san and her are unrelated for sure
I know all.
Your face tells so
Fuji-san
What?
Don't tell anyone
Sure
Trust you?
Of course
In fact, I saw Miyama
He was, after all, one of them.
No. he is not
He borrowed money from her
I was surprised and made a noise
So you were caught peeking and you got mad.
I was caught by them when I tried to escape
And they told me not to tell anyone.
If I'm sued, I'll be guilty
It was 3 million yen in total
Miyama gave her a receipt and documents, didn't he?
Yes many
I think it's a mortgage document
But it's strange
Police have not found that document after the incident
So Yayoi Akazuka left those documents with someone else or
Miyama stole it
I'm scared.
Don't tell anyone I talked to you
Do not worry
I don't tell anyone
Really?
Your working condition seems to be very bad these days.
I know you're upset.
But Think a little seriously
By the way, you want to take a vacation
Yes
I want a week off
For what?
I'm going to find out about the incident the other day
It's a police job
If you want to find the culprit, be the police
If nothing is done, it will affect my credit
Don't say bullshit
This is also the credit of the company
The company's credibility has fallen as reported in the newspaper
You don't understand?
This can't be helped anymore
You should act carefully from now on
Yes
I was sorry
Find out more about this article
I see
Thanks
There is a call from Mr.Kasumi
Mr.Kasumi?
You seem to have something to do with Hisako
No way
I want you to take out some documents from the company
As a compensation to me
Recently Yachiyo Metals is planning to build a new factory
It seems that the place is also decided
But I don't know where
Yuzaki has The documents
Get it at the shooting range at 10am the day after tomorrow
There will be a board meeting from 10 o'clock tomorrow
Yuzaki will be there
If you succeed, I'll forget all about Hisako
By the way,Do you know Mr. Miyama appeared to the police and said you were suspicious?
Really?
I know a lot of information
Stop here
Hello?
Oh...Kasumi...
It's his trap that he approved our relationship
I won't say anything
What are you going to do than that
I have no choice but to obey him
He has a meeting tomorrow, so I'll see what I can do.
See you
Sorry I'm late
You work late
I'm always skipping work so
Good night
You can't find the documents?
I don't think so
I will wait till tomorrow
About your alibi, tell Naoko to appear at the police and testify.
You haven't fulfilled my promise yet, but I will help you
Anyway you bring the document or I'll do something to you
Come here, Fuji-kun
It's hard to say, but There was a private announcement from the personnel manager
You're being transferred to Osaka, Mikawa-kikai.
To Mikawa-kikai?
Of course, it has a job title
But that is a very small company
I think I have a much better position over there.
That's bullshit
Listen, Fuji-kun
The incident during this time gave a very bad impression to the company.
You know,right?
Yuzaki chief had no choice but to do this
I have something to tell you in secret
I heard you said the police suspected me and Furuya.
What?
Listen
I'll tell the police everything as you did to the police
Tell the police the fact that you killed her
Don't say bullshit
I know you borrowed 3 million yen from her
A girl told me
But the collateral you deposited and the loan book are nowhere to be found.
So you killed her and robbed her of the documents
It's not true
I tell the police everything I want to do
Wait
It is true that I borrowed 3 million yen as you say
But I didn't kill her
I tell you everything
She was so black-hearted.
She demanded three times the interest she'd promised.
I went to ask her that day
But she was already dead
I was surprised to take the documents and ran away
This is true.
Trust me
I wonder the police trust you
Even if the police believe
It will be a problem in the company
You will be like me or you will be fired
Because This is a criminal issue
I don't tell anyone about it but
Instead of it, I want you to take a document from Yuzaki chief
Yuzaki chief is calling you,Fuji-san
Thanks
Did you hear about your personnel changes?
Yes
I'm sorry to disagree with your expectations
It was my fault.
Managing Director Domoto suddenly said at yesterday's meeting
So I made a prompt decision
Good luck for 3 years
Take it easy on your work.
We need your skills
I know about you very well
I thought I was betrayed but
You were unlucky
It was what anyone would do.
The question is, will it be public knowledge or not?
Hey, there is
Guess where there was
This was hidden among the documents to be disposed of.
This is okay with your promise
I know, let me borrow this
What do you use?
I'll return this tomorrow morning
This was hidden among the documents to be disposed of,right?
It wasn't this document?
This is
Give me the document case,Hisako
If they're scrapping it, it means the project's been scrapped.
This is useless
So..what you will do with this documents?
Don't worry
This is useless but You succeeded in your work
I will forget all about her and you, as I promised.
Planned acquisition site Sumiyoshi-ku, Osaka
Yayoi Akatsuka
Oh yeah, Landfill of the sea in Sumiyoshi-ku, Osaka has been decided
The price has increased 13 times due to the acquisition of it from a company in Tokyo
Hey, what's wrong?
This person is a female doctor who was killed during this time
Oh I didn't know that
Who is the planner for this acquisition plan?
Yuzaki, your boss
Yuzaki...
What is the reason for canceling this plan?
I'm not into it
Hey
It seems you are into him.
Did you have any trouble with Yuzaki?
Well..nothing
Do you know whose fault it is that you were moved to a rural area?
What?
You misunderstand that I am involved
You are misguided
The Yuzaki decided it
Other executives didn't think so much
But Yuzaki pushed it
He got in between the company and her and was taking a brokerage fee
But Yayoi suddenly raised the price and got into trouble
And
This consultation is over
Originally I didn't ask your company
There are many other companies they want to buy
But the plan was pretty much executed
You took 5 million yen
That's called embezzlement.
Do you threaten me?
What are you talking about?
You came to talk to me with that intention from the beginning
You slept with me and You also tried to rob the land
Wait, how you know he slept with her?
No, but I'm sure
I want the police to look it up
It's a personal matter.
and Akatsuka was already dead
I meet the president and talk about everything
Then you will be fired, and your company make up 5 million yen for me
Go home now!
What are you doing?
But is that true?
No matter how much it becomes a problem, I don't think he killed her
If she died, he should have negotiated with her aunt
However,he tried to issue this plan because he thought someone could find his embezzlement.
I'm afraid this is just speculation on your part.
I think there is something wrong with this plan
Your speculation does not allow the police to investigate
Ok..I'm fine
I won't count on you
He's very excited
Because he is innocent, so he doesn’t have to do anymore
Yuzaki...
Documents related to Yachiyo Metal
Inspector Tadokoro of the Akatsuka Case Investigation Headquarters, please.
Chief, thanks for this
Come here, Fuji-kun
A difficult thing happened
It seems that your dismissal was decided at the board meeting this morning
I'll be fired?
So I don't need to go Mikawa-kikai too
Yes
Where is Yuzaki Chief?
He's just gone
Chief
Furuya's already know I'll be fired
If I make a noise here I'm just miserable
I have to calm down
We are going down
First we have to confirm his criminal activity
But how can I do it...
Yuzaki...Yuzaki...
Oh yeah, I'll ask Yuzaki.
He is a cheif
He often see Dr.Akatsuka
Yes long time ago.
4,5 times
She suddenly quit her job a week ago
Where has she gone?
She said she'll go home
But I don't know where
Where's her home?
Well..I think near Ara-liver
I'll check her Resume
Thank you
Hello?
I can't go out
I just got call from Kasumi
Money?
Please lend me 100,000 yen as soon as possible
The criminal must be Yuzaki
I need money to find out
I was also fired from a company in Osaka
I can't just sit here and cry myself to sleep.
by when do you need it
day after tomorrow?
Eh
The day after tomorrow is my brother's wedding
What time is the day after tomorrow?
It's 3 o'clock but I have to get ready from the morning
Then I'll need your help by the morning of the day after tomorrow.
But....
I'll pay for it
I owe you 30,000yen
30,000yen?
Really?
So please
I'll be fine until the morning after tomorrow?
I promise you
I'll ask my mom
I at the time she was killed
I saw Yuzaki coming out from behind the hospital
Oh, I didn't see him
Don't worry.
You saw him
I see, so you'll give me 30,000yen
Then read aloud what you have written so far
I'm sorry to write you a letter suddenly.
Do you remember me?
I'm Emiko Toyama, a nurse who worked with her at the hospital
Do you know why I am writing to you?
I saw you come out of the back of the hospital at the time she was killed
I've been silent about that until now
How do you write it?
write whatever you like
I've been silent about that until now
Because I hated her and
Because I thought it didn't matter to me who killed her
It's hot
Put the fan on me.
However, due to some recent circumstances
Speak more slowly
However,recently
I suddenly needed money for some reason
Please prepare 1 million yen by 12:00 tomorrow
1 million yen?
Please bring it
Yuzaki has not left yet?
He is on the meeting
Then he has a sales meeting
He's been in the office for a while
I see.
Thank you
Make sure you come.
Don't bring the money
Yes. to Myogadani
This is for you as we promised
Thanks
I'm sorry for the unreasonable request.
what do you use this money for ?
I'll find out soon
I will reveal his true identity
So I need this money
You're going to catch the criminal yourself
You want to take a revenge?
Of course
He ruined my life
He is the culprit for sure
You're the one who knows I had nothing to do with this.
You're the one who knows
Yes I know
But I couldn't say anything
Not only me
You too
You were afraid if Kazumi knows
You were afraid to get rid of the company
But in the end nothing remained
When I first met you, you were so nice.
You were very hopeful
I felt so fresh.
I was thinking of going on a new life with you
I thought life with Kasumi was very miserable
But in the end it didn't work
You couldn't forget about the company after all.
Position, promotion
That's all you needed
Hisako
Don't say anything
You didn't choose me
So I couldn't leave from Kasumi
You couldn't understand my feelings
Thanks
I wanted more
578-3521
If Yuzaki brought me 1 million yen, how much would you give me?
I'll give you all
I'm glad
Hello? are you yuzaki residence?
Can I talk to Mr.Yuzaki?
Hi, it's me
Oh you don't remember?
I'm Toyama who wrote a letter to you
What about my request?
I saw you for sure
Call me when you make a decision
I'll wait by 6 am tomorrow
I'll go to police if you don't come
Here is my number 851-2751
See you then
See?
It worth 30,000yen
Hello?
Connect here if someone call for Toyama
Hey
There is a calling
Oh sorry. I called wrong number
Are you going home?
Because It's already past 6 o'clock
Please wait a little more
OK?
No
We don't get a call from him anymore
It takes time to go home
Please wait a little more
We promised that
Thanks for 30,000yen
No! Get off of me.
Get off of me.
Wait!
We are arresting you for murder.
Stay down!
Get off of me
What the hell?
Come to police
It doesn't matter to you whether he's the culprit or not
That's bullshit. listen,
Yuzaki tried to fire me
He was arrested for murder
And Chief Miyama has also been arrested as an embezzlement of 3 million yen.
I have nothing to do with the incident
I am innocent
So the company needs to reconsider my resignation.
You have been deemed unfit to be our employee.
It's needless to talk with you
I speak directly with Managing Director Domoto
Wait
It's waste to go.
Your return to the company was denied at the meeting.
What? at the meeting?
An urgent meeting was held last night
Your disposition also became an issue at the meeting
Our company does not allow your reinstatement to protect the authority of the company
So decided
This is what we have to do.
They don't have time to care about you
There is a call for you,chief
I'm the section chief now, instead of you.
Hello? I'm Furuya
It's challenging to get the job back up and running again.
Thanks in advance
We will contact you about that material within a few days.
You've had a terrible time.
You were unlucky
Fuji-san
It seems that Chief Miyama was arrested.
Our editor-in-chief wants to see you
He wants to know because you know the inside story of the case
The department chief is a murderer and the section chief is an embezzlement
This is interesting
You may be entitled to compensation from the company.
Please don't make such an unpleasant face
You are already banished from the company
It's all over.
This is our number
Our editor chief is waiting for you
I've left from Kasumi
Eh?
I suffered a lot trying to forget you
But I couldn't
Let's get together
I have nothing for me anymore
The company didn't protect me either
Is that ok for you
Sure
I'll follow you