Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Maiko Monogatari (1954)
A train departing from Tokyo is currently arriving at platform 4.
Kyoto.Kyoto.
Arrived in Kyoto
You can transfer here
Thank you very much.
Take care.
See you.
Oh Tome!
Over here!
Thank you for coming early.
I think you're tired after a long train ride.
How is your mother?
I hope she's doing well.
Let's go to the hospital together.
Eiji.
Welcome back.
Is she someone you know?
She was next to me.
Will you come to my house tonight?
It's my birthday.
I forgot about that.
Mom.
I'm glad you came back.
You didn't have to force yourself to come back.
I can't concentrate on studying until I see how mom is doing for a minute
that's true. You don't have to worry because you're well-off
I told her not to worry and that she could come.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
What are you saying? It's better for you to have her by your side
I've been taking care of you.
What is your temperature today?
It seems good.
so please take care of yourself
Thank you very much.
Our work is lonely without you.
I'm not that important.
Really.
Will you return with me?
I'm going to stay right here by my mother's side
You're good.
Please do that.
You are the only two parents.
I have a party today.
Take care.
I'll be here again.
Please look after her.
See you.
Take care.
How about your condition?
Are you okay if you don't go to school?
It's ok.Even if I take a little break, I'll show you that I can make up for it quickly.
I'm smart.
What are you planning to do if you graduate?
I want to go back to Kyoto and do clinical work at my father's hospital
I think your father would be pleased with that.
You two should take your time and enjoy your conversation.
Thank you.
Are there any other customers here?
Yoko left it just the two of us.
let's start.
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Thank you
Welcome back!
Sorry for being so late, it's been a while
Dad, congratulations
Brother, today is my birthday.
Sorry.
Congratulations!
It's like you're married.
It's kind of that.
Since I saw your face and instantly I became lively again
Don't worry about me. I'll be back in Tokyo in a few days.
I will do that.
but your is so energetic
I feel relieved
But since I've finally come back, I'll do my best to look after you.
That's silly, there's no need to take that seriously, is there?
Please eat that meal quickly.
Have a eat.
I've been on the train all this time so my stomach's not feeling well.
That's bad.
So, what happened?
Well.
Is there something wrong?
You look like you're in pain
Yes.
Do you have a stomach ache?
I'll bring you some water now.
Please eat this.
Sorry about that.
Thank you very much.
Please take a rest.
You should lie down since the medicine is still working
But....
I'm still a medical student, so of course I'm taking care of you.
But.
Follow my advice
I'm sorry.
You received a very honest response from him, but you never heard his name.
What were you doing?
You can't repay him
I was embarrassed to hear his name.
There's no need to be embarrassed to say thank him
You are too shy.
When did you come back?
I came back last night on the night train.
Did you see your mom?
I think you were surprised.
Have you been here for a while?
Take good care of your mom.
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Come in.
How was her?
She look fine.
Is her illness serious?
According to the doctor, there are a lot of bad things with her body.
so what are you going to do about it? The hospital costs are ridiculous,
and until now, your aunt has been helping out
Sorry for the inconvenience.
If I'm fine, my job is fine.
I think it'll be okay without your mother.
Even if I want to help somehow,
Last night I thought about various things.
About the house
If your mother is hospitalized for a long time
How about cutting back on that economy?
How about firing the maid?
I don't think it's worth the money to pay them.
I was against you going to school in Tokyo.
Your Mom understood, but think about it—like mother, like child;
If you were a Maiko,
I'd take care of you
Think about that.
I can say that this obi suits that kimono.
If you say something like that,I sing like this
My throat hurts.
Is someone making a strange noise?
I felt bad.
Why you're here?
I'm here to pay my bill.
Thank you very much.
Have a seat.
I'm leaving.
Think about that.
Please.
Who's her?
Satogiku's daughter.
Isn't she a nice girl?
Is she your sister?
She's my daughter.
I didn't know there was such a big daughter.
Take care.
Mom.
I see.
Why did they let her get this bad?
People in that kind of society tend to push themselves without realizing it
Does she have cirrhosis?
That's a possibility, so we're taking x-rays to investigate.
If it's a cancer?.
there's no hope at all.
Her daughter knows that?
Nobody knows about it yet.
How're you?
Thank you very much.
You took care of my daughter on the train.
I want to thank you a lot.
She's out right now but will be back soon.
She received your kind help.
But she didn't ask your name. Sorry.
Don't worry.
Please.
I apologize for that earlier.
My mother said she wanted to meet you and express her gratitude
I just visited her.
Oh really?
She was so politely thanked that I ended up feeling troubled.
How is my mother's condition?
I don't really understand well
but I don't think there's anything to worry about
I see.
I was relieved to hear that.
What a nice mother she is
How long will you be staying in Kyoto?
I have school
so I can't stay for too long
You want to go to music college, right?
Did my mother even tell you about that?
but I might have to give up on that now
Why?
Are you just your mother and your family?
Don't worry.
I don't really understand much about music
The other day in Tokyo, I was so moved to watch a concert.
It was amazing.
Were you there too?
We might meet.
I was on the third floor.
Me too.
but speaking of which
There was a female student next to me who sighed at that time.
Was she you?
Really?
The man next to me at the time was snoring the whole time.
I remember it well.
Well, he might have been me.
Will my illness get better?
I'll do my best with what I can,
but I think it's ultimately a matter of time
What do you mean?
It would be nice if she will alive for six months.
I feel sorry about her.
Is that so?
I see.
It's quite lively now.
She was talking interesting.
I came a little too late.
Even though you are always busy,
I'm glad you visit me.
Your complexion has improved.
I'm glad
As expected, Tome is back so you get better.
Thank you very much.
Let me know if you need something.
She has really done well, so I am not inconvenienced.
Tome,you're great.
I'm going to buy you a reward.
that would make me happy
I wonder what I want.
Tome.
What do you want?
Wanna have lunch?
Let's have a lunch with me as a reward,
I'll get ready.
It's better to wear nice clothes.
And get your hair done.
Yes.
It must look beautiful from here on the day of Daimonji
Next time, let's take Mom to see it!
Tome.
What will you do if Mom's illness doesn't get better?
According to the doctor,her liver is really bad.
Her liver?
Mom's cancer?
No no.
If she has cancer, she won't live six months.
She'll get better?
Even if she recover, she won't be able to go out.
You shouldn't let your mother know about this.
Why don't you become Maiko?
In the end, making your mother feel at ease and emotionally supported means you have to work
If you want to work, how about becoming a maiko?
You're good at both singing and dancing
Your mother was really looking forward to that
I know you have to think about it.
But it's okay to take your time to think about it
Don't push yourself.
I will come up with various ideas for you, understood?
Wanna have a tea? No?
Let's go.
Thank you very much.
Hello?
It's been ages.
See you.
Who's her?
She's Gion's tea house madam.
I need to make a phone call.
Hello, I'm Eiji.
Yoko?
I have an internship tomorrow
I absolutely have to be in Tokyo tonight.
I have preparations to make, so I'm going home
Well then, please take care of Keisuke.
From Yoko?
Yes.
Why did you turn down?
She'll take me to the station tonight.
Yes.
How's your mom?
Yes, Mom is sleeping right now.
Excuse me.
I'm heading to Tokyo.
I don't have much time left,
but I was worried about you.
so I'm sorry.
Make sure not to lose hope for your mother.
You heard it from Aunts, right?
She still has a hope.
you need to make sure she gets as much nutrition as possible through your efforts
In the case of liver cancer, she has to be careful about the body's weakness caused by loss of appetite
She has cancer as I thought?
You didn't know that?
Tomeko.
That's fine.
I'll know it later.
It's better to find out sooner.
Miss Makihara is pick up you.
I'll be there soon.
It's time for the train,right?
Please go.
I've asked my father about your mother, and I will return after I graduate,
so I will do my best to help as much as I can
You have been doing your best without being pushed down
See you then.
Take care.
What are you doing?
Is your mom's ok?
Aunt.
I'll become Maiko.
What?
That's good.
You have made up your mind well.
So, Did your mom agree?
I don't think she will agree.
Have you not told your mom yet?
I see.
if that's how you feel,
I'll tell her again, so that's good
That's good,that's good.
Tome.
I am relieved.
You'll become nice geisha.
Taking your mom's name,
you'll go to the second generation Satogiku.
You might be much prettier than when your mom was Maiko
Please stand up a bit
Look sideways.
Look at me.
You look so nice.
If I show you to your mom, she will probably be happy
she's angry, she won't be happy
I don't think so.
Go to the hospital as it is.
Hey anyone there?
Oh you are there?
Are you ok?
Mom.
Can you walk?
Are you ok?
You came back well.
I tried to stop her, but she wanted to see her daughter's first job.
Parents love their daughters after all.
I’m worried about various things,.
Please look after Tomeko.
I'll do my best.
Tome.
I'm proud of you.
Be nice Geisha.
Mom.
Don't cry.
it will ruin your face.
I wanted to see how you dress geisha outfit.
It's not embarrassing no matter where you go
Please go.
Mom, so I'm off now
Be careful.
Please take care of her.
Don't worry, Leave it to me.
so let's go.
I'm going.
Take care.
You have to be in the bed.
Oh Geisha girl.
She's nice.
I want your signature.
Don't push me.
I've been waiting about an hour.
I’m sorry.
president ,I finally bring her here.
Good evening
You go there.
Sis.
Hurry up.
What's the hell?
You're too popular these days.
Have a drink.
I'll have it little.
Let's drink a lot.
Have a drink more.
I can't drink this anymore.
I see.
You wanted to go to music college, didn't you?
How did you know?
Do you want me to support you to go to the college?
Thanks.
Instead, scary things happen, don't they?
You're so mean.
He has no ulterior motive.
He is kind man.
Are you sure?
Shut up!
I'm right?
Let me know if you wanna go to the college.
I was really hoping for something, but I have completely given up.
Don't worry about me.
but instead, let's play around, shall we?
Do you know about this?
10....10 game.
What's the hell?
Say it slowly.
10....10 game.
10....?
What's the hell?
I'll teach you.
Look at me.
10....10.
You get it?
That word?
Word like this.
Yeah.
Like this.
You love me?
president, This is very nice.
She's telling her feelings inside
Don't say anything inappropriate.
Yamazaki-san is like a dragonfly in a thunderstorm
What do you mean?
What?
The dragonfly is shaped
Thunder is like this.
It means I hate you.
I see.
Want to know your nickname?
Stop it....
Tell me.
No fists.
No fists?
What if there is no rock-paper-scissors goo
paper-scissors only.
It means you are asshole.
You're so mean.
Satoi named it.
She's very smart.
How about me?
You are a fluorescent light.
I am a fluorescent light.
Don't tell him the reason.
I don't understand it unless I think about it carefully.
You said the answer yourself
Who?
You.
Me?
What's wrong?
I'm going to turn the lights on now so please take a good look.
Ready?
I see.
It's Half dark.
You are stupid.
Forgive me....
Don't make fun of me.
For Tomiko.
Thank you for your work.
Letter?
From a young doctor in Tokyo
I received your letter,Tomeko.
Thank you.
I read your letter.
I'm glad to hear that your mother's condition has improved
I can't say how much your love is more effective
for your mother than medicine right now
I finally finished writing my graduation thesis and submitted it to the school
And I went to listen to Beethoven's Symphony No. 6 for the first time in a while
How much fun would it be if you were here with me?
I'm a bit disappointed
but when I return to Kyoto, there are
definitely things I want to talk to you about
I'm sure you'll be happy to hear about it too
The letter is from a young doctor at the hospital,right?
He is very worried about you
He's kind.
Please say thank you to him.
Does he know that you are a geisha?
I only told him that I had dropped out of school.
I think he's surprised.
Do you know what's making noise next door?
Yuhi?
That's right,
This is my favourite song.
Do you remember me singing?
Yes.
I saw you singing when I was just a kid.
Tears were starting to well up.
It was beautiful! I also thought that I wanted to try it once I grew up, and I was watching it with all my might
This song is great every time I hear it.
Go home safe.
Thanks.
Take care.
See you.
See you then.
Take care.
I just visited your home and saw your mother.
I heard that you were discharged from the hospital
I was wondering what you needed afterward
Thank you for going out of your way.
Are you alright?
Satogiku?
Is her condition worse than before?
It seems like she's gradually getting weaker
In front of me,she pretend to be lively on purpose,
so I act like I don't notice
Congratulations on your graduation!
You have changed.
Somehow, you all seem like different people to me.
I didn't like this outfit at first either.
But I've completely gotten used to it now
After all, a frog's child is a frog.
I never imagined you would become a Geisha.
Why didn't you let me know?
Well..
But
I'm not in a position to go to school
If I don't work, neither of us can survive
It must be tough
There is no job that isn't hard, right?
But when I see you like this, dressed as Maiko,
it somehow feels like my heart is being squeezed
Why is that?
Why are you so interested in me?
Is that bad?
Tome.
Can we meet again another day?
It would be fine during the day?
Eiji.
Did you think I'd come dressed as a geisha?
Yes.
Yeah
I felt bad for you if I came in my Geisha form.
Washing this hair is a hassle.
it's all greasy, right?
How about this?
Doesn't it look like the Tomoko that Eri-san knows?
It feels like it's been a while, and dressing like this makes me feel like I've really returned to being a student
That's Gion over there.
It's small.
I thought about how we cried and laughed every day in a place like that
It's ridiculous to think that way
You think so?
That's why it's sometimes necessary for us to view our lives from a different perspective
Have a seat.
Do you intend to continue this job forever?
I won't do this job when I get older.
Did you read my letter?
Of course, but I'm not thinking about marriage.
Not right now
It might be a long way off, but I want to make a promise
I was really happy when I read your letter.
But aren't you engaged?
engaged?
A woman who was driving you around.
Oh her.
Our fathers are friends
We've been close since childhood, but not engagement?
Really?
Will you make a promise with me?
Would you mind if I were a Geisha?
It doesn't matter if you're a maiko or a student;
my feelings won't change
But I have debts
I intend to somehow repay.
As long as you hold it together
Geisha is also a great job.
I accept your offer.
It hurts.
Eiji.
Are you alright?
Oh you are here.
I just visited your house.
She has just started working so she doesn't know much about it.
Is it okay to leave her as she is?
We need her to become a top-notch Geisha.
For that, I really think she needs to avoid relying on Edano
I believe Fukutome would be perfect,right?
I am saying this with her future in mind.
I’m saying this for your sake,
I want you to have a good rest.
I understand that very well.
But I need to her feelings as well.
Well, of course
I don't force her.
but Fukutome-san is quite nice.
He paid for all of your hospital bills and her debut.
He's really great.
Fukutome is taking care of us very well.
You should repay him.
I'm home.
Thanks for coming.
Welcome back.
It's hard for you to tell her that.
Do you want me to ask her?
but you should think it over carefully, okay?
Where did you go dressed like that?
Where were you?
Please come back quickly and manage it.
I'm leaving.
You should call Fujino.
Take care.
See you.
What brings her here?
She just came to visit
Something good happened to me.
What do you think it is?
Today I met Eiji and make a promise to get married.
Make a promise to get married?
That's very difficult
Not now.
it's something far ahead
I don't know what the hell you're thinking.
You didn't consult me ​​about anything.
I have to go now
Tome.
Hello?
You didn't officially get engaged to Yoko,
there was an understanding between you two
I've never even thought about such a thing, not once
I think Yoko thinks she's engaged to you.
Eiji, I hadn't talked to you about it yet
Actually, I owe a debt of gratitude to Makihara-san for
providing the funds to build this hospital after the war
Of course, I am paying back that money little by little every year
If possible, it would be a great relief for me,
at least mentally, if you could marry Yoko.
We won't force you.
However, it seems that you were quite close to Yoko
If my relationship with Yoko is perceived that way,
I feel responsible towards her
But I don't consider her as a marriage candidate.
I'm sorry, but please let me choose my own marriage partner
What on earth my mom going to do?
She depends on you alone.
I think if you understand that feeling, she would gladly agree
But you'll have to depend on someone someday.
If that's the case, wouldn't it be better to do it a little earlier?
But he must be quite an eccentric person
Who on earth is he?
Musa.
I understand it's either the fluorescent light.
He is the president of a shipbuilding company.
I know.
I'll discuss it with mom and think about it.
I see, I see,
then that's good
Oh, and there's something I want to show you.
Just wait a moment.
Take a look at this.
it's something mom's Testimonials.
Testimonials?
Are the customers waiting?
I'll take a look it later.
Anytime.
Good evening!
Hello?
Are you Satogiku?
Yes.
Come in.
Thank you for coming.
My sister wants to talk to you
I'll go over there
Please stay here.
I have been getting close with Eiji-san.
Since I was a child.
So if you are friends with Eri,
I would like to be friend too
Friend?
Thank you.
But am I really can't be your friend.
Why not?
I don't really know what kind of relationship you and Eiji have,
but if it's okay, please tell me
Please feel free to ask Eiji
Right.
Well, that's ok, but
can I ask just one thing?
What do you think of Eri?
I love him.
Are you planning to get married?
I love him too
I also want to get married.
I've been wondering what kind of person you are, but you're a nice person
If you were a bad person, I wouldn't even get close to you, Eiji
I'm starting to like you.
I want to be friends, but that's separate from how I feel about Eiji
I don't want to give up for your sake
Is it okay if you don't hold back with me.
From now on, let's have a beautiful relationship with each other
No hard feelings no matter who wins.
What happened?
Let's shake hands.
I guess that you met her and wanted to clarify your position by meeting,
but I don't think it was very effective
I can't explain my feelings to you.
No....
It must be a big deal that she came to see you.
She really likes Eiji.
I know you like him too.
She's a rich girl who's known him since he was a child.
I don't know what's in his future, whether she's with you or not with her.
I think about it a lot.
Don't say like that.
Tome-chan
Your mother? You might think that's an old-fashioned thing to say, but...
I believe that human emotions haven't changed from the past to the present, and for the sake of happiness
For Eiji's happiness. sometimes you
have to accept what you can't give up
I can't.
You grew up in Honmachi
I am sure you understand my intentions.
Geisha have their own way.
It's painful and sadness.
It is the geisha who put up with it.
That's what a geisha is.
Mom.
Please understand me.
Please give up on him.
I'm glad you gave up on him.
In return, I will definitely decline Fukudome's offer.
I feel sorry for you.
You're still child.
Mom.
From your perspective, she still look like a child
But now she is a fine Geisha.
The times are different from the past, right?
I will not make unreasonable demands.
How will you repay your debt to Fukudome?
I will sell the property and pay off the debt.
But I don't think it's an easy sell.
If you sell it, you're out of business.
How do I plan to make a living?
Hello,Yes.
I wanna see you.
please come out for just a little while, won't you?
Hello?
Do not answer the phone.
Do not answer the phone
You know what?
I think about you all too much
In the end, it seems like I've ended up making you all suffer
Sorry.
I don't want to deal with anymore
Do as you like.
From now on, I won't talk much about Tome-san.
Sorry.
Are you alright?
Please come here!
Kikue is in toruble.
Hello?
Do not answer the phone.
Say I'm not here.
Really?
Hold on.
Did your mother collapse at Hatsuya?
She wants you to come back right away
Hello?
She's going.
I’m sorry.
You must be very tired
She seems to be sleeping well
Take a little break.
Please rest.
I'm in the room, so if you need something,let me know.
Mom, mom.
Tome.
mom, are you feeling unwell?
Should I call doctor?
Tome.
Stay here.
Stay strong.
Tome.
I tell you.
I told you to give up on Eiji.
I will cancel it
Mom.
What Did You Say?
Say it again.
I told you to give up on Eiji.
I will cancel it
Do as you like!
Mom, is that true?
When I die, you should quit being a geisha and be with Eiji.
I don't want you to die.
Don't worry.
I want to do many things to you.
I couldn't do anything for you.
If I could always do it for you, I wouldn't have to worry
You shouldn't say things like that!
Tome.
Who is playing the shamisen?
Yuki?
I like this music.
Please stay strong.
I can't hear anything
What a nice.
Who is playing this beautiful piece?
Please stay strong.
I'll call doctor.
Mom!
Mom, Please don't die.
Ume-chan is here too.
Thank you for coming.
I'm glad you are here.
Today is her birthday.
Excuse me.
You should cheer up and do your best.
I'll support you.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Thank you for coming.
Welcome back.
I'm starving.
Tomoe wants to eat sushi.
Prepare those meals.
Tome-san is lonely now that she is alone
What are you going to do from now on?
I've been resting for a long time.
I'm going to work from tomorrow.
Yes.
You feel better when you work.
You have to pay back Fukudome's debt.
You can't just ignore the fact that everyone helped with the funeral expenses.
You have to work hard.
Oh yes.
This is because Mr. Fukudome was worried about you and prepared the money for you.
Take it.
What happened?
I appreciate his feelings, but I can't accept this.
You wouldn't be able to manage without someone's help if you want to be a fine Geisha.
I'll thank Fukutome-san
and then receive it.
That's a good decision.
You know what?
I have no relatives.
When Tomoe-chan was born into a world,
I asked her to adopt you as my adopted daughter.
I you have the ability to do other work,
I want to let you quit even now,
but it seems that someone raised in this society
It's hard to get a normal job.
I am also doing her best to support you
You too will become a wonderful geisha, understood?
Where did she go?
She is on the second floor
Let me go there.
What are you doing?
Is that Love letter?
Our president is happy
He's been restless since this morning at the company
He was busy, so I came first.
around 5 o'clock the president will be here, so please take care of it.
Satogiku.
It took a lot for me to get to this point.
I'm counting on you.
See you then.
Hello, Is that Takatsugi hospital?
Is Mr. Eiji there?
This is Itami.
I see, thank you very much.
Hello, is that Takatsugi? Is Mr
Is Mr. Eiji there?
I also tried calling the hospital.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Hello, yes, this is it.
Mr Eiji? Please hold on a moment
From who?
She didn't say anything.
Hello, it's me, Eiji.
Hello?
Satogiku has come.
I see.
Tome.
Thanks for coming.
Fukudome is waiting for you.
I'll have one drink.
Come in.
What's wrong?
Can you drink?
Just little.
Are you alright?
I'll let you know as soon as she's ready
Thanks.
Let's go together with him tomorrow morning
I am also going along with you.
Please come in.
Are you ready?
I'm counting on you.
Wanna change clothes?
I'll help it myself.
Sorry for making you wait.
She's all set.
President, please relax.
You are stupid.
Excuse me.
She's still child.
Please look after her.
I know.
I'm counting on you.
Shall we wake up a little and talk?
Satogiku
How's it going? Have you already gone to sleep?
You sleep with your kimono on.
Take it off.
Okami!
I have always believed that there is nothing stronger than love in this world
As long as I love, I thought I could overcome any obstacle
But I have various burdens that I cannot bear alone
I am sorry for making you, Eiji, chase after those burdens as well
I have decided to pursue those burdens on my own
After all, that was my destiny.
I had a foolish heart with happiness I didn't want
Laughing at myself now
I hope you and Eiji will live a happy life together.
I see.
From hospital?
Yes.
She's saved.
Brother, do you have a favor to ask me?
Why didn't you consult me?
You are stupid.
You can do anything if you are willing to die for it.
Don't ever do anything like that again.
Yes.
Is it okay if I come in?
I'm glad you are saved.
I read the letter and understood your feelings
I'm very happy.
and I came to thank you.
Tomeko.
It must have been tough for you, Tomoko-san, right? But it's okay now
Are you only thinking about Eri-san?
But...
Don't say anything.
We are fair now.
then, take care.
I have something to talk with you,Eiji.
I would like you to receive this, Tomoko-san,
TOMEKO's Testimonials.
TOMEKO's Testimonials?
Why do you have this?
This is present for you.
It's troubling for me.
Why not?
I don't want to cause trouble for your family
Why do you say like that?
Why can't you just accept it quietly?
I really understand your actions
But that wouldn't settle my feelings
Keep this with me until I make up my mind.
Just take it as it comes.
Please.
Look, over there.
Tome is there.
Stop it.
1.2.3.
Tome-chan!
THE END