Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Betrayer
No... I don't like it
I don't want to leave from you
For the past two years, I've been tired.
If you stay with me, your life will be ruined.
They say once a woman is ruined, she can't be
resurrected.
If you don't like me anymore, please speak up.
I'm glad if you come to see me sometime
When I heard that you'd introduced me to the
Shinwa Corporation, I knew I could bounce back.
I figured if I could get a fixed salary of 50,000 yen
plus a 30% commission on sales, I could pay off my debt.
I knew I could make a comeback if I took the right
chances.
But No sales at all for two months.
I found out.
Our expensive massager won't sell now.
Mr.Sawai said clearly
He said he'd hire you as a partner in a partnership, not a
salesman.
The name doesn't matter.
I can't live on 50,000 yen.
Of course, I can't pay my debts.
But a fixed salary of 50,000 yen sounds good to
you
If I don't, I'll never recover my life
Damn it
I need money
Please stop saying it.
Money does not matter
For the last two months I've been trying, but I haven't sold a single
unit.
I don't think I can sell from now
Can I sell different products?
Regardless of whether you sell or not, your salary is
guaranteed.
I know but 50000 yen is too less
You want more?
To be honest,I made a lot of money when I worked at a brokerage
firm.
But the stock market crashed and I lost 7 million
yen.
I made up for it a little by selling off some of our unwanted
items.
I'll be sued if I don't repay the 5 million yen.
So I need money anyway
You're in dire straits.
I'll do anything for money besides erotic things
I feel secure knowing you are with me.
What are you doing?
Go home
Yes
You are the one whom I expected
You told me you'll do anything for money
Yes
To be honest,It has nothing to do with selling electric
massagers.
In short, I've wanted the word from you
Please drink
Have you ever heard of industrial espionage?
Yes
I'm the head of an industrial espionage agency.
It's to disguise the existence of a Shinwa
company and the sale of electric massages.
All the other employees are industrial spies?
No.
You're the only candidate for industrial espionage.
I plan to increase that number later
I'm carefully selecting people now
When I started this job, I wanted a competent
employee at a brokerage firm to start with.
He has knowledge of stocks and is accustomed to interacting with people
He's used to business news
In other words, it is the best human resource for a spy.
I happened to hear from Kazumi-san, so I talked to you.
If you succeed in one case, you can get 200000,300,000yen
In some cases you can get 1 million yen
You decide if you want to do it or not.
But if you're going to do it, you'll have to quit your current job today.
Don't tell this story to anyone.
Promise me
You can decide
I do
Really?
My life is at rock bottom.
I can take the risk to get back my life
Let's get the job done right away
Take advantage of your friendship to do this job
My friendships?
Nanayou chemistry
Shoichi Ogino, managing director of that company, is a classmate at your university.
You and he are very close
I researched a lot about you
There is an engineer named Nishiwaki in the
laboratory of that company. Do you know him?
I don't know
The husband of his sister,Sadako is this man
You know her,right?
Yes I have met her
The Nishiwaki recently made a wonderful invention.
I found out he invented a great appliance
I want to know how the product was made
Actually I don't want to meet Ogino
Because of His wife,Eiko?
I told you I researched a lot about you
Since you were a student, you were planning to have a romantic relationship with Eiko and get married.
But two years ago, Eiko married Ogino.
I don't know the season, but You lost Eiko to Ogino.
The reason is money
Because I couldn't repay my debt
I didn't know that
Mr. Ogino took her from you because of your debt
How much was your debt?
It was 200000 yen
This is a prepayment of success fees
Please return as much as your work is completed
Mr. Ogino feels sorry for you.
I think this is a chance
I'm trying to betray my friendship with Mr. Ogino
But this may be the reward taken by Eiko
Now I have no choice but to do this
Maybe I was destined to be a spy
Ogino called me and declared a marriage to you
He seemed to be victorious
It might have been good that I couldn't repay my debt
I felt humiliated.
I couldn't stand Ogino getting married to her
You don't care if I marry to Ogino?
I want to know your opinion
Please
I can't do anything now
I can't make you happy because I don't have money
To be clear, I can't afford to pay for today's meals
But I think this is my last date with you
Stop it
Have you seriously considered the well-being of women?
I wanted you to oppose my marriage to Mr. Ogino
Two years have passed since then,
I do this job to live
What does Eiko think of me?
I have a hard time meeting Eiko
Oh, Segawa-san
Long time, no see
Toshiko-san,
I met you in a strange place
Because this is my sister's house
That's right
Please come in
How's your health?
I'm fine now
Are you married?
I'm still single.
Please introduce someone good
Long time, no see
She is my sister's classmate Kyoko Honda
I'm Segawa
Nice to meet you,I'm Kyoko
Do you know Kazumi Yamaguchi,right?
Yes
They are all classmates
All three were close friends
I see
Segawa-san is..well how can I say....
He is my sister's old friend
Sister
Is there any problem?
Excuse me
Please come to the alumni association
I'm going home
Thanks
See you
What happened to you
Come in
How have you been doing?
Yes
You haven't sat down yet
Here is your tea
Oh he came back
He should've come home later.
You are cowardly
cowardly?
Yes,
You played with my sister's heart
Do you think my sister is happy now?
At least she didn't have to marry me
No
Anyway, take your time to talk to her once.
Oh, sorry to keep you wait
I've just come here
You knew he was coming
He called me
Oh I see
I want to drink whiskey
OK
What have you been doing lately?
I'm sorry I didn't contact you
I had a lot of problems
I was worried about you
I was a wanderer, and I was feeling down.
wanderer?
I recently started a small company with a friend
That's good
This is part of the money I borrowed from you
I can't give you all your money back.
Is it okay to pay in installments?
No way.
You don't have to worry about that at all
Thank you for waiting
Thank you for this money
Don't worry about the rest of the money
Thank you
Where is Eiko,Toshiko-san?
She said she is dizzy
I see
She is sick
Yes
Please enjoy
By the way, thanks this
You are welcome
What do you want to talk about?
Actually I need your help
I see.
What kind?
I want to sell your company's products.
I would be happy to sign a distributorship with you.
However, many of our products are special.
First you have to study it
So I want to visit your company's factory for the study
I will guide you at any time.
How about tomorrow?
That's good
The start went better than I expected
Finally Betrayal to Mr. Ogino begins
Your company is making various new products, isn't it?
Yes.
There is a research institute in this, and professionals are doing research
Person called Nishiwaki is the best of them
Not at all
What kind of research are you doing now?
It's like a supermarket?
I will go back to work
Please guide him later
Thank you in advance
My pleasure
He is the husband of my sister Sadako
He is my brother-in-law
Boss
What?
I have a phone call from the president
I see
He is my secretary Fujita
Excuse me
I'm Fujita.
Pleased to meet you
I'm Segawa, Ogino's classmate
I see.
Mr.Ogino takes care of me well
This is from Nishiwaki
This is a brochure of the company's products so
far
Thank you
She's Mr. Nishiwaki's secretary at the institute.
She knows everything about our institute.
Please take care of him before boss come back
I have to leave now
He is very friendly
There's a lot of activity in this lab.
According to Ogino you've recently developed a new
product.
Is that Paramizale?
Yes Paramizale
I hear it's great product
But I don't know anything about that product.
How is Ogino's reputation?
What?
He is manager, good looking and has wife
Is he popular among women workers?
Are you one of his fan?
Ah.. Can I get this?
I need to thank you
Oh yeah, I can use this woman
Shall we dance?
I can't dance
Let's dance?
Please go to dance
Who is she?
For my business
Mr.Sawai left me a big work
I might be able to pay off my debt if it goes
well
What is your relationship with your work and
her?
I'll tell you later
I met Eiko at the class meeting yesterday.
She is beautiful as it is
Stop talking about her
Come to our place tonight?
Find out more about that new product,Paramizale.
Find out the connection between Nishiwaki, Kondo and Fujita.
You looked into this on your first visit.
It's amazing.
Which of these four points of contact shall we examine first?
Find out the connection between Nishiwaki, Kondo and Fujita.
That's the point
Come in
Segawa-san,
There is a call from Murazaki
Murazaki
Yes a woman
Thanks
Ah, I'm Toshiko
Can I meet you tonight?
I want to talk with you
Yes, It's very important
What kind?
I want to see you in person
Please come to Ginza
I got a call from Toshiko
Me too
She told me there is a important thing
One coffee,please
I get it
Mr.Segawa, There is a call for you
How's going?
Are you upset with me?
Or you appreciate with me?
Not at all
I was so concerned about my sister.
Enjoy
I didn't know my sister's made this
You don't change anything
No.. I've changed
I felt it when I visited you the other day
I've changed
Madam
Oh Eiko-san
Sadako-san,
You know him? Ogino's classmate, Segawa
Oh I remember, I'm sorry I didn't realize you
You have changed a lot.
I'm sorry I didn't realize you
You visited us, but I couldn't show you around,
I was sorry
He visited your company?
He came with Mr.Ogino
Oh I see
Can I take a seat?
Please
I was about to leave
You don't have to worry.
It's been a whole
I went to shop and I happened to meet Segawa-san
By chance?
Yes
I asked her to have a coffee
Please take your time
See you
I need to go too
Are you busy?
Kind of
See you
Was it bad?
Don't worry
They're having an affair, too.
We are same
You have an open mind.
You like me?
One coffee,please
Certainly
Welcome back
Our boss is not here
I see
I got call from Ogino from Nanayo company
He told me you come to his home tonight
Is that all?
Yes
I see
Your wife is not at home?
She has urgent business in Shinjuku
Our house maid went back home
To be honest, I felt lonely so I called you
I'm glad you invited me
Enjoy yourself
By the way, you told me you want to be our
retailer agent
Yes I want
This might be rude, Funding is required for the agency
contract.
Your partner, who pays the money, has the right
to run the business, and you become the servant.
I understand
If you want to start your own business, we'll help you finance
it.
Are you sure?
Yes
By the way, what do you think about Setsuko
Kondo?
I have no idea
She said you asked her out a few times
Oh, She is pure and nice woman
Her father is a scholar.
He used to give us a lot of advice.
And in return, I let her join us.
She's a woman, and I want her to marry someone
I see
Do you want to marry her?
Me?
Yes I know you very much, and if you marry her,
I will support you about your agent
Ah thanks
To be honest, I never think about that
I've never known you to be so concerned about
her.
Let me think about it, thank you anyway
No problem.
I hope you think about her
Excuse me
I was relax but I got urgent business
Are you going out?
Someone will come here
You are very busy
I'll go home
It will be done in 15mins, you can wait here
I have time so it's ok to wait
Now go and have a drink in my room
I see
I will finish my work soon, so please wait
(Patent notification)
What are you doing?
What did you shoot?
I just touched the camera
Don't lie.
You were filming it
You are a spy after all
There was a tip-off at the company that you were an industrial spy who knew the secrets of paramizale.
I didn't make it a problem
I thought you were indebted to me.
I thought you wouldn't betray me
What I was curious about was that you were approaching Setsuko Kondo
I didn't think you were interested in that sober woman
I talked about the agency, marriage to know your true intentions
You were confused
This is the last test I tried
Take it if you want
This is a fake to test you
I also know the relationship between you and Eiko
That's not true.
You don't have to make an excuse
She will be surprised to know your identity
Go home
Don't show up in front of us again
Of course,  stay away from Ms. Kondo
You
You are human scum.
You tried to spy on our friendship
I am very angry with you
He is stupid
I'm a human scum.
What happened?
You look down
I'll go home
Hello?
Oh you
What have you been doing since then?
It's not your business
I went to about three bars.
Tell me the truth
Did you kill Ogino?
Did I kill Ogino?
There was a phone call from Eiko
Ogino was killed?
This is the weapon
It looks like the criminal hit him and strangled him
Did he has a visitor?
Yes
Looking at the cup, there were at least 2,3 visitors
If we know the visitor, we will know the criminal immediately.
The first discoverer was his wife?
Yes
But she's in a state of confusion and can't talk now
You can talk to her sister
I knew there were customers
I don't know who that is.
So?
I was here this evening
I'm sure there was a phone call from the company after 6 o'clock
I was told to prepare sake and snacks because customers are coming
So?
My sister was going to visit her relatives
But she decided not to go if customers came
If they're going to have drinks with other men, she thought, she'd rather not have her.
So she went out
Manager
I know who the customer was
So quick
He heard the incident and rushed here
Really?
From who?
Kazumi Yamaguchi
Yamaguchi?
Why she knows?
She got call from Ogino's wife
I see
You were classmate
Did you visit him because you had a promise?
yes
We were going to discuss the agency contract
Then?
We were drinking but he got a call from his company and someone came
Then I went home
Did you ask if anyone from the company is coming?
No
What time did you left?
It was about 8 pm
What time did you hear the case from Yamaguchi?
I heard when I returned to my apartment after 10 o'clock
Talk to me about what you did between 8:00 and 10:00.
I thought I'd take a detour.
I called Ms. Yamaguchi from the public phone in front of this house.
Then I killed time in the cafeteria from 8:30 to 1 hour.
The I separated with Yamaguchi
Then it's a little past 9 o'clock
Yes
Then I went to about 2 cafes by myself
When I got home, Ms. Yamaguchi was there and told me about the incident.
OK I get it
I'm sorry, but please let me take your fingerprint for operation
Yes
Please
Did you enter this room when you came then?
He showed me this room
Was there a camera on the desk at that time?
Camera?
This camera
Certainly it was
How is Eiko?
The potion put her to sleep.
That's good to hear
Hello, Fujita-san
Ah Nice to see you again
We are treated as suspects and unpleasant
By the way
Don't you think Eiko is a little strange?
What?
She called the police and Toshiko
Then she should have informed her relatives
But she informed Kazumi first
It might be so
I'm not blaming Kazumi
I’m sorry
I think my sister was confused.
So she didn't let you know
You think so?
By the way Who is the culprit?
We had a business rival, but I have no idea
How was his female relationship?
He was OK.
His female relationship was normal
You're the one who called me at 7:30, but what did you talk about?
Please
We asked for a loan, but we were planning to get the answer at 7 o'clock tonight.
I was told to report the contents 30 minutes later
Then I called him
Was it at 8 pm?
Yes just before 8 pm
Did you call him and come here?
Me?
No.
I was planning to report it at the company tomorrow
Where did you call from?
A restaurant Erika in Akasaka
You swear you're not the culprit
I swear
This company is over when you find out that you are an industrial espionage
So I called Kazumi to make a fake alibi.
he got a call at 8 o'clock.
It was past 8:30 when I had an argument with Ogino.
Actions during this time are absolutely secret
So He got a call and I decided to go home soon
I used Kazumi for 30 minutes during that time.
But you called from Kazumi-san's bar
Don't worry about time.
She was off at that day
Alibi camouflage is not good.
But It can't help but doing it
If you find the true criminal, my fake alibi will be overlooked
It's hard to find the real culprit
The person who came after I returned is the true criminal
And another key is...A whistleblower who taught him about me
What is the whistleblower's aim?
I think it's about keeping me away from him
What do you mean?
Paramizale
What?
The Whistleblowers also want it
I see, I get it
But he didn't have to kill Ogino to trap you
That's right
I don't think the guilty flag and the guilty flag have anything to do with each other
But I think they have some contact
If I know that, this case will be resolved
No fingerprints were found on the weapon
Did you get fingerprints from the camera and film?
Yes only Segawa and Ogino's
The fingerprints overlapped, but the victim's were on top.
Victim touched the camera after Segawa
That's right
Manager! I've visited
Thanks
Do you have any information?
The president was wondering.
He said there was no such loan offer.
Really?
He said that
Is Fujita's testimony a lie?
Ok, we should investigate Fujita
Are you going home,Segawa-san
Humans are mysterious creatures
Did you meet him last night?
It feels like he was killed because I returned early
You don't have to care too much
Because you haven’t had a quarrel.
You don't have to feel responsible
By the way There was a quarrel at the board meeting yesterday.
Do you know?
No
Shouichi-kun and Furuwsaka depending on whether to mass-produce and sell new products
There was a great quarrel between
It was a very quarrel
Shouichi-kun is secretly advancing the matter of the loan partner
Secretary Fujita leaked it
He is Furuwsaka
I'm sorry
You
Segawa-san
Do you gave time?
Eiko said she will contact you later
Tell her to get better and trust me
I know she trusts you
What can I do for you?
I forgot my bag
I wonder if I made a mistake in the room.
I'm sorry
He is nasty.
He is checking around
By the way,The police came in the morning and asked me about you and your sister
I think Sadako talked them
Sadako?
What's wrong?
I'm being followed
Are you OK?
I'm OK
If you don't do it early, they'll know the alibi
I know.
Eventually they'll know
I have to find the criminal by then
Do your best even if the police pursue,Kazumi
Yes
Who and who knows that you are approaching Ogino knowing the paramizale?
Only Sawai
It's impossible
Because the whistleblower also said that
Oh yeah
I get it
Who's the whistleblower?
If we know the whistleblower,we know the criminal
But Secretary Fujita is very suspicious
He called that night.
That phone call was a trap, too?
Ogino was so upset
The cup proves that I was there
Are the whistleblower and the criminal the same person?
It's impossible
The interests of the informant and the killer are opposed.
Yes
There is no doubt that the criminal is an official of Nanayou company
I have to leave for urgent business
Please lock the door when you go out
I have another key so it ’s okay.
Hello?
This is Segawa
Hello? what?
Who?
What? you are not Shinwa company?
It's me.
Who knows about my purpose other than you
There is a person who has informed me as I'm spy
Hello? can you wait?
Polyethylene material will arrive today
Yes, it works well
I'm having visitors, so I'll call you later.
Yes please
Why?Did the detective who came yesterday asked you anything other than Eiko?
They were at my company?
Did your alibi get caught?
You told them You called Kazumi from a pay phone in front of my house that night
But that phone was out of order
What?
Of course I won't tell anyone
But Why did you have to create a fake alibi?
No way, do you doubt me?
It's impossible I don't doubt you perfectly
Sorry to ask but can you trust Kazumi-san?
Why?
I don't understand why Ms. Kazumi helped you create an
alibi.
No way she is the criminal?
Kazumi?
She may be pretending to help you so she can help
herself.
She has no motive to kill him.
She has.
She wants revenge on Ogino.
revenge?
Kazumi loved Ogino but Ogino married her sister
She was pretending to be nice, but inside she was
frustrated.
And that's why she became a hostess.
Am I think too much?
Kazumi?
No way, but by any chance she might be the
whistleblower
The whistleblower's real goal may not be
industrial espionage, but to destroy the Oginos.
I'm leaving now
It hurts me!
Fuck you!
Did you find him?
Yes this guy! I'm sure this guy!
You found so quick
Yes this guy
For sure
He ran away when I said I fuck you
Thanks
It's shame I knew this, I could catch him
Imamura,
Put an APB out on him.
This is the task force.
Manager, call from Kojima cop
I'm Ishida,
Thanks for your work
We've put out an APB on Segawa now.
We don't know Segawa's motive for the crime.
Oh I see, I'll go there
No one saw Segawa choke her.
Segawa just left the room.
Of course, that's what we are going to
investigate.
So we need your help
I trust Segawa completely
Segawa was suspected in the recent incident, and I was not happy about
it.
I want you to talk the truth
the truth?
Yes
You've hired Segawa with good benefits
despite his poor performance as a salesman.
Isn't that a pretense?
Well....I have no idea
Please say clearly
Then I'll say
You're letting Segawa spy on your industry.
No way, Is there any evidence?
As you may know,This is a special lens for
espionage.
It was at the scene of the incident.
Segawa's fingerprints were on it.
So what?
This doesn't prove that Segawa is the killer.
If he's not the culprit, why is Segawa on the
run?
He might be afraid of police
There's been a lot of unjustified arrests
lately.
Sawai-san, Are you making fun of us?
Ishida-san
Please let us know if Segawa call you
Certainly
Sorry to disturb you
You are completely suspected
You should hide until the criminal is caught
But in this case I'm definitely not the culprit
I'll give you 100,000 yen.
Use this money to run away
I will send you money if you contact me
I won't run away
What are you talking about?
If you get caught, I'm in danger too
But I'm not really the culprit
If I run away, I may be the culprit
I used to be a guy who did everything for money
Kazumi and Ogino were killed in front of me and I was about to be the criminal.
I can't stand
I try to catch the criminal myself
But you're a wanted man.
If I get caught, that's it
You must not be caught
Use this money to hide for a while.
Police is not stupid
Please do your best until the criminal is caught
Please be sure to contact me
You change clothes
I know
No worry
Absolutely I'm not
The criminal is the same as the one who killed Ogino
I try to catch the criminal myself
Hello?
Please do not let Eiko know about this
She has already seen the newspaper
Really?
She suffered from brain anemia and collapsed
She is fine now
I'll talk about you.
Where are you now?
Eh?
You are there?
I'll hide here for a while.
I try to catch the criminal myself
Ah, Hello?
Like this
Segawa is following us
Don't look at him
Damn it.
He noticed
Hey
Are you going to turn yourself in to the police?
It's no good.
The hard work up to now will be wasted
I can't move
I think I should tell the police everything
Please think again.
Let's meet with me and discuss it.
The night is better
But it ’s dangerous to go to your office.
Police are sometimes near our office
Shall we meet at Jingu Gaien?
South exit of the second stadium
Yes at 8 pm
OK?
Watch out,Segawa!
Run away!
Police!
She seems to be able to sleep in the daytime
I see
She's been neurotic since that incident
She may get seriously ill
Why don't you invite her to a foreign trip for a change?
That's good idea
The more you say that Mr. Segawa is not the culprit, the more the result will be the opposite.
Where is Segawa now?
I don't know
You sure?
I don't tell you even if I know,because you may be a police spy
You are too bad
If something happens to Mr. Segawa, my sister may die
I introduced my sister Segawa-san
It's also my responsibility
Who is it?
Excuse me
Sadako is here, she wants to see my sis
Oh my god
Don't go home please
What are you saying?
Do you think I killed Ogino?
Because you are a scary woman
You conspired with your lover to take his property, and you killed him.
Stop saying it!
You are too bad
He was killed.
I'm right to say it
You're trying to be nice.
I don't want to see your face
If you have a conscience, please call the police yourself.
But you don't have such a conscience
Go home
Here is sister's house,
go home now
Of course, I go home!
You are a really bad person
This case will be resolved in a little while.
Eiko...
Even so, I didn't think Sadako was such a terrible woman.
Women are scared when they get angry
Women are especially strong when property issues are involved.
property issues?
Yes
It's legally resolved
Eiko takes 2/3, Sadako takes 1/3
If it is as it is
What do you mean?
Can't we talk by phone?
It's very important
Can I meet you in Shibuya because I also want to hear important things?
I'm ok but Eiko will be alone
No worry, she took a pill so she is fine now
Let's meet 2F of Bon at 3 pm
Is that Ok?
I think Sadako got angry on propose
What kind?
It's a case of inheritance by murder.
If the heir is criminally liable
In other words, when Eiko is an accomplice.
In that case, the right to inherit the inheritance will be lost.
Then all of Ogino's heritage will belong to Sadako.
I didn't know that
Sadako suddenly spoke.
I hope someone can help her
Support her?
The criminal is surely that person
I think so
Can we meet again?
I want to tell my sister that story and encourage her
It smells like gas
Eh?
Upstairs
Eiko!
Let's call an ambulance anyway
Wait
I feel sorry for my sister when everyone knows this
I can call my doctor
Take care of her
Wake up, Eiko!
Get well, Eiko
I'm sorry I left home
This didn't happen
I'll answer
Hello?
It's me
Ah? who?
Hello?
Are you Segawa?
Eiko tried to commit suicide by gas
Hello?
Can you hear?
I need to use the phone
Damn it
Eiko tried to commit suicide because of everyone
I have to find the whistleblower
Whistleblower forced Eiko to commit suicide
It was all because of the whistleblower that Ogino and Kazumi were killed and that I did this.
I have to find the whistleblower
Secretary Fujita?
He may have a reason to kill Ogino but
He has no reason to kill Kazumi
Who knew I was a spy
Kazumi said the same thing
Kazumi said the whistleblower and the criminal were the same person
And the next day Kazumi was killed
Police did not attack me at Jingu Gaien
Who knew I was going to Jingu Gaien
Are you doctor?
Yes,Are the sick people upstairs?
Yes
Segawa-san
keep quiet
How's Eiko?
She's okay because she was discovered early
upstairs?
Wait Segawa
A doctor is here
You think I'm the culprit
No..but...
You are the one who forced Eiko to commit suicide
I was hiding until today because I wanted to find the culprit myself
I found the culprit
Eh? who?
Segawa-san...
Eiko, Are you OK?
Eiko
Segawa-san...
Bring brandy or wine
Yes
Segawa-san...
Doctor is here?
Yes
I have no time
I need to meet her
Segawa-san...
You!
Wait!
Call police!
He is the culprit
Wait!
Damn it!
Take your seat
Why did you guys bring me here?
Let's sit down and talk about it.
My sister is sick
I need to go home
We can't let you go home
Why?
Persuade him,Segawa-san
Who will take responsibility if something happens to my sister?
You are hoping that Eiko will die
I am?
Am I hoping that Eiko will die?
To get the property of the Ogino family
You tried kill her
Don't say stupid things
I was more worried about my sister than anyone else.
You know that too, right?
That was the blind spot in this case
We have fallen into that blind spot
Come in
Your lover confessed as an accomplice
Mikio Sawai confessed that he was involved in the murder of Mr. Ogino, Ms. Yamaguchi and
and his sister.
He was collusion with you
I don't know
Whatever he says. I know nothing
Don't pretend you don't know
You wanted the property of the Ogino family,right?
First, you killed Mr. Ogino and transferred all my property to his wife Eiko.
Then you tried to kill Eiko and take her fortune.
Is that right?
No....
Confess!
If Eiko's discovery was a little later, your plan might have succeeded.
You tried to kill her by making your accomplice a fake doctor, so this plan failed.
It's all crap
This man tried to kill them all.
I know nothing
I don't know him
I was deceived
This man tried to kill them all.
Imamura-kun
Well.....let's go
The cause of this incident was money
I thought the criminal had no motivation to kill Mr. Ogino
This was the problem until the end
Segawa-san suffered the worst.
You were hired as a criminal from the beginning
And you were raised from him
Thinking about it now, I should have noticed when Kazumi was killed
Kazumi made it clear that the whistleblower was the killer.
By the way Toshiko is a perfect bad woman
But
I think the real cause of this crime was in Toshiko's heart.
So?
Toshiko Murozaki is
She was born as a shaded girl
So, deep down inside her, she felt inferior to Eiko.
Have a safe trip
I will go abroad and refresh my mind
I will start over again
I will definitely recover by the time you come back
Yes
Let's be happy with me next time
See you
Finish