Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Modae / The Night of the Honeymoon (1964)
The bride and groom will now depart for their honeymoon in Hakone!
Please send them off with a round of applause to celebrate their new beginnings!
Congratulations.
Hello.
I'm so jealous!
She lets her husband carry all the luggage.
The beginning of everything is important.
Thank you very much.
Take care!
Have a safe trip.
Thank you.
Take care!
Have a safe trip.
The ceremony we just had.
I am now at the gate of marriage.
Tonight I will be a married woman.
My heart is filled with both anxiety and anticipation.
But I will gladly go to my new life as a wife
The bath is ready.
Thank you.
If you need me, please call me.
Good night.
Something is closing in on me.
My heart is stepping back into the unknown
My skin is already waiting for it
You take bath first.
I'll take later.
You first.
Thanks.
Go ahead.
Excuse me.
It was a very nice bath.
What are you looking at?
A novel.
Take the bath.
Oh, you're not going to take a bath?
I'm a little tired, so I just wiped myself down.
Are you in a bad mood?
No no.
Good night.
We are still a couple in form only.
I've really extended my day to be a wife by a day.
I resent my husband's extra thoughtfulness.
But Shoichiro is a really kind man.
I'm happy.
Same here.
Here it is.
That's the road you just drove down.
I'm going to play.
Foe what?
I saw a pool at the main building.
You're going now? I'm coming with you.
Can you play?
I can't, but you have to teach me.
It's not that easy.
I brought you some fruit.
I didn't ask for it.
Your husband told me to deliver it to you.
I see.
He's dancing so happily.
I don't really like that kind of play.
What do you mean by that?
I think they should just enjoy themselves.
You just got married, but you're alone and lonely.
Why don't you take the rest and wait?
Excuse me.
You and your wife are a perfect match.
I am very honored to have it.
Among our friends, we think your wife will be a great person.
Because he is a great feminist
I envy you.
I'm happy for you
Welcome back.
You didn't sleep yet?
I was waiting for you.
I'm going to write a letter.
Why don't you write tomorrow?
No, I'll write when I feel like it.
You go ahead and get some rest.
What's the matter?
You don't like me.
Maybe you like someone else.
Tell me.
I'm going back to Tokyo.
Don't get me wrong.
I like you.
That's why I married you.
You are so terrible.
Because this is too much.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I tried to be honest with you but I can't have sex.
What do you mean?
I was in a car accident the year before last.
The man's nerves were ruined.
The doctor said he'd be fine.
So I got engaged, thinking I'd be better by the time of the wedding.
But it's not gonna work.
So..
I'm not worthy of being a man.
During the wedding and after you're here. With your charm.
I've tried so hard to make up for what I've lost.
But it's not gonna work.
Forgive me.
I'm sure you're disappointed.
I've been too selfish.
I'm at your disposal.
If need be, I am willing to humiliate myself and publicly disclose my flaws to prove your innocence.
I didn't know that.
I thought you hated me.
I love you.
Please believe me on this.
I was wondering if we should postpone the ceremony until I was healed.
But the doctor said there was a chance that marriage could cure me.
I wanted to marry you no matter what.
That's true.
I'm so happy that you thought of me.
You don't know what it's like to be a woman.
I don't just want sex.
That's what makes me different from men.
We're not only married for our bodies.
And it's curable, right?
The doctor said so.
Then let's work together to cure it.
We are a couple.
Chieko.
And...
Let's be a beautiful couple.
Thank you.
Good morning.
He's sleeping well. Please don't wake him.
why don't you go to the hot spring pool?
Over there.
Let's swim together.
Oh.
Chieko.
It's been a while.
Since graduation?
Are you alone?
My husband is here.
Are you newlyweds?
What about you?
I'm here in Recreation.
I missed out on getting married.
Well, you can only have so much fun while you still can.
I envy you.
And you're not here to play, are you?It's on the third floor of the main building.
I'm with these guys. They're all very interesting people.
I'd go.
Bring your husband.
Are you awake?
You slept so well.
I went for a walk.
You didn't run away, did you?
Don't be kidding.
Thanks so much.
We can't?
If I kiss you, you'll do more than that.
I'm afraid of that.
That's not gonna happen.
Please go back to bed and take off your pajamas.
Why?
I've been trying to get you washed in hot water since before we were married.
This feels so good.
Thanks so much.
Lie face down.
The year before last, the other car's brakes went out, and I hit this spot.
I don't know how much more I can take from you.
We bonded more strongly last night than any married couple ever has.
I feel as if I've already settled down with your wife.
I feel as if you're mine now.
Let's stop talking like this.
I just met a friend from high school at the pool.
She invited me to come visit them.
Please go.
She invited you too.
I don't wanna go.
I want to fully enjoy my stay-at-home husband's company.
You won.
Keep going.
Come on.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to introduce you.
This is my friend from high school, Chieko.
They're all boyfriends and friends.
I'm Ueda. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Are you newlyweds?
How about you bring your husband along?
He's not feeling well.
Because you had a lot of sex?
Good morning.
You overslept.
She was always with me.
It's so nice to be in love.
She's my friend.
How about your wife?
She's sleeping.
Let's enjoy time together.
Do you think they look bad? Actually, police officers and civil servants are people with serious occupations.
You guys look like you're having a good time.
Here it is.
I can't drink.
You come in here, have a drink, get your freak on.
It's a way to forget the angst of reality.
You worry about her husband?
I don't care. I don't care.
He's tired. That's bad.
Have a drink.
What are your thoughts on the marriage?
I'll leave that to your imagination.
Let me guess.
Disappointing, of course.
No way.
You're rude.
I know what on your mind.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be here playing.
Well, I'm leaving.
I won't give it back.
I fell in love with you.
That's bad.
It's your fault.
Don't get jealous.
I think marriage is a stupid habit.
The only thing between a man and a woman is their instincts, and that's all that matters.
But there is love between a husband and wife.
That's not why marriage is worth it.
That's ridiculous.
Why don't we just live from the heart?
Let go of your hypocrisy.
Is this a theory of life?
There's no need to think so hard.
Just enjoy the life in front of you.
Yes.
Be thorough.
I'm thorough in my own way.
I want to be affectionate above all else.
But a woman's body doesn't work that way.
I have to say.
I think you'll get divorced in six months and we'll join the group.
You think so?
Hello?
Who?
Ueda?
My wife is supposed to be there.
Hold on.
Your husband.
Oh you.
Sorry.
I'm leaving right now.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Did you have fun?
Yeah, it's been a while.
You're angry?
Tell me.
I knew you regretted marrying me.
That's why you didn't want to come back.
Well, I didn't mean it like that.
Chieko.
What's wrong?
Are you ok?
Don't look at me.
I can't..
You shouldn't be in such a hurry.
We just made a promise to each other that we'd stay rational until you got better.
That's why I'm afraid you'll leave.
No worries.
If I didn't love you, I'd have run away this morning.
If you're too pessimistic, I'll still be unhappy.
Cheer up.
Let's go have a cold drink.
Welcome.
Please.
Hey, Chief.
You're here, too.
I took a vacation.
Are you alone?
Just a couple of friends.
He's Ishikawa.
My wife.
Nice to meet you.
He's always been a great help to me.
Congratulations.
Let's have a drink together.
Please.
I'll excuse.
Come join us for just one drink.
Thanks.
what do you drink?
I'll have brandy.
I'll have coke.
I'll have whiskey.
You'll have to get a wife soon.
I'm sure you've got plenty girls.
I'm surrounded by an icy desert.
It's a cold world without sun.
It's not like you.
I'm jealous.
You got a very nice wife.
May I dance with her?
Go ahead.
Thanks.
Here it is.
I was surprised that the section manager is your husband.
What a coincidence.
Look, look, your husband is jealous of us.
Don't tell anyone, but see me from time to time.
I can't..
Welcome.
Who?
Shit.
What's wrong,Sadao?
They are the company's section chief and his wife.
Nice to meet you.
You are sometimes away from home for three days without saying a word.
It took me half a day to find a place to stay!
She's my aunt, Fusaki Shirako.
she is a beautician.
Yes I know.
Nice to meet you.
He's my nephew. He's a real pain in the ass.
He often goes out without telling me.
Let's go home.
You're kind of rude.
Because you are bad.
I beg your pardon.
See you.
I was in despair about my body until yesterday.
But today I have hope.
Maybe the doctor's right, maybe marrying you will cure me.
Really?
You were dancing with him earlier and I was so jealous.
So I think if you go with another man I'll be so excited that I'll be cured of my illness.
You're kidding.
You know, Ishikawa, he has a serious face at the office, but he's quite a playboy.
Think about it.
Are you serious?
I'm starting to get the feeling that this is where the doctor meant for me to go.
I decline.
You're not getting any unnatural stimulation, and I'm fine the way I am.
From now on, don't tell me about it.
I hope you won't even think about it.
I see.
Sorry.
Do you want to take this home?
I'm sorry for everything.
Your husband ok?
Don't worry.
He's concern about you.
Can't you have a baby yet?
Not yet.
How's Shuichiro?
He's very healthy.
Would he be so kind?
Yes he is.
I wipe him down every morning.
He is very calm like a baby while I wash him.
He comes home on time every night.?
Yeah, why?
Actually, your father saw him get into a car with a strange woman in Ginza.
What kind of woman?
He said she might be bar girl.
I'm worried about you because you've been so down lately.
Are things going well with you?
Of course we're doing fine.
Welcome home.
Come in.
He's Dr. Terada.
M wife.
I'm glad to meet you.
I'm Dr. Terada of Principle Therapy.
My husband has always been a great help.
Come in.
It is quite a splendid residence!
No way.
Would you like to have a drink while you treat yourself?
I'm very sorry, but I'll have.
Thanks.
Please bring ice and water.
Did you buy this house?
Yes.
I think the price was high.
I'll have it.
Go ahead.
Shall we start?
Where?
Here's fine.
Do you want to eat dinner?
I ate out.
Someone invited?
I finished my meal while waiting for my teacher in Ginza.
Excuse me.
I knew you had a problem with your third and fourth lumbar vertebrae.
I am the only one who can cure your husband's illness.
I'm sorry to hear you're ill with such a beautiful wife.
It must be hard for you, too.
But please be patient for a while longer
I'm sure I'll make you happy.
Life is very difficult when you have this disease.
My patient suddenly disappeared at her home.
It's not because of marital quarrels.
Are you still late tomorrow?
Why?
These days, even if I cook, you don't eat it, so it goes to waste.
I have to invite the Kyushu branch manager tomorrow, so I'll be home around this time.
He's leaving.
Come to see me again.
Do you drink brandy?
Same here.
I want beer.
You guys are good friends.
Don't be jealous.
Oh my god.
Bring ice.
What's the hell?
Nothing.
Chieko, come on.
It's me.
Oh mitsuko.
Thanks for the other night.
You look scared.
Nothing.
I'm going to Shiraki's beauty salon now. Wanna go out with me?
It'll be fun.
Get in the car.
Oh  madam.
Thank you very much for the other day
Sorry to bother you.
You look so nice.
But I think it would be better to expand it a little bit like this.
Where's Sadao?
Do you have something to do with him?
Kind of.
He's been attracted to someone else for a while now.
He seems to be having a hard time.
She must be me.
I'm thinking of marrying to Sadao.
He doesn't take you seriously.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you really going to marry Mr. Ishikawa?
That's a lie.
I was just teasing.
It's funny how she gets so mad when I mention him.
she has a very short temper.
She seems to get very excited when she gets jealous.
Mr. Ishikawa and her are blood related, right?
He's her nephew, but he's the nephew of her deceased husband.
I mean, he is a young swallows.
I see.
He's crazy about her too?
I hear you're interested in him, too.
I'm not.
It's okay. You don't have to hide it.
You're not happy with your husband.
No...
It's written on your face.
Maybe it's time you joined our group.
I'll make it fun for you.
Can you come next Saturday?
I can't.
You say that, but secretly you want to go.
Well, whenever you feel like it.
You need to take better care of yourself.
Look at us.
And live like a human being.
Where the hell did you go?
It's already 0:30 a.m.
I went to the hairdresser and then to Roppongi.
What did you do in Roppongi?
I think you're getting tired of living with me.
Why don't you just tell me what you really want?
I'm sure you'd like to have more fun.
What did you do in Roppongi?
Men are so free.
Once they're out, they can do whatever they want and come home and be fine.
A woman can be blamed for the slightest thing.
What's your point?
Don't pretend you don't know.
I saw you at the bar with a woman.
Chieko.
You're terrible.
You were with that woman every night.
I was meeting with that woman for treatment of my body.
Please don't make excuses like that.
I want to die.
I think I'm going crazy.
Even my own wife makes fun of me because of my body.
We're over.
I don't know what to do.
Don't run away, please.
No.
I can't live if you run away.
No..
Chieko.
I did it again...
Don't be disappointed.
It's a sign that you're getting better.
Don't go to the bar.
Let's cure it with the power of just the two of us
I'm sorry,
I won't go out with her anymore.
I'll be home early tonight.
Do me a favor.
What?
Now I'd like to go on an overnight trip with a class reunion on Saturday and Sunday, if you don't mind if I go.
Class reunion? Really?
It's true.
Sawaki is coming, too.
He's jealous...
I'm going for him.
Don't be afraid.
Three congratulatory gifts for the pair.
You?
Call.
If I lose any more, the wife will scold me.
Why did you ever get married?
Marriage is the graveyard of life.
I feel sorry for wives.
Thanks for coming.
But I guess I should go home now
We come here to free ourselves, escape from society and relax.
That's what this group is for.
I understand.
Is that all?
You're just waiting for Suda?
No way.
He's into you.
I know.
He's coming.
You came late.
What's the matter, are you late or something?
I'm having trouble because my section manager has invited me to play golf tomorrow.
My husband?
He noticed that I was a member of this group.
Haha I was kidding.
He was waiting for you.
I should go home now
No, no.
Forget about everything but your own pleasure.
I missed you so much.
I can't tell you how many times I wanted to call you.
Don't get nervous.
No..
You're pure.
That's what I love about you.
Stop it.
Don't worry.
No..
Stop it.
Don't touch my body.
Why?
Stop it.
You are dry.
Men find a thirsty woman attractive.
Ma'am, you're not a child.
You know what you're doing here.
I can't betray my husband.
That kind of sentimentalism doesn't make sense.
Let's just remain close friends.
Don't make it sound like a novel.
You don't like me?
You like me.
If you like each other, what's wrong with being physical?
Anyway, I'm going home today.
No.
Please
I want you.
No.
Let me go.
Forgive me..
Stop it..
I can't hold back.
You're not sure if you're inviting guys or being nice.
You are too old fashioned.
I am disappointed in you.
May I help you?
She's waiting.
Please bring cold water.
I wasn't wrong.
It's Sunday.
I'll make myself at home.
Lie down.
Do you want to have a baby?
Baby? but..
There's also the artificial conception method.
Dr. Terada came to my office yesterday and recommended it.
He said he'd carry it off in secret.
I want to have a baby, but I don't want it.
I'm sure he's colluding with some doctor, because he's a shrewd guy.
But I want you to have a baby, too.
As long as we have a child, things will settle down between us.
Are you sure you can love a child that isn't yours?
I could love your child.
I have a very talented young man working for me.
I'm willing to ask him to do it.
Who?
I can't tell.
I wonder if he is Ishikawa..
Why you think so?
Because you said he's your man.
No, he's a much better young man than him.
Or maybe you should ask Terada-san to pick someone who doesn't know each other at all.
I'm worried about whether you're in love with that person.
Oh you.
Good morning.
I've come to ask a favor of you.
Come in.
Thank you for the other day.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Please.
I have some business to attend to.
Have a seat.
What would you like?
Cold tea please.
Here's nice place.
This is good kitchen.
What I mean is...
I'd like you to visit us often.
Because Sadao is always out of home.
I've been thinking about it a lot, trying to calm him down, but...
Here's fine?
If he's with you I think he's at home.
I'm afraid..
Please help me.
He likes you so much.
So I'm asking you.
Hello?
I'm Ishikawa.
A woman.
I'll connect you.
Hello?
I'm Ishikawa, from Koi Bussan.
Who is this?
I'm Ueda.
Oh madam.
Sorry to call you.
I don't mind.
What's wrong?
I'd like to meet with you to discuss some things.
Can I see you?
Well..
Well, we'll look into it, and we'll call you back.
We'll call you later.
Thanks.
Who was it?
Private call for me.
I'm going to go to the office.
Hi. it's Ueda.
Chieko-san?
Ishikawa here.
The Chief is nearby.
It's not good if the exchange agent hears me.
Please call me as Ishikawa's sister from now on.
I'm sorry for troubling you.
I'm a little inconvenient tonight.
You have an appointment with someone?
My aunt is setting up a blind date with me.
I must meet with her.
I see.
I'm sure she's beautiful.
I hope so.
Hello?
Are you upset?
I hope your blind date goes well.
It's been a while.
Ueda is at work.
I'm here to see Mrs. Ueda.
Excuse me.
Please come in.
You must be bored.
Alone and without any pleasure.
Actually...
I wonder if your husband told you about our little talk.
I'm not sure what you mean.
About artificial conception.
Mr. Ueda is very enthusiastic. I wanted to bring it to you as soon as possible.
I'm sorry, but I'm not ready to do that yet.
If we have a chance, please contact me.
Please be considerate of your husband's feelings.
Mr. Ueda, you want to bond with this family.
He knows how much you are suffering because of his unhappiness.
I understand.
Please give birth to a child for your husband.
I will ask you then, but not now.
I heard you attended a class reunion the other day.
He's been neurotic ever since.
He suspects you, but he's having a hard time saying it.
I have some shopping to do.
I'll see you later.
But I'm not saying it's a bad thing
In case of emergency. It would be more convenient for you to have a conception.
Don't be rude.
I am very honest.
When I see these unfortunate families, I take kindly to them.
Thank you for your time.
I'll see you later.
Looks delicious!
I'll bake too.
You cook well.
Mr. Ueda's wife is here.
My aunt's a little concerned, so we decided we liked each other enough to get engaged.
That'll make everything go more smoothly.
But you know what? I don't like her.
In what way?
She's too familiar with Sadao.
Please try to judge her.
Hey, guys.
Welcome.
This is Miyakojima Shizuko-san.
This is Mr. Ueda's wife.
I'm Ueda. Nice to meet you.
You're beautiful.
We've decided to get engaged.
It's only been two hours since you met.
Why don't you try to get to know each other a little better?
We like each other, don't we?
Love at first sight, huh?
Please serve her.
Would you like something to drink?
I'll have brandy.
I told you we're engaged, but I lied.
She just wanted to live in Tokyo.
You are bad.
When shall we meet again?
Would you like something to drink?
Don't worry.
Don't be humble.
Let's drink grape wine together.
Let's have fun.
Oh, come on.
Dance with me again.
No, you're gonna have to give it up.
One more time.
Welcome back.
Are you alright?
Water, water.
Where the hell have you been all day?
I called you three times.
Here it is.
At shiraki's house.
You went to see Ishikawa, didn't you?
You must be very drunk.
Tell me.
I want to talk to you tonight.
Sit down.
I'll be honest with you.
I went back to that place to see that woman again.
And she laughed at me.
I know I sound pathetic.
I'm a really bad guy...
I don't want to hear it.
Hey, wait a minute.
I want to hear you this time.
You've been acting really weird lately.
What the hell did you do?
There's nothing going on.
Tell me the truth.
You're in the company of the crazy group.
That trip you took the other day was with that group, wasn't it?
Tell me the truth.
There's no such thing as a mistake. I'm as virgin as ever.
Are you sure?
Yes.
And I don't want to undergo artificial conception because I want to remain a virgin until you're cured.
Okay. Okay.
Don't betray me.
It's okay.
You're never going to go out with that woman again,ok?
If you're willing to try out your body on someone like that, why aren't you willing to try it on me?
I would do anything for you.
What's wrong with my body?
Don't make me suffer so much.
Come on.
Darling.
Chieko.
It's okay.
You don't have to do that.
I am your wife.
Chieko.
You are a poor person.
You are more pitiful than I am.
I need you.
Thank you.
I'm so pissed off.
Sadao is going to marry that woman..
If that little bitch takes Sadao away from me, all the hard work I put into taking care of him will be meaningless!
But it's an arranged marriage.
Don't be so cruel.
Give me some water.
I think he will listen to you.
I don't think there's anyone but you who can fix this situation.
Do they get along well?
They're like a married couple.
I beg you.
Then I'll talk to him.
Sadao.
Madam.
Sadao, where are you going?
I promised my friends I'd go bowling.
Chieko wants to talk to you.
She wants to talk to you in a small room on the third floor.
Ok.
There's a room like this
This is the employee break room.
I can almost imagine what you're talking about.
My aunt asked you, didn't she?
She's trying to get me and someone else to be friends in order to make her jealous.
Shizuko's being used as a tool.
So are you.
I understand.
That's why I'm not here to help you play jealousy games with your aunt.
I have something important for me, and I was wondering if you could help me with it.
What is it?
I'm thinking of having a conception.
A conception?
Ueda lost his male faculties due to his car accident injuries.
Poor guy.
I didn't know that.
Please don't let anyone know about this.
Ok.
So you want to talk to me about it?
You want me to be the father?
I'd rather that than someone I don't know at all.
He knows about it?
No.
Then why are you asking me to do this?
Because you like me?
I can't ask you to do this if I don't like you.
If you cared about me that much...
I wouldn't have to use the artificial conception method.
I can't.
What's the difference?
Artificial conception is more hypocritical.
I take this back.
Forget it.
You're a terrible person.
You seduced me.
It's the same thing.
I like you.
I can't.
Madam.
Your heart desires me.
Chieko.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Okay, okay, yes.
She heard us outside the door.
I'll go and check on her.
Sadao.
Ma'am.
Please don't get mad at me.
Ah, that's the only thing I can do
This is the penalty I have to pay.
I can't hold back.
I don't want to hear about you anymore.
Hold on.
I'm sure she'll come to me.
Ma'am.
I've been expecting you.
What can I do for you?
I wish you wouldn't play with Sadao so much.
He is picking on me.
I feel sorry for Sadao.
He's being played by two people, you and his aunt.
You like Sadao too, don't you?
I don't like him.
But you're so mean, so I'm so frustrated.
But you know that we have no advantage in this game.
Why?
You know how attractive a married woman like your wife is to him.
That makes me a challenge.
It's true, I'm liking Sadao more and more.
But in the end, he's Mrs. Shiraki's.
No one can imitate that crazy way of loving him.
You think so?
I think you're a more formidable foe than his aunt.
If his aunt is a raccoon dog, then you are a fox.
A raccoon dog and a fox scare each other.
Don't be rude.
I bet Sadao will be corrupted by you playing with him.
If that happens, will you take responsibility?
You can't take responsibility.
It's just a game.
I'd give up the world and my family for him.
What a stupid.
I don't believe you.
What's the hell?
If you don't even like Sadao, why don't you stop meddling?
Don't get so excited.
Your beautiful face is becoming more and more foxy.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
You have a visitor?
Good evening. I'm sorry to disturb you.
I'm asking you to do what I just said.
Who?
A relative of my mother's came from Kansai to say hello.
Hello, is Ueda residence?
Yes.
I'm Mr. Tsutsumi's deputy.
Has Chief Ueda left already?
Yes, please wait a moment.
I have a call from Executive Director Tsutsumi's secretary.
From Tsustumi's secretary?
This is Ueda.
Are you Manager Ueda?
I'm not Tsutsumi's secretary.
My name is Shizuko Miyajima and I visited your house earlier.
I have something to tell you about your wife.
What's that?
Your wife is in love with someone.
So, who's your business partner?
What?
He's my lover.
He's the one who's going to get your wife.
I need your help.
What's wrong?
You've been quiet.
We've been married six months.
I'm sure you must be disgusted by the tastelessness of our life together.
I'm thinking about having a baby.
I've finally made up my mind to have conception.
Why aren't you happy about it?
why did you change your mind?
I feel like having a baby would help you and me a little.
You're not having someone else's baby, are you?
What a horrible thing to say.
If it's happened, tell me.
It's easier for me to know the truth, no matter what the truth is.
If you're that suspicious, I don't have a place to stand.
I can't stand anymore.
I hate you.
Chieko.
You so mean.
You've never done anything for me, and I've always been suspicious of you.
I can't stand anymore.
I'm leaving.
Chieko.
If it makes you happy, I'll leave.
You're right, I didn't do anything.
I have no right to stop you.
Surgery... is that a big deal?
No, no, no, it's very simple.
You made a good decision.
Wouldn't you like to know whose the partner is?
Ueda-san has strictly forbidden me to tell you, but I'd be happy to do so in secret.
I don't want to know.
Here.
come in.
Go ahead.
Is this a hospital?
This is his home.
He is the head of the gynecology department at a general hospital.
He only sees patients he's close to.
Wait here.
You must be Chieko Ueda.
come in.
I heard from Mr. Terada.
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone.
Please take off your clothes and lie down there.
I'd still like my husband to be present.
Why?
It's a sacred thing for us.
I think it would be better if he were present.
That won't be necessary.
Go ahead.
Take it easy.
Are you going to give me that injection?
It'll be easier if you get some sleep, so just lie down.
Stop it!
I don't want to do this today.
But you don't have to worry about it.
Hey!
I'm leaving.
It's too late.
What's wrong with you?
Wait.
Hey madam!
I'm Ishikawa from the Research Division.
This is Chieko.
I feel very miserable and don't know what to do.
I really need to see you.
Please.
Help me.
Oh no..
I'll see you at 4:00. I'm sure we can work something out.
Okay, where should I meet you?
Okay, sure.
Just in case, please don't change your mind.
See you then.
I have some urgent business at home.
I have to leave early at 3:30.
I see.
Do you know Shizuko Mikoshima?
My fiancée.
Your fiancée?
Do you know her?
Someone asked me to do a little favor for you the other day.
When are you getting married?
Not yet.
I'd like to ask the Chief and his wife to join us for dinner then.
I'd be delighted.
I'll be happy to.
Uno.
It's hard to say.
Actually, I was wondering if you could do me a favor.
What is it?
I got here at 4:00 exactly.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
Mr. Ishikawa, take me somewhere.
This is a big change of your heart.
You don't worry about your husband?
Please don't talk about my husband .
I'm not meeting you behind my husband's back.
I called you here to be true to myself.
I'll take responsibility for my actions.
You look so unhappy.
But I'm afraid you're going to run away again.
I won't.
Never?
Yeah.
Hello, I'm calling from the front desk of the Silvermont Hotel.
Mr. Ishikawa came into the hotel with a woman.
Uh, yes, she's about 25 years old and looks like a young wife.
Let's have a toast.
To great love.
Did we look like a couple?
I don't care what people think about me.
I'm going my way.
You're great.
Mr. Ishikawa.
What do you think of Shizuko-san?
I don't really care.
You know, my Chief was asking me about Shizuko earlier, but I wonder if he met her.
Please don't talk about my husband .
Sorry.
How about Mitsuko?
She's a whore.
She thinks she's so progressive.
She's nice to play with, but...
How about your aunt?
With my aunt, for purely financial reasons.
I don't like it.
It's as if you're being probed.
Well, I'm young and single, so I've had played women.
But I like you the best.
The other women don't matter.
She's trembling.
I've never had sex before.
I don't know anything about it.
Who?
That's what I thought.
Chieko!
Ishikawa!
I was just trying to weigh her down.
I wish you could thank me for that.
You idiot!
Stop it.
This is my fault.
It's true.
This is what happens when you can't give your wife the pleasure of a woman.
It's not right to marry a man who can't have sex!
You idiot!
Stop it.
Please leave.
Please, no violence.
You guys are gonna have to talk this through.
I mean, it's an old-fashioned moral imperative.
What?
Let me go.
Are you alright?
You told that man about my body.
You idiot!
Sorry...
You are such a terrible person.
Chieko!
I'm getting better, aren't I?
The moment I heard you went into that hotel room, my period changed.
Now we're really married.
Forgive me?
You don’t have to  forgive me.
It's all because of you.
Are you sick?
I'm sorry to call you.
I'm afraid I'm going out of my mind.
What's wrong?
Michiko Sawaki got pregnant because of SADAO.
Sadao pretended to be in love with Shizuko and you and met that woman every day.
I am so frustrated.
There's a phone call for Mrs. Ueda.
From who?
From Michiko Sawaki.
why does she call us?
Please take it.
please encourage her to have an abortion.
Hello, it's me, Chieko.
I heard.
You're in a lot of trouble.
I want to be a mom.
Thanks to you, I have become an ordinary woman.
I don't care what kind of games you play, but having a baby is just too sloppy.
I know Shiraki's there.
Tell her.
I can't have a baby but I won't get married him.
Chieko can play with him too.
You are very irresponsible.
I don't care what you say
I'll have a baby and live without getting married for the rest of my life
I want to live in a way no Japanese woman has ever lived before.
That's all I wanted to say to you.
Well, good-bye.
what did she say?
She's trying to be tough, but She is still lonely.
she said she was going to have a baby.
Don't you regret that she gave birth to Mr. Sadao's child?
I'm just a bystander.
I just want to watch over her.
You love Sadao, don't you?
For a time.
But there was no love.
Because... I have a husband I love.
But you were so close to him.
If that's all I can do, I'll leave you to it.
Take care.
You all make fun of me.
Can I have a glass of water, please?
I have this calm gait.
I'm already sitting on the throne of wife.
This peace of mind of an ordinary woman seeking happiness
It's been a nightmarish six months.
THE END