Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Namari no Bohyo / Lead Tombstone (1964)
Help me.
No, forgive me!
No!!!
Forgive me....
Forgive me!
No!!!
Forgive me....
Hold on.
Hold on. I'll shoot you.
Come out!
Or are you crawling around like that all night trying to turn back?
Who are you!
Let's have a proper greeting.
You just went and stuffed yourself under someone else's car without even asking
You're speaking properly for a change.
Come out,
I'll run you over.
Hurry up
what are we going to do?
It can't possibly get worse than it is now
Am I coming in here?
It’s probably better than coffin, right?
You need to stay still until I open it.
Even if I want to move, I can't.
You have guts.
Hey, where the hell is here?
If you follow me, you'll understand.
Who?
It's me.
Come in.
You're late
This is a synthetic room.
Bring me alcohol and bandages
What the hell is going on? You brought a man I've never seen before.
Just hurry up and bring it.
This guy is injured.
I get it,
You'll just buy an ambulance or It would be nice if you opened a hospital,
Take off your shirt
What exactly is your business?
Don't speak unnecessarily.
Someone shot you.
Damn it.
Lucky guy.
There's no bullet in.
It was only a graze.
Hurry up,what are you doing?
Ok done.
Bandage him up.
How old are you?
I'm 23.
You have been chased by the police.
You're not going to have a good life.
You should probably let your husband hear that line too
You are well-spoken.
Come on, drink up.
it'll help you forget the pain.
Let me ask you something, do you have a criminal record?
I wouldn't make a mistake that would get I caught.
Drugs?
That's something only trash does.
I can sell it to others, but I won't do it myself.
Alright, then...
just cut it out.
You're not police.
I don't remember asking you for help me at all
You brought me here on your own, didn't you?
You're a strong-willed one, I see
I won't ask anything more.
Just make sure to sleep well at home tonight.
You probably can't sleep with that injury, so just try to stay calm
Got it?
You're an interesting kid
After all, I take care of your wounds and bandage you up
Is it okay if I at least get to know your name?
Or can I call you 'boy'?
I'm Mitsugu.
That's such a cute name.
but just so you know,
I won't be indebted to you
You've got some guts
I like you.
Hey, bring a blanket here
Good night.
Hey, where did you pick up that kid?
That kid is a strange one
He came crawling under my car like a stray dog.
Isn't that dangerous?
Carrying someone like that.
Still you do not get pregnant?
If I was to have a child, I feel sorry for the baby.
That's what I've been saying
I'll quit this business once we have kids
Is it really that easy?
The main boss won't allow it
What the hell are you doing?
Damn it.
What are they doing?
Did you sleep well?
I'd been listening to plenty of lullabies
Don't act like an adult.
Are you going out?
You shouldn't overdo it until your injury heals
Please let the boy eat something good.
Just wait a moment.
Take me with you too
I'm not going out to play, you know
Well, I'll take you to a nice place eventually, so just behave yourself
I'm asking you to introduce me to your boss
my boss?
Yes.
what about your relatives?
My father was taken by the army
before I could even remember his face,he die.
and my mother was choked by an American
Even if I owe something to the people out there, I don't have any debts
If you tell me to do something, I'll do anything
When I look at you, I feel like
I have no idea what you're going to do next
I've picked up quite a troublemaker.
Can you take me with you?
Ah, just wait a bit longer.
Wait.
Don't say anything.
Do you even know what kind of man the boss is?
I'll come to meet him if I know.
Once you meet him, you won't want to see him again
You act like a tough guy,
but compared to the boss, you're still just a kid
Don't get it twisted; it means you still have some humanity left
Do you have a lover?
Women are just a pain in the ass.
See, you immediately turn that way; it's proof that you are still kid.
I'm not saying anything bad,
so just go home as you are
What the hell are you?
Try if I'm still kid.
I'm not easy.
Damn it.
You are just a woman.
You're whore!
Please take that ball.
Here you go.
Thank you!
Good morning
Hello?
When did you come?
Uncle is doing well?
Yes.
Cycling races don't make any money.
Tell him.
I told him.
He wouldn't have heard it right?
He said he was quitting today so please lend me some money.
Did you owe him?
so there's no helping it.
How much is it?
He will return it with some interest, right?
But that's not good.
Can you let me eat something instead?
So are you eating apples?
It's better than drinking water.
You get hurt?
It's nothing.
You did something wrong?
No way.
Fighting?
It's none of your business.
It tastes good.
Eat a lot.
But that's not good.
why?
Because You wanted me to cook from
now you treat me
It's the opposite.
I'm not asking for a meal
because I don't have money
so why did you come?
It's fine, isn't it?
it's not fine,that's the important part for me
Why is that?
Insensitive.
insensitive?
Kumi.
is something wrong?
See you then.
Where are you going?
Big brother
Oh you.
I told you to behave yourself, didn't I?
I won't care if your arm rots
Go home.
Big brother.
I told you to go home
but I didn't follow you for any reason
Weren't you just walking in front of me on your own?
You said to let you meet the boss, right?
Yes.
I'll let you meet him, so go home.
Really?
You're a smart boy, aren't you?
Where did Shimura go?
Can't you hear me?
He went on shopping.
shopping?
Are you getting ready for a high-flying adventure?
Where's money?
You are lying
It's true, I'm just going to wait until that person comes back
I'll stay here until he comes back.
There's no need to wait
Don't move.
sometimes a man should try going to the kitchen
Well, how about you drink the coffee I made?
It's a 3 million yen coffee
Isn't that a lavish amount?
Do you really think you can steal the
boss's money and get away with it?
That's some bad talk about
The money was originally earned by my own hands
I just got tired of having it taken away from me so easily
Hey you!
Hey, don't go that far.
that's enough already!
On no.
There's no way that could happen.
If I don't do it, you'll be the one getting hurt.
You, you, you!
You idiot, there was no need to kill
You're loud
It's daytime.
, and this guy has hidden the boss's money somewhere
I should have heard it from him.
I just thought there was no need to hold back against a guy who swings his weapon around like that
You are a murderer
As long as the money comes through, that's all that matters, right?
She does not know
I'll ask  anyway
Hey, what are you planning to do?
Come in.
Where did the money go?
You beast!
Do you think you're human?
Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it?
You bastard!
Damn it!
I'll tell you.
Where is it?
Can you share it with me?
It's in the pillow.
1 million is fine, right?
Please.
You'll forget your husband's grudge for 1 million?
He didn't buy me anything
He is dead so he is of no use
Please share the 500,000 yen with me.
Please.
You have a good attitude.
If you're feeling that way,
then I'm not going to hold back either
It's better not to say that! Come here!
He is.
This guy.
He's so terrible.
He doesn't think anything of killing someone
How did you clean up afterwards?
It's okay
No one has seen it.
The police are also unaware of his connection.
What have you been doing until now?
It's basically the same thing you all have been doing.
What?
I mean, I've done it all by myself up until now
Be careful with the words that say
Well, that's fine
This guy is useful.
Well then
Be careful.
Before long, you might end up being bossed around by this guy
I see.
If this keeps up, I might even lose my head
that's joke, boss
I'm not kidding.
That's why a man like that can be useful.
Before you start working, first make the
clothes, got it?
Don't make cheap clothes
In this world, a miserly man won't be taken seriously
You are a lucky man
I have no luck
If there is any, it's just something I create myself.
You are as usual
it's a bit too flashy
I haven't seen anything like that, but if that's the case,
how about this?
which one is better?
I'll buy both.
That's quite extravagant
How much?
Thank you very much
Is it okay with just one.
I see.
I'm the one asking here
Yes, please wait a moment
This is troubling for me
I can't have my wife saying such stingy things
Wife?
Starting tonight
Tonight?
Yeah, let's do it grandly,
just the two of us
Are you serious?
You don't like it?
I can't believe it.
I'll tell your uncle later that it's fine, right?
It's not a dream, is it?
It may not be enough for our main event, but bear with it
I'll rent out the Imperial Hotel for our wedding anniversary next year.
Hmm, it feels like a waste even this way
Don't say stingy things.
Don't say lines like that until I've become a bigger deal
What does that mean?
What are you thinking?
And what happened to the money you spent today?
I told you not to ask unnecessary questions, right?
But.
You're angry, aren't you?
I'm sorry, I won't ask anything anymore
Kumi
I understand
Come on, don't make such a dull face.
What do you want?
It's you, Mr. Kariya?
That's right, what time do you think it is?
Sorry,
this is an outside line
I'll connect you
Hurry up.
Do you understand it's me?
Ah, what the hell is going on?
I feel sorry for you
Your first night should be next time.
What?
Come out to the hotel entrance in about 10 minutes
The car should be waiting
Give me a break.
Hey, it's exactly 10 minutes later
Wait a minute.
I'm telling you
The president's work doesn't distinguish between day and night
Damn it.
What's wrong?
Who is it from?
Are you going out?
Where's he?
Thank you for your work.
Hurry up, I've got a bride waiting
It's a job suitable for a first day like this
Thank me.
What are you going to do with it.
You know how to use it, right?
Am I planning to kill someone?
What else can you do?
But.
there's only one bullet in the pistol.
You can't redo it, got it?
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say;
I won't say it again
First, let's set the clock
It's 3:15.
Good.
so we should do it at exactly 4:30
Who do we kill?
There is a man who arrives exactly at 4:30 at the entrance of the Nichigeki Cultural Center
What kind of guy is he?
I don't know anything about that
Anyway, just do as you were told, got it?
I get it.
It's exactly 4:30, don't get it wrong, exactly 4:30, okay?
Just 3 more minutes.
Damn it.
I hope the guy will come out at 4:30,
there's no mistake in the boss's orders
What?
There's no mistake in the boss's orders
You seem very great.
It's 4:30, you know
Go.
Are you alright?
You were having a nightmare, weren't you?
What kind of dream did you have?
Give me some water.
You're tired.
You've probably been having nightmares every night lately
Oh, what time is it?
It's 5 o'clock
Should I make some coffee?
Please.
Why don't you take a break from work for a while?
It would be terrible if you got sick, you know.
You never tell me.
When you do work, what kind of things do you do?
Like you leave early in the morning
Or you  sometimes not coming home all night,
I don't really understand it well, but
Sometimes I become extremely anxious
It's none of your business
That's not true. I wonder if there are any wives who don't know their husband's job.
I'm going to sleep.
Good morning
You look very scary
Knock on the door
I forgot about those kinds of formalities
You've really risen in rank since I last saw you
Well, you look really worn out.
Are you having a kid?
I didn't know that.
When?
In two months,
huh? I have to celebrate that.
What would be good?
Just tell me anything
No stingy stuff allowed
I don't need anything.
That's not good.
I want to give something to celebrate your newborn baby.
You shouldn't have any reason to refuse
If you're going to say that much, I have one request. Is that okay?
Go on, then
I never want you to come back
Harumi.
I don't want my baby to be like you guys
If you want to laugh, go ahead,
but I too have my own story
Even if I think I know well what kind of life I've lived until now,
the child that is born will be different
From now on, he should be able to become any kind of person
I understand.
I promise I won't come back again.
Hey, wait a minute!
Don't get her wrong.
A woman is just a female
before she gives birth,
but once she has a child, she changes.
In other words, she becomes a mom
I'm weak against those who have changed.
He hasn't changed at all
Who the hell are you?
I'm Nomira
What?
What do you want from me...
You.
Boss, who is this guy?
whatever
He's my right-hand man.
His name is Tashiro
Please take care of him.
Don't look down on me.
Come on, don't be so angry.
He remind me a lot of the way you used to be
By the way, are you going to meet Kaneko?
I met him at his house this morning.
he was still there?
What do you mean?
He came to me last night and said he wanted to quit.
Quit?
I heard he's going to have a child
Eight months?
huh? Yeah, that's what it seems
I see, that's why
I thought about having you do it
but this time the opponent is different
I am thinking of having this man do it.
You mean kill him?
You shouldn't be too surprised
That's the rule.
What a foolish guy.
Boss, I'll do it.
Can you?
What will the woman do?
I want to help her
but it seems that's not possible
I understand.
You.
I've been waiting
Hey, wait a minute
I'm on my way to tell the boss that I give up to quit.
Why didn't you do it sooner?
If you had done that, I wouldn't have had to take on such an unpleasant role
She didn't listen to me.
So that's why it took so long?
please just let her go, I'm begging you
Anyway, just get the car out
Where are you going?
Kill me whenever you want.
Shut up and There's no need to rush to die.
Run away.
Don't go dying.
I was planning to save only you,
That's not like you anymore
But I thought it was unnecessary for you to be so pushy after all
That's what I thought.
I thought it would be better to finish the work quickly
Just so you know,
I'm refusing to work with you
Even if it's the boss's order.
Never mind.
It's best to do work alone, after all
Let's clean up anyway
That's dangerous!
What's wrong?
You're so drunk.
Shut up.
are you hurt somewhere?
You are stupid.
I'm fine.
Bring water.
Hey.
Kumi.
What are you doing?
If call you, at least reply!
What happened last night? There was blood on your dress shirt
I must have gotten into a fight while drunk, right?
Wait.
I had known what it was for a long time,
About what?
but just thinking about it was scary
I've been deceiving myself all along
What do you mean by that?
It's about what you're doing
Ordinary people can't earn this much even in a year
You brought me a large sum of money as if it were pocket change
I'm doing that much work
It's not normal
You're crazy.
The world is crazy.
It could be.
What do you want to say?
I don't understand that
Something's off.
it seems like you're overthinking trivial things
Please take me somewhere far away
Please. Anywhere is fine. The farther away, the better.
What?
I have money. I have enough to live without doing anything for two or three years
I believe I will eventually find a job.
There are jobs everywhere.
That's what I dislike. It's scary
I don't really understand what it is
I can tell that it's not a normal job,
and that's probably a terrifying thing, right?
Hey, you know how my mother died, don't you?
What did the people of the world do at that time?
What did police do to help?
The police said my mother was a prostitute.
Since then, I've been living all alone, by myself
Not once has anyone in the world treated me like normal.
I have no obligation to be criticized for whatever I do
That's not it
That's not right
What's different?
I may owe something to the people out there, but I don't owe them anything
So, does that mean you can do whatever you want to the people out there?
I am who I am
I'll show the world what kind of big shot a kid who has lived alone can become.
Did Kaneko say something?
The words of the person being targeted are always the same, right?
What's wrong? You look troubled, which isn't like you at all
It's not like this is your first time doing this job
Well, for now, just take it easy
If anything comes up, I'll contact you again.
For our maid, you have a certain elegance about you.
Do you need something?
or have we met somewhere before?
I'm Kariya's...
What a troublesome man to forget such a cute wife like you.
I followed him quietly
Do you think that your husband might be cheating?
Please don't let that person do any more bad things
Bad thing?
It seems like you're misunderstanding something.
He doesn't anything wrong.
But please don't try to deceive me.
I understand it well
But I won't say anything
Please let him go.
Please.
Please return that person to me
That person is not really someone who can do such bad things
Something is definitely wrong, and that's why such things happen
It's okay, right? I'll let him quit this job.
Thank you, I apologize for the inconvenience
Do you know the woman now?
No.
She's Kariya's wife.
and it's become a hassle
What do you think of that woman?
If money could buy her, I would buy her for a million dollars.
but she's Kariya's woman
I guess it's good to let Kariya handle it after all
This is awesome.
I can't do this anymore.
Hey come on.
You look so nice.
Boy.
You.
I came to pick you up.
Pick me up?
Our president wants to see you right away
Our president?
Drink this.
This is good for sobering up.
Do you think I drink this?
Our president hate drunker.
What happened to Tashiro?
I have no idea.
You're as usual.
How about you stop competing with each other?
Both of us have a personality that prefers being alone
Take it.
I met for your wife first time,
and she's quite a lovely wife,
Did you meet her?
She came today
Kumi?
You've got quite an eye, haven't you?
So, did my wife say something?
She mentioned wanting to cut you off from this world
She...
It seems that she followed you today
Our conversation was completely overheard
She's a woman unmoved by money.
You took a troublesome woman as your wife.
I'll do something.
there's only one way to deal with it
I wonder if you can.
Boss.
I can't believe it.
I feel sorry but
Close her eyes
It's for your sake
Let's just say the deadline will last until tomorrow.
Once it's over, take some time off and go on a trip.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh we are closed.
Don't worry.
Please.
what can I offer you?
Whiskey.
I understood.
I sincerely apologize.
Who are you?
Excuse me.
Stop it....
No...
Stay down.
Stop it....
No..
No... no... ah...
Customer.
It has already gone past 1 am.
Ah 608.
Kumi?, it's me.
You told me you'd like to go somewhere far.
Get ready and wait in front of the apartment.
Did you make up your mind?
You're going to quit your current job, right?
I will.
Is there anyone who cries?
Hurry up.
You.
Kumi...
Kumi.
Why?
why is this happening?
I was so close to becoming a mom, you know?
Become a mom?
You haven't noticed it?
I can't believe it.
It's too late...
Kumi?
Kumi....
THE END