Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
(A rainbow at every turn)
Hi, Little boy
No rainbows today, huh?
I passed by here in the evening soon after she was born
It was winter, but suddenly there was a rainbow over the lake
Oh really?
Rainbows in winter are rare
Yes true
The colors of that rainbow were like spring and summer
When I see a big rainbow, I feel like happiness is coming
I showed it to this kid
He didn't seem to get it
Because he's a little boy
How old is he now?
He is 5 month plus a few months years old
Would you excuse me a minute?
I will take care of him
Can you?
Thank you very much
Chu chu
Shall I do it for you?
I'm used to it
ooh-la-la!
His mother is in Kyoto now
Have you ever taken care of a baby?
No No
But I learnt it at school
Oh! at school!
Yes
Someone'll make you do it soon enough
Well..Are you living in Tokyo?
Yes,
I had some business in Kyoto
I'm on the way to return to Tokyo
I see, I understand
Oh,lalalala
Stop here
Why did you go to Kyoto?
I went to see my friend who got married
You are lying
I'm not lying
But the real purpose is different
The sister that you went to look for, did you find her in Kyoto?
Did you find her?
I see
I think She's lucky you didn't find her
Sister,
Our father does not know about it at all
Asako went to Kyoto with that in mind
I can't say
Our father has a good intuition
I also have a good intuition
What did our father say?
He didn't say anything
For whom did you go to Kyoto?
For our father?
Or for us?
For your mother? or
For the sister in Kyoto?
It's not for anyone
So did you feel morally responsible?
If not, For your viewing pleasure?
I don't know...
Before Asako's mother died, she was worried about her child in Kyoto
So you went there?
But..
I'm sorry I need to leave now
Sister
I have a favor of you.
Please don't make a distinction
between Asako's mother and your mother.
Asako's mother is your mother now
I hope you understand
Right
She was very nice
I had a mother of my own who committed suicide
There is no choice to say it
Don't cry.
You don't have to cry
You are sweet,Asako
You went to see her because you have feelings for your sister in Kyoto
But Asako
Before your mother die
I don't know if she meant it when she acknowledged the girl from Kyoto as our sister
Why do you think so?
She's dying, herself...
Asako's mother is miserable
If the Kyoto kid comes into our house later
She might as well acknowledge the Kyoto girl while she's still alive, she thought.
You are going to Kyoto for your mother
You are stupid
Sister...
Everyone has their own way of life and their own environment
I think the girl in Kyoto will be confused when they enter the house
Brothers are just the beginning of strangers
Let her do whatever she wants
Go home!
Why aren't you waiting in your usual spot?
I had been waiting you there
Why are you snooping around my house like a thief?
Because you often skip our dates
Our father's car
Where is Momoko?
She has just let house
Oh welcome home
When did you back home?
Just now
Mmmm..
You must be tired
Not at all
Shall we prepare the meal?
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
Not yet
I bought your favorite boiled rice soaked with tea
Really? Thank you very much
Please prepare a meal for him
Yes
Where are the hangers,Sumi?
Was it cold in Kyoto?
It was not cold much
Miss, the spinach is cooked
Did you drain it well?
Yes
Okay, you can cut up the bacon.
Then open a can of olive oil.
Yes
It's inconvenient and annoying without Asako
For a meal
and for everything
Because my mother taught me
I'm thinking of going to Atami for work in a couple of days
Do you want to come with me?
Yes I would like to go
Shall we ask my sister too?
Um
But...I wonder she wants to come
It's a tragedy to be thrown away after just a few peeks at your house
What are you talking about?
You're just passing through me
Passing through you?
You will like another student girl soon
No way, you think so?
I'd have to die if you left me
I'm serious
You don't have to say that
So You don't get angry anymore?
Please promise it
Ok, I do
In exchange, I'll take you to Hakone
Really?
I'm glad,You really should take me to Hakone
It's quiet here
Yes
You changed your mind suddenly
You preferred Hakone to Atami
I think this change would have been better
Excuse me
The bath is ready
Oh, Thank you
Shall we take a bath?
I'm shy
You will be shy with me?
Because
Then I will take first
I see
Ah...
Father
I will take a bath with you too
I will go for a walk there
Yes
I will take care of your luggage
Take care
Ah...
I'm going to build Asako a house
My house?
I will live there alone?
Is there anyone you want to live with yet?
I have no idea
If so, you can live there alone
A home worthy of your beauty
I'm an architect
Even in a small house for my daughter
I want to leave you a house, like will testament
A house like a will?
I don't like it
But listen to me
Recently I feel something...
I feel the fate of architects in the age of atomic and hydrogen bombs
You say the loneliest things
To build a house for my daughter...
It's fatherly love
or rather I should say
It's a fatherly touch
Yes, It's a fatherly touch
Hey you
Yes
Where is the best view spot?
It's a badminton court there
Father
Hum?
You have three houses to build for your daughters
What?
For my sister
For my younger sister in Kyoto too
Oh
Asako
Don't go there, let's go back
You know what?
My sister thinks we've been to Atami
It's like we're doing something wrong and hiding
What are you going to do with my sister?
Can you just leave my sister alone?
Is that OK with you?
Thanks for the meal
Not at all
She seduced such a young boy
I don't understand what she thinks
Find the real wound in Momoko's mind
Find the real wound ?
I don't know what to do too
She would only confide in her real mother,I think...
Who knows?
And She's strong-minded
But father....
Asako
I've been in love twice, married once
Momoko is the child of my first love
You are the child of the woman I married.
And the last child, Wakako
Am I dirty man?
Anyway each my daughters are very beautiful
Whenever I see you,I forget my sins
That's just another selfish thought on my part
I took Momoko in despite your mother's presence
Because Momoko's mother committed suicide
That may broke Momoko's heart
You have 3 children
In truth, I'm the only one
You are right
If so...
I feel sorry for you
But,Asako
Children and parents cannot be separated from each other
I would like to see my sister in Kyoto
I want you to meet her
But Momoko won't allow it
Want to eat some?
Who would take out a motorboat this late in the day?
Close the door,Asako.
It's cold
What's wrong?
I thought that person was my sister
But I don't see the boat. I only can hear the sound
Are you thinking the same thing?
The same thing?
Momoko plays with dangerous men because she has bad experiences in the past
Momoko resents that you're a filthy man
So
It might be so
Whenever I've been watching her behavior
I think she's willing to try to kill herself.
kill herself?
Father,Not only for my sister but
What if I and my sister in Kyoto are three like my sister?
Such as Suicide, hating their father,
being far away from you
What are you talking about,Asako?
I don't like our current situation
We are sister
I want everyone to be happy
Oh,I wondered who you were, but I guess you're Mizuhara.
It's been a whole
You came here all of a sudden
Yes
Anyway Please come in
Nothing has changed here
No way
I don't take much care of it
You came here alone tonight?
No.
We came here with my daughters
I see.
That would be nice
There is someone who wants to build a tea house here
I came here for the work
I see
In fact, I wanted to meet Kikue
What?
I used to come here with her
I see
I once came holding a child
She left me during the war.
She sometime comes here?
Yes maybe
I see.
I'll serve tea when she comes in
Yes
I'll go get Oku-san
She'll be happy to know that Mr. Mizuhara is here.
Are you still sleeping?
Asako
I feel sleepy
Do you know what time is it now?
It's past ten o'clock
Oh really?
Where is father?
He's already gone
To where?
I have no idea
There are two tickets on the desk
I see
This?
Yes
He meant for us to watch it
You know what?
I think he's making arrangements to meet your sister in Kyoto
I don't like it
You came all this way to be with me, didn't you?
I refused to go to atami last time. so this time I have no choice to come here
But I want to meet her, so you should meet her
Hey Asako
My father wants us to meet your sister in Kyoto
He doesn't want you to meet her, he wants me to meet her
You have come here to meet her before
Our father does not care
I don't want to acknowledge her as my sister
So I think he'd really like me to have her
It's complicated
It's complicated... for your mother?
Because your mother was a stepmother?
She was not
Asako's mother was very good to me
How many times I should tell you about it?
The reason our father took us to here is not for meeting my sister
He feels lonely if he comes here alone
Why our father feels lonely?
Because you are..
Me what?
I don't know what he is doing in Kyoto
(singing)
How old are you right now?
I have no idea
Ha?
In this temple,There is no cherry blossom
Hahaha
Cherry blossoms mess up the garden
I see you've lost your hearing
It's true
Cherry blossoms are too flashy for a temple
It's strange for a priest to pay to plant cherry trees
She has come
Thanks
I put her through to the sitting room
It's nice to see you again
It's nice to see you again too
It's been a long time
When was the last time you saw me?
It was long time ago
In this morning,I have come here while our daughter was sleeping
Oh I see.
That sounds tough
You have not changed yourself anything
No way,
I'm so tired from all the hard work
I've aged
Actually, my wife was dead last year
I'm sorry to hear it
Of the three parents of my daughter, you are the only one still alive
You are the only ex-wife who reminds me
Don't be so lonely
It's not what I want you to think of me when I'm dead
I regret that I should have been better to you
I feel regret
What are you saying?
You'll have to tell that to your wife
You took care of me well
I never forgot what you did to me
Would you like something to eat?
I'll take it
Wakako must have grown up
Thanks to you
I'm being raised with great care
I should have brought her
If...
If I ever met her, though, I wouldn't be her father
No way
She hasn't forgotten how to be pretty.
She said she was going to see my father.
She said this with tears in her eyes
I escorted her out
I see
Ah
I will take care
Hi
I met you on the train before
Ummm...
Olalalala
Oh,take your seat
Never mind
Please sit down
Please
You take your baby everywhere
I'm not going to show the dance to the baby
I'm going to show the dance to this babysitter
Hmmmm
She is my sister
This is Mr.Otani
Nice to meet you
The other day, I had your sister care for my baby
I see
What a cute baby
Cute ears
Her ears look a lot like her mother
Oh I see
This babysitter is my mother's sister
She takes care my baby better
Older sister isn't kind everywhere
No..No at all
By the way how do you know my name is Otani?
Did I give you my business card?
No
I saw your name tag on your luggage at the time
Is that so
Asako
This is our father's business card by the way
Thanks
Mr. Tsuneo Mizuhara...
Ah! That famous architect
If I remember currently..his office is around here
Yes
Waka-Chan! Waka-Chan!
What happened?
I have no idea
Hmmm
(Baby crying)
Actually Asako was last year...
She came here to find her sister without asking me and Momoko
Oh I see
I don't think it's just the sentiment of losing her mother
If Wakako knows it, I'm sure she'd glad
I want Asako to meet Wakako at this opportunity
I know Wakako will be glad but..
Momoko won't be happy
I don't make Wakako feel embarrassed
I will ask her to meet Asako
I would really appreciate it
It's not big deal
This is a souvenir I got from a temple
Can you show this to Wakako?
Sure
This petals are wonderful
I think she will be glad
Did u see our father?
Did you come back without seeing the dance?
Mr.Otani worried about you
Mom
Did you come by Kaburenjo?
What hell you talk about?
You escaped from there
I didn't escape from there
I met my sisters in Tokyo
What?
They are so beautiful girls
Oh really? then why did you escaped from there?
I don't know..but it was hard to stay
Both of them are your sister
But I...
If I said too them I am your younger sister at that time
I felt that I would have the same fate as my mother
What do you mean,Wakako?
She was always reluctant
My mother always gave up something
But I don't like it
If my sisters really want to meet me,I'd happy to meet them
Otherwise I don't want to meet them
Your father gives this to you
Let me display it in my room
Is that so?
Our father has gone again?
Yes he has gone to Nara
He said there is something helpful for work
I see
I got tired with Kyoto
Excuse me
Yes
Someone visit you
Who?
His name is Natsuji Aoki
Who is he?
He is a student
I invited him to room over there
I see
Do you know him?
Do you know?
I was successfully deceived by my father
I should have come here
What's wrong with you?
I finally get it
The person who asked my father to design a tea room is Aoki's father
Eh?
Natsuji is Keita's younger brother
Kita is my ex boyfriend
He died in Okinawa at WW2
Oh...
You didn't know anything because you were small
My dad doesn't even know the truth
Please go to see him ,Asako
Why me?
Please talk with him
But what should we talk about...
It is ok if you just listen to him
Ok?
What you will do then?
I will go after calming down
Momoko!
Recently I'm always like this!
When I'm up for it
I felt hot all over my body
I suddenly feel like drawing my sword
People trust their lives to this sword
I feel ridiculous
The room upstairs, that's the problem
I'm a suicide bomber
I am ready to die
I remember my baby sometimes
Why is that?
Babies don't know the horror and terror of war
I sometime think of it
Am I a coward?
I know how you feel
Momoko-san
I want to see your face under the light
Ah...
Momoko-san!
I want to mold your breasts
What?
I'll make a bowl out of a mold of your breasts
I want to finish my last life drinking from that bowl
No! No I don't like it!
With the bowl of your breast
I want to finish my life
No! No I don't like it!
Momoko-san! May I?
She is my sister.
This is Natsuji-san
Natsuji's father invited us over for dinner.
Are you university student now?
Yes. and I will graduate next year
His school is in Tokyo, but He is here for his graduation thesis
I see
So you're the same age as your dead brother
Yes
You two are very much alike
It's like copycat!
Yes, many people say that
Is that your brother's hat?
Yes
It was small at first, but gradually it became just right
I've made it!
Look, Momoko-san!
Ah, so delicious!
Your blood runs through here
Please drink it
No...
Do not be hesitate
Oh! it's cold!
(air-raid alarm)
Oh..eh!!
Stop it!
No!
(air-raid alarm)
Oh my god, You are bad
Maybe it would have been better if we'd broken up instead of letting this happen
I find other women much more interesting
I have to leave now
Wait!
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
Because I feel disappointed
You are terrible
I'm going
Please
Tell me the season
Because
You are not a woman!
Keita-san!
So What you will do?
If you want to refuse, you have to tell Natsuji-san
I will visit you
I feel at ease
Thank you for visiting us
Momoko-san
I'm sorry I didn't inform you of Keita's death in battle
I didn't inform you on purpose
I'm sorry for his loss too
I just wanted to thank you for what you did for Keita
and I wanted to apologize too
It's between him and me.
I don't want anyone else to apologize to me
Yes you are right..but
Anyway
I want to say thank you, and apologize to you
I will forget everything
It is not easy to forget for me
Ok, Let's forget it
After Keita's death, I'll miss you
I can't wait to see you
I was going to kill myself
Oh, sister...
At that time,I had just been drafted too
I had cyanide from the factory, just in case
I took it
When was it?
But it was sugar
Before I knew it, the contents had been replaced
Your mother replaced it for me
When I felt it tasted sweet
It hit me
My mother killed herself with cyanide
I thanks to Asako's mother
I've always found human life to be a strange thing.
And then I'll never think of dying again
I licked the sugar with the intention of dying
Your mother probably doesn't know either
No one knows
They don't know anything
Why you planned to suicide?
Even if I talk to you, I won't forget
Um
Please take your seat
You were supposed to come here
Um
What's wrong,Aoki-san?
You're very quiet
We have been tried of waiting for  you
Please drink
What are you looking at?
Pictures of Katsuyagi-kyu
Natsuji-san who was there with me took photos of me
Asako read the book as soon as she got home
Asako is always like that
You listen to Mozart, then studies Mozart's history
Yes..No choice
What if you investigate him after you're married?
You are too bad
I'm sure you talk with Natsuji-san about me
Because Sister..
Even though you don't know anything
I never talk about you badly
I don't like the attitude!
You always pretend to be nice
I'm sure Natsuji-san pretend to talk nicely about his brother
That's not true
You know what,Asako?
If you're going to talk about me, you should talk about the world
I am..
If Keita had died in that war, I wish I had killed him
I hated Keita
My mother also...
If she wanted to kill herself, she should have killed my father
Why you say that?
She probably hates my father
That's for my mother?
Because you are sweet
You try to help the sister in Kyoto,me and out father
I didn't mean I try to help you
I've never had a cheeky thought like that
You know what,Asako?
Shall I tell you that you don't know?
What is that?
About my health
Tell me
I want to know all about you
Let me pass this time
You are too bad
You tried to say..
It's not your business
By the way You will invite Natuji-san Tomorrow, Sunday?
Our father said that
But I won't be here
Why?
I will go on trip a few days
You should take care of him
Why do you always pick on me?
I probably envy you
You should meet Natsuji-san then remind of Keita-san
What the hell you talk about?
Natsuji-san wants to know about you
He worries about you
I don't want your sympathy
I don't like the way you talk to me
Sister
What?
So You will go to Hakone
Then you will drive motorboat at night
Why you don't look at me?
Sister
I worry as if I get after your back
You act like a girl
Because you read book all the time
I've been arguing with Asako
Is that so?
Hey Miya-Chan, for us
There is a sister in Kyoto too
But each sister has different mother
That doesn't matter right now
That does matter for me
That doesn't matter for you and me
I feel pain
What are you going to do to me?
Give me your necklace
What you will use it for
I will kill myself with that necklace if you left me
Miya-Chan
Have you ever lived in resistance to your own sadness?
sadness?
It's sad that You and me do like this
Oh..you are kidding
You try to make me sad
You try to dump me
You are annoying baby
I give you
You mean I have to suicide
I got letter from your mother
She said in the letter Please make him back home
What the hell
I probably forget that you have your parents
I'm sorry for that
I will be bad boy if you dump me
I will play with girl as many as possible
But I am better than you
Yes you are good boy
I won't leave from you!
You may be a demon, but you can't leave me
Can you dump me?
You will dump me?
Ah...
This is the only thing left of my brother
Did Keita do this kind of plasterwork?
Yes,My father used to make tea bowls from clay
He made it by imitation
But What is this shape?
You will know if you ask to Momoko
She always talk with Asako
As his brother, I feel responsible for him
I feel responsible for Momoko too
Sorry for keeping you wait
Not at all
You know what,Asako?
I think...
Momoko is afraid of normal love
She's rebelling against it
My brother abused her
And my brother was dead
So She's fighting the ghost of my brother
In her mind
So She doesn't want to see you because you're just like your brother.
I think so
But How bad he did to her?
I don't know that
Because Momoko never talk about that
You know what,Asako?
Whenever I see you, we always talk about Momoko
I'm glad because you think of my sister very much
But we should talk about us at least
That's true.  It must be fun
What's wrong?
I'm ok
Let's go back
I'm back
Welcome back
It's cold
It's warm today
I feel a chill
Good evening
Welcome
Oh that's for our dad
Just a passing fancy
I will stop when I feel tiered
I will have nothing to do if you work like that
It is ok if you play with Natsuji
Natsuji-san will go back to Kyoto for job interview
I see
Asako, Did you show her the item my brother made?
Oh.. That is in my father's room
What is that? Natsuji
That is the only thing left of my brother
Natsuji  brought this the other day
Oh..
What's wrong with it?
It arrived from his war zone
Why you have brought this!
I have brought this to ask you what this bowl
Do you know it,Sister?
Please tell me what is this
My...
That bowl is in the shape of my breasts.
Where was it?
He had it in the war
That's not true
He died with it in his arms
No....You are lying
He died with it in his arms on his chest
I don't know what happened between you and he
But He loved you!
This is the evidence
I don't believe it
Sister!
Do you know how he felt to look at that?
You never know about it!
But Momoko-san
Don't defend your brother when you don't know anything about him
You go home!
I can't be calm if you are here Because I feel like Keita is here
There is a phone call for you,Momoko
I see
I will go home
Hello?
Ah..Miya-Chan
Why you don't want to see me?
I feel lonely
That's not good
No, I can't
Where is Natsuji?
He has left
Why did you bring that?
Because you loved Keita
I didn't love him
I hated him!
I know that's not true.
You said something you didn't mean
I know how you feel
You loved him so you let him to mold your breasts
It was probably just happening
Oh my god..you say that...
You don't feel sorry for the person who was dead,Sister?
I thought you and Keita has been loved each other
But you say like that..
I hate you!
Asako got serious fever.
She's lying in the kitchen
Oh Doctor, How is her?
Oh don't worry
Thank you very much
Take care
Thanks for taking care of her
I have brought this drawing
Thanks
Dad,When will that tea house in Kyoto be build?
It will take time more
I wish I could go to Kyoto too
I want to see my sister
You can see her soon
I haven't seen her after you have grown
That's bad
I give up to see her
A rainbow in the spring
Dad...Why My sister does not understand how Keita was thinking..
She does not understand men feeling, not only Keita...
Time will solve everything
You don't have to think about it.
You should get better your health, OK?
Then, I will go home
Thank you for coming to see me
Oh You have come here
How is Asako?
She will be fine.
I will go back to my office
How are you?
I'm good
Good
I feel at ease
Didn't you inform Natsuji in Kyoto that you were hospitalized?
No..I have not...
You want to see him, don't you?
He is busy with job hunting
You are very thoughtful
OH that drawing is Mirei no haru
Yes, our father has brought this
I have a lot of feelings about this painting
Really?
When my father returned from abroad with this,
I was taken into your home.
Oh really
When did you know our mother is different?
It was when I was 7 years old
You started crying when I told you about it
I felt very sad
I remember it clearly
Then you have started to care me very well
I understood how you feel
I sweared I won't betray you in my mind
But I couldn't
I'll apologize to you when I'm dead and in my bones
Oh Sister...
Forget about this talking
You know what,Asako?
Shall I continue with what I was saying the other day?
Ah! About your health?
Yes
Actually...
It looks like pouring rain tonight
Really?
Sister! Sister!
Sister.. I have come here
Come in
Oh cold! cold..
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
You mean say good bye?
I see
OK then let's do it
Please be good man, and go for it
This is my farewell word
But.. I don't want to leave you
Sister!
Miya-Chan!
I will die with you
What the hell you do,Miya-Chan!
Stop it
Miya-Chan.. Miya-Chan's
Your baby is in my body
I'm having your baby
You are kidding
What is baby?
I'm still baby
You are already mature
Sister..It's joking,right?
It's not joking
He is not my baby!
You are probably right.
He is not your baby
My baby
No!
You are lair!
I won't be cheated
Oh shit!
I'm already back home
Momoko...
I need to talk with you tonight
Go to my room and wait for me
Welcome back home
Lock up the house and get some rest
Thank you!
I see
Keita and You did such a thing
Thanks for telling me ,anyway
But Momoko..
I think he said that because he wanted to let you free
What do you mean?
He was going to die soon
He said bad on purpose, then He wanted you to stop loving him
Because he didn't want you to be sad
He did it because he loved you so much
This is what I think
You're not qualified to decide
Why you say that?
If you loved my mother...
She didn't committed suicide
Momoko!
Oh!
I hear you are hospitalized
Who told you?
Momoko
She said to me to see you in this hospital
Oh..My sister is in Kyoto?
Yes, she visited us last night
Oh.. since pouring rain day, she disappeared..
My father worried about her
I made a phone call from Kyoto as soon as she visited us
Your father will be in Kyoto soon
She goes to Kyoto.. After all she can't forget about your brother
I think so
I showed her the bowl,I felt she still love him.
There was a big trouble after she disappeared
What was it?
Well.. Do you remember the little boy called Takemiya?
Yes
He committed suicide in Hakone after he left my sister
Oh really...
I feel sorry for my sister... There are many problem
Oh?
What's wrong?
I was looking for you
I shouldn't have come here?
I was writing testamentary letter if I commit suicide
You are distressed
At that night, You got angry and left.
I'm distressed too
Takemiya committed suicide
Eh?
He loved you?
No..
Because I'm having his baby..
Hum?
Dad...
My mother wasn't a woman?
What the hell you say?
Dad.. I...
While thinking of Keita
I slept with him to be his woman
About Miya-Chan, same things
I sew your Kimono dress
I cooked Miso soup for you
But the Kimono dress looks ugly
Miso soup I cooked taste bad
I...
Your mother was not good at them
She gave up on herself and killed herself
In doing so, She thought it would free me
But Momoko...
Affection requires a deep love for each other
Your mother didn't understand me
About Keita
You should think of his pure mind deeply
This is the only way how to save you from your suffering
Stop talking!
You never know what is real love
Please leave me alone
I see
There is no words to say
I don't think I ask you to forgive me
I will go home without meeting Wakako and her mother
But can you see Keita's dad again?
Momoko
I want to read the letter what you write on the train
Awwww
Awwwww
I talked with your father all over the night
Anyway take your seat
I probably will remind you
I'm crazy about my kids
I want to feel same with Mr.Mizuhara about Keita
In a short... It was bad that Keita was dead
People says when you die, all is forgiven
Momoko
Let's make the dead person pay for their sins
Your mother too
I don't know why she commuted suicide
Momoko
If I forgive those who died,and I'm going to hell.
What do you think about this?
People who live must forgive people who was dead
You're going to have a baby so
You know about I am having baby
Mr. Mizuhara told me about it just before he left
Momoko
It might be good if you think the child you will have is your truly love
I know this is selfish of me, but...
May I consider your child as my grandchild?
Aww..Aww..
I'm sorry for being selfish
Not at all
By the way How do you think about your father?
Well...This is my own imaginaion
Your father is in memory of your mother
You have your own mother
Wakako has her own mother
That is typically men's selfish
Yes you probably right
But this happens often in the world
There is no way to help your father...
You are too young to feel what I talk
I'm sorry that you blame your father for this
Recently ,Everyday I...
I feel the joy of being alive today
To live
you can get over your pain and sorrow
I think this is the joy of life
What do you think?
Wakako and her mother are the people who lives too
It seems your father is very tired
You blame your father too much
You think so?
How about this?
Let's make the dead bad
Then We can feel the joy of life
You and your coming baby
Please live your  life as who you are
OK?
I can refuse it if you don't like to go
But my father has come to see me
Yes An errand boy brought you this ticket.
Then I'm going
Are you going?
Yes
He will be sure to pick you up at Tokyo station
I'm sad to say good bye this baby
She has just come to our house
Hello?
Oh you... from your sister
Hmm..Hmmm...The room is available
Hmm..Hmmm...That's just fine
Wakako prepares to go to Tokyo.
Please come home early
Hmm..Hmmm...That's right
I'm going to Tokyo
Tokyo Tokyo Tokyo Tokyo Tokyo
Are you Wakako from Kyoto?
Yes
I'm here to pick you up for Mr.Mizuhara
Please get in the car
Thank you
Please come this way
When you see this painting " Haru no niji",Happiness will come to you
I see
Wanna smoke?
I don't smoke
Oh You don't
Hmm..You've come
She'll be out of the hospital in a few days
That's good to hear
I'm glad to hear that
Oh Hello
Do you drink,Natsuji?
I can't drink
Come in
Wakako
Yes
Thank you for the ticket
A ticket?
Yes train ticket
But I've been brought here.
I don't know what should I do...
Who gave her the ticket?
I sent
You sent?
Yes
Welcome, Wakako
But It is not the first time to see me
Yes
Why did you run away from me when we were on stage dancing?
I didn't run away. I was just surprised
Why?
And...I didn't want to feel ostracized
I'm crossing the world
I knew I wouldn't be relying on my sisters in Tokyo.
And at that time. you looks very scary
Me?
Please don't get upset
I won't
I'm glad to hear that
But I could see you again
I will count on you if I have a hard time in the future.
Dad.. It is good to see her,isn't it?
Oh I will introduce you.
She is your sister,Asako
The other day, Mr. Otani came to visit me with a baby in his arms
Oh really? Mr.Otani came
He is Natsuji,Aoki
He will be Asako's husband
Haha, you are kidding
It's good, you think so,Natsuji?
Yes, That's good.
Very nice to meet you
Very nice to meet you too
Dad, Please shake hands with her
You've grown up
Momoko
Dad...
Who do you think of?
My mother?
Right?
Dad...
I'm going to have a baby
My mother and Asako's mother also said same things like I said
At the time You didn't say anything too?
No... I said both of them like "you can have a baby.."
I see
Then you don't have to worry about me
Dead people are cold
Everyone who is alive is warm,
You think so,Dad?
Momoko
I want to shake hands with you again
Really? Whenever we see " Haru no niji ( A rainbow in the spring)",
We will be happy?
Yes, I've heard that
I've been lucky from the start
Ah, rainbow...
What?
Where is the rainbow,sister?
I don't see
It was not rainbow
I'm sorry.. I had a feeling that there is a rainbow
That was well said
Sorry for my imagination,Asa-Chan
My sister is good at kidding