Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
The Gorgeous Geisha / Nikutai no Seiso (1964)
Yeah,It's nice wind.
It's too late now,
You're terrible.
I didn't want to be your wife.
When I want to break up, I will break up
You're too cold.
so when the money runs out, then you leave me?
It could be.
Our relationship is tied to money.
It's hard for me to break up with you
I will rebuild my business. I am a well-known face in the brokers.
so I'm sure I'll make it. Please
Let's continue our relationship.
I have to go.
Thank you very much.
Is that a farewell greeting?
You took a lot of money from me.
Don't say that.
I'm offering my precious body to you
Wait.
What the hell?
Get your hands off of me!
It's funny.
Good evening.
Welcome.
Good evening,sis.
Yamashita is upset again.
Oh Yamashita...
Did you meet a good man?
No way.
My face is telling that.
Oh my god.
It's written on your face in big letters.
It's written like Yamashita.
Oh, I really appreciate it
I don't wanna bother you.
Sorry for making you wait.
but it's fine. I only waited an hour.
More importantly, I brought the promised thing
Did you really bring it?
I promised you, didn't I?
I'm not the kind of guy who would lie
Take it.
Thanks.
I'm so sorry
I was surprised yesterday,
You shouldn't have called the store.
I wanted to see you in sudden.
I am Yamashita, a promotion officer who has
worked diligently for 20 years
If anyone finds out about this, my credibility will be ruined.
Which is more important, me or SOKUSHINGAN?
Either way, both are important
I know it's no good, but just tell me straight out
You're annoying.
I guess you know how I feel.
So, you chose me?
Let me tell you straight away
You're so cute.
Harue?
What is she doing?
Can you call her again?
Tell her to come here soon.
No.
Kimicho?
I got a call from your home.
I get it.
Sis?
It's Taeko.
Our mom said you have to come back right away.
What's wrong?
Watanabe-san?
Is he there again?
I told you not to pay him any attention,
Don't complain to me.
Come back quickly.
I'm going.
Which room?
It's Suzumoto
Well, Please stop by Fukujiro for a bit and tell
my sister to come home early.
OK.
I'm going.
Fukuya, you haven't eaten yet?
I'll have it later.
So, if you're not feeling well, you can take a rest
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm off now.
Please polish Watanabe-san's shoes.
I know it's not a good idea to ask you, but I have nowhere to go
I see. I will do my best
Please rest assured
If you could say that to me, it would be a great help
Please.
Don't do stupid things.
I'll try to get back to you within 3,4 days
Thank you for your kind words
I was going to ask Kimicho.
but I'll come back again
Well then.
please say hello to Goikkyo.
I guess you refused.
Did you go home?
He wanted to meet you.
Why didn't you come?
When I look at that person's face, I feel sick to my stomach
Is he asking for money again?
How did you reply?
Did you pretend to be good?
He relies on me.
I can't be cold to him.
It's not cold.
We cannot provide 2 million yen.
It's something you can understand if you think about it
His company will go bankrupt and employees will run away with the money
He's really miserable.
If he's having financial difficulties
He is going to jail
I wish He'd go to prison.
He's drunk and eaten here
He defaulted on his debts,
and now he wants to lend us 2 million yen?
What's the hell he's doing?
You're true but please think about it.
What about you and Hideyoshi? Aren't you half-brothers?
I am the child of his mistress.
that's enough now.
You shut up
When Watanabe died,
we cut all ties
They cut ties with us.
The Watanabe family is a complete stranger now.
But...
so he's an annoying person
Ours doesn't have that kind of money.
If we mortgage this house we can borrow money
Don't say stupid things
If this house is gone,
where will we sleep?
Are the three of them going to be homeless?
Mom.
Something has happened.
Fukuya...
What?
She collapsed, vomiting blood.
so please go quickly
She was just taken to the hospital
Only bad things happen.
Sis.
What's wrong?
Today I'm going to talk about marriage
It's fine.
Go ahead.
Please go soon
I'm going by bike today.
Good morning. Good morning
Is she Taeko of Shizunoya?
She's grown well.
She works for the city's tourism association
It's such a waste,
Why you don't work as Geisha?
that's true.
Good morning
I was late.
It's ok.
Good morning. Good morning
I'm going.
I'm going to ask you to do this
Hello?
May I come in?
Yes.
It's me. What are you going to do?
I'll show my mom this.
I talked to my mom last night.
She said ok.
Really?I will talk today too.
I'll make a great wife.
Turn on the lights.
Tae.
You can't do this here.
Landlady?
Oh I see.
The doctors said to stay at my home.
I see.
Take good care of you.
Thank you.
Get well soon,Fukuya-san
Welcome back.
Have you made her bed?
Yes.
What a bad luck.
I'll give you a hand
What are you talking about? You're a sick person
Now, you need to get changed quickly and go to bed quietly
The doctor at the hospital told you
Rest is the best thing you can do. You have to stay still
Mom, I'm sorry.
but this is what happened anyway
You don't have to say anything.
I'm sorry.
Mom?
Come here.
Fukuya....
Did you mortgage this house?
Why did you do that without telling me?
If I told you, you wouldn't forgive me
What kind of person is you?
Everyone around here is laughing at us.
For you, helping others is giving back, right?
But our lives must come first.
How would you prepare the 2 million yen?
Someone buy this house for us
What if I could just borrow from that person?
Where in the world do idiots like that live these days?
They'd be kicked us out before we could even borrow from them
I want to repay.
I'm going to work again soon
I can work as Geisha again.
What are you talking about?
You're too old for Geisha.
Maybe you can just work as housekeeper.
But Hideo-san was shedding tears
He will never forget our kindness,
He pushed his hands together
Stop saying it.
Fukuya seems to be in a bad state, so I wonder how she will be until summer
Bloodline is nothing to be scared of these days
That's not the case
She has severe tuberculosis.
Because she doesn't have enough enthusiasm,she got disease.
She can hear.
You don't have to shout out loud.
We have a sick person and debts.
Do whatever you want.
Let's go.
See you.
See you later.
Welcome back.
Where's Mom?
She's here.
I see.
Oh, Isehama has come here.
That story has a reputation.
We mortgaged this house and paid for it.
He did something reckless.
That's good story.
He's a fall guy.
That's enough.
Thanks.
Apparently Shizunoya and you are a childhood friend
You've been sisters since the time of Maiko.
Well, that's how we are.
Good night.
Okiku has always loved to do stupid things
She's a nice girl who can have a decent husband.
She was even loyal to the Watanabe
She's happy to mortgage the house.
It's amazing, but not everyone can do it
I'll try it if it comes down to it.
You are really excited
I buy a horse, ok?
Don't say stupid things
Mom, the young master...
He has gone home?
He seems to be on a different business.
What's wrong?
Well.
What do you want?
So Okiku of the Shizunoya and watanabe got fight.
For Dead OKIKU's husband?
Well, in the end, Okiku did win.
So Chiyo was broken heart.
I didn't know.
but humans don't know what happiness is
Well, Chiyo was dumped and picked up
by the Kono clan of the Minyuto Party,
and he paid for here.
The Kono was dead, right?
Of course. so I am boss now.
Are you saying you're going to marry with Taeko of Shizunoya?
We've promised for a year now.
You can't.
Please break her up.
But.
She's a daughter of tea houses
Even if you say that, our family is same, isn't it?
Even among tea houses, the status is different
So, mom, is it really not okay?
Absolutely not
But we have been in contact with the Shizunoya up until now.
It's just a superficial obligation
No matter how many times you say this,
You have to flatly refuse
If it's too big for you,
I will refuse.
Ko-chan.
Good evening
Welcome
It's me.
It's been a while.
Ochiyo.
Thank you for coming. Please feel free to come in.
Thanks. just a little bit.
Please come in.
Thanks.
It's been a while.
Same here.
so please don't worry about it. I'll leaving soon.
You don't have to say that,
just take your time
You are always the same.
You're not getting any older
You think so?
You are always the same too.
Mom.
Welcome.
Good evening.
She's grown well.
Yes she is.
You should drink this.
it's turtle blood.
I heard it's good for chest problems.
Thank you very much.
And I thought you'd get bored so I bought some for you even though it's out of season
I'm here to talk about Taeko-san
Thank you very much
I was hoping to visit you once
but I didn't know anything about it
I was shocked when I heard from Koji today
I see. Koji-san came to see her later that month
I wanted to decline their marriage.
Koji works for a tourism company as a hobby,
but he will have to take over the family business someday
I think a bride needs to come from a decent family
You mean Taeko is too bad?
I don't want you to misunderstand that
I don't mean she's bad
A tea house in Gion,Kikutei that is somewhat well known
We have prestige.
Please tell Taeko about it
From now on, please keep him as a friend.
Mom, you've been made fun of so much, you can't say anything?
Stay away
I don't know how great you are
We are same human being.
How great does that thing make?
Anyway, if it's just a tea shop.
It's just water business.
Is there something special about you guys?
You have become a fine speaker.
I'll remember that.
Please remember that.
We are same.
I've heard rumors about you, but you're brilliant.
I hear you do a bullish business.
Are you dealing a Sokushingan watchman?
Well, you know very much.
I'm a physical type, so if he's a good man,
I'll make a move on you as many times as I can
Please stop it.
Forgive me....
Well, I flatly refused about Taeko
Stop talking and get out.
Thank you.
Ochiyo.
Mom, hurry up and pour salt.
Are you drunk?
I hate this world
I'm leaving the house
so you should leave too
Let's do that
It's not that easy
If we work together, it will work out
I'm not as free here as you are
I am an adopted child.
I understand your pain, but if things continue like this, what will happen to us?
Tae...
Tae..., don't leave me
You too.
We can't do this.
Get your hands off of me.
Let me go.
Tae-chan. It's okay. Please forgive me.
Will you marry me?
Marry me
Marry me, promise me
Say it, say it.
Why don't say it?
You won't give me any promises?
You are coward.
Can't you do something about it?
If I get 2 million, that's a lot of money
Well, I have some ideas too.
Good evening.
I guess if I spend about 200,000 yen,I can probably do something about it.
It's okay now.
Are you angry?
What if I get angry?
Let's go home.
Yes.
I don't want anyone to see.
Good evening.
Oh Kimi.
Dance with me.
I'm not good at dancing.
I might step on your foot
I want you to step on my feet.
I am very honored.
You are good at dancing.
I'm doing my best.
Please hold me tight
Someone gets angry at you?
you're a stupid person
I'm lonely.
Is there anyone nice?
It hurts.
I'm sorry
Where is she gone?
Welcome.
Good evening
Oh Kimi.
Are you busy?
I'm doing okay.
New food orders have been placed.
I get it.
Hey, mom, good evening.
What are you up to?
What happened? Please come and see me sometimes
So, are you alone today?
Yes, I came to invite  Isehama-san.
Thank you very much.
please enjoy the big party
After all, He loves dancing very much.
so she's a good mother
Among here, no one cares about me.
I can't believe it, let's go dancing.
Oh, wait a minute, our cook is coming back now
What do you want to eat?
Thank you very much.
What do you like?
I'll have a beer.
Bring beer.
Who is that?
No, it's nothing.
Please.
Tae came to dance.
You should be a little wary of her.
She is very well known.
Most men like her.
Ah, it feels so good.
I feel hot.
Sorry.
Don't sleep, you'll catch a cold.
I like you Isehama.
maybe I'll fall in love with you,
Let's have fun.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Okiku! Thank you for coming
It's a great restaurant.
You seem like a real businessman.
I'm still an apprentice, but I'm trying my best
Thanks to you.
Please don't say such flattery.
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
Okiku is here, come on.
Welcome.
You look good.
It's been ages.
Your child has grown so much
Thanks to you,
Here's sloppy place, but please come in.
Thanks.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Okiku is here
It's been a while
Thank you for coming
Thanks.
You saved our family.
I can't do anything about it,
I apologize for treating you like a mistress.
Forgive me....
Please don't say anything anymore.
It's raining again
Yes.
It's time for dinner.
Thanks.
It's your favorite dish.
Eat your favorite miso stew
Thanks.
You need to eat properly.
Will I get better?
You will get better
Don't worry.
What if I won't get better?
That's not good
It's no good if it's too squishy
If I die,
I don't know what to do about the damage to my house
What are you talking about?
You don't need to worry about that
I've caused a lot of trouble to the hospital and the medicine bills
You've lived here since you were 13.
We are just like brothers
Nobody thinks it's a bother
Thanks.
Hello,this is Shizunoya.
Is your sister there?
I'm Yamashita.
Please call her.
Someone called you.
Sister.
Yamashita-san is calling you.
Say I'm not here.
I got two call from him today.
Hello?
She's not here now.
Welcome.
Good evening,
I wanna see Fukuya.
Please,thanks always.
Good evening.
Tae?what happened with Koji-san?
Did you talk to him about anything?
Who cares about his mother?
If you both love each other, why don't you just get married?
Koji
He hasn’t come to the city hall lately.
Why?
Is Isehama there?
I'm Kimi.
We're closed today.
He hasn't been here since this morning.
I know that you and Kimi are dating.
Don't say that, you are not even old enough to be jealous.
Don't be stupid, I'm not a bit of a fool.
I'm still a woman,.
where are you going, ko-chan?
Don't meet Taeko.
She's such a playgirl.
Oh yeah,There's a tax meeting
Why are you so nervous?
You're going to dance with Kimi, right?
Hey,I get angry.
I'm just an old lady,
Hurry up and get going.
What are you doing?
Massage here.
Yes, yes.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
What were you doing?
I’m sorry.
Were you at Kiku-tei?
Don't get angry.
Look at me! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
What's the hell?
If I pinch you once more ,I will forgive you.
That's stupid, that's outrageous!
I won't play around with you! What a nasty accusation!
You are mean.
What's the hell?
I wonder if I pinch you
I wanna pinch you.
It hurts, it hurts.
Thank you very much.
I'll cure you.
How is it? Is it still pain?
It works a lot.
That's right
Hello, I'm going to have to hurry up today
Why not?
I have to run around worrying about money.
My house is being foreclosed
What's wrong?
Well, My mother did something stupid.
Is this enough?
I might have to say goodbye to this house
Isn't that okay?
They can't wait.
There's only one week left.
Let's take this opportunity to quit this business.
But Fukuya is sleeping like that.
There's a telegram.
Thank you very much.
Yukiko will arrive tomorrow at noon.
Please come down to white line.
Kyoto.
Transfer to Kyoto Honin Line.
If you are getting off, please be careful not to leave anything behind.
Welcome.
It's been a while, how are you?
We came to Kyoto for the first time in five years.
I'm Daddy's Friend
Tomorrow I'll be at a university here and I'll be heading to Hiroshima again soon.
so I'll be able to hang out tomorrow with you.
I'm like a guide for her.
I'll bring it.
Thank you. Well then.
What's wrong? Did you have a broken heart?
The other party's mother was against it, so it's no good.
They say it's because the status is different
That's quite feudal
Destroy that with your own hands
It's not that easy
That's why I hate Kyoto
Even a woman like you will become old
Well, that's terrible
Please come to Tokyo with him.
I will introduce you to my work.
But.
You have to be brave, you have to create your own happiness.
Look.
Fortunately, Kyoto was not burned down during the war.
but I don't know if that was a good thing for the city.
The traces of the ancient history may have been preserved,
but in exchange, It's very feudal here.
Under those beautiful roof tiles, They remain there.
I'm sorry it's been so long.
What are you talking about?
I haven't done anything to you.
Forgive me....
I can't even repay you
Fukuya, please don't die.
Mom, there are 20,000 yen here.
Please use them for something.
Fukuya, you are...
I'll send this money to your house
Daughter.
Thank you for always being so kind to me,
Even if I die now I will never forget.
Fukuya.
Get your act together.
Thanks.
Forgive me....
Fukuya.
At least you'll get to go to a good place in heaven.
Ah... Fukuyama...
Hello, this is Shizunoya.
It's Kimi.
Yes, I understand
I'll be there right away.
Why don't you take a rest tonight, sister?
Do geisha have Sundays and holidays?
It is the duty of a geisha
Please stay by Fukuya's side tonight.
Mom, do you know when the 2 million yen deadline expires?
It's tomorrow.
It can't be helped.
It'll work out somehow
That's right, it'll work out somehow
We will be kicked out of this house
You are fine with it but I can't accept it.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
What's wrong?
I've run so far.
Please drink.
Oh yeah.
This is the 2 million yen we promised.
Thank you very much.
I won't have to be homeless.
Please cut ties with Sokushingan.
Please cut ties with Kikutei too.
I've already cut ties with them.
Let's do dancing.
Oh yeah.
It hurts me.
I’m sorry.
Please treat me nice forever.
Let's be friends forever.
Support our next event.
I'll be with you.
Don't worry.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Why did you do this?
I heard that Kikutei is very prestigious.
But you came into the other room without permission.
What?
You are vulgar inclination geisha.
You lost your man to a woman like that.
Please show me your stupid face.
You said it.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Let's go home.
Isehama-san, Are you off to home?
Yes.
And what are you going to do now?
I got call for Kimi.
We are in the business of fighting for men.
I'm frustrated
what happened?
Nothing.
It's me.
Please make arrangements somehow
Yamashita-san says he wants to meet you.
I'll be waiting for you at Umenoya.
Please wait for me.
I'll just come over for a bit
It's just a little.
Kimi.
Me?
I'm Kasama.
I was wondering who it was,
I'm doing this.
When did it start?
Today is the opening day of the store.
so I'll be able to get a drink.
Please feel free to come.
I am honored to have you celebrate with me on my opening day.
Here it is.
I will come again.
I see
Take it.
I'll serve you today
What are you talking about?
You have to take it.
Keep working.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since we last met, isn't it?
What have you been doing?
You never met me
I was very busy practicing for the event.
You seem to be in a very passionate relationship with Isehama
Please stop saying stupid things
I hate guys these days.
That's enough.
Actually, I came here today to ask you a favor.
Would you mind listening to me?
I don't know what kind of good things it is,
but please tell me.
Please lend me 50,000 yen.
I can't.
I don't have that kind of money.
I beg you.
I'm going to quit my job and go independent.
Can you go independent for just 50,000 yen?
Actually, I got fired from Sokushingan.
The money I spent was discovered
What a fool you did. Did you buy a horse or something?
The money I spent is to see you.
Is it my responsibility?
No but...
but I completely ruined the store where I worked for 20 years because of you
Please don't make such baseless accusations
It sounds like I am bad.
I know about it.
Kimi.
I'd like you to help me out, so could you please give me 50,000 yen?
Starting tomorrow, my wife and children will be in trouble
I need your help.
I turn down.
Please don't bully me too much.
I am such a weak woman.
I beg you.
My last hope is in you, please help me
You are man.
Please don't do anything embarrassing like that
Please.
Kimi.
I can't.
You're too cold.
that's a man's one-liner.
You bought a woman's body with money
and now, please help me?
Where is the selfishness in that?
The money I spent on you was 500,000 to 1 million
yen
I was offering my precious body
Even though you have a wife and children,
you still go to geisha parties
Learn your lesson and take time to reflect on your actions
Wait.
What?
You'll hit me?
You'll kill me?
If you had the courage, do it.
you would have gone to prison.
Thanks for coming.
Sorry for making you wait.
Kimi is now really dating with Isehama.
She had a fight with KikuTei's lady.
I can't believe Kiku Tei's lady backed out.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Your mom is calling you.
I'm sorry.
What?
Can you just go home?
It's almost my turn,
but Koji from Kikutei is there.
I'm sorry, I broke our promise.
You don't need to say that anymore
Please understand
In my position, I can't go against my mother's words
He came to say goodbye to Taeko
That's right, sister, we've come to an agreement.
Don't worry.
I have something to say about this.
You really love Taeko
It's all up to you.
You're free to do whatever you want, just take her somewhere and run away
Can't you do that?
Or maybe you never truly fell in love with Taeko from the first.
I love her.
Then you should protect her.
If you have any concerns about your life, I am here to support you.
I'll take care of her for the rest of your life.
Kimi, I'm an adopted child
We are doing this kind of business.
I want Taeko to find a proper happiness
Please marry her.
Please.
Please forgive me.
I'm no good
It is your turn.
Please hurry up and get ready
Sorry,Tae.
Mommy, don't worry.
Now I can give up.
Please give up.
Please.
Please hurry up and take care of me.
I get it.
It's almost your turn.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
Is it okay to be awake?
Today I was allowed.
She's made up her mind.
Are you going?
I don't know what kind of life awaits me in Tokyo,
but I'll go.
Do what you want.
You're not like us. You don't belong here.
You can leave.
You'll have to try everything to find out.
You know what?
What?
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
Please in.
I will go with him.
I'm sorry the other day,Kimi.
I'm sorry too.
Forgive me.
Big sis, we don't have much time left.
Take care and do your best.
Please take care of her.
Big sis, you should go and see Yamashita-san once
He's in Yamashina Prison.
I don't want to meet such a stupid guy.
I want to start a new life now
What are you going to do now?
Well....I'll think about it carefully
You too, do your best.
Take care and do your best.
Well then we are off.
See you.
THE END