Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
No!!!!
Please forgive me.
Nora Inu / Stray Dog (1966)
(Inu/Dog Series #7)
Hurry up
Please forgive me.
I really don't know anything!
What are you going to do with me?
Where are you taking me?
Please forgive me, help me
Come
please stop
No...
Don't do this
Let's go, okay,
Let's start with temperatures around -3 degrees Celsius.
It's cold, cold, cold
Isn't this a good spot?
Hey! Brother!
It's Tokyo!
We made it to Tokyo!
Really?
Thank you very much.
Alright, let's go to Tokyo!
Hello?
I want to meet Inspector Sasaki.
Oh
When did you come back to Tokyo?
Just now
How's about police in Osaka, idiot, Junta Kimura?
He's really fired up in the 4th Investigation Division,
That's good
What can I do for you?
Do you think I could get a job at the Metropolitan Police Department?
What?
Just once, I want to wear that police uniform
and proudly carry my gun at my waist!
Is it okay to ask?
Don't you have a gun right now?
No.
Are you sure?
Do you want to check?
He is Daisuke Kamoi
What?
Don't say it like a product,kid
Call me by a more polite name.
Come on
Can I become a police officer?
Don't say such foolish things
If you keep this up, you'll get pulled back into something boring
You think so?
Yeah.
I'm asking you because I want to work diligently.
Such coincidences can happen.
I see, the skills are good,
but it seems you're not quite suited for being a police officer
You have a criminal record.
Wow, You have no heart or blood
Kamoi!
Ahaha, I apologize, you actually do have heart or blood, don't you?
Well then,
Hey!
3,500
2,000,
Come on.
I'll definitely do it!
Down
Straight
Hold on.
Flash.
I lost again. Today is not my day.
Kamoi is losing badly.
How much is it?
35,000 yen
Call!
Call
Let's combine
2,000
Call
Down
I quit
Call
Are you heading home?
Yes.
it seems that Western Hanafuda really suits me
Can I somehow play that Japanese Hanafuda?
Even if you don't do that, you don't have any money anymore.
Yes,you are right.
I have no more money.
Are you heading home?
You're worried about the money I borrowed, aren't you?
You have very good intuition.
I'm smart
I'm different from the other customers.
That table, please take it quickly!
President,
but I don't want to touch this anymore
I'll return it
It's the gun you were fond of
Did you change your mind while you were in prison?
My mother back home is sick and wants to see me
Once I received the letter, I suddenly felt homesick
I can't help but be laughed at for being weak
Please.
The president is trying to celebrate your release from prison and promote you.
You should listen to what he has to say.
Please.
President
That's interesting, bring him here.
You went to prison in my place. It couldn't be helped.
Now it's your turn to listen to my side
So, will you listen to me?
Thank you
It's okay
Well, more importantly, could you show me your playing skills?
I want to use it as a conversation starter
I've brought him.
I believe your name is Mr. Kamoi
I am President Fukuoka
What do you want after bringing me here?
I'll pay off my debts with my pistol.
Before that, I would like to see your playing
You also want to see the farewell party for the performance, don't you think?
Mr. Kamoi, could you let this guy participate as well?
Well, president, then.
Your skills are amazing.
You don't need to repay your debts, so you should stay here for a while.
After all, maybe I should stop
It seems uncomfortable here
Well, it's sad, isn't it?
I'll be parting ways with this pistol for a while.
You don't need to push yourself.
It would be rude to just part ways like this
Let's have a farewell party as a second gathering.
Let's step back a bit
I will definitely give this to you.
He is a very valuable man.
President ,We are taking care of Kazama.
Didn't get hurt too much?
Of course, but
why is that?
Nakayama will really bring back the sales machine from Osaka tomorrow
It's true that Nakayama was involved with Satomi
Really?
The one who touched my belongings was.....
I took care of Satomi
Nakayama, it's next.
We'll assume that Kazama killed those two.
Kazama, fearing punishment, will commit suicide.
So that's what it means to betray the president
Oh no
Today is not my day either.
We don't do very well in Tokyo.
Please give me some shochu.
Please give me some oden.
Yes, um, daikon, chikuwa, konnyaku
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
What are you talking about?
It'll work out somehow
But today, I didn't feel particularly anxious
I thought I could get my gun back.
Thank you
Hey
Why are you grinning?
You look disgusting
Tamura Tamako, Peaceful....
What is this? Huh?
You have no place to stay, right?
If that's the case, then...
Go to this apartment
from tonight,
But
Anyway, let's go and see
Don't worry about money
So, am I really going to live in this apartment?
yes yes
It's more comfortable than a dorm,
and there are girls....
Girls?
Hey,are you okay?
Hey!
Wait!
Hold on!
Stop
No.
Hey stop!
I will
You hit and ran
I can't forgive you
No way
It was her fault
What did you say?
Get out from the car.
I'll teach you.
You bastard!
You get it?
I wish I had been in an accident if that's the case,
Brother.
Dr.Matsuda from the 1st Surgery Department,please come to the medical office
Alright, Fumiko-chan, the juice is ready
Hey brother, I'm thirsty too,
You bastard!
No juice for you
How is it?
It tastes good.
Good
Your legs are still painful?
Yeah, my right ankle is ...
But it would be good that it was not serious
Stay down
Help me.
Please stop!
Anyone who is violent in the hospital will be asked to leave
I’m sorry.
She looks nice
What's wrong?
It seems you are pretty cool
Well, at the hospital, we make every effort to save even the most critically ill patients
This is quite humorous, isn't it?
Are you feeling okay, old man?
Hey, don't say that here!
Was it you who caught Tomizawa Saburo?
Yes.
He is a repeat offender who specializes in car theft.
Please investigate Hit-and-run as well
Hey Kamoi, you shouldn't talk so big
If you're getting lectured for a hit-and-run,
that's just unfortunate
You should probably leave the hospital
I heard that a yakuza-looking
guy was causing trouble in the hospital.
Yakuza-looking?
That's sad.
I look like British gentleman
What about the treatment costs for that girl?
And what will happen to her medical fees?
It's difficult to deal with both
medical fees and treatment costs.
Why?
The perpetrator is a criminal, so he should be detained
It's one thing if it's just a hit-and-run offender, but the
fact that he's a habitual car thief is also a problem.
We can't just make the car owner pay for it
Don't say like that.
You should contact your relatives or someone close
What if she has no family?
I have relatives
Is that really true?
My mother is in Morioka,
But she's sick.
but my brother is in Tokyo
I see
He's 10 years older than I
So he's 27?
Whereabouts Tokyo?
Let me see the letter
Here?
I hadn't heard from him for about two years
but I just recently got one
4-10 Harumi-cho, Fuchu City, Tokyo
Even if I ask at the police box, I won't understand it
That's ridiculous.
I can't believe you don't understand
Alright then
I'll go and definitely find it
So just relax and wait a bit,
um,
Hey.
Me?
I have a quick question to ask
Where's 4-10 Harumi-cho, Fuchu City?
4-10?
Yeah, this is it...
Oh
This is a prison
It brings back memories
Wait.
Excuse me, but could you check if Shoichi Kazama is inside?
Prisons are under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Justice,
while the police fall under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Police, so that can't be done
Don't say complicated things;
both the police and prisons are like relatives, right?
It's not just a simple
Don't be so reserved
I'm on patrol,
I have to go
You bastard!
if I had time to patrol around the prison,
Go patrol the town
Hello?
Excuse me.
Good evening.
Welcome.
You're Daisuke Kamoi,right?
Yes I am
I am Tamako Tamamura
You know, I heard from Tsune that you would be coming yesterday
Well, I have been waiting for you
I thought I would come yesterday
but I was a bit busy with some work
I see.
It's a bit cramped here, but please come in
Here?
Um, I'm going to laid a curtain down here
This 3-tatami mat area is mine, and this 2-tatami mat area belongs to you, right?
I sleep here?
Please excuse me for a moment
I have a quick question,
Tsune...
but what is your relationship with Tsune-san?
Was that my ex-husband
ex-husband?
He can't  earn much,
But he always talk big
He’s always into keirin and horse racing
You see, I kicked  him out after
I see.
As he was leaving, I told him to introduce me to a nice guy.
Well then, the one who was laughed at there was you
Please.
Is that so?
But Tsune didn't say anything.
But I suppose he was concerned about it.
Well, I don't know, but...
If you say it in such a formal tone when you do it, I can't settle down, you know.
I'm always like that.
I'll do it straightforwardly
That's better
By the way, what about the room fee and the light bill?
It depends.
Yes
What do you mean by that?
If you live there,
you'll understand
I see.
Do you have any luggage?
My only possession is this body.
Please feel free to use everything.
Really?
You're kind.
Using a frying pan and pot costs 1 yen per use.
Using tap water costs 2 yen per minute, and using electricity costs 3 yen per minute.
You can find more detailed information on that bulletin board.
This room shakes a lot, doesn't it?
It can't be helped.
Is big brother really coming back?
In about 10 days
I heard he's coming back from the construction site on his business trip
Really?
I'm so glad your X-ray results were normal.
When will she  be discharged?
The doctor has told her to be hospitalized for 10 days.
Oh, really?
My discharge and my brother's
return are on the same day
Uh-huh
Well, that's how it is
Mr. Kamoi
You're lying to her, aren't you?
Please tell me the truth.
The address on that letter is a prison.
Mr. Kazama has just been released from prison.
By the way, what crime did Fumiko-chan's brother commit?
they say it was attempted murder
He was released from prison, but it's unclear where he's been.
I feel sorry for her
but in this vast Tokyo, searching for one person isn't easy at all
It's really troubling.
I have a good idea.
maybe we could place a missing person ad in the newspaper
That's good.
How much would that cost?
Well, it probably depends on the size of the ad
I think it might start around 3000 yen
3000 yen, huh?
If you explain the situation, they
should be able to publish it urgently
Thanks to this, I feel energized
By the way, there's something I'd like to ask
Do I look like a role actor?
I'm serious about this
Well then, let me speak frankly
You need to take a bath
and change your clothes
Why?
You must be wonderful, right?
Are you sure?
What's wrong?
An emergency autopsy
Is it a police autopsy
It must be murder?
He's really a good-looking guy, isn't he?
You think so?
You are so cool
Don't be half-asleep.
Now, please hold me tightly
I'll waive today's room fee.
What?
If you hold my hand,
I'll give you a discount of several yen,
and if it's a kiss, then...
I'll give you 50 yen from my side,
just wait a moment
How many times the regular price is this 2-tatami room for one night?
100 yen per day
I really thought the bill would be 3000 yen next time
This area is just the market rate
I can't believe it actually became a mechanism that gradually gets cheaper
Wait a minute,
if you jump in from that side or
if you touch from that side, then...
How much is that?
In that case, I will charge you money.
What?
I didn't even ask for that, did I?
that's because my job is a massage, right?
Even if I just take a little touch,
I will still charge you
Well, I see
What should I do
If you touch me, the room rate will be discounted.
I get it.
She's very articulate.
Good night
By the way, the front room over there is 125 yen for one night in a 3-tatami mat space
What?
Look, I'm holding your hand,
Really?
Please give me a 20 yen discount.
No.
what should we do, all right!
Hey, it's 105 yen, right,
(Mr. Shoichi Kazama, please let us know where you are.)
(Daisuke Kamoi)
Sasaki
Shoichi Kazama is featured in the column about missing people
Kazama Shoichi? Is he
the suspect in last night's Madame murder?
kamoi is looking for Kazama
Why is he looking for Kazama?
Huh? Is it about competing in playing skills?
President, Nakayama's brother has returned from Osaka
Get through him
Well, anyway, it means Kazama can't call that ad
President, I returned
Thank you for your hard work
How was Osaka?
Yes, everything went well
I see, You're a reporter for the Social Daily News that placed this ad, aren't you?
You know I'm a rookie named Takao Kimura
Need to say
What was the purpose of placing the ad?
I was asked by someone
Who?
I can't tell you who.
Shoichi Kazama is being reassigned due to a murder suspicion
Kazama killed someone?
The madam of a bar was found dead along the Tamagawa River.
In the autopsy results of Satomi Kohama's shooting incident,
A modified Ruger.32 caliber bullet
was found
Ruger modified .32 caliber
Kazama
Is Kazama the guy who used to be at Fukuoka Institute of Technology? I've heard he's quite skilled at playing
Yes.
I can't believe he committed murder.
I believe you've met him before.
Where did you meet him?
You fool!
How can I say something like that!
Even if you don't say it, I can figure it out
I have something I need to take care of,
sorry about that
Hey, why do you need that much money?
It's because I can't go anywhere without properly getting ready
Is that a nightclub?
Come on, it's still noon
so please
I will lend you money.
Thank you very much.
But we are not lovers.
I will receive interest from you.
Good morning!
How is her?
She's very good, indeed
I see
She couldn't sleep last night because of the pain in her legs,
so now she's sound asleep
Well...
What's wrong?
Ok.... By the way, you...
The fact that Kazama is a murder suspect....Fumiko-chan knows?
She doesn't know
I see, that's good
So, they're saying it's a suspicion that someone killed Satomi Kohama,who was autopsied yesterday?
Is that lady at the bar madam?
It was a strange autopsy report
What do you mean by a strange autopsy report?
A bullet was extracted from the corpse,
but the amount of blood was surprisingly low
Isn't it because she originally had anemia and had less blood?
No, in short,she was in a state of clinical death when the bullet was shot into her
I saw frostbite on the fingertips of her corpse.
Frostbite in cold places?
Is that chilblains?
Yes.
Well, if that's the case,
it's clear that Kazama didn't kill her, right?
Why is that?
he? Don't you think that's a lie?
I don't really understand it well, though
Anyway, you absolutely must not let this reach Fumiko-chan's ears
Where's my brother?
He'll be back from his business trip soon.
Today, I want to go to the company and hope to return him as soon as possible
I came to ask for a favor
Thank you,
so make sure to rest a little
Today's your outfit is cool.
Really?
That's what you call a cool style
Kamoi.
We often run into each other by chance, don't we?
What do you want at Fukuoka Institute of Technology?
If you wanted an article,
why don't you just hang yourself and turn it into material?
Kazama.
How have you been?
What are you going to do with me?
what should I do?
Well, don't panic. I'll think of a way to use you
It's not that easy to kill you.
Don't say stupid things!
Get me out of here!
Why me?
Shut up.
President,
please listen to what I'm saying!
President
Stay down.
So he said he would be here
He was really persistent
Aren't you making me wait a long time?
Are you not going to serve tea to the customers?
Serve me some tea
Can you not hear me in this shop?
Is your hearing bad?
Can you hear me?
So, is it just your head that's the problem?
You've kept me waiting for a long time.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
What can I do for you?
I want to get back what I have deposited
How much do I owe him?
It's 35,000 yen
It seems like it's still quite short, Kamoi-san
Since it's a special occasion, I can't return it unless you pay the full amount
Alright, with that?
We're not a pawn shop,
Please go home.
then I guess I'll gather the money and bring it over sometime
By the way, I want to ask you a little about Shoichi Kazama
According to Kazama News, it seems like he killed a woman and He is currently a wanted fugitive.
He's such a fool, Kamoi-san
You're also quite the man yourself
You should definitely be careful with women
I think that, despite your kindness
I'm the only one who believes that Shoichi Kazama isn't bad at it
He has excellent pistol skills, but he doesn't use those skills to commit murder.
See you
Hey, wait a minute.
When it comes to women, men tend to lose their minds, so remember that,Kamoi
You should add 'san' to my name; it's rude
You still need to address Kamoi with 'san'
Is it getting serious? Hey!
What's going on? How is everyone still surviving? Come on,
Ready?
Don't catch a cold.
This is a children's toy.
Goodbye
Hey.
Wait.
What has he sniffed out?
He's an interesting guy
I will use him someday
What? someone’s looking for me in the newspaper?
Oh, that guy named Kamoi
Kamoi is looking for me?
Hold me tighter.
I will lend you 20,000 yen.
I've had enough of you
It's not like I'm just asking for 20,000 yen for nothing
Just borrowing it for a little while
I'm just taking out something important to me
Hey, when you say something important, you're talking about a woman, right?
Don't say bullshit.
Hey, you just lent me money for my clothes earlier, didn't you?
If you call it noon, it changes
the mood,
It can't be helped.
This isn't enough, it's only 5,000 yen.
If you keep talking about the price, we won't get anywhere with this mood
Money is more important than mood.
It's very strange to be able to hug with a white coat woman
What did you just say?
Did something happen to the white coat?
Nothing
Hold me tighter.
If I hold you any tighter than this, you will die.
If that's the case,
I will give you all my possessions.
then I'll end up being a murder suspect,
How about that!
That's 20,000 yen!
it's still 18,000 yen!
Just a bit more, 19,000 yen!
How about that!
Stop it
That's 20,000 yen!
It's like...
a balloon filled with air
Don't say such things,
I'm actually complimenting you
really! I'm so happy!
You know what?
If you could seriously think
about marriage, that would be great
I wouldn't mind if you canceled this 20,000 yen debt
Wait a minute, if you get married,
You know, you only live once as a human, right?
So I want to really think about that
Really? If that's the case,
will you think about it seriously?
Got it, got it? Thanks
Hold on.
Write the loan document,
I wonder where the romantic feelings
start and where the goodwill feelings begin
So, the loan document?
the loan document!
Who is it?
Is Kamoi here?
Hi
What's wrong?
we want you to come here as an important witness,
but what kind of witness?
we want to know that you were
in contact with Shoichi Kazama, the 'Madam Killer.'
We have the evidence
What did you say?
What does it mean that I'm in a group with Kazama?
What does this advertisement mean?
Is that really it?
What is the purpose of searching for Kazama?
That's none of your business.
just say the reason that has nothing to do with it
I was just asked
Who?
I can't say who asked me
If you don't say it, I'll arrest you.
This is a matter of humanism,
I can't tell
I see.
But I will tell you one thing.
What?
Kazama was not the one who killed the bar madam.
He is innocent.
Do you have evidence?
The weapon was a modified Luger 32, right?
Yes
That proves he's not the culprit.
That person costs 150,000 yen. He just got out of prison, how can he afford that?
Use your head a little,
this isn't a show, you know?
Please step back so I can enjoy my meal.
What?
You're really smelly,aren't you?
These cost 50 yen each.
Hi.
it's you, Kamoyan!
Oh Tsune.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
What's going on? Huh?
I peeled off the rubber boots from the chicken
That was quite a sudden thing to do, wasn't it?
The chicken legs are short, aren't they?
It's the kind that gets stuck in your shoe, isn't it?
Three have come in
How many pairs of shoes do you have?
No, it's five pairs
Then you've walked 30 steps, right?
Maybe....
I was arrested by the police for theft.
Of course.
What about you?
It's about our family situation,
but I'm in the middle of a meal
so please go ahead
That's a luxurious bento box!
Did the woman give it to you?
Look at this.
It looks really good though
Does this whet your appetite?
Wow, each of these dishes has a price tag, huh?
Yes.
I get it.
These are eggs.
Yeah
This boiled egg doesn't have a price tag.
Her name is Tamako, so she couldn't put a price on the eggs.
Hi.
Sasaki.
Could you bring out the Kamoi?
As long as he answer our questions, we won't let him out
It's about the missing person advertisement, isn't it?
Why is he contacting Kazama?
As long as he doesn't have the answer, we can't release him even if I want to
It's for Kazama's sister
Sister?
No, no, no, please don't ask
where the news came from
Please trust me and Kamoi
Kamoi Daisuke, come out!
Did you call for me? Tsune,
Do you want to eat this?
After eating this,you won't be forced to pay taxes, right?
Don't say like that.
kamoi.
I know
When will you be released?
Soon
The chicken was safe, after all
This is a very minor offense.
I have a request for you.
I'll be waiting at home in Shinjuku, so please
I get it.
Hurry up
I know
I know you're acting all high and mighty, but I can hear you loud and clear
You think Kazama isn't the real culprit?
But why?
You asked Sasaki-san about that reason?
He said it would be difficult to get such a handgun right after getting out of prison.
But isn't that a bit weak?
Kazama is Innocent
why is that?
It's just a hunch on my part.
Hey
Even if you try to get something out of me
it won't work.
That trick is old
Just wait
If you believe in Kazama that much, then please cooperate with me
Cooperate?
Yes.
Actually, I have my reasons,
and I believe in Kazama's innocence too
Really?
Then let's work together to find Kazama
and prove his innocence
This is the cost for that.
Are you trying to use me for your money?
I want to say that a good samurai doesn't eat for money
But I need to pull out something important,
so I'll borrow this.
Refrigerated truck
Chilblains
Go
Please forgive me! Help me!
What's wrong?
Are you worried?
Hurry up
Please! Forgive me....
You stole the president's girlfriend.
You and Satomi tried to transport goods from Yokohama to Kansai.
That is not true.
Shut up.
The president has always been a general who thinks things through
You should know that.
Please forgive me! Help me!
Even if you apologize now, it doesn't really matter
Well then,Say hello to Satomi!
Hey.
You bastard!
Come on!
Nakayama! Show yourself!
Get it together!
Show yourself!
Wait!
Help me!
Damn it!
Hey, get it together!
Where the hell is Kazama?
Don't you know Kazama?
where is Kazama? I avenged you!
Where is Kazama?
Boiler....
Boiler?
What was the cause of death?
It penetrated the left chest   from close range,
but there's no need to get angry, I'm off now
Boiler, right? If you keep saying boiler,
Club boiler, cabaret boiler,
boiler room...
Imprisoning someone in a boiler room is a very old method.
but wait,
He said this before he die, and there's no lie in that
It's definitely the boiler room, huh?
Kazama?
Is Kazama not here?
Who is it?
It's me,Daisuke Kamoi!
Who is it!
Hey
There
What's wrong?
who is that guy outside?
Aren't you going to say?
If you don't want to say it,
then you don't have to
Instead, Your favorite pistol....
Damn it
what?
Did he run away?
I'm sorry
how far do you guys have to mess up?
You all should be careful
You know Kazama's playing skills, right?
So what?
The trick behind Satomi and Nakayama's
disappearance is already figured out by Kazama
That means Kazama will definitely target you next
Does that guy even have the guts for that
President?
That guy from Kamoi wants to see you
The president is busy right now,
wait, wait, go call him, okay?
But president....
well, that's fine
Who is it?
Is Mr.Kamoi here?
He is not here right now.
Who is it?
but I'm just a friend of Mr. Kamoi. Is he not home?
So, there was an advertisement about the whereabouts of Kazama sokichi, right?
Oh, you saw it too?
why do Kamoi-san want to meet Kazama-san?
His sister is in Tokyo.
His sister?
Why are you surprised? She's Kazama's sister, right?
Oh yeah.
Where is his sister?
At the hospital
Hospital?
Because of a traffic accident
She is hospitalized due to a traffic accident?
traffic accident?
Yes.
You must pay before you go.
I will return this to you unconditionally.
huh? Unconditionally?
Kazama's next target is me
Why?
That guy is bloodthirsty.
We've received threatening phone calls multiple times
Is the reason you returned this pistol to me because you want me to be your bodyguard?
That's right. I'll pay you a lot of money.
Unfortunately, I'm not interested in money.
But that's what I want to say.
Alright, let's do it.
Are you sure?
I also want to meet Kazama a little.
It's okay, just step forward with confidence.
It's alright
see, little by little, you'll get used to it
Brother,
it is said that you went to work on the dam construction
Brother
Fumi
I've been waiting for you all this time.
How's mom doing?
She's been getting quite weak.
That's why I came right after your letter arrived
Why didn't you send me a letter for such a long time?
I was worried since I came to Tokyo,
I've been thinking about it
I can be discharged from the hospital in three days.
That's good.
During that time I want to finish up my work too
Can't you go back to my country first?
and then do it?
Once I go back,I want to live in my country forever
I will definitely finish my work within three days.
Please just wait for those three days
Shoichi Kazama is at hospital now
He's talking with his sister in the hospital now,
but huh? speak a little louder?
I'll manage somehow,
But he must have a weapon.
I see, he has no weapon.
Kamoi brother
Brother?
I'm glad you said that
This is for you.
Thank you very much.
I don't usually get thanked for coming to see someone,
but big brother was here
When?
Just little whole ago
Was he ok?
Yes
What did he say?
Um, he said he would come back to the country with me
I see,
but he still have work to do
Work?
He have to finish it within three days
and go home with me
Within three days,  I see
Is it true that Fumiko will be discharged in three days?
Did your brother leave?
He have to work
He said he would definitely come on the day of my discharge
Fumiko-chan ,I will come again,
Sister?
I wonder what's wrong with Kamoi's brother?
He seems to be in a bad mood
Oh, welcome back!
Oh you are here.
As expected,I was released because my offense was minor.
I rushed over right away,
Thank you for your hard work.
How about Tama-chan?
Oh, she is at work
I see
Tsune
I have a favor to ask
What?
I'm not familiar with Tokyo
Right
Well, I want you to look for Kazama
Kazama?
He's wanted by the police, isn't he?
yes
Well, that's impossible,
but I have to search him first before police find him
Please break a leg for me, okay?
I'm counting on you.
This 3000 yen for you.
What's wrong?
It can't be helped
Another 2000yen for you
What do you think?
It can't be helped.
I've realized the meaning of life
It's 5000 yen, so feel it as much as you can
Is the president here?
Kazama?
Come out!
Shoot him
Don't shoot Kazama!
I need to talk with you
Wait
Get after him
Don't let him out of house
Kazama
Leave from here!
Kamoi is their dog?
(Come back,brother)
The Japan Newspaper published a feature article
However, there is still no clear evidence to support this article.
Committing a crime for the sake of one’s younger sister is a compassionate act
Hold on.
It's written by Kibata,I have no idea.
Wanna go to society department?
There are also rumors that he has romantic relationships
You're saying like that
So, shall I provide something new and special
What?
The incident with the gun at the Fukuoka apartment yesterday was also done by Shoichi Kazama
Is that true?
That executive Matsuo also properly acknowledges that
It was done by Shoichi Kazama
You're calling for him to give up his autonomy for his sister
Where's her now?
Come on.
Tell me
I tell you.
She is Currently hospitalized at the hospital
this newspaper article...
Fumiko-chan has not read
I see, I wonder who wrote something like this
Where's Fumiko Kazama's room?
Here!
Who are you?
We are from the first-class newspaper
Get out of the way
What kind of permission do you have?
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
Hey, stop gathering around and making a fuss
Go home, go home, go home
Kamoi.
You've written this
That's right
who gave you permission to write something like this?
Wait
I don't think what I did was wrong
We must not let the damage to the general public
increase any further
I believed that we could restore Kazama's twisted heart
What are you talking about?
This is the position of a newspaper reporter
Hey, stop it!
I get it.
You all have your own positions, methods, and
identifications,
but for me,it's just about protecting Fumiko-chan with my body!
Do you really think that kind of
popularity will work in modern times?
That's right, that's right!
Is it the media that makes sick
people talk and causes trouble for them?
You are not the media! You're just trash!
Get out.
Kamoi-san
! We have the right to write articles!
What? Are you even human?
Do you have any compassion?
Stop it, stop it,
Stop it, stop it!
He's just Yakuza after all.
If you think you can solve everything
with violence, you're making a big mistake.
What's wrong?
A fight?
It's nothing at all
Go over there and take a break,
Bet,bet bet,bet
Here we go.
Come on.
It's cheating
Hey.
What?
Kazama,right?
Don't hide it
I understood after seeing the photo in the newspaper
Don't worry.
I'm a police informant or something
I was asked by someone.
I will deliver you a message
Who?
Kamoi
Kamoi?
Yes
But why?
I don't really know why, though
He wants to meet you before the police catch you
So he told me to catch you, and he would give me 5000yen.
What?
That's our side of the story,
but how about it?
Will you meet him?
Yap.
I'll meet him.
I'm glad.
Are you sure?
Tell him to come out with Fukuoka
Oh really, who is that guy, Fukuoka?
His boss.
I'll help clean up together
He just wants to meet you and talk,
I know.
I won't be fooled
Kamoi is the watchman of Fukuoka.
he turned my sister into a bird to lure me in
It's not true.
but look, these are the marks from being shot by Kamoi
Seriously?
That's why I'm going to settle this
You're in bad mood.
I'm heartbroken.
Come on.
Do you understand?
I understand
I am your lover.
What's wrong?
Did you choke on something?
You're not my lover
I haven't experienced heartbreak with you.
Isn't that wrong?
Of course,
Is there a woman more beautiful than me?
Is that why all women are like this?
Tamako, it's just a phone call
Yes, who?
For Daisuke Kamoi from Tsune-san
From Tsune-yan? Alright!
I found him.
Is that really true? Well, thank you for your hard work
No, no, no, that's not it
Well, I'll talk about the details later,
but that man...
He intend to kill you
What?
He said you're Mr. Fukuoka's pet dog.
You know
He says to clean you up together with Fukuoka
And he also gave me a map of the meeting place
Alright, I got it. Tell me about that
He's not here.
He's not here?
Damn it.
I wonder where he went.
Hello,
From Kazama.
This is Fukuoka
President?
Listen carefully to what I say.
You only have two choices:
either turn yourself in to the police or battle with me
What?
If you say you don't want to,
then I'll report you to the police
What will you do?
Alright, where is that place?
Yeah, I've already informed
Kamoi, so come out together
I'll settle this all at once.
He's such a fool
Tonight at 10 o'clock
come on
Let's hold on tight
See,good job!
You did it! It's all right now!
This is a reward for you, Fumiko-chan, for your hard work
I'll let your brother meet you tonight.
So Looking forward to it!
If you can meet your brother,
everything will be just fine!
Right, Michiko? Huh?
Where did she go?
Oh, me! Tonight,
Kamoi-san seems to meet with kazama
Kazuma, get out
It's me.
Daisuke Kamoi here.
Kazuma
Don't shoot, I've got something to say,
Komori! Come out, dog from Fukuoka!
Don't shoot Kazama! What am I...
Kamoi
Hurry up and shoot Kazama
Stop talking nonsense, I quit your guard man
What?
I am not for you to use.
You are stupid.
You're the one who's being deceived
Shut up.
Don't move
Don't do anything unnecessary to me.
You are stupid.
You must cherish your life.
Don't move from here,
understand?
There are 2 people on the stairs,
3 people on the second floor,
and 1 person behind the luggage, got it
His shots are 5 rounds
It takes 3 seconds to reload
Do it in the meantime
Just two more shots
Now.
Don't move
It's finally the end for you, Kamoi
You got involved in something boring
and now you're going to die
Shoot him.
Just five more people left
Okay.
Here I go
Kamoi-san
Hey, Kazama!
You should understand now, right?
Hey, hurry up
One more shot of your handshake!
You are stupid.
Hold on.
You should change your clothes.
You wear my clothes.
But Kamoi-san
Don't worry.
I have a lot of my clothes at home.
Fumiko
Brother
Have you finished work yet?
I'm done! I can be with Fumiko for as long as I want!
You did it, didn't you?
Yes
Takao-san, what a big scoop!
Takao-san?
It's thanks to you, Michan
I'm so happy, Takao-san
I was completely mistaken.
That's absolutely ridiculous.
Thank you, Kamoi-san.
You guys are so hot, I don't need to wear a jacket.
Damn it.
Kamoi-san
I am very grateful to you.
You don't need to say that.
I'm weak against girls like Fumiko-chan who are so cute.
Did I go too far?
My sister completely believes that I am a decent person
That's good.
I can't think of anything more joyful than this
I'm in trouble
You're right, don't let Fumiko-chan feel sad after burning it too much
Well, if I had such a cute little sister,
my life might have changed, and I can't help but think about that
Do you feel good?
And starting tonight, there's a free big service
That's enough.
Durable and long-lasting – that's me.
There is a problem with your design.
Come on.
Hey, even if it's an electric appliance or anything,
it doesn't matter how good the design is if it doesn't work, right?
That's true.
You don't need to work.
Kamoi
Hug me
I will not charge you for the room.
A man cannot be a woman's kept man.
What did he say?
Well then, see you!
THE END