Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
The view of Mount Fuji is really nice today
Are you from Tokyo, ma'am?
I was born in this area
I used the bath water from this hot spring.
Then you must have gone to Fujimidai Elementary School
Yes.
Are you my classmate?
Well  I was a bit of a junior,
Your teacher was Kubo?
That strong teacher, right?
I wonder if he's doing well?
he actually retired a long time ago.
He hit the principal
I didn't know any of that
It had been quite a while since I come here.
but he was a good teacher
There were rumors going around about the hot spring geisha with him  in this area
So he argued with the principal.
With all that said, it seems that the geisha was actually one of the his former students
Somehow that geisha found a good husband and disappeared from this area,
but I was also a hot spring geisha
Oh you were?
Sorry.
Natsuko Take Off Her Kimono / Obi o toku Natsuko (1965)
Thank you very much.
Welcome back.
Thanks to you,
What do you think this?
It looks like department store wrapping paper.
Your  mouth is a bit harsh
This is the trend of fortune for this year.
there been anything unusual in the world.
What's news?
There was an order for a party.
Hosome-chan, Wakamatsu-chan, and Ai-chan
You?
Me?
Fuku-chan doesn't want to go to that Imo bros party.
What do you mean by saying that?
A man who smells like a potato.
it's a party for the agricultural association
They are our customers.
I can't afford to be picky
This is awesome.
Oh Natsuko's.
Was he here?
As soon as you go out,
She came out of the house right away
She' strange
Where did she go?
She wants to see Mount Fuji.
but that's just how it is
Whenever she says they want to see Mount Fuji, there's always something going on
Speaking of which, she wasn't feeling well,
She's becoming more and more dignified as a lady
That means Natsuko's mother must have been a wonderful geisha too
I guess beautiful mothers are just like that
When Natsuko was four, She died from eating puffer fish
So, did you raise her all this time?
She became a geisha at 16,
but that's not something I'm proud of.
Mom, I've heard that story many times
Natsuko must have been quite popular
Hello,it's Shinkaneya.
Yes, I am.
Well, it's been a while, Kawashima-san
Honestly, let's skip the greetings and get right to it; Natsuko-san is probably on her way there
I see,She's there
Well then, I'll switch to the president
She's out now?
Yeah, actually there are various complicated circumstances
Well, it's not a big deal, I want to talk to her anyway.
Yes, I'll talk
Hello, this is Sakuma.
It's been a while, President
I'm sorry I couldn't go to your wife's funeral.
What's wrong with Natsuko?
She's saying she wants to break up.
5 years with her and she said she wanted to break up
It's completely out of the question
There was a strange rumor
There is a rumor that I am going to remarry.
Remarriage
What are you talking about?
Is it a problem to joke around?
That's why Natsuko lost her cool
and left.
It's because her husband didn't provide enough service
that Natsuko went crazy
Oh, there's no doubt about that
You're not that old yet,
so please get it together
Last month, you received medical compensation at the racetrack, right?
It's not that troublesome?
You don't have to bathe your whole body
It's fine to focus only on the areas
you want to strengthen
Well, well, I appreciate that
and I'll take my time to rely on you regarding for nasuko
Got it, got it, I'll hustle hard from now on
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
She's an old woman who never loses her charm
She must have been quite something in her younger days
I heard that She loved a certain sumo wrestler and even chased after him to the tour location
She used a futon as a Sumo ring
But is she okay?
If you'd like,
I can go over there
and meet with Natsuko directly,
that would be appreciated.
After all, I can't consult about Natsuko
You're the only one here
Thank you very much.
The president and Natsuko's tie
It's me, after all
I didn't expect him to take on Natsuko along with the president's chair
it's only been three months since the former president and Natsuko was together
It's nothing.
It's been five years since then; time flies, doesn't it?
Absolutely
Thanks to the president, Natsuko has completely nicer
it's hard to let go of her.
She is very affectionate
I think there's a difference between amateurs and professionals
You should make new rules
Don't say bullshit.
Seriously
You think so?
I'm kinda....
What's the rule?
that's what that law is
The law is becoming an issue in this session of the Diet
This is the law of the financial industry.
and as the financial situation evolves into this kind of world, various laws will emerge
You came late.
Was there an accident or something?
No,There was plenty of time before the plane arrived.
it's been a while
it's been a while too.
It seems my brother has been taken care of
in various ways,
Not at all.
President, I need to go.
I would like you to take it easy for a while,
but I also have to go out soon
President
Well...
You need a gift,
I had you pay for it last month.
It was 50,000.
Not 30000yen?
Brother, you're not up to any mischief again, are you?
What?
I hate Kawashima
He is quite a good guy
If anything happens that makes Taeko cry,
I won't stand for it,
so shall we head out soon?
President goes to Haneda Airport
Don't try to fool me.
I know it's now law matter.
Are you doing it too?
Are you kidding?
Would a woman do that?
You're right.
What happened?
Sometimes I get stomach aches
I've been feeling unwell since this morning.
You're pretending to be sick
What do you mean?
Brother, you actually dislike the idea of marrying Taeko, don't you?
It's very profitable for the company.
Why would I, as the president, dislike it?
That's fine,
but I was wondering if there is someone you might love
Don't use your imagination.
Well, anyway, let's go.
Are you alright?
I’ll go even if it’s difficult
It’s easy to say, but you broke up, so what are you supposed to do?
I’ll work again at this hot spring resort,
and then you’ll find another husband?
Isn’t that just a pointless repetition? If that’s the
case, it’s better to endure things as they are for now
At this point, Get the allowance will be significantly increased
How much are you getting now?
Is it the amount you take home?
Don't talk like the tax office
Well, the salary hasn't changed from last year
It's bad.
I don't care that money matter.
That's bad.
You make a living from it
A professional has to be professional and draw the line
You give service a lot instead.
But you You've become more refined but you've
lost your allure, haven't you?
Even though you have such a nice skin tone,
are you really staring like that?
Are you not having sex right now?
What do you mean?
Don't act like an amateur
That's the worst, Mom.
That's an incredibly great worry
Are you still in there?
Someone is here to pick you up from Tokyo
Well...
The president is selfish
I can't think of anyone other than Natsuko-san for wife.
You're good, Kawashima-san.
Honestly,even if I could have half of what the president has,
If I had a bit of wealth, I wouldn't just leave Natsuko-san like this
Well, that's a nice thing to say,
How about taking a trip around here for a change of pace?
That sounds great
Natsuko
have a good time fro a few days!
then if that's decided, I might just speed off in the car right now
Fuku-chan, come along with us too
Let's go, cheerful sister
As for you, your business has come up
I was allowed by her.
Well, you see,I'll serve you.
it's about Natsuko-san
I assure you, Kawashima-san, Natsuko is still not broken up with her husband.
it's troubling to be suspected of having ulterior motives
I am just a fan of Natsuko-san
You're on Her husband's side, right?
It's really cold, very cold
If you really are on my side,
won't you help me save face?
What do you mean?
Will you persuade Papa-san to reconsider marriage?
Or will he settle things nicely with me?
Natsuko
but the president is getting old.
You just need to be patient
I'll tell him.
I’m sorry.
No, no, I absolutely won't take the phone.
You're such a spoiled child
that's right
This is the residence in Kameoka
Shoichi?
Who?
Well, main house's
What? The president ?did what?
Did something happen?
I'll pass the phone to Natsuko.
I heard that the president collapsed at at Haneda Airport
This is Natsuko
I heard about you from my husband.
Oh Papa
He suddenly collapsed at the airport and was rushed to the hospital
It seems they closed the peritoneum
I thought I'd let you know.
I see.
Thank you
It's not something you need to thank me so much for
Also, it's better if you try not to come to the hospital for various reasons.
In return, I will take responsibility
and make sure to inform you
Thank you very much indeed
Did he pass away?
No,
I’m sorry.
Shoichi is really nice guy.
your father returned to the hospital room
They said it was almost too late
Since it's right after the surgery, there will be a bit of a fever
Taiko, you can go ahead and back in hotel now
I truly apologize for the trouble I've caused you
Last year, I was almost always by my father's side while he was hospitalized for stomach ulcer surgery
I'm used to dealing with patients
But it's a shame that you finally went out
to have some fun after a long time
But you know, my brother absolutely needs someone like you
I look forward to your assistance
My father is also very much in favor of this discussion;
the reason I came so suddenly is regarding the wedding
I wanted to consult with you,
and my brother will be fine soon
He is originally a sturdy person,
so our conversation with you
It would be better to do it as soon as possible
Hey, Shoichi, you shouldn't be wandering around like that,
Taiko is really tired
Take her to hotel
I'll be taking care of things here tonight
But in that case...
, please don't worry at all
You're so kind.
Say thank her
You're undependable
Natsuko
What's wrong?
He said something, right?
You want a summer orange?
Oh no
but you can't have any moisture
Dad, that's not okay
When he has a fever, he really crave fruit
Hello.
How's papa?
like the results are quite good
I wanna visit him just for a moment.
but it seems that many main residence people are gathered
I would like to meet Shoichi,
I will take the opportunity to bring you along someday
Since it's late tonight,
I'll accompany you home
It's fine, just stay by Papa's side
I won't leave Natsuko-san alone at a time like this
Please go
Excuse me.
I'm tired.
Thank you for your patience
It's a bit stylish to be able to hear a song at the perm shop
I really like this
I'm looking forward to it.
Today, you are different because you've learnt singing
I feel happy when I'm praised, but it's just singing
It's still strange, isn't it?
You are improved
because the teacher is good
Thank you for your hard work
Don't worry about me,
I'm fine
If you're going out, have a good time
Are you going out?
I'm just going to school,
He's a member of PTA.
It's hard.
He is the son of the main family.
It can't be helped.
Are you staying over?
I'll be back tonight
Make sure to take a bath
I won't be coming to your stupid place
I can't believe it.
Take your time.
You're quite straightforward, aren't you?
Well, if someone who doesn't know me sees this,
they would probably think I'm the real wife
I hear he visit you once a week
That's right
He came back after playing with the kids on Sunday night
Saturday night is the problem.
He hasn't said anything,
but it seems that he's had a baby.
It's disgusting.
How's your husband like?
I can't say anything
I haven't visited him even once
Why not just go?
It's not that easy.
having a kind girlfriend like you is so happy.
Natsuko, I can tell you're feeling a bit needy, huh?
How dare you
There's a phone call
Me?
It's me,Sono.
if that's the case, I'll really head home right away
Thank you for having me
Oh, isn't it still fine?
We need to give you this month's tuition as well
anytime is fine.
What's wrong?
Welcome home.
He's looking forward to seeing you
I'll prepare the bath
Natsuko.
Papa.
How are you?
Natsuko.
This smell...
Natsuko's
Today, for the first time, I was allowed to take a bath
and while I was soaking in the hot water,
I just couldn't help but want to see Natsuko
I secretly snuck out of the hospital
Have you been discharged yet?
So I can't afford to take it.
Ok?
You can't
Your body still isn't well enough, is it?
Moreover, the conclusion of the important discussion has not been reached yet
What are you saying?
Are we breaking up? My illness cancels that out
It's been a month, so there's no need to say something boring
But for me, it's important
When you decide on a new wife at your main residence
I can't continue living like this,
Don't make me mess
You know what?
I was only thinking about you in that hospital room
I've always wanted to do so many things with you.
but what about you? Have you come to dislike me?
Don't get me wrong.
But let's talk first.
Don't be selfish.
Can we talk later.
It's more important that my unauthorized outing doesn't get found out
Listen to what I say
It's strange.
It's still noon.
We always have no plan.
This isn't something that only happens today
Natsuko, come on.
today is fine, you know
But, husband?
Natsuko
Don't you need to go shopping for dinner?
You went to the market, right?
But He said like that.
I'm going to department store again.
Take your time
and be careful
She's careful woman
Natsuko
What?
What's the hell?
Come this way
You're so self-centered
I think it would be better to resist the natural course of things later on
I don't have to do that now.
How about you untie your obi?
No
Are you still frustrated?
Alright, can I help?
Are you alright?
Was that too much?
Should I call a doctor?
No
Can you rub here?
You...
It's all about you.
What a nice.
You're very bad.
It's been a while since we last met
Please be careful with strong things
Dad.
Oh you are here.
Patients must follow the hospital rules
If the doctor finds out, it'll be a big deal
Everybody's been looking for you
I’m sorry.
I had something I was a bit concerned about
I went to the bank,
It was important that I needed to go.
Maybe I've walked too much, my back hurts
Was there something you needed?
I thought I'd take a look at that
What?
Isn't that a wedding invitation?
Yes.
Oh my, have you already decided on the date?
In this case, it seems better to do it as soon as possible
Ms. Taiko has returned home for now on the morning flight
Next time, we decided to discuss the detailed arrangements for the wedding
You work very fast.
It's been approved at the executive level.
You should be more aware
Mr. Shoichi, please watch him
Well then, I'll head home a bit earlier
She seems very frustrated
Of course
Were you at Kamioka?
Where's cigarette?
I was so pursued and in trouble.
Women can become strict when they turn 40 years old.
Has anything changed at the company?
Not really
I really need you to hold back
I understand, and Natsuko was grateful for what you did
You were the first to inform me about my condition
It was you, wasn't it?
You were nice.
Now I half-regret now
It's easier to maintain neutrality regarding your private life
I'm still tired
It's still impossible
What?
It's ok.
Why don't we go for golf later
It's been a while
It's good for your health
Thank you very much.
Ma'am.
It's sad to be alone, isn't it?
Why?
Because...
I'm shy
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Oh, Kawashima, how unusual!
I suddenly wanted to see you.
Do you expand the house?
May I come in?
The weather is very nice.
You came to see me because Papa asked you right?
Don't get me wrong.
I came because I was concerned about you.
There's no need to worry;
I've long since given up
It's no use chasing him.
No way.
The president doesn't hate you and is marrying another wife.
He's just concerned about public opinion
He said like that.
It seems like all men say similar things
I can start getting involved in work as early as next week
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you
but the president seems to be quite considerate, doesn't he?
What kind of expansion will you be doing this time?
Tea house
That's good.
You saw this too, right?
This....
This is the invitation to the president's wedding reception
He probably sent me for example.
He is very nosy.
No, it's truly surprising
Who did this?
I want to know
At first, I thought it was you
Give me a break
There's no way I would do something like that
Is someone making fun of me?
If it comes to this, I'll be stubborn about it
No matter what anyone says, I'm not going to break up with Papa
That's for sure; there's absolutely no need
You know, I think I might try to meet that Taeko person
That's not good, ma'am
Why?
This is not good idea.
It's very dangerous for the two of you to meet.
I think you're very hated
Who on earth would make a woman do such a disgraceful thing?
Of course, it's the president's way, but This is not good idea.
Try forgiving the president with this.
You will be a problem
What does it mean?
It can't be helped.
Generous people like me are easily made fun of by others.
What's the hell?
Of course.
I can't tolerate any more insults than this
If you meet papa, tell him this
If you really love me, please treat me like a human being.
This is the fourth row
You remembered him, didn't you?
I came here because I want you to forget him.
It's just about the time the wedding has started
It's too late to regret it now
But it can't be helped
Forget about that.
What house you bet?
Star Ruby, Papa likes her.
Your predictions are excellent
I can't believe Star Rubin would win
We got a lot of money
I was able to treat you
I'll enjoy the feast
Where should we go?
How about some Kawagoe cuisine around here?
Be careful
What are you doing?
You're speeding over there
That car was just picked up from a factory.
This one is a brand new car
Look at that wound.
The dump truck driver drives recklessly.
Aren't you drinking or something?
You idiot
I don't drink from the daytime.
Don't assume I'm a woman
I have witnesses
Isn't it because you're wearing colored glasses
Kubo teacher.
Nacchan.
Come with me.
It's been ages.
I never thought that you worked at a car repair shop
Could you stop calling me Sensei, please?
Should I call you Kubo-san?
Or Kenji?
You really are a teacher after all
But you've changed, haven't you?
You've become quite impressive
You seem like a bourgeois young lady
As I mentioned earlier, that's how I feel about myself
Please don't make a fool of me.
But you look happy
Let's drink
I haven't asked anything about you at all.
I think you're probably married already.
I am a clumsy guy
I still haven't caught a single one
Your ideals are too high?
I'm doing my best to keep up
I can't afford to get married.
I think you have at least one person you like.
you're still so young.
You think you are inconvenient being alone
For what?
I mean.
You are stupid.
That's silly
I'm like that.
But you are still shy as always, in a way that doesn't change
I still sometimes remember things from the past
It was a short teaching career,
but I have a deep impression of you
You want to become a great geisha and succeed in the future by having to write an essay
There was a time when I was troubled
I was scolded quite a bit, wasn't I?
But I was happy about it
Do you remember what happened that night?
What do you mean?
You are pretending not to know
You are mean.
It was about my most dangerous night
Nacchan, Nacchan
Did you see her?
She's not in the hall
Kusumi is waiting for her
Oh my god.
She might have gone home, so just to be safe,
try calling and see what they say
Yes.
What on earth is she doing?
What's that?
peach-colored outfit
You look good.
Thanks.
I won.
Damn it.
I skipped work and came here.
Are you okay if you don't come back?
Please order me tonight
A cheap price is fine too.
Your salary is low, so I'll pay later.
Don't say things like that.
I am still an adult
My breasts are small but people say they are nicely shaped.
Speaking of which, you looked the most mature during the physical examination
but that's just part of our business
Naturally, it's surprisingly so
Were you watching me?
Can't be helped, can it?
Then take responsibility for having seen me naked
Please take responsibility for this matter
If I took on that responsibility,
I have to marry every woman in my class.
But even the teacher...
Eventually, marriage, when will that be?
Yes.
With what kind of person?
What kind of women do you like?
I have no idea.
Don't say that, just tell me
That's right
Clean, cute, and modest
She forgives my selfishness
Am I bad?
I'll take you.
No
that's a problem. I have some research to do,
You are a novice
Go home quietly
What's wrong?
Are you crying?
There's something strange about you tonight
I was a kid.
But you knew my true feelings,
and even if they knew, there was nothing to be done about it
That was good in its own way
That's why you can wear such a splendid kimono
and adorn your fingers with amazing jewels
Becoming the wife of a man who still can't be independent at this age
and is doing such things
You must have managed to keep those beautiful hands from getting chapped
You thinks that I am living a satisfying life?
Well, no one can live a completely fulfilling life every day
You chose your own path,
so don't get distracted
and trip over trivial stones
As expected, you're a teacher; giving lectures is your specialty
Shall I bring beer?
Yes.
Well, no, it's fine now
I have to go now
Please stay here.
No, really, it's fine,.
I get it.
Please come to my house
I'm going to be scolded by Sakuma-san.
Is it okay to do a little bad thing tonight?
Come over to my place
If you don't like my place,
a bar or a nightclub is fine too
I will accompany you
After all, we finally met
I don't want to say good bye.
His new wife is in good health.
I wonder if his body can handle it
She has a mole on her face.
It means she is compassionate.
Yes,that's it.
Is this Sakurai?
This tobacco is very good
I'm worried that he might not come here anymore.
you know? Natsuko really has to hustle
Did she really say to go to horse racing?
Yes.
Still, it's late
She didn't actually go to see Mount Fuji?
Mount Fuji?
There are times when she get really frustrated
She often come to see Mount Fuji
I don't know how to run this house.
You only have tea, so you must have whiskey, right?
But you know, she rarely serves customers
She puts it in a locked locker.
Just bring it
The key is with the wife,
so she's careful.
I'm sorry.
I was treated to a feast at the hotel
Please don't worry
What's the hell?
She's back
I'm home.
You look happy.
Sorry to bother you.
I wanted to see the bar-code dance
Also, it's been a while since I've watched the bicycle race
Shioya is beautiful, isn't it?
I was just teasing at the night market
Alone?
being alone with a nice person
I think you've been very busy.
I don't want to hear about his wedding.
Of course, I wouldn't do anything
But Shoichi, gives you a splendid gift
This must be a top-quality item
This is awesome.
Mr. Shoichi said?
He is concerned about your mood
he's quite an observant young man
Papa should learn a lot from him.
Please give my regards and thanks to Mr. Shoichi
Come on, Nacchan, cheer up! It's been a while
Let's drink up,
Get the keys
It's locker keys.
The whiskey is locked up, right?
How did you know?
Yes, I'll take it out
You must be properly tired, right?
It was magnificent
Many important people from the political world were there.
Come on,Nacchan.
We've been fed up with just tea for a while now
We have a new Wife in this house
Tomika, you should be a little more careful with your words
Where's Taiko?
She just went out.
Kanako's place?
I'm sure something happened again.
She came to talk about Shizu-san.
They're such trivial people
I'm busy but I'm at home on weekends.
I'm going out too.
Where are you going?
We have a guest from Hong Kong.
so I should at least serve a meal.
What's wrong? you are in a hurry
I was shopping at the supermarket
a strange noise right behind me
What kind of guy?
He was in a dirty state.
Your clothes are torn
I can't believe it.
He is a pervert
Be careful!
It would be good to report it to the police box later
Ma'am,I'm popular with men
You are happy to have your skirt torn
but hurry up and change.
Oh Papa
I thought you were a pervert.
Isn't it rude to say that?
It's been a while
I was wondering what was going on with that
You concern only the tea room?
Don't say like that.
How is your life?
For what?
Your new wife
That's not a big deal.
That's not bad, is it?
Please don't tease me
I don't do that.
You've lost a little weight and look very smart
I lost 7 pounds
pounds?
It's the same as when your wife uses
She is the daughter of the Koshiba Butter family
I have always been British in everything
This isn't something that just started now.
Oh, it's true that women like us in UK?
This garden is very beautiful.
Please tell me the truth.
Please bring me a cold drink.
What is the reason for losing weight?
Our company has been in a mess, you know
Is that all?
What do you mean?
I think you know that
Because of Taiko?
Even if I say I'm newlywed,
I have grandchildren
You think so?
That's enough.
I thought I might have a whiskey,
but I've already had one long ago
There's no one to drink with,
so I can't afford to be extravagant
I send you money every month.
Yes but I've been keeping it aside
What do you mean?
I leave the check as it is.
Are you leaving now?
I think I'll change into my yukata.
I already took it to the cleaners
It's fine with yours
Welcome back.
How are you?
Is that all there is?
I bought something at the bargain sale,
is that strange?
I think that would be very sexy for him
It's good for my eyes.
What are you talking about?
She's a huge difference from us.
You are very eloquent.
It's true
There are always problems in my house
I'm going to take a look at another house.
Come with me.
What do you mean? It's ridiculous.
it’s fine to be noisy about it
You came all this way,
We can't
You think there is frustration
Women and men are different
Let's go out together
We can't
You're being too rigid
This is our secret
We can't
Do you need anything from me?
I'm going to that laundromat
to get Yukata
It's fine today
I heard Papa is busy, so he'll be back soon
Natsuko
Shall we get some eel?
You shouldn't eat such things
I want to take a little nap
He is tired so please give him a massage.
It's a man.
A man?  I don't need a male masseuse.
I don't understand where you guys are focusing your attention
If you don't entertain to the bar,
We can't deal.
You can't have such old-fashioned ideas.
We should deal honestly with others
Ok?
That's enough.
What's wrong?
I have business in Muroran
is it a business trip?
When are you going?
It's the evening flight
Shall we stop by Sapporo on our way back?
It's been a month, and it's about time you returned
Dad, something happened, didn't it?
Actually,it seems that Taiko has been getting involved with Natsuko
Do you know that maid?
Oharu?
Tomiko said she heard the information from the driver.
Please be careful of her.
We both have our struggles.
You and I are different.
Thank you very much.
Could you go for me?
Don't worry about money
I'm going now
I'm counting on you.
He's it's too much for me.
He is very educated
It's me.
What are my plans for tonight?
Nothing today
I get it.
Yes.
Is that husband?
your wife?
She just left a little while ago.
Without mentioning the destination
She seemed to be in quite a hurry.
Was she calling a man or a woman?
You don't know?
Check it out.
I'll call you later.
She's useless
Come in.
Excuse me
Clean up after the boss leaves.
It's ok.
Leave it
Who's her?
She's a part-time job worker
This is truly modern
Let her keep working.
It's not really a bother, so don't worry
Well then.
That job is dangerous.
If you slip, you'll be dead
I have to do what others won't do
I'm a student at a PE university.
I'm used to it
PE?
Are you able to open your legs and put your head on the floor?
It's easy.
I can do even more amazing things
Well then, I'd like to see it once
Feel free to anytime
Shall we have a meal together?
I'm starving.
You're so honest.
Welcome.
I've prepared the usual room,
but I wonder if I couldn't accommodate four people?
It's just two
Weren't you together?
What do you mean?
Are you getting with the lady from Kamakura?
Is she here?
Just a moment ago
This is not good idea.
I'll come again.
It's ok.
It's not good for me.
and it's a bit unpleasant, so well then!
As I hear a lot here at Okawabata,
it seems like I've forgotten about the unpleasant stories,
but it can't be helped
It's a bit tough, isn't it?
Please feel free to speak up
I have made up my mind properly during the call earlier.
Are you sure?
Please pour
How about you?
You are like someone who has been to a hot spring at all,
You don't look like one either.
I’m Kanako, born in Canada, and I don’t have to introduce myself that way
But you do know, don’t you?
Well then, let's get straight to the point
Go ahead.
Actually, you see, Taeko-san knew about you then she returned to Hokkaido.
I suppose some meddlesome person
must have informed her out of loyalty
The responsibility that directly connects Taiko-san and my brother
I have to tell you
Are you saying we should break up?
You're right;
a life like this won't last in the end.
I really think it's better to have a proper marriage
If it were you, I'm sure you'd have plenty of chances
If that's the case,
Do you want me to take care of it?
But I am Geisha girl.
You can handle it down there
I wonder if I was praised for something?
Of course,
it's unfortunate
I'm no good
I can if Papa allows me to, but being pressured like this by those around me only complicates my feelings
Besides, I really like Papa.
Oh I see
But what’s so good about such an old man?
He is twice your age, isn't he?
I'm not that different from Taiko
She does not care of his age?
I see.
That's interesting
Thank you very much
But please don't bully me too much.
I like you now.
Don't make such a scary face?
Please shake my hand.
Your hands are cold.
I feel good...
She's a strategist.
Yes She is
Be careful,
Have some drink?
Thank you
Where's the husband?
We are in trouble.
The person over there had a miscarriage, and I was able to accompany her after all
Was she pregnant?
Yeah. Men are just doing things behind the scenes.
He hate wife and He ended up like this,
You see?
Don't you know what Papa is doing outside?
If I keep singing about it,
I'll just get more wrinkles
It's true that women are like that,
Yeah.
Are you okay?
I don't get tired easily from things like this
You're looking cool
That's something to celebrate!
What's the hell?
I'm tired.
Stay with me tonight.
You may get collapse
I don't mind
Then let's go all out
How about this?
It suits you.
This is good for you.
But it's expensive, isn't it?
Can this really sell?
It's still cheaper than buying at a local store,
but it's a good business idea you've come up with
This person is in charge of procurement
while I handle sales
If I just dress nice, they'll buy.
If that's the case, I guess I have to buy something too
Thank you for your cooperation for our wedding.
Hello.
Who?
Excuse me.
Hello.
is there something you need?
Are you wife?
Yes.
could you let me clean the windows?
Do you clean window?
Yes.
Are you a part-timer?
Yes, that's right
But there are only a few windows, and my family can clean them,
so it's fine
Please don't say that, let me wipe it off
in that outfit?
I'll change into work cloth.
Papa.
Papa?
Hello?
Oh you.
It would be bad if these guys found out
I won't make such a mistake.
I came here to avoid being found
I came up the back stairs,
Hey, just wait in the apartment.
No way, I can't let Natsuko-san win
Did you meet her?
I just went there.
She was very nice.
But I'm a little jealous
What?
Kamiyama Natsuko.
Natsuko-san really love you.
Yes.
You are acting like nice.
But you are really popular
Do you like me?
Yes.
Same here.
Since I started liking you
I haven't been able to notice any other men at all
But younger people probably prefer younger men
The other day I was hit on, but I turned him down
How many girls do you have?
Don't say bullshit.
But there is no limit to the number of girls, right?
You say some interesting things.
I intend not to lose to Natsuko-san
But I feel sorry for her.
Why?
There's really no freedom.
She is not recognized as an individual
She has a lot of freedom.
She seems to be in a cage
You think so?
I also want a house.
But at that time, it is still my house, which means my personality dominate every corner of the room.
Natsuko's house is all about what you want, after all
In my case, You will be treated as a guest
You did something bad.
It's okay
They haven't noticed anything
Look.
Hello,it's me.
What?
There's a problem.
When Taeko returned from Hokkaido
She collapse on her way back from Hokkaido
What collapsed? What's happening?
You don't know?
Shoichi is accompanying her?
Alright, then I'll head to the hospital right away;
this is serious
It's boring.
What?
I can't stay with you tonight.
I don't know how she is
I might not be able to join you again.
You're asking for too much again
Then kiss me
Can I do a silly American movie imitation ?
It can't be helped.
Hello?
Oh Shoichi.
What's going on?
She appears to be pregnant
She made a baby.
So you guys
have had another baby,
that's wonderful!
How's Taiko now?
You're in the hospital now, right?
That Ms Taeko and you have had a baby
Are you sure?
Yes, it's true.
Congratulations.
Can you come here right away?
Oh no..my baby.
Kiss me,papa
Isn't everyone coming?
Oh my god.
Hide here.
Come in.
I don't have any plans for today?
at least not at the moment
I'm going out for a bit now
Well then, that's fine
Get the car.
I heard from Shoichi.
I was worried because you
didn't come back for a long time
Well, I'm glad about that
So, is it all settled
Can I have a baby?
What?
I will give birth if you want.
Now that we have a child, I hope you will take care of her.
Her?
What do you mean?
You are pretending not to understand
Of course, I'm talking about Natsuko Kamioka,
You will break up with me, won't you?
At this point, I would like a clear answer,
You give vague responses
We're breaking up
You really promise me, don't you?
You shouldn't think that I'm saying this
the baby in my belly is saying something.
I don't want my kids to say they have two moms.
But you really do take responsibility, don't you?
But do you really have a bay?
go ahead and touch it
I can tell just from being stabbed from above?
Just touch it.
I’m sorry.
You had an appendicitis operation.
I'm glad, congratulations!
Take it off.
But that's not good
Why are you teasing me?
You are impatient and always does whatever you want
There's no mood.
Because I'm young.
Damn it.
I don't even have enough money to surround myself with a deluxe apartment
Just keep it up.
When I get to be as old as Sakuma?
I'll refuse it
Even if I keep you
A young man like me is not good enough for you
Hey, I don't like that old man's photo,
Come on.
Who?
That old man?
Hide yourself.
Where to hide?
Under the bed.
I'll cleverly take him outside.
The old man's photo
Yes.
Hide yourself.
It's cold,
Did I surprise you?
Mind if I come in for a bit?
Please.
How did you know here?
You dropped this, didn't you?
I searched for it quite a while.
Oh you got it.
I was thinking of delivering it right away,
but I thought you might pick this up.
so I'm sorry for the trouble
There is something I want to ask you before I return it.
What is it?
You see, I happened to look inside this
Then this came out.
You knew about Sakuma, didn't you?
Seeing where Sakuma's belongings are, it seems
like you might not just be acquaintances
If I misunderstood, please forgive me
Since when have you been involved with Sakuma?
If you stay silent, I won't understand
But You have a future together, so you shouldn't be with Sakuma.
Do you really love him,
Do you truly love Sakuma?
What about you?
Well,I don't dislike him.
That's about it?
Yes.
But I might come to like it even more from now on
Please don't worry about it.
It's a cat, you know
Sakuma didn't know animals at all
I didn't know.
You only understand that much about that person, huh?
Do you know more?
It's been 5 years now
The passage of time isn't the issue
You know, I'm much younger than you, but I'm a good people watcher.
I also researched Sakuma in a short period of time.
So this is the result of that research;
he is the most typical Japanese man, isn't he?
He has an exceptionally strong desire for business,
He has ulterior motives for women.
I'm strong against that kind of person
I want to get a lot of money from men who play around with women.
Even you know that?
You don't really love that old man
from the bottom of your heart
Tell me.
I'm different.
so that's love?
Yes.
Is it strange?
It's comedy
It's old.
old, old, old? Is it bad?
Shouldn't it be miserable?
Is there really a need to love for someone you
can't even officially marry?
Let's work together.
We'll just work together to get money from him.
After that, we'll just marry the person
we like the most
How about that?
you're angry?
It seems I don't need to listen to you any longer
You are innocent and simple
But you might lose your mistress job.
I heard that a child is going to be born at his home
You didn't know that?
He is currently with his wife,
and he was not able to come back here
Let him play properly,Mrs. Natsuko
Saeko
What's wrong?
Mom and the Master argue about his wife
Master got angry and said he was going to break up with Mama
She took the fruit knife
Did she stab him with a fruit knife?
what happened to the master?
he was a carried by ambulance
he's serious case
Mom called 110 herself right away
Oh Saeko.
Thank you for your hard work
Oh Nacchan.
What's wrong with a pale face?
Ah, wait a moment, I have work to do soon
I'm thinking that if a reasonably priced apartment comes up, I might consider it
It's a waste to do live alone
But I'm sorry
You came all this way for me
I don't want anything other than this.
Are you okay to drink so much?
I'm very used to it
You should drink too, teacher
I can't drink.
I can't help but drink tonight
where you said Saeko?
I never thought she would do something like that.
When the time comes, women don't know what to do.
You same?
I am also a woman.
That's scary
I feel bad.
Can I untie?
Go ahead.
take it easy
Excuse me.
Are you alright?
Teacher.
You said when we met the other
day that I looked happy.
Do you really think so?
Yeah.
Well, I tell you a nice story
About My New Year's Day
About your New Year's Day?
That's Natsuko's New Year's Day
I wake up alone on New Year's Day
My partner is a maid.
When that maid goes out to play,
I will be all alone in the house
Of course, I don't want to see people coming for New Year's greetings either
A cheerful shopkeeper at the vegetable store don't come.
Neighborhood kids are surrounded by their parents,
squealing and playing with kites and flying kite.
Sometimes I have trouble dealing with drunken customers
But you know, teacher
Am I just sitting quietly at home?
Even so, I'm happy?
I eat freshly cooked rice facing my husband and his wife.
I am the wife And you are my husband
I often have such dreams like this.
If it's a dream, that's fine
Can't that be true?
Why not?
You see?
Just look
Can you endure this room for three days?
I'll clean it and make it nice
I can do that.
Do you think you can live on my meager salary after getting used to a luxurious lifestyle?
Even buying one side dish for dinner requires consulting my wallet every time
I am prepared. What I want now is a love.
while living a poor life, The love might fade away
If love disappears, that would truly be miserable
I don't want you to go through that kind of experience now
You don't like me, do you?
You don't like a woman like me,right?
That's not true.
I really don't have the confidence to make you happy.
Saying something so spineless
You were strong.
Be my teacher again like in the old days
Teacher.
Give me courage
I can't live like this anymore.
I don't want to go home tonight.
But until you have clearly received permission from Sakuma.
we are both adults
It's okay to stay like this? Please hold me tight
Welcome back.
He came last night.
I told him you were at Lunar's mom's place.
Where were you?
Who were you with?
Say something.
So you were with Lunar's mom?
Don't lie about that,
just look at this
Natsuko, is it okay to lie.
Who were you with?
I visited Mr.Kubo.
So you came back in the morning?
is he your first love man?
Are you trying to make me jealous by cheating?
you are so dirty.
Don't get me wrong.
It's ridiculous to say that a man and a woman can share a room and nothing happened
it was nothing happen
I'm sure you're lying.
Call Kubo
I meet him
what if you meet him?
you will be with him too
We'll discuss it among the three of us and come to a conclusion
Did you come home in the morning again?
Ms. Taeko is going back to Hokkaido again
But, big brother,
Do you like Natsuko that much?
Is it hard for you to break up with her?
At this age, I still can't grasp the feelings of men.
Kawashima is here.
Get her throgh
Do you mind if you go home?
I will go home even if you don't tell me to
But let me make this clear:
I am on Taeko's side until the very end
See?
How was she?
I hear she will definitely visit.
I see, that's at a tiny repair shop
I heard he is a public servant there,
but what kind of man is he?
He had a good physique
He's quite a handsome guy, isn't he?
However, he doesn't really have much life skills, does he?
You also got in touch with Natsuko, didn't you?
Of course.
Ma'am.
The car has arrived, but
it seems that a bad cold is trending this year
I'm glad to hear you are doing well.
thanks to that, he hasn't fallen ill at all
Your condition should be very good.
it is windy now
Wanna drink?
women don't keep time at all.
Here it is.
You're late
I’m sorry.
Natsuko. Come here and sit down.
Now that everyone is here, let's get to the questions
First, I'd like to hear Mr. Kubo's determination
Speaking of determination?
I heard from her that you intend to marry Natsuko
Right?
Ask him.
Tell me.
Of course, I have those feelings.
That is not a lie
However, the one who must make up their mind is you, Natsuko
Will you come to my place?
Or will you stay at him?
That's up to Natsuko.
But suppose
Natsuko chose you
In that case,
From my perspective, I have no choice but to treat you as
a thief for taking someone else's things without permission
Please wait a moment
You say it's someone else's, but humans are not objects
Of course, that's right
However, I have cherished and protected Nasuko for five years
I would like you to consider that effort
Isn't she more important than material things
or even property?
I see women as property
That's in the past
Now that's not a problem even a child, or a grandchild,
They are treasures more important than any property.
If we seek peace in this world today,
True peace among humans must be based on truth.
You came here to threaten this old man's peace
Of course, you are free to love Natsuko,
but you disrupted my room for that
Still, Are you okay with it?
My words might be a bit harsh
Seeing that there is no response, it seems
that Mr Kubo has understood my feelings.
Natsuko, what on earth is going on with you?
It seems you've underestimated me a bit too much
Did you think I would allow you to marry him?
Did you think I would let it go in front of him?
I realize now that I was indeed naive
Isn't that right?
But don't get me wrong.
I had been relying too much on others.
I have been living for a long time relying on others' help
That habit became ingrained, and I couldn't do anything without relying on others.
To say goodbye to you
I felt that I needed Mr. Kubo's power
But He only lent me half of his strength
Teacher!
To be honest,
I really resented you
You won't listen to my request
I thought you were a cold person.
But now I finally understood.
Natsuko, are you going to Kubo-kun's place?
No.
Are you with me as before?
I don't like it either
I've really been taken care of for a long time.
but I'm tired of living with the help of others
I want to try living on my own strength
What are you saying?
What exactly do you think you can do?
You'll only get hurt.
It could be.
But at that time, I won't rely anyone.
I cry alone and wipe my tears alone
Natsuko, what about you?
Papa.
Natsuko will try walking again
Natsuko.
Thank you very much.
Driver.
Anywhere is fine, just go to a place where I can see Mount Fuji.
THE END