Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
You guys become, from this day the henchmen of the master.
You have to listen to your master whatever he says
Take the sake for the promise
Now that you have accepted this cup, you will lay down your life for your master.
We'll have this
I'll kill your master!
This trip is a rush trip.
It's going to be hard for you, but you're going to do it because it's your way up the ladder, and you're going to do it well.
Yes
I'm going
Please take care of your health
Thanks
Have a safe trip
I'm going
Here it is
Okayo
This is a good luck charm for you
I'll be back after 3 years
Please wait for me
Hideji
He's gone to somewhere
Don't worry. He'll be back
hey, time for fight
Please bet
Let's play
Damn it
This isn't just gambling
Hey guest
That's is our sign board.
If you take it, I can't see my boss anymore
Can you get it back to me?
It's none of my business
You wanna be killed too?
You are stubborn
Odeiri (1964)
Hey traveler
Do you want to earn money?
IF you help us, I will pay 1 ryo 3
Which group are you belonging to?
I forgot, sorry
We are Komoro unit from Akaiyoi
Akaiyoi?
Our opponent is ODAIJUKU's Katsuma.
He is very stingy.
Akaiyoi and Katsuma are brother team?
Why are they fighting?
AKAIWA threw a drink at TOUBE for a little cause.
a fight is not worth talking about unless you win
So we need helpers
It's none of my business
Hold on
I know you are Hideji from Katsuma Unit
You remember?
I'm Matsukura's Hanji from Sasajima unit
I will beat you
Our boss will revenge you
You don't worry about your Unit?
In the three years I've been gone, there have been more strange people.
Shut up. Gets your hands off of me
Don't get excited.
It's still daytime
Damn it
Hanji.
No need to panic.
He'll be killed soon
I will show you around
Hey hold on
I'll ask you again.
The helper fee is 1 ryo 3?
Yes
1 ryo 3?
I'll talk to my mate
Mate?
He's my close mate
What do you think?
That's what I though
He said that
Hey
You walk so fast
I will ask to Katsuma unit about the helper fee
The fee will be high if they will fight
1 ryo 3 is too cheap for me
Business is thriving.
Thank you
We can sell all in 10 days
I hear there are more people than usual this year
Thank you for every time
Please take a look at them
Yuki
Are you going to see the gambling guy?
You are daughter of bitch
They are Yakuza.
I told you
Don't talk badly about him
You are in love with him.
So you lost yourself
You'll be in trouble
Mind your own business
Yuki
She's idiot
Hey you
You know what,Yoshi
To be honest, I worry about you
You are strange these days
I'm not comfortable because of him
I will proof that he is not my brother
You can't, He is your only brother
Stop it
What are you doing?
Akaiwa unit will manage around Kinuichi from today
Did you talk to Katsuma unit?
I'll talk them later
Give me money for today
I won't pay
You bastard!
Please show how strong you are
I will beat you
Killing people is a career.
Right?
Help me!
Hey you guys
Dad
Here's our territory
I will beat you
You've been picking fights with me
Wait
Akaiwa units are at Kinuichi to break down
You bastard!
Hey stop it!
Don't fight
It's none of your business,bros
Cut it out!
They are good brothers
Get out!
Hey stop it!
Hold on
Bros
Hideji
Inawa
Akaiwa units's been picking fights with us
Hold on
I will kill you guys if you fight
Yakuza shouldn't bother ordinary citizens
I'm sorry to trouble you
I will talk to them and solve the problem
solve the problem? How?
We can kill him
Don't make a noise
Leave it to me
OK
Come
Let's talk about it in different places.
I'm sorry to trouble you
Please keep working
Let;s go
Bros.
How much is the helper fee?
We don't fight.
I don't need it
Wait
Here's fine
Come on
Are you guys over?
Go home
Go home!
Hideji
Oh Yoshi
Thanks in advance
I didn't know You've become one of us.
They are not my bros
It's up to you
What's wrong about it?
Just as you saw it.
What?
we met for the first time in three years.
You are so rude
I'm no longer Yakuza
i want to talk to you
Hold on
You can talk him later.
See our boss. He will be glad
I'm back now
welcome back
It's been a year
This place has changed while you were gone
why did Akaiwa cut ties with you?
They wanted our territory for money
they don't follow the rules
The Sasajima unit collapsed while you were gone
Akaiwa gets them and now they have great force
they have been harassing us
They are terrible
They are scam of Yakuza
I had been patient
I don't want to cause trouble for that market.
they are gathering helpers
We can't fight
I know
We can't do anything until that market is over
i think I’ll ask someone to stop them
Can you ask for him?
By the way, Why inosuke went Meaka?
He wanted leave us
Forget what happened in past
Where are you going?
There is nowhere you can go
Wait. You really go?
Don't go
What are you doing?
You are annoying
You have no money.
I looked after you
you pay off my debt to sell your body
Akaiwa are targeting at Kimuichi
I see.
so you want our help
We are brother.
We are willing to help you
Thank you very much.
I will tell my boss
Hen, Sanpei
Don't look down us.
You should pay
I have no money
What's the hell?
You bastard!
It was better to kill scam
You
Are you the master?
Do you wanna hire me?
You killed our staff.
You are too selfish
I see
I listened your conversation by happening.If you fight, one of you will collapse
One way of doing things can destroy both.
This is good for you, I think
I will talk about it later
It's ok Katsuma and Akaiwa is going to fight
Boss
I don't see the girl
Is she alright?
I told you to forget about past
Hideji bros
What brings you to this place?
She's Oyuki
She's a good girl, ain't she?
Yoshi
Inosuke is at origin house?
Yes
I feel sorry about him
Don't talk badly about your brother
Sorry, I can't say
Hi
Give me a break,Ino
Ino
Thank you very much
I don't want you to catch a cold.
I wonder What is Hideji doing now?
Okayo
We can't
I love you
You betrayed me
You took my girl.
You bastard!
Ino!
I don't care what you say.
I loved Okayo
I wanted to make her happy
What's the hell?
You think I can't make her happy?
yeah
You’re Yakuza,
You can't make her happy
I left from Yakuza,
Now I understand what's world
You can't live a decent life in the yakuza world.
Hideji, please leave Okayo to me
Please
Please Hideji
I can't
For three years while I was traveling, I thought only of her.
She's mine
I'll get her back to me
I don't wanna talk with you
Hideji
Okayo
You can go to Hideji if you want
You
I wanna drink
i had a stupid dream
Don't be hesitate
Drinking sake is better than her
Hideiji is here?
This is going to be an interesting
I found him
Really? he is here?
i will pay you back
Don't fight here!
Stop it!
stop it!
Damn it
Oh my god.
We should go home
Shit
He's stronger than you
Who are you?
Akaiwa get mad if you go back
Can you help me?
We pay you a lot
I don't want
What do you want?
Your life
Excuse me
Sensei
Please get up
Akaiwa will pay you back.
Because his henchman was killed
We can earn 2 ryo
or 3 ryo
It seems the battle is over
There is no helper for Katsuma
I wanna see how he cries
they came to attack
Don't be scared.
He's alone
I'm not here for fighting
I have a favor to ask from you
What?
Please don't fight until Kimuichi is over
Do you afraid?
I'm not talking to you guys.
I'm talking to Akaiwa
You ask me to wait?
You killed our henchmen
What's the hell?
They weren't killed by Katsuma unit
How can we trust you?
i only tell the truth
I don't trust you
It seemed you killed our 5 henchmen
What?
So you don't trust me
No!
I see so it can't be helped
i gave my little finger
your little finger won't solve the problem
What?
You should go home
You're stubborn
I speak in yakuza terms
It won't work
In this world, the stronger one wins
Any more involvement with us, we will kill you.
Go home
Damn it
Don't move
I will kill him if you move
You're not fair
You too
i have my own way
Wait
what do you do with him?
I'll keep this man until the market is over.
Don't go.
He might kill him
I can't believe it
We're unlucky
I got the money, but we are in this situation
I’m out of luck
Is your son a hostage?
He is my only son
Attacking him could get my son killed.
So please help me
You are Akaiwa but You love your son too much.
You care more about your child than the market
Give me a break
you always compliment me but...
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
What can I do for you?
I have or I don't have, but I tell you
Looks like you've done me right so far today.I will surely rain blood between Katsuma and Akaiwa.
Don't feel like you've won just because you took a hostage
why are you defying me?
I don't hate you
I just wanna kill all of Yakuza
You bastard!
Hold on
What are you doing?
Get out from here
Hideji,
Can you guys leave from here?
What's the hell?
you guys are causing a lot of trouble here
Can you guys leave from here?
It's none of my business
What?
Cut it out,Ina
that sword of yours is useless
I want to calm down the current commotion
Or you want me to leave here?
I see. that's right
What?
Hideji
What are you doing?
Our boss is waiting for you
I tell you.
I won't listen to you
I won't let you do what you think
You should show them around
I kept you waiting
This way
I will beat you later
Maybe something interesting will happen before that
Okayo
You don't have to reply.
Let's go with me
Dad
She's not my daughter
Okayo
I feel sorry about you and our boss
Please go back to our boss
I feel sorry about my dad
But I don't want to go back to the gangster life again.
Okayo
Please stop to disturb us
I worry about you
Don't worry
You hate me?
Don't get me wrong
I still love you
Mom
What should I do
Okayo
Who?
Are you Okayo?
I'd been waiting for you
I can give your son to Katsuma
Wait, I'll give you money
i have as much money as you want
Okayo
Okayo?
I'm here to talk with you
I want Okayo
You kidnapped her
What?
You're not fair
Where is she now?
I have no idea
I'm here to talk with you
What's wrong?
She is at Akaiwa
What?
Akaiwa told me he needed her
Don't go there
They are Yakiza.
They don't listen to us
It's pointless
you got her into a yakuza fight
She's my wife
Please accept what Akaiwa says
We'll get into the fray.
We will lose
I know that
She is not Yakiza.
We need to have her leave from them
So please, boss
I can't.
We cut a tie but She's my daughter
I can't give my territory because of her
Boss
Territory is the life of the Yakuza.
No
Darling
Help me
You guys!
Darling
Sorry
Sensei
Boss is calling you
Get me OKAYO back
you still don't understand
If you give Taichi back to me, I will give her back.
It's nothing to do with Okayo
She's not Yakuza
She's your wife but she is Tobei's daughter
IF you listen to me, I will take an action
I'll take her
She's not here
You
Come here
How far would you go?
Where's Okayo?
I won't let her back to you
What?
You took her, so I slept with her for revenge
I wanted to make you feel bad
Don't get me wrong
I'm talking right
You bastard!
Bros
Boss
Ina..sorry
Damn it,Akaiwa!
Yoshitaro
Let me go
You are stupid
You can't do anything alone
I will fight with them
Bros
Boss
Reply Akaiwa.
We won't forgive him
We have to fight with them one day
Let's count down, and start
OK
Wait
What are you doing?
Throw away your sword
You're not fair
Do whatever you want.
I'm not afraid to die
But you have to let her go
Hideji
You are man,
just kill me
Cut me in front
Let her go
She's our boss's
Don't go for fighting
Okayo..It can't be helped
I have an idea
You leave from here
I can't do that
Why?
I should have traveled with you 3 years ago
I should have been stronger
Okayo
Ina was killed
If he had lived, he would have taken you with him and left here.
But he was died.
You are still his wife
He died for you,Okayo
Stay stronger from now on,Okayo
Katsuma and Akaiwa are asking for helpers.
They will be fighting soon
You don't need me anymore?
No way, You have to work
As you may know, Yakuza fights are won when the odds are stacked against them.
It's inconvenience or us if they finish soon
I want to have you keep fighting them as long as possible
Both of them got damages, then I will appear
Will it work out?
See how it goes
I replied for sure
Get ready!
Bros, I'm here to help you
Oh you
How much?
Give you
3 ryo?
Thank you very much
Listen, after starting fighting, it's hard to recognize who are you
Put on this tag not to mistake
Don't be alone when you fight
Joshuya is late
After fighting. get gathering at Henchmen inn
She's here
Yoshi
What's wrong?
Don't go
Please
You'll be killed
Yoshi
Oyuki, this is Yakuza rule.
I have to fight for my bros
Let me go
No
Forget about Yakuza rule.
I can't live without you
Yoshi
Women does not understand about my feeling
I have to go
You don't listen to me?
No!
You are stupid
Bros
You'd better not to go
What?
I told you not to go
Why?
You know how she feels?
What are you talking about?
Yoshi
I don't listen to you
Don’t go
I'm going
Boss
Yoshi,You can't go
It's time to go
Hanji has not come yet?
He went to check how Katsuma was...
Not me
Wait
Let's go
Don't leave from here
They will start to fight
Don't run away!
Kill them!
I've escaped
Thanks
What's wrong?
I was surprised
You are so great
Wait
Oh my god
i don't hate you
Dad
Taichi
You bastard!
Boss, Joshuya's boss is..
Joshuya has come?
Thank for coming
I appreciate you
My pleasure
You bastard!
Bros
Oyuki
Yoshi
Don't go
He's stupid
Wait
Joshuya's boss
Toubei was died
I'll manage here from today
Let's deal.
Do you wanna work with us?
What?
I hate scums
Looks like I'm on the right track.
Damn it
Just bring it!
You first
Are you freaking out?
I killed all of scums.
But One is still alive
Look after Okayo
THE END