Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Ojosan / Young Miss (1961)
Excuse me, sir, a little more to the right.
Where's Kasumi?
I have no idea.
I'll find her.
Just call her.
Hey! Kasumi!
This is a company photo, so let's get along and shoot.
Sorry to make you waiting.
We already have a good reputation in the company for our pictures.
We went to the U.S. last year, so they think we're a bright, open, Americanized family.
I'm so happy to be in the sun.
Kasumi is here.
Shall we take the photo?
I'm not much of a photographer.
Why Sawai is not here today?
You like salmon roe?
I like salmon roe.
You know, usually you eat it like this.
I learned a very nice way to eat it the other day.
I see.
My brother has finally become a common husband.
Excuse me, a little more to the right.
Smile a little more.
Ma'am.
Sushi has arrived.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Let's have some sushi and do an interview.
Please.
I have to go out.
From now on?
It's Sunday.
We're all here.
I promised Ochiyo I'd study for the exam with her.
It can't be helped.
I'll be back in time for dinner.
Have a good evening.
I'm impressed about you.
How you can study here.
I might have an arranged marriage.
It's good.
No way.
Why?
You don't have to worry about me?
That's Juliette's line.
The next line is from Juliette.
I don't want to meet a guy I don't know.
It can't be helped.
It's an arranged marriage.
If I want to get married, I want a love marriage.
That's too boring.
It's like a drama.
I read that in a women's magazine.
Marriage for love is the fastest way to a perfect marriage.
There you go again with your superficial knowledge.
You know, when I read that, it hit me.
My mom had an arranged marriage.
My mom demanded a perfect marriage so much that my dad cheated on her and ran away from home.
But I don't think that's all the fault of arranged marriages.
So you're going to get married in an arranged marriage?
Of course I would, if I had the chance.
It's funny, isn't it?
It's like a lottery and dramatic.
I'm bad luck in lottery
You could win third prize at least.
That's why I'm going to do.
I'd like to win third prize at least.
I don't wanna go home.
You're not kid.
We can't go too far.
Let's go to Izu.
They'd be surprised.
I'll buy you some milk.
Maybe we should get some sandwiches.
Look, There are too only lovers on board.
They're going back from Atami or Yugawara.
Shall we really take a trip too?
No way.
If we do that, we'll get caught in the middle of a manhunt!
Come here.
What's wrong?
You know him?
He's Sawai.
He works for this company with our father.
He's one of three guys who often come over to our house on Sundays.
I don't wanna leave.
Don't cry.
People are watching you.
Sawai.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I just saved your trouble.
See you.
Kasumi.
You've been daydreaming again, haven't you?
They left.
They scared me.
People are not always what they seem.
I told you about my birthday party.
He's supposed to be at that party.
If he comes, I'll ask him a lot of questions.
Come on, let's dance!
Don't be shy.
Yes, please.
Oh, and just in case you're wondering.
Are you sure there's no one here you like?
Why?
Did you find anyone nice?
Are you into Sawai?
He's playboy.
I'm kind of curious.
I can't wait to see how he turns out.
He is very serious when he comes to my house.
3rd prize, 2nd prize, 1st prize, maybe
He's coming.
Please dance with me,Kasumi.
Let's dance too.
It's been a year since I left the company.
You've changed a lot, haven't you?
You were the director's secretary.
You look wonderful now.
Are you relieved that the exam is over?
No way,
I don't think schoolwork is very important.
So your goal is to have a family life?
I'm not into that too.
Why?
I'm a sucker for the dramatic.
I'm not interested in a mediocre life.
Dramatic?
That's so you.
Keep dancing.
I bragged that I was having a birthday party for my daughter at a restaurant in Shinbashi.
The madam brought a bottle of champagne.
She said, "Please take it home and give it to everyone!"
My wife will bring it.
That's awesome, isn't it?
Shall I open it?
It's fine, it's been chilled for a while.
Please have fun,
I'll change my clothes.
Enjoy yourself.
He's a good father.
He's talking so loudly, like he's trying to teach us a lesson or something, it's like a company party.
He's very black-hearted.
Cheers.
Serve me.
It tastes good.
I saw you at Tokyo station.
So what?
You are easy to forget.
Could you explain it a little more?
Second clue.
She got off the train on her way home from Atami.
Did you see us?
I thought she had the nerve to get on a crowd.
Oh my god.
I have to admit.
She is a geisha named Beniko.
I don't want to know more than that.
But that dramatic scene was very appealing to me.
Could you be more specific?
But here..
Shall we dance?
You can tell me all the details, but you never know when the director might show up here.
Is it such a secret?
It's a secret. He's a hard man to deal with.
Let's talk about it some other time, some other place.
Sure.
But I'll make you a deal.
What kind?
I'll tell you everything if you keep it a secret from your father.
Ok.
Promise me?
How about Sunday this time?
Okay, I'll take you up on it.
You're a very dignified man, aren't you?
We are also wearing the same color clothes.
How late do you need to be home today?
I can't take my time.
I am planning to go to a concert with a friend and then go home soon.
I feel sorry for your parents because they are so strict.
Are you hungry?
You haven't had lunch yet?
No,
I've been watching a movie.
Where?
I know a good place.
Welcome.
The seats on the second floor are full.
Here's ok.
Make yourself at home.
You're bad boy.
Me?
You went to the second floor with Beniko.
You're pursuing me.
But first, let me ask you something.
Are you a friend of mine or are you a detective?
Which is it?
Let me ask you.
Don't act like that.
I can't tell anything.
If you don't talk to me, I'll tell your father.
Call me Kei-chan.
Then I can call you Kasumi.
Fine.
I give you permission.
So where do I begin with my confession?
First, explain how that day turned out so dramatic.
Well, it wasn't that dramatic.
I'd been in Atami since Saturday, and we'd spent the night together, and we'd finally said goodbye.
And then we comes back to Tokyo Station... and she said  she doesn't want to say goodbye.
I had no choice but to go out to eat with her.
So you're back together again.
No way.
We broke up over dinner.
Really?
Of course I'm sure.
But she was crying.
Yeah.
Are you jealous of me?
I'm not.
I'm talking about the food. .
Yes, it's done.
But how did you come to know the geisha?
Well, I have to tell the story.
When I was a student, I got into a fight in a nightclub.
I ended up getting into a fight with him outside the store.
He had 5 friends and I wanted to run away.
And she showed up.
She took my hand and we were in the car in no time at all.
There was another Geisha and her fat, funny husband in the car.
I like your personality.
Would you like to go to Atami with us?
Ok?
She's into you.
Please go with her
Please come with us.
You also want to be with a woman, right?
But.
You hate me?
I like you.
It was fun.
It's a bit like a melodramatic movie.
You made it up, didn't you?
No way.
Because it's too well done.
That's how it is between a man and a woman.
I've had this experience more times than I can count.
No way.
It's true.
But my current state of mind is that I wanted a girlfriend.
Like you.
You told me there are many women.
There's a difference between a girl and a girlfriend.
I can get a girl in a minute.
I can't trust you.
I'll show it now.
Really?
Are you a student?
Of course I'm a student.
It's okay even if you are a student.
What's the hell?
I'm older than you.
Sorry.
Your attitude is so cute.
Coffee please.
This jacket is very cool.
You think so?
You like me?
You're nice.
Wanna hang out?
Ok.
Where do you want to go?
Let's have a night out.
I really like you.
Do you need something?
You're alone?
Hangout with me
Did you hear something just now?
maybe Kasumi is back.
Actually, the director asked me today if Kasumi marry to Maki.
Maki?
I hear Director's taken a shine to Maki because they're from the same prefecture.
That's good, it was Maki, and I think it's a good idea.
But does she intend to get married?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Sorry I'm late.
How was the concert?
It was fun.
Didn't she wear a kimono?
But she didn't want to wear a kimono.
I see.
Is that baked?
I'm not jealous.
That fish.
This..
what did you do wrong?
Oh...I'm surprised.
That's dirty.
For what?
It's nothing.
You said something.
Sometimes unexplainable wonders happen in the world.
When I went to America, mediumship was all the rage.
Anyway..
Are you still not going to marry for the time being?
I don't care.
Where she's gone?
What do you think about Maki?
He's your candidate of choice?
I'm going to leave it up to you.
But most of all, I want you to have a spiritually happy marriage.
But what do you mean by happy?
Peace.
And quiet love.
It's not being dramatic at all.
It's good.
After all, marriage is a long venture.
If it makes you happy, it doesn't have to be Maki.
But you must promise me this.
If you find a young man you like, I want you to report him to me immediately.
And I will find out who he is.
If he passes, I will bless you all.
OK?
OK.
But now I don't have a man like that.
So please wait.
I don't force you.
I have a phone call from Mrs. Tamura.
She said thank you for coming today.
I haven't met her yet. She's so polite.
Answer the phone.
Hello?
Are you Kasumi?
Hold on.
It's me.
Sorry for the last time.
She's a madam at restaurant.
I asked her to pretend as Tamura's madam.
You're bad.
I'm upset.
Why?
Because you wouldn't believe me, so I got the girl and I showed her to you.
I felt bad for her, so we ate okonomiyaki together.
I'm not asking you that.
After you left, I was seduced by certain men.
Most men think you're too conservative.
Anyway, I'll see you soon.
When you call me at the office, please use the name Tamura to call me.
He's so bad.
They're staring at us.
They're from the food department.
That's disgusting.
They are always talking about calories, vitamins.
They wear a lot of makeup.
I wonder if they're wearing makeup with vitamins.
Let's go there.
So last Sunday was the first of many memorable dates for you.
It wasn't a date.
I was just listening to him.
So it's a date.
You're an idiot.
A date is something that only two people in love do.
You two are in love now.
Why you think so?
They say love begins with a mental strip.
What's that?
Sawai confided in you.
You peeked into his secret parts.
He's just talking on his own.
He wants to peek at his secret parts
You want to peek.
It says in the book that only when a man and a woman develop a taste for stripping from a spiritual to a physical relationship does a man and a woman fall in love.
In a women's magazine?
It's a psychoanalytical book.
Come.
They say that a woman should never reveal her secret parts.
They say you should always wear a mystical veil over your bed, even when you're married.
Is that even in the psychoanalysis book?
This is from a women's magazine.
Don't make fun of me.
That's not why I confided in you.
I'm thinking of turning down his offer.
You're going on a second date already?
He said we'd go skating.
Well, we can't be outdone.
What do you mean?
Actually, you know, this past Sunday was the first date for me and Maki as well, a memorable one.
I'm sorry.
So did you have a mental strip down too?
No at all.
I've been trying to get him to take his clothes off too.
He seems to have developed a sense of shame, and he doesn't want to take off his clothes.
That's a little weird.
Anyway, let's go skating together.
I'll call him and ask him.
Can you come over?
I made you one of my good ones.
What did you make?
Clothes for Skating.
I believe the other day the director spoke to your father....
Didn't your father say something about me?
I heard it.
I'm waiting for your answer.
My father made me promise...
If I like someone, I should tell him right away.
He's a sensible guy.
He's going to investigate before he approves.
He's going to investigate me?
Teach me,Maki.
Ready? 1.2.
I feel scared.
Watch out!
What are you doing?
You are stupid.
You hit her.
What's the hell?
What?
What's wrong?
What is this, a fight?
All right, let's get loud.
Come on!
Please wait over there.
Let's go.
Bring it on!
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
Where are you going?
Oh.
What's wrong?
I only have 50 yen.
My bag was taken by Kasumi...
Please drive as far as you can go for 50 yen.
Please go to Higashi Ginza
I'm home.
Mom, pay for the cab.
Please come in.
Tend to his wounds.
Sorry to interrupt.
Don't worry.
My mom's a little wary of men.
My father is cheating.
is this fine?
She's my mom.
This is Maki.
Nice to meet you.
I've always wanted to meet you.
I have a phone call from Kasumi Fujisawa.
I'll be back in a minute.
Please come in.
I was worried about you.
How come you didn't have any money?
Are you with Maki?
Have fun.
We're just leaving.
I'm trying to think of something to say to Mother, so I'm having Kei-chan come up with an excuse.
Hello, tickets?
I'm just buying the program.
Suppose you were with Ochiyo.
It's like that melodroma you hate.
You know her?
Yes.
Hi.
I'll take you home.
Is she one of the your girls?
Kind of.
She's still looking.
I don't care.
Welcome.
I'll give you some gifts.
Thanks.
Kasumi wouldn't visit you?
She said she was visiting you from college on Saturday.
Maybe we've crossed paths.
She told me she visited you often these days.
No?
Yes she is vising me often.
This pickle... a long, thin cucumber... pickled with sake lees or something...
This is awesome.
What do you wanna talk?
Actually, I'm depressed.
Why?
A woman threatens me if I don't marry her.
Okay, okay.
The woman with the long hair outside the movie theater the other night?
Yes. She's a woman named Asako from a supply store on Miyuki Rd.
I'm tired of it, and she keeps trying to scare me.
You didn't handle her?
Yeah..
That's bad.
Have a seat.
Hey, you don't have to worry.
Women often say they're going to die. It's just a threat.
But she is serious.
Don't think too much.
No one fall in love a man like you.
I feel a little better now.
Don't do that.
We're such weird friends.
Why?
When I see you, I have this habit of confiding in you about everything.
I feel something weird.
Something tells me.
Don't think too much.
We're just normal friend.
But we're lying about something.
Everything you've said has been a lie?
It could be.
You are kind of weird today.
Don't think too much.
I'm going to be weird too.
What are you looking at?
That fountain.
Same here.
You were talking about that woman...
I don't wanna talk about her.
If you want to get away from that woman, there is a way.
You're going to do something.
I feel sorry for her at the time, but it's the best way to give up.
What?
Why don't you just get married?
with someone.
For example, with me.
Oh, my God. I can't believe I'm going to marry you.
You're not kidding, are you?
Okay, let's get married.
I feel weird.
Don't worry.
But..
So you're saying you kissed him twice?
I don't know.
I didn't count it.
So did you do it more?
No.
Anyway, let's get serious.
What did it feel like to kiss him?
I don't know what it felt like.
Did you feel good?
I don't know, but it felt like I was getting hot and my body was evaporating.
Oh my god.
That's good to know,
Then what happened next?
Next?
Talk to me!
I'm going to use it as a reference.
Then what happened next?
Then we went to eat okonomiyaki.
I'm going to make an offer to your father tomorrow.
Don't do that.
Why?
Keep it until you finish college?
I don't care to quit college.
I promised my dad I'd tell him if I ever met someone I liked.
Then do it.
That's where he'll look into it.
Don't scare me.
Really.
What are you going to do?
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
I don't know what to do.
Leave it to me.
Yes.
In exchange, I have a condition.
What?
From now on, you will not hide anything from me, either before or after our marriage.
You all have to confide in each other.
Ok.
Really?
I want to marry you tomorrow.
Even now.
Why you are impressed?
That's pretty good for Kasumi.
But what about that supply store's girl problem?
That's actually what's bothering me.
If our father hears about it, of course he'll say no.
So we're going to have the wedding ceremony as soon as possible.
That's dangerous.
Instead of that, go see that Asako-san and ask her to give up on Kei-chan.
Here it is.
There's a woman here. Is she Asako?
I don't wanna do it.
Why?
I don't wanna meet her.
It can't be helped.
I'm checking her.
Welcome.
Looking for a gift?
For your dad?
No.
For young man.
How about this?
I bought Maki a present.
Was she?
She's nice.I asked her who you were, just in case.
Would you like to meet her?
I don't wanna meet her.
I just called and arranged to meet Kei-chan.
It was good you didn't meet her.
Yeah.
You think so?
You got a better idea that your dad wouldn't have to investigate me?
Cartoonishly good idea.
I haven't got it.
He's giving me a headache.
I leave it to you.
Why don't you have him look into Kei-chan, and maybe He won't find out.
I don't think so.
He often calls our office.
I see.
I won't give my father time to check Kei-chan out.
Well, we'll ask him permission on the spot.
Ok let's get started!
You're too simple.
I went to shopping.
Be more polite.
Didn't Kasumi say something about stopping somewhere today?
Yes, she said she was going to visit her brother.
I see.
To Asamichi.
Hello?
Are you Kasumi?
Welcome.
It's unusual you visit us.
I happened to come here.
Anyway thanks for coming.
Come on in, we have just the cake for you.
You want coffee?
I'll have tea.
I'll heat some water.
I'll answer.
Hello?
Hey, Kasumi. I didn't know you were there.
I knew you'd be there.
I just wanted you to leave early before it gets too late.
Say hello to Akiko.
I guess I was wrong.
Oh you.
What can I do for you?
Sawai is coming here?
I'll get ready..
I agree.
Really?
I knew Sawai well when he worked with me.
I'm sure he's perfect for you.
Thank you, sister.
I was thinking maybe it was.
Why?
I met him at birthday party.
I know exactly what you mean.
So you guys have figured it out by now?
Just me.
Our family don't know about it.
I'm relieved.
Have a eat.
If our family disagrees, will you support us?
Of course I would.
Please.
I'm on your side.
Why he suddenly is coming.
He might be visiting for asking money.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
No way.
Maybe he should ask my husband to play matchmaker.
It would make sense to bring the fiancée along.
He's here.
Please answer.
Welcome back.
Welcome.
Excuse me.
Come in.
Wait in the room.
Serve him a beer.
I wanna kiss you.
Please don't worry.
You're so cute, I could eat you.
You have to be serious.
It's cold, isn't it?
Welcome.
He says he has something important to discuss with me.
Please get out.
What do you mean?
Well...
I'd like to have your daughter.
What are you talking about?
What happened?
He's here to borrow some money.
Serve him another beer.
I see what you mean.
I'll have to discuss these issues with my wife.
Wait a minute, please.
Excuse me.
He's here to borrow some money?
No at all.
I'm sure he'll come back and investigate about you and get back to you.
Don't worry.
But I worry.
You're a jerk.
That doesn't make me feel any safer.
I'll drink this if I have to.
Are you dying?
Don't tell anyone, but it's got sugar in it.
You can't deceive him.
But he's late.
I'll go to see him.
I had my staff check it out, and here's Sawai-kun and Maki-kun's report.
Take a look.
Really?
We have no chance.
I don't have a choice in the matter, and I don't care if it's a act,
I'll take sugar or whatever.
You're such a bad girl.
You never tell me anything.
I'm so glad.
Let's have party.
Prepare the food.
I'll get it.
Kasumi.
Yes.
You have good eyes for men.
Of the three, your father and I trusted Maki the most.
Your father just showed me the report about him.
Sawai is super good.
Keep eye on the food.
His relationships with women are spotless.
And he's got 150000 yen in the bank at such a young age.
The report is so nice.
Here.
Let's have a seat.
It's a nice view.
Is it?
It's too dark for me.
We're such weird friends.
Why?
When I see you, I have this habit of confiding in you about everything.
I feel something weird.
Don't think too much.
But we're lying about something.
You are kind of weird today.
You think so?
I'm going to be weird too.
Maki.
Chieko.
I have to cook Okonomiyaki.
So, what about the wedding?
I don't care if it's tonight or anytime soon.
Don't rush.
Maybe sooner would be better.
I can't wait long.
What about college, you got a year left?
I could quit.
She's proactive.
Have a eat.
Maki has already been living with a woman at a bar in Ginza for a year and and they have continued their de facto marital relationship.
He's a dreadful man.
You'll see me when you're married to her.
I like younger women like you.
I don't like a girl over 20.
I'll never leave from you.
If you marry someone behind my back, I'll kill you or I'll die.
Kei-chan.
Oh you.
Please treat me nice.
You won't wake up.
From now on, don't ever cheat on me.
I know.
You smell good.
How about you take a bath?
And after we eat, we'll go for a walk.
You are naked.
Don't look at me.
Oh Ochiyo?
Good morning.
I thought you were still sleeping.
Because...
Was he nice to you this morning?
Very.
I wasn't afraid of him.
No, I don't know.
No, you don't.
What's wrong?
What did Kei-chan? do to you?
Don't provoke me, it'll make me sad.
I have to go.
I wish you all the best.
Maki?
I'm sorry. Secretary, Maki please.
She killed herself.
She was heartbroken.
She left a suicide note.
She died?
She tried to kill herself.
I was relieved
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Sawai.
She was heartbroken.
I know what it's like to die of rejection.
I want to die, too.
I was just kidding.
That's what I thought at the time.
Is she your wife?
Congratulations.
I came here by chance.
What a coincidence.
Come here,dad.
See you.
What happened to you?
I thought she was Asako.
You don't have to worry about that.
Look at the Beniko.
She is fine.
Yeah.
Promise me you won't worry about that anymore.
You're gonna be late.
Oshiyo, How are you?
I'm fine.
I'm very busy.
Oh, of course I'm having fun.
How much one of your eggs?
Egg?
Just a minute.
Mom, how much is one egg around here?
Egg?
How much is one egg around here?
about 14 yen.
13yen.
It's 13yen.
Thirteen yen?
Wow, that's expensive!
I found a store that sells four for 50 yen
I go there every day!
Why so many eggs?
Okay, I get it.
You're newlyweds, so you drink every day?
I use eggs in many ways. Boil them, fry them...
He has a lot of ingredients these days, so I'm trying to feed him nutritious food.
Excuse me.
How is Kasumi?
She's fine.
Would you like to have a party with us this Christmas?
That's good.
Try talking to her about it.
I think she'll be happy.
Sorry to bother you.
Salt and pepper to taste.
He came back too early.
Welcome back.
Kei-chan is not here?
Who are you?
Tell him I am Asako.
I'll wait for him.
They say a thief is more than a victim in that he's full of fear.
I must stay strong.
I'll turn on the stove.Take off your coat.
Please, read this.
You got married last month?
You don't have to answer if you don't want to.
You did nothing wrong.
Where are you going?
I'll go get the laundry.
I'll have to ask you for the permission?
Welcome back.
Why did you let her in the house?
She forced her way into the house.
I'm going to make pork stew tonight, so please let me know after you talk to her.
Why did you come?
I wanted to make sure.
I was in shock.
I couldn't sleep.
I'm sorry.
You're a coward.
You should have gotten married after you told me.
You threatened me with death.
You bastard!
What do you want me to do?
What are you looking at?
There's nothing to be done.
I had a glimmer of hope before I came here.
I feel better now that I'm here.
And now that I've met you...
Are you leaving?
I'm sorry to bother you.
See you.
I'm going back through that door.
She's in danger.
Close the door.
I'm sorry to bother you.
You should send her.
You're right.
Don't worry.
I've had enough of your pretense of kindness.
Don't say that.
I'll be alright.
I'll go home alone. I'll live on my own.
But.
If you come, I'll scream on the stairs.
I'll scream your name out loud.
Is she ok?
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Don't say that.
Let's eat early.
Are you starving?
I don't feel like eating right now.
You are too weak.
What's this?
Your sister brought me a Christmas present from the office today.
This is for you.
What's that?
This is awesome.
I wonder what she'll do now.
That's what I was just thinking about.
Maybe I should have sent her home after all.
She's in danger.
I should've just grabbed her and taken her to the hospital.
But she's not sick.
So, the police?
I wonder if the police will give her protection.
Does she have any relatives?
And it's none of my business.
What should we do...
I feel worry.
Do you have any ideas?
Excuse me.
You really look like a wife.
we have been waiting for you for a long time.
There's so much to talk about !
But I'll start with Kasumi's story.
Why did you call me?
I'll tell you later.
As a matter of fact, Asako was at our home the other day.
She finally showed up.
But I'm glad it didn't become a big problem.
Not really.
I get nervous every morning when I read the paper.
Why?
I wonder why there's an article about Asako's suicide.
You think too much.
I want to hear your story.
It's Christmas Eve tonight.
I'm thinking of having an all-nighter with Maki.
all-nighter?
I'm really into him.
What do you mean?
You can't sleep with him.
It's ok.
That's bad.
Why?
Actually. I never told you this, but...
Don't be offended.
Maki's been living with a woman for about a year.
That's a lie.
It's true.
The detective took full responsibility for the report
You're a big talker, aren't you?
What right do you have to investigate Maki?
Don't get me wrong.
It's none of your business.
If you have time to check on Maki-san, why don't you keep a closer eye on your own precious husband?
What's wrong with Kei-chan?
I'm appalled.
When did Kasumi become such an idiot?
That Asako didn't know about your marriage until recently.
That's because Kei-chan acted like he was single.
And the reason she didn't kill herself after you yelled at her...
Kei-chan talked her into getting back together with you.
I don't think he would do that.
You think so?
Yeah.
He has come home every day since we got married.
How stupid can you be?
The other day Kasumi called and said he's been working late.
Lately, lunchtime affairs are all the rage among office workers.
You make him eat eggs every day and you feel stupid.
Maki said your sister was very close to Kei-chan when she was single.
You two are a man and a woman, so be careful.
You never know, you might have enemies among your own people.
You want some?
No thanks.
Just one cup.
That's enough.
You want some?
You are very black-hearted.
I won't be fooled.
I think it's strange to have a party outside on Christmas Eve.
In America, Christmas Eve is a family affair.
Please give me more wine.
It's fine to celebrate at home. But if you drink too much, you won't get anywhere.
I have to go.
Take that.
One for Kasumi.
For Kasumi, too?
Because I'm really sorry to Kasumi for doing this.
Won't you dance?
Let's dance.
I don't want.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
I'm not.
Anyway, let's play a record.
I don't like it without music.
Akiko, put on a record.
I have a record in my room.
Please think about it seriously.
I don't know why he laughed.
I don't like the idea of he laughing at hisself.
I'm sure he's just trying to impress some other girl when I'm not looking.
I'm off.
I knew it. You misunderstood me, didn't you?
Misunderstood what?
Your sis worried about you.
She said you were suspicious of us.
I told her that's not true.
And she says, "You can't be so optimistic.
She said, "You've got to really think about it.
And then you come down the stairs... and you put on a record.
Were you crying?
You'll be late.
Okay, bye.
I'm off.
Excuse me.
This is the candy I forgot to give you last night.
You scared me.
Come in.
I was told not to talk to you long.
I get it.
Your husband has been coming home late lately.
Why?
There are rumors that he has an affair with a woman at the bar.
Is that true?
Oops..
But I thought I'd better warn you.
I'm leaving.
Don't you dare tell your mother what you just said.
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
That's what I thought.
There's a phone call for you.
Thank you very much.
Kasumi? It's me.
I'm going to be home a little late today.
You said you'd be home early.
Why?
Because I have to take care of something.
What errands? It's not for the company, is it?
What kind of errands?
It's none of your business.
Ok I get it...
Who?
It's me.
KASUMI
Come in.
I just thought I'd stop by.
Going on a trip or something?
Yes, with Chieko.
So Keiichi will be lonely.
I'm currently working on this, so please wait a moment.
I think he'd be happier without me.
Am I intruding?
Why?
But you keep looking at your watch.
No, it's time for the stock market broadcast.
I bought my first stock yesterday.
I thought it might go down.
I see.
You have something to worry about?
That's what I thought.
I knew you were crying last night.
I was worried about you.
I was doubting your relationship.
I knew it.
It was hard for me.  Because I like you.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad we got it all straightened out.
You know what?
Kei-chan seems to be having an affair with someone.
with who?
With a bar girl.
Your bros saw them.
Your bros said that last night?
I can't believe it.
What did your brother say about her?
He said he sometimes saw them together at a bar in Ginza these days.
What bar?
I didn't ask that much.
What's she like?
I heard she had long hair.
She must be Asako.
Is she tall and thin?
Yes.
Your brother said so too?
No..
So you saw her?
Yes.
When?
Where?
I only saw them together in Ginza 10 days ago.
That's what I thought.
Asako's turned to be bar girl.
Please don't hate me.
I never thought I'd be able to live with you for so long.
I played a strange role this time.
I think you are lucky to have a friend like Sawai.
Thank you very much.
I was sorry.
Never mind.
I told you I didn't care.
Welcome.
Ms. Asako, who used to work here, where is she working now?
She's  still working here.
Asako, you have a guest.
Oh Sawai's wife.
Are you going on a trip?
I have something to say to you.
I'm just about to go home too.
Let's have a coffee.
Hold on.
I did meet your husband 10 days ago.
We came to this coffee shop after work.
I had something to consult with him
What do you want to consult with me?
I'm thinking of getting married.
With who?
Mr. Kawakami, an architectural engineer.
He didn't get married until he was 35 because he was busy working on the dam.
He is a regular customer of my shop.
It's been 3 months since I met him.
At first I was dating him because I was lonely.
I went to your apartment the other day,right?
At that moment I felt you were no longer my concern.
After that, I started to understand Kawakami's charm.
So I decided to restart.
I'm thinking of telling him everything about you before I respond with his proposal.
About me?
I don't care but...
I think you should not tell him.
That's a common response.
But I don't think it should be hidden.
I want him to know my true feelings.
I know how you feel but..
What do you think?
I think you should not tell him...
I have no idea.
I have to reply to him soon.
It's too sudden.
I was very confused and decided to talk to you.
What do you think?
Oh my god..
Oh.
I couldn't wait for you to reply.
He’s My male friend,Sawai.
I'm Kawakami.
Nice to meet you.
I'm leaving.
Please stay here.
But I'm on the way working.
See you.
He looks nice.
I want to tell you something before I reply to you.
What?
About my past.
Hold on.
I think you should not tell me...
I'm not going to marry your past.
I'm going to marry you from now on.
You don't need to tell me about your past, and I don't need to listen.
I want to hear your reply about marriage.
Kawakami...
Oh I see.
He's so nice.
Yes he is.
He is the most wonderful man in the world.
What's wrong?
Do you think this bag is a travel bag?
I left the letter and left the house.
It seems Kei is having an affair with someone.
With whom?
A bar girl.
I thought that woman was you.
I heard that the woman has long hair.
I thought I'd give him to you.
No way.
Kei-chan is nice.
I don't think your husband would ever cheat under any circumstances.
He really loves you.
Don't doubt him and go home quickly.
There were 2 people who saw them.
At Ginza and bar.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to meet you on Christmas Eve because I was busy.
I heard that you live with a woman.
Really?
I’m sorry.
Just as it was written in a women's magazine.
A woman can only love one man, but a man can love many women.
A man can only love one woman too.
You are lair.
At least I am.
I was thinking of breaking up with my girlfriend and proposing to you.
Don't make any more excuses
You want to have an affair during your lunch break, right?
What do you mean?
This is written.
In a women's magazine?
In a weekly magazine
Do you believe everything you read in magazines?
I believe it.
Kei might be cheating too.
No way,
Sawai is good man.
He's pretending to be my girl's lover right now for me.
He also lent me money.
Really?
Sawai told me to make you happy.
Oh my god.
This is all the fault of the women's magazines and the weeklies.
What's wrong?
I have to go apologize to her right away.
Come with me.
I have to apologize you.
Dear Keiichi,
I'm going on a trip so don't look for me. Kasumi.
Hello?
Oh Keiichi?
That's what I thought.
Actually..
She's an idiot.
What should I do if she commits suicide?
No way.
I'll call my dad and tell him about it.
I'll be there soon.
Stay strong.
Kasumi.
why couldn't you believe me?
Get your hands off of me!
why did you doubt me?
There are many reasons.
You withdrew 100,000 yen.
I lent the money to Maki.
Why did you smile when you looked in the mirror this morning?
Did I smile when I looked in the mirror this morning?
you were laughing.
I don't remember about that.
Ouch.
It's true that I lent Maki 100,000 yen.
He wanted to marry Chieko, so he gave her to her as alimony.
He had a girlfriend who lived with him.
What I didn't tell you about it.
I thought you would tell Chieko-san.
I met Maki and Ochiyo.
I've heard a lot about you too.
You're nice man.
What's the hell?
I want to live a quiet and peaceful life.
Really?
Yes for sure.
You are a very ordinary woman.
Yes I am.
I don't wanna stay in the corner.
Oh my god.
Oh.
You guys too?
Congratulations.
THE END