Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Naked Ambition / Onna Gokuakucho (1970)
Come with me!
It's urgent business!
What's wrong?
You are too noisy
Someone snuck into the mansion at dawn and murdered OKugata.
What?
Okugata is safe?
She's just got little injury
That's good to hear
Please go back to your house
It seems Okugata is safe
Yes
I will kill her later
Security at their homes will be tight.
I have another plan
I worry she gives birth male baby
We should kill her before she gives birth.
Sure
My boyfriend,Isogai is waiting in the yard
I can finally meet your lover
Yes
I hear he is as handsome as an actor.
What if I fall in love with him?
I'm just kidding.
He's your lover
Isogai, She's Oheya
I'm here to see you
We got ready a room for you
We will hire you if you work hard
Put your face up
You're handsome
Are you coming in?
I'm Rokusuke from Chugengashira
I'm Isogai from Kamiyashiki
Nice to meet you
You are from Kamiyashiki
I know you would say I was left behind.
Kind of
KAMIYASHIKI is the front of the Daimyo
Here is the opposite of it
There's Okugata at Kamiyashiki
Here's his mistress house
But there might be chance for your promotion
You're still young.
You should get along with them
You are too thin.
You are unreliable.
You are overreacting.
I cherish these relationships.
I will never forget what you have done for me.
Let's work together
Then you can get married with him
Thanks
He's 10 years younger than you.
How did you get him?
Are you prepared for hardship in the future?
I put my life on the line for this love.
It can't be helped.
You are over 30 years old. and this is your first love
hell or high paradise
Teruchiyo
Welcome
That one is beautiful, isn't it?
I'm glad you are a boy.
He's cute
he is a tool for women's advancement.
Let's take advantage of this child.
Look at that
Person called Matajuro Akaza is here to meet you
Even though you couldn't kill her, you have the courage to come to this house again.
I'll try to kill her again
do you do it the same way?
There is also the possibility
You should be honest.
You want money,right?
it's natural to get money
I won't forgive your mistakes
Being women are good
The people who lived in Fukagawa Yagurashita lived in a large mansion like this.
I would be happy if you could give me a lot of rewards
I have added you to my group.
But if you were killed in the upper mansion, you wouldn't be here now.
your life ends here
give me money for hush money
keep your mouth shut
SHINDO's OGIN was originally a geisha from Fukagawa
Before that, she is a prostitute of YAGURASHITA
He seduced the master of the Shindo family.
She tried to kill his wife for the sake of his child's career
I will speak your secrets to everyone
To where
To whom?
you're begging for money like a beggar
Who can trust what you say
do you think I have no proof?
I have to go
Hold on
You'll be honest?
I'm not so useless that women worry about me
I murdered him for the crime of breaking into this house with the aim of killing your life.
You made it
I paid you a lot
I just took some money
I made you feel so good
I'll go to bathroom,Umeno
I have a plan
Sure
Let's Add gentaku hosoi to our group
That doctor?
I’ll get the poison from him
let's give it to someone and use that poison to kill her
What do you think about this?
Thanks for coming.
It's been a while
What can I do for you?
Today you will receive a request from OYAYA
I gave him the order firmly
I think it's good that there are many members
But I'm worried about GENTAKU's ability to do its job properly.
You really think so?
Better to murder the man who tried to kill her who went to the upper house.
I've already killed him
That's good for us
Please relax.
I will have Gentaku wait in another room if he comes
Yes please
You're late
We can have fun tomorrow
I won't let you go home tonight
I worry about Gentaku who are good at flirting
Are you jealous?
You are so play boy
You too
I gave my wife to the Daimyo because I have a bad temper
Do you regret?
You and me and Teruchiyo get together later
Control Okugata and Lord
After that I will be Teruchiyo guardian
I will take over this house
I hope it will happen soon
The only person who knows about our relationship is that doctor named Gentaku.
I don't know your relationship with that doctor.
You are cheeky
Oheya let gentaku wait
So are you ready?
I'll leave
I see
Please visit me tomorrow night
I had a guest.
Come in
Let's relax and talk tonight
we are old friends.
Don't hesitate.
It's wasteful
Did you read the letter I gave Umeno?
Yes I did
So I'm here to see you
I'm always bringing with it
How about the item I asked?
it is currently being arranged
Please wait for a while
Gentaku
I'm sorry
We're in bad mood.
Let's have a drink together
It's been a long time since I've had a drink with you
You were still young then
I haven't changed but you have changed so much
You are much prettier than before and I am very impressed.
Unlike before, you have so much dignity.
I am very happy that you praised me
GOKARO-san's kindness I think you'd like to forget
Yukie?
I don't want to think about him
you have a relationship with him
I know everything about you and him
I see.
You might be right
I was threatened by him that I would inform him of my secret.
I can't help but I had a little relationship with him
How did Makoto etc know about your relationship with GOKARO?
Whose child do you think Teruchiyo is?
He's not lord's son
I was wondering about that
He's Gokaro's son
You're free to think about
he thinks TERUCHIYO is his son.
He wants to use the son in the future to raise his position.
he gave me a good position
To be honest, Teruchiyo is your son
No way
Only you know whose child TERUCHIYO is
I am not cynical like you.
Let's kill GOKARO as soon as possible and be happy together, the two of us.
I appreciate what you said
he can't live long.
you try the effect of that poison
I get it.
I'm looking forward what happens
I will definitely give the poison you ask for
Are you sure?
Yes
I'm glad
this poison is very effective
If you drink this poison once, your body will become paralyzed and you will die immediately.
Let's kill GOKARO's YUKIE with this potion
I'll take this
Hold on
I was going to give this to you, but it's my duty to kill him.
I'll give you 1 package
I'll give you again if you need
I'll keep 2 packages
This is your reward
Oheya
no..Ogin
I want something more than money.
What do you want?
You don't need me to tell you that.
You have to please me
what are you talking about?
Don't pretend you don't know
Gentaku
you'd better take it easy
I know your secret, so let's come to the bottom of hell together.
It can't be helped
Do whatever you want
Ogin
I have never forgotten your body
Treat me nicely
You have a nice figure
All men excites about your body
You're using your body as a weapon to seduce men
The lord spends nights with you every day, so he won't live long.
Ogin
I thought we were always doing something like this
I remember those days
I'll make you feel good
I heard the news
you are very suspicious
I get to know what you think
Whose child is Teruchiyo?
you tried to poison me
I was going to be deceived by you too
I worried a lot
I'm happy
Hold me tight
I am here because of you.
let's work hard together
you can't even make a career out of it
I am still of low status.
I don't care about your statues.
I am very happy if you are here
I will go to a senior position in the future
let's work hard together
I worry about our age deference
I'm too old for you
Please keep silent
Oyoi
I have no money for you to gamble
You don't have to come here to gamble from Kamiyashiki
Please
Welcome
I'm counting on you
I'll do my best
we got the poison
who should put the poison?
I have an idea.
There's a person called Chinsai Gokubouzu
He's Coward
I'm not counting on him
I think it's convenient because he is loved by everyone
Let's threaten him with a knife.
Do you think that will solve the problem?
I think you should try to intimidate him so you can control him.
If we feel risk
We should kill her otherwise they will kill you
I feel scary
I don't wanna die
Brother
We should tell to Okugata what Oheya plans
But..
We should deal with him
We ask him for money
What the hell you are saying
We can be rich
We might be killed before that
You are chicken
You always ask me for money
You really do it?
Yes I do
You have risen in the world, but you should learn more about geisha.
Do you ignore us?
Go back to lower house
Don't frustrate so much
Because
You should have told them you were going to get back at them.
Your life is just beginning.
Actually,Lord is interesting in you
Me?
You'll be promoted
Really?
Yeah
I can promote myself
And my reputation will be on the line.
Am I your tool for your promotion?
I might be your tool
I see.
I will take a revenge to them
But be careful. lord might know who you were before
From now on, we can carry on our relation
Look at this,Teruchiyo
Teruchiyo
I tell you
Hachiro Sugauma and Ujiie are here to see you
Jodai ask me to do that?
Lord
I don't wanna hear from you
I'm sorry but we should take care of Jodai
Jodai is more important than I?
I'm sorry
If you continue this behavior, we will have no more patience.
What the hell?
You are killing innocents every day.
Are you making fun of me?
Get out!
We hope you understand
Anyone here?
Lord
Lord,calm down
Oheya and us are worried about you
Shut up!
Are they not working now?
Please do not hit them
If you settle with them, JODAI complains.
and they don't worry about die
Bring Sake
Are you trying to settle with me?
I am making calculations and taking action.
I hear you have some weapon
Even vassals change their positions in various ways.
Lord is too moody.
It's hard to calculation and taking action.
I know.
We need to get Lord into retirement as soon as possible.
Or we might get problem
We may be destroyed.
We are nothing if we perish.
We'll hold out until the next generation.
We work according to JODAI
I hope that lord will give in to our threats and become more mature.
The future heir has already been chosen.
Generation after generation, Lord's life will not be long
Hold on
Do it right away
You appeal to them
You can do it yourself
That's your duty
You get money from him
Do it right away
I'll be killed
You say same again
You do or don't?
Hold on
You're man
We can start business after you get money
I don't wanna die
Chinsai
Traitor goes like this.
see how your sister dies
You escaped
Why you visit me again!
I'm sorry but We need to ask you a favor
Tell me
she's trying to kill you with poison
we would like to dispose of Oheya
What?
You kill us or you protect her
Please choose
You are too rude
Please listen to us
Shut up
If you want to kill me, kill me anytime
I’m not afraid to die
I am not afraid to die, but I am afraid for lord because of my relationship with my lord.
you are using him
Bring her
I feel sorry about you
They want to kill me so we have to kill them quickly
Use Chinsai
I didn't try to tell her secret
We have to kill you
Sorry
Help me
Stay down
hold on
It can't be helped
I'll do anything please don't kill me
We're not counting on you
You're useless
Don't get me wrong.
I'll do my best
it's better than being killed
I'll do anything please don't kill me
please
What do you think?
Well
Okugara likes him.
so we can use him
You think so?
Rusty scissors can be cut depending on how you use them
So we can use him in any way
It's better to kill him,Umeno
Kill Okugata or you'll be killed.
Which one?
I want to go for a long time, even one or two days
I'll definitely kill Okugata
Use this
Thanks
I will never forget your kindness
Cut it out!
Don't get carried away
Stop it
They are arguing about Oheya's life
are you going to commit suicide after that
are you ready for that?
If you're a suicide corpse, we'll prepare for it
I'm not going to sell you flattery
It's not your business
Get your hands off
Excuse me
I understand your situation
I really want to fight with them
What's your name?
I'm Isogai
He's still boy.
Ok fight with them
Kid, I'll kill you
He lost!
You're interesting.
Let's have a drink
Come here
Take this
Hey
Umeno
Yes
I heard you are good at using swords
Fight with him
But Oheya...
This is my order
Iyori
I won't
Sorry
Please forgive me
You must fight
Let's fight
Are you sure?
You're nasty man
start now.
Everyone is looking forward to it!
kill that woman,Iyori
I'll tell everything
Iyori
It worked well
Umeno wanna be your wife
I really feel bad for her
she was very persistent for her career
I was frustrated about her
Please treat me nice,Iyori
Ogin
Lord!
It's urgent business
What's wrong?
Okugata at the Kamiyashiki died
What?
he was poisoned and vomited blood to death
Who did it?
We don't know but Chinsai has run away
Chinsai?
Please go there
Damn it!!!!
That coward Chinsai did good job
In the upper house, he must have slipped the poison in there, bypassing GOKARO's surveillance.
Chinsai's role is over.
I hope Gokaro caught and kill him
Gokato is just left
How shall we kill him?
you don't hate him,right?
he used me to raise his status
he sold me
I have no regrets against him
If you say so
You are still young but good at teasing women
Gokaro is useless comparing with you
He's stingy and useless
I'll kill you
I had a feeling about it.
That's what I thought
I mist kill you
Then I use Teruchiyo to control Shundo house
Help me!
Forgive me!
If you kill me, you will be killed
What?
What do you plan?
If I do not return within three days, they will receive a letter containing your secret.
You made a good idea
I don't wanna die
We have no choice but to add him to our group
Thank you very much
Chinsai
If I do not return within three days,
Thank you very much
You've all been cheating on me.
I was watching you guys
So what?
what?
life has hell and paradise
Damn it.
Kill him
Kill him!
Iyori
Gokaro yukie disobeyed your orders
He confronted the lord, ready to be punished, and they died in combat.
I think that would be a problem if the higher-ups found out about it.
I think they will punish us
Think hard about what happened
don't tell anyone about what happened
There is no choice but to make TERUCHIYO the lord as the successor to the Shundo family.
TERUCHIYO
You made Tatami dirty
I'll clean up
Let's play outside
TERUCHIYO
Iyori
You got your hopes up.
I used Teruchiyo to control this house
Can I ask who is his dad?
Do you think you are his dad?
I'm not?
I don't even know who is it
You tried to kill me too
Iyori
Don't get me wrong
Oheya
I tell you
Okugata is alive
It's not true that Chinsai put poison at him
You are loser
I feel scary
I was saved.
They all have their desires.
Life is the most important thing.I'm the winner
THE END