Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
It was a fall when I was sixteen years old.
I saw the sign of a late woman in the fall of my sixteenth year, and shortly afterwards I was suddenly blinded by an illness.
My parents left me early and I was left on my own.
For a while, I thought I was going crazy with sadness and despair.
But then I changed my mind and practiced, and it was worth it.
Soon after, I began working as a masseuse on the downstream floor of Yotsuya Tsunokami.
But there were those who made fun of me and misbehaved because I am a woman.
I sometimes feel deeply saddened.
Why are men like this?
No matter how blind I am, it's still a terrible thing to do
Onna Mekura Monogatari / The Story of a Blind Woman (1965)
Be careful.
Here it is.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Up there, in the waiting area.
Come with me.
I'll give you my hands.
Thank you.
That's a cold wind.
It must be hard to be at work now, isn't it?
But I'm used to it.
I'll leave here.
Thank you very much for your kindness.
I'll visit here too.
Oh really?
Please take care of it.
Thank you very much.
Come here and take some rests.
The guy who just came here.
Is he our regular customer?
Why?
He saved me from falling down a stone staircase.
He was very kind.
He is Kigoshi.
He sometime visits us.
Kigoshi?
What's wrong?
You're red all the way up to your ears.
It's a frostbite.
Two dishes please.
Go to see Momiji.
I get it.
They are drinking so be careful.
Momiji?
Hara is here?
Yes.
He's bad customer...
Where's masseuse?
I'm sorry. Please help me.
She's blind.
Oops, excuse me.
Where's her?
You are saved.
Sorry.
Thank you very much for your help.
You're a beauty.
You're too good for a girl from around here.
Excuse me.
He's too drunk.
Can you help us?
Can you take her to me?
I'll get just one drink and go home.
Thank you very much.
Ok, tsuru?
Yes.
Are you called Tsuru?
She's great worker..
She can handle all of our customers.
So please.
Yes.
Do you know what work I do?
I have no idea.
Are you sales man?
Why?
Because you smell good.
That's true.
It's cold, isn't it?
Let's have drink.
I can't drink at all.
Why don't you call some Geisha girls?
It's ok if I leave.
Don't worry.
Kikuchi always take care of you?
When I was a kid, we were neighbors.
Whenever I get stressed out, I come here.
You look a little sad, don't you?
Why?
There's a pause for a drink.
I get it.
It's like you know what's going on in my mind.
No way.
I'm lost in a lot of things right now.
If you know,just tell me.
You're leaving a woman, aren't you?
That's why you're lonely.
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
Why you think so?
Your ring, which was there when you pulled me off the stone steps, was gone when you covered for me earlier.
I didn't want to see the ring, so I took it off.
I'm thinking of getting divorced.
When business goes bad, everything falls apart.
Life is like building blocks.
That day, my wife and I had a fight over a trivial matter.
I thought I'd expand my business to hold her down, and that's when I made a mistake.
Not caring about people can actually make or break you for the rest of your life.
You'd better watch out because you're young.
I will.
Sorry to complain about this.
If you are here, could you call me again?
Why?
Your story is very intimate.
I don't feel like you are a customer.
I was hoping you could tell me more.
I don't feel like you are massagist.
I'll ask you to come.
I'm glad to know you.
Please.
But if I see a beautiful person like you often...
I might fall in love with you.
Shall I massage you?
Please.
I couldn't help but shiver as I rubbed his shoulders tonight.
When he held me to get rid of a drunken man
I think it must have been because I felt the man before I felt the customer.
He told me that one moment can change a person's whole life.
What happened tonight will have a profound effect on me for the rest of my life.
What's your name?
I'm Itoko Yamaguchi.
How long have you been working this job?
3 years.
You can rub my shoulder.
I have to take a test?
I have 3 years experiences.
3 years experiences are not enough.
But I've never rubbed the shoulders of someone as famous as you.
I'm horned.
Are you blind?
Yes.
Why you wear sun glass?
How you know?
I know you just sticked out your tongue.
Put more pressure on your thumb.
Like this?
You've got the body of a 20-something.
I feel hard to massage you.
Have some noodles?
No.
I'm hungry.
I'll have it.
That's enough.
Thanks.
We can't hire you.
Why not?
Your skills are not good enough.
I've been working a lot of places.
I know you worry about her skills but please consider some more.
We don't have enough workers.
I think we can hire her.
She can't massage well.
She came here all the way.
You're serious about your training, aren't you?
I've never screwed up before.
I think we can hire her.
Would you take money for such a skill?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Was it cold?
He was a very nice customer, and I got a nice tip.
Here it is.
Thanks.
I'm Itoko.
I'll work here from today.
I'm Tsuruko.
Nice to meet you.
I'm going to make a lot of money.
Why don't you sit down and eat?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Take some rests.
Good night.
Tsuruko.
You seem awfully excited.
Your footsteps are different. Did something happen?
It's nothing.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
have some noodles.
I don't want.
I've just been treating a client to cake.
That's nice of you,
My clients asked me too much to massage.
And told me to discount 100 yen.
Let's go to bed.
Good night.
Keep reading.
OK.
I did receive the 2,000 yen.
Thank you.
I'm so grateful for Hisae's monthly contribution to my school fund.
I'm very motivated!
I will ask for your help again next month.
Please take care of yourself for me.
Good bye!
Are you ok with her?
You seem to be his ATM.
You're rude.
He's nice man.
He was so kind to me last day.
I can't say about it anymore.
You lost your virgin?
Good night.
I wanna see him.
Don't make your voice sound so irresistible.
What is this all about?
I have heard and done many lewd things in the past, but nothing has ever aroused my interest in such things.
But tonight, I can't help but feel dreamy and enchanted all over my body.
I had given up on being human, but perhaps the flames of love have been kindled in me.
Is this what a woman's heart is like?
Good morning.
Wake up.
Come on, you, get up.
Get ready!
I'm surprised.
This family uses their apprentice as a maid.
They like to do it.
I see.
Come on, help me out.
I don't want to get my hands dirty.
She's cheeky.
I don't feel like working with her.
Would you like to go to the department store with me today?
I'm going to the salon.
You're out of your mind.
You've been so nervous all morning.
No..stop it.
I feel ticklish.
This is our way.
Remember this.
You're mean.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Vegetables are so expensive these days.
I had my head done.
Do you think it looks good?
It's nice.
Madam.
I am..
You're weird.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
I'm having teacher teach me about pressure points right now.
He's so great.
You have to study up and get some clients.
You work hard.
Teacher gave compliment to you.
Why you are upset?
I have no idea.
She became a cook's maid and went to a lot of trouble to get him to where he is today.
So what?
I thought you should know.
It's none of my business.
Itoko
You look scared.
Why don't you find someone else?
Then you won't look so scared.
But you're blind, so you can't see the face of the one you care about.
I've been dying to meet him every day since then.
If I weren't blind, I would have gone to see him or asked him to come to me.
But I can't.
The sadness of waiting patiently for the call to come.
You have to be a masseuse to understand this pain.
I miss him.
I want him to say a word to Tsuru-chan.
What are you doing?
Stop being so jealous!
You're old enough...
You're old enough.
Because of Itoko,Shigeo left here.
You are stupid.
SHIGEO resigned because Yae left.
He says if you kick Itoko out , he'll come back.
I don't accept him.
I have pride now.
You are stupid.
I know what you and her do here every day.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
It's late, so go to sleep.
Okay, I'll see you later, good night.
Tsuru！
Do you know a man called Mr. Kigoshi?
Mr. Kigoshi?
He called earlier and said he's at kohana.
It's been an hour already.
I've got ITOKO going instead.
Itoko?
Kohana-san?
I wonder if Kigoshi-san's there...
Me?
I am...
Tsuruko.
Tonight's guest is very handsome.
He was disappointed you didn't show up.
Treat me Ramen.
I'll eat.
Was he alone?
Yes.
Did you massage him?
Just back,not legs.
He said he needed you.
Stupid.
Won't you eat?
I don't want.
Let me eat this.
Did you notice anything unusual about him?
Nothing at all.
I was thinking about seducing him, but he always talked about you.
What he said?
You love him?
Don't talk to me like that.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
It's a gold badge.
I found it on the floor.
Kigoshi's?
It could be.
You know, our teacher told you never to touch a customer's goods
He didn't tell me not to pick it up.
please return this.
It's none of your business.
I'm sure he's looking for it.
please return this.
Give me 500 yen.
You can buy it and do whatever you want with it.
Thank you.
Take care.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, is Kigoshi-san here?
He's just leaving.
Excuse me.
Massagist.
What's wrong?
I have a favor to ask your sister Kikuchi.
Sis.
Oh you.
Can I help you?
I heard you have been friends with a Mr. Kigoshi since childhood.
Is that true?
Nihonbashi's.
What's wrong with him?
I'm sorry, but could you please call them and ask when they will be here next time?
Please make the call yourself.
But I'm a Massagist.
I don't want the company to know.
They don't care if you're a masseuse or a maid.
You know what?
Really?
Masseuses these days are very proactive.
They are whore.
Don't say bullshit.
Excuse me.
Hold on.
I'll call him.
Thank you very much.
Come in.
I'm sorry.
I said a lot of things.
No, of course not.
I'll just ask when he's coming next time.?
I have something for him.
Hello? Mr. President is there?
He's there.
Hello, this is Kikuchi.
You've been busy for a while.
No, it's not that.
There's someone who wants to see you today.
She wants to know when you'll be here.
He wants to talk with you.
Hello?
This is Tsuruko.
Are you coming tonight?
Really?
Are you sure you don't want to leave?
If I leave, I'll have to go to work, so I'll just wait here.
He's late, he said he'd call you here.
What's wrong with Tsuruko?
She also feels frustrated with Itoko.
Toyoko also said she wanted to quit here.
Don't get angry
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Don't read my magazines without asking.
This isn't funny at all.
Please don't throw this at me.
Chihaya needs you.
Itoko, go there.
You out too?
I'm going to Kojimachi for treatment.
Could you pick up a car for me on the street?
Get my the bag.
You're blind.
We have a bad reputation because of her.
No wonder you're so mad, Mom.
Okay, I'm definitely quitting.
I'm going to go take a bath, please.
Please.
Hello?
I'm sorry, no one is available.
Then I waited for a long time.
But at last he didn't call me back.
Perhaps I am selfishly imagining his feelings and worrying about them on my own.
Itoko ran away from here with her luggage.
Did you really go to Kojimachi for treatment?
If you have any doubts, please call them.
I guess you're going to live with her without telling me.
Don't say bullshit.
Itoko stole 50,000 yen?
It's our reputation on the line.
Can we assume that she stole from the guests while he's sleeping and then returned here to retrieve her belongings?
I'm sorry.
Can you come to police?
I'll reimburse you for the money, and we'll call it a settlement.
Soon after a hard winter at work, spring has come
But not only did I never see him again, he never called me back.
Rumor had it that his company was going under and might go out of business.
I was blind and there was nothing I could do about it.
I started saving money so that I could heal my eyes and have her as a normal woman for even one day.
If I open my eyes, will he tell me I'm still beautiful?
Will he be kinder to me than before?
Tsuru?
Oh Kigoshi?
Why you are here?
I'm here with everyone at the annual consolation party.
What a incident.
Let's go there.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Where are you staying?
Kinsaikan.
I'm staying at the Hotel New Ocean.
Are you with someone from work?
I'm alone.
Business is not going well. I'm pissed off. I was driving around.
But it was a close call.
I almost hit you.
I don't think it's a disaster if I get hit by your car
Would you like to drive with me?
Please drive fast.
Aren't you afraid to go too fast?
I'm fine with you.
I thought I'd return this.
I don't need it anymore.
I'll give it to you.
I’m glad.
Are you alright?
Yes.
I'll drive faster.
By any chance.
What?
We might fall into the sea.
I don't care if I die.
It's pour raining.
Sorry if I drove fast.
I was crazy.
The moment I saw your face, I got myself return.
Because I am blind?
I was so focused.
You lied.
What?
I knew it.
Your heart was pounding when I touched you.
You tried to die.
I could have died.
I wasn't afraid.
But you felt sorry for me  because I am blind, and you couldn't dive into sea.
I'm sorry. I'm just finally getting the hang of it.
About the job or about the girl?
Forget it.
I promise not to do anything stupid again.
I wish I could see.
If I did, you might treat me like a woman.
I don't care if you are blind.
You and I will meet when I'm confused.
I mean, when I'm blind in my mind's eye.
We're same.
You think so?
There once was a couple of ugly Blind beggars.
It's a fairy tale.
But the villagers, out of mischief, told them they were the most beautiful couple in the world.
They believed it and were very happy.
And then the great doctor came in and opened their eyes.
They must have been disappointed.
So they went back to the blind again, and this time they felt sorry for the villagers who could see the dirt.
Okay, I'll stop worrying about my eyes.
But if I are not blind...
We might not be able to stay as we are.
At least you'll be far away from me
You're beautiful.
The rain stop.
Yeah.
I'll send you.
Thanks.
I'll pick you up at 6:00.
Here's evening paper.
Thanks.
Oh, you're still not eating?
I don't wanna eat.
It's a waste.
I'll eat it for you.
Go ahead.
I'll eat while I watch the ocean.
What's news?
Gas tank explosion kills three workers.
Oh my god.
What time is it?
It's just after 7:00.
after 7:00.
No other unusual news.
Small businesses are going out of business.
Must be the recession.
The president of Kiketsu Cosmetics is feared suicidal at his home
A CEO would be a fool to do such a thing.
Hello, Hotel New Ocean please.
May I talk to Mr.Kigoshi?
He's not there?
Are you sure?
Is someone looking for him from Tokyo too?
Hello?
I never heard from him again.
He must have killed himself.
I should have stopped him at that time.
But even though we've only met twice.
My girlishness never goes away, and it makes me lonely every day.
And the jokes and pranks that didn't bother me before somehow started to leave a lump in my heart and I became a person who doesn't put in the work.
Watch out!
Thank you very much.
They say it's bad luck to have a cat cross the street in front of you.
Watch out!
I'll help you.
Have you ever heard of the Kumada massage?
It's our home.
Oh.
You're going to study?
How do you even know that?
You have calluses on your fingers.
Really?
I hear they are so hard.
Yes.
I hope I don't embarrass myself.
Don't worry.
I'll talk to him.
You're blind in one eye?
You've been out of school for five years now?
Yes.
You've been working at many places.
Yes, I tried as many as I could, thinking of it as training.
Five years of experience is not enough for us.
Please hire him.
I'm only worker here.
We need more hands.
Please, I will study hard.
I'm planning to attend the school's study group too.
Excuse me.
We came to say hello to you!
His name is Kenkichi and he just joined our family.
Please take care of him.
I had a feeling that Kenkichi and I had a connection because of Kigoshi.
I was lonely, so Kigoshi must have sent him to me.
When I think about it, I can't help but feel close to Kenkichi, even though I don't know him yet.
And then summer came.
Tsuruko.
Oh Ito.
How are you?
What's going on?
It was hard, back then.
But you settled the case, didn't you?
I'm sure he'll pay for that.
I hear you and a man are working here only.
But how did you know about that?
I heard it from someone.
What are you doing?
Same job.
I work at Yoshi-town.
Keep working.
I beg you.
Give it to Teacher.
Did you wait?
An hour.
I had a free customer.
Ken.
What?
Is there anyone around here?
No.
Lead me.
It's nice to be blind.
Why?
I always see things in my mind's eye.
So I can remember everything clearly.
What do you remember?
I can't tell you. It's all in my mind.
You're stingy.
Welcome.
Give us 2 soda.
I'll ask you something.
What?
Do you see anyone?
I don't.
What is that?
Love letter?
No.
This letter is from my ex-teacher.
Don't read my letter.
Don't worry.
I have to read for you.
You can't.
This is awesome.
I've thought about it a lot since then, but I'm still short 100,000 yen, so I have no choice but to turn to you.
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow at 2:00 at our usual place.
Please lend me the money.
I still can't get you out of my mind.
I'm the happiest when you love me.
Tomorrow, you can make love to me for the first time in a long time.
Itoko.
This is good for you.
Don't pick on me.
I'll throw this out later.
Please.
Don't tell my wife.
I know.
Buy some water melon.
Really?
You're the kindest man I've ever met.
It's hot.
Massage me.
I have stiff shoulder.
Don't use him.
He'll go out with tsuruko soon.
Why I have to use cold patch.
What's wrong?
I have a tummy ache.
Oh my god.
What should I do.
Are you alright?
Do you think it's okay if you don't take pills?
I'm fine.
The pain has stopped.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
Are you ready to go?
I'll have to keep an eye on myself.
But how did you know about this place?
You've been here before, haven't you?
No way.
I worked around here.
Let's go home.
Let's take it easy.
It's so bright.
What do you think of me?
What?
Do you like me or not?
Let's not talk about that.
Tsuru-chan...
I liked you when I first met you.
I would do anything for you.
I'd die for you.
Let's not do this.
You don't hate me either.
You were happy to back out.
Don't get me wrong.
What do you mean?
I'm leaving.
Ken.
You lied about having a stomach ache.
You were just trying to get me in here.
Don't be so angry.
What are you going to do with me?
I like you very much.
Let me go!
Ken,Let me go!
No.
Let me go!
This is not good idea.
I must not lose.
I resisted with all my heart.
But on the contrary, I gradually relaxed and felt a kind of comfort, but I couldn't do anything about it.
Forgive me....  Kigoshi.
I thought I was a woman with a little better hope.
I thought of myself as a woman with hope.
But before I knew it, I had fallen into the trap of ordinary women.
I tried to make my life worth living by indulging in Kenkichi's love.
But then, women are weak.
I loved him so much that I became obsessed with discovering the best parts of him.
Don't move.
I'll give you an extra copy later.
I can't see the photo.
I want to take lots of photos of you and put them up in my room.
You're stupid.
You're not going to school today?
I'm not going.
I have to pay my monthly fee.
Don't you have the money I gave you the other day?
I used it.
You are busy but I have no income.
You really go to school?
You're not lying, are you?
I'm going.
Don't waste your money
Thanks.
I heard that you save a lot of money.
Who said that?
It doesn't matter who said it.
200,000, 300,000?
I can't tell.
Mr. Kimura call you.
Go, Tsuru-chan.
I have a cold.
I'll leave it to Ken.
But he's not good enough.
He likes it strong, so ken is better.
Take care of him.
Leave it to me.
I have to go away for four or five days.
Oh, where are you going?
My sister has had a stroke.
I might be a little late.
Take care of my husband.
What are you doing?
Kenkichi.
Try it on.
My kimono?
I worked all night to surprise you.
Try it on.
It's perfect.
I'm sure it'll look good on you.
This is nice pattern.
The shop staff helped me find a good color.
Thank you.
Someone might come.
Come here,Kenkichi.
I met Mr. Sakai from Omori at a union meeting.
He said you were there until this spring.
Then there's nothing more to say.
Pack up your things and come out.
Master.
I will not hire someone who will assault your master.
Don't get me wrong.
Because he hit me.
You have so many excuses.
Get out.
Are you sure you fire me?
I don't think it's good for you.
What are you talking about?
Don't pretend you don't know.
About Itoko.
I know about that.
Are you threatening me?
Get the hell out of here.
I'm very angry with you.
You have a bad attitude.
Please apologize to him.
I'm leaving.
Ken.
I'll apologize so please don't fire him.
He have no where to go.
He might do something bad.
Do you have anything to do with him?
If that's the case, be careful.
He's a dead end.
I'll take care of us myself.
So please don't kick him out.
If the union finds out, he won't be able to work in Tokyo.
I'll work for both of us.
I'll start paying for his food tomorrow.
Tsuruko...
Ken.
Stay here.
I don't wanna leave.
He didn't ask me why.
He's strict, but he's also very kind-hearted.
And for my sake, Please be Patience.
Please
OK.
Kenkichi, who had been irritable for a while since then, finally calmed down.
Peaceful happiness has come to last between us.
This may be thanks to Mr. Kigoshi.
I secretly think in a corner of my mind
I'm home.
What's the matter?
Itoko is here.
She's brazen.
She'll stay here.
I'll kick her out.
Master called her.
Stop it.
Please, don't do this.
We can't.
Don't worry.
You sure?
Someone is there.
I'm sure our mother's back.
Don't scare me.
Go to check it.
What should I do if she comes back?
We shouldn't do this.
Are you still awake?
I heard a noise in the kitchen. I thought someone was coming.
No one would come now.
But your wife might be home.
Did you hear?
She must be mom.
Who?
Post office.
Thank you.
You have received a telegram.
I'll open the door.
Don't open.
Read it.
9:15 p.m. Sister dead.
She's dead?
I'll get a telegram in the morning, so get some sleep.
Good night.
They are having fun.
We should go to bed now.
I can't hold back.
I'm worried about someone finding out.
I have two more stores to go, so I'll be home late.
get a cab.
I know.
Take care.
Hello, this is Kumada Massage.
thank you for your continued patronage
Yes, I'll be right.
I can't have you sneaking around our house like a cat burglar.
I wish you'd get out of here.
I'm not a cat burglar.
You're in love with Kenichi, too.
We're going to get married when I work a little more.
I'm not like you.
Don't tell your mother about me.
I'll pay you back.
Don't make fun of me just because I'm blind.
I sent her off.
I'm going to see Mr. Yabe.
If there's a call, take it.
I left the alcohol.
You're bad.
You just got little money from her.
But She's clever.
She doesn't pay if I say I go to school.
I don't like such a smart woman.
Because you love her.
No way.
I'm jealous of you and master.
Don't get jealous.
I'll get money as I plan.
I'm counting on you.
Hug me.
Oh you are here.
What's the hell?
Don't hit him.
I tell you. We have been dating.
You said I was burglar cat, but you took my man, too.
Don't get upset.
Let's talk democratically, the three of us.
How much will you give me?
I loaned you my man for a few months.
I won't part with him for free.
How much will you give me?
We'll talk before master come back.
Don't touch me.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Kigoshi.
Tsuru.
Hello again.
You're alive.
I'm fine.
One beer.
Welcome.
Give me a towel.
Come in.
Here's a towel.
You get wet.
Sorry I didn't call you.
Don't worry.
I had to disappear when my creditors came to the hotel.
I thought you die.
I promised you I wouldn't kill myself.
I've been running around amongst my friends ever since and I'm trying to get back on track.
Order?
Sake and foods.
You haven't changed at all.
You haven't changed at all too.
I even stayed in a love hotel.
I thought about you sometimes when it was raining.
I wonder how you're doing
I wonder if you are happy.
I wonder if you're still using your intuition.
Thinking about you has been a strange relief from the loneliness.
Are you still at that house?
It's hard to work when it's cold again, isn't it?
What's the matter?
Your beautiful eyes are sweating profusely.
Don't be mad at me.
I have a favor to ask you.
Say it.
Will you use my savings?
It's only a little.
What are you talking about?
It's only 300,000 yen.
Please...
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm a man for nothing now.
I don't think you have to invest me.
I don't care.
I don't need it for my own convenience.
If I can be of any help, I'll be happy.
Are you watching my face?
Keep an eye on it.
So you remember me sometimes.
What are you thinking?
Say it.
I think nothing.
But.
But?
It's just... it's sad not seeing your face.
Are you mad?
No.
Here it is.
Thanks.
I'll have it.
You can't drink.
I wanna drink.
It's delicious.
Would you like to go to the countryside with me?
And now you're going to need me to be your confidant.
I don't know what's going on, but I know you've made up your mind.
But let's leave all that behind, and let's just be born again and live together.
We don't have to be rich.
If our hearts and minds are perfectly in tune with each other, there is no happiness above that.
Let's go to the country, just the two of us.
I'm not who I used to be.
I made a stupid mistake.
It doesn't matter.
I'll take you away.
I don't need anything but you.
I'd be happy in any corner of the country.
Okay?
You promise?
You're taking pity on me, aren't you?
Because I'm blind.
No.
I love you.
Ever since we first met.
But don't be so cavalier about a man making a commitment based on a passing fancy.
I've made up my mind.
Then why don't you make up your mind to start working again?
I thought you were that kind of man.
I beg you.
Please use my savings to support your business.
Why don't you tell me?
Is it because I'm massagist?
Is that so?
You don't want my money?
Thank you.
You're going to use it?
I won't let your feelings go to waste.
I'm glad.
I'll return this to you.
Wait for me.
I'll be right back with my savings book.
I have one more favor to ask.
What?
I don't know your face yet.
Let me touch you just once.
I knew it.
Kenkichi and Itoko steel money from the safe and ran away.
I'm relieved.
We're closed
The customer who just went to the back of the room is where?
He left.
He left?
He said I appreciate that,
But I'll do it myself.
This was all right.
I told myself that this was the right thing to do.
I had no choice but to do this in order to keep his love unclouded and in my heart for the rest of my life.
I am sure he will recover.
And one day he will call me again.
As a customer and massagist.
I somehow got out of all sorts of trouble.
I seem to have gained a sense of security as a blind person.
I can now live as a massagist for the rest of my life.
THE END