Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Meiji 38 (Year 1905)
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's embarrassing for the neighbors,
You have to stop
Hey.
Stop doing that because it's not a nuisance to the neighbors.
She was holding hands with Shin, the fishmonger.
What?
And she was so happy that she kicked the iron kettle
I almost got burned.
You are stupid.
You are still a brat
Don't show off your charm.
But I didn't do anything.
Shinchan did it.
Don't make excuses.
If you have time to go out and have fun, work hard
I take care a baby and kitchen
Don't make excuses.
But I've never gone to bed earlier than 12 o'clock at night
But you did something wrong.
Forgive me....
I won't do it any more.
Are you sure?
She's so sassy.
We had a troublesome person come to our house.
But She's my younger brother's only child.
She has no parents.
You say that but
Are you not planning to sell her to a geisha?
Right?
I feel sorry for her.
Besides, Shinbashi and Yanagibashi say it's troublesome
because her guarantor stuff.
You don't think about anything.
our house is on fire
What will you do if this child grows up?
I know.
If you know, you're not in a good mood to be drinking.
You bastard!
Did you go to see the lantern procession?
Please wash my clothes too.
Help yourself.
You're a freeloader, yet you act all high and mighty.
This Kimono is mine. My mom bought it for me before she died
I wore this a long time ago before I came here.
It's none of my business.
Don't wear it.
Kei hit me!
What?
Again?
Get out again.
Don't ever come back
Onna no Issho / Life of a Woman (1962)
Son.
If we defeat Russia and withdraw from Manchuria, your inner palace will be safe
We avoid becoming a Russian colony
Japanese military is strong enough.
The Japanese military has the Yamato spirit.
No.
Because Japan is a modern nation
A preemptive nation like Russia is no good.
My country is no good either.
We must overthrow the Qing government and bring about reforms.
Is it a revolution?
We are finally here! The sleeping lion is roaring.
I'm home.
Welcome back
Good evening
Welcome
Are you studying?
Has your Japanese improved?
Yes I'm studying hard.
He's really good
Your father in Tianjin is worried about you
He said you haven't written me recently.
He is young and busy with various things.
As your guarantor, I am also responsible for
supervising you, so that would be a problem
You need to cherish your parents more
Mom, this is your birthday present
Thank you very much.
It's a beautiful comb
But it seems a bit too flashy for your mother
But I really like it, so maybe not?
I'm really happy.
I'm happy about your feelings.
I made it.
I see, the painting looks a lot better than the real.
but he said he'd give it to me as a gift
It's pretty well done, you're lucky
Besides these two wonderful sons,
You have two beautiful daughters.
If only my father were still alive,
Don't be so greedy.
The Mitsui Industries he founded prospered through trade with China.
That's quite good.
He was a really great man
His success was in the First Sino-Japanese War,
in which he defeated Russia
It will become easier to trade
Let's work together with Son's father to expand the business.
The fruits are here
Thank you very much.
Seizo.
No, I love this kind of thing.
so this looks good
He is a hardworking banker.
He will take care of you for the rest of his life.
When will you have a baby?
I have no idea.
Instead of that, you should find your bride.
There will soon be no more bride.
Good evening, Seizo-san
No, Fumi-san, Thanks.
I'll sing my favorite song to celebrate her birthday
Is that so? That's great
Can you please accompany me?
But...
but I'm begging you
It's for my mother
Wait a minute
Who are you?
Where did you come from?
The wooden gate to the garden over there was open
Did you come in quietly
You came to get the comb.
sorry
I didn't mean to take it
I just thought it was so pretty
so I gave it back
Here, please take it.
Forgive me....
I'll do anything you ask me to do
You could hold my hand.
Stop it.
It hurts.
You're so violent.
Come in.
Mom, I feel so sorry for this girl.
She ran away from home because her uncle kept interfering with er life
You've known her for a while?
No, that's not it.
I was wrong.
I left the wooden gate to the garden open,
so she must have come through there
What's the hell?
Mother
Today is also her birthday, just like my mother's
Do you have no mother?
My mother has died.
How about your dad?
My father died in the war.
I see.
It was the last war
The Sino-Japanese?
Where?
It was Taito Ward
that's where I got injured.
What group did your father belong to?
I don't know
I was still young
so please
Please don't take me to the police.
I'm never going into a stranger's house again.
Don't worry.
I won't tell the police
so hurry up and go home.
I'm sure they are worried about you.
Maybe no one in her house is worried about her.
Your Uncles and aunties
I'm sure they are feeling sorry for what they've done
and is searching for you
I'm not saying anything bad, so hurry up and go home.
Shall I send someone to you?
No, I'm fine alone
So be careful
Please come and visit us again at lunchtime
Yes sorry
Goodbye.
Sis...the world is full of variety
I lost my legs in the war.
Thanks to the war,
I was successful in business
You get birthday celebrations from children
There are also people who lost their fathers in the same war.
There is someone who has the same birthday as her.
Hey, wait a minute
I'll give this to you,
what happened to you?
I can't go home.
I have nowhere to go.
They told me never coming back
Meiji 43 (Year 1910)
You're always working.
Isn't it hard?
I don't wanna playing around and I think it's a waste
You're not a maid anymore
I gave my uncle money
and you have clearly adopted me as his daughter,
so I don't have to work that much
I'm very happy the way it is
It's like a dream, it's all thanks to you.
Are you leaving now?
I'm going out to Kanda
Are you going to buy another law book in Kanda?
It's tough, you have to study that much at university
What do you plan to do in the future?
That's right, my father became a continental ronin after his death
I'm afraid I might follow my father's example and become the leader of the demons.
What's the hell?
So then
What kind of person do you want to be as a wife?
I have never thought about that
But I don't want to be the wife of someone who wants to become a demon
Because this is the first time you've done this,
You said I could hold your hand.
I don't like it.
It's too late.
At that time, I wanted to do something to avoid being handed over to the police
I was trying my best,
so I just said stuff that came out of my mouth
I didn't know.
I thought you liked me a little bit
I shouldn't have given you the comb.
I'll get this back
That's no good, please give it back
No.
it like a treasure
I won't give this back to you.
Please.
Welcome back.
I want tea.
I'll give this back.
Have a nice day.
Did you finish the exam today?
I'm finally graduating.
You will finally become the president, replacing your mother.
I don't want to be the president
Why?
You learn Chinese at a foreign language school
to help you with business?
Well, that was my mother's wish
I find it interesting to read books that have nothing to do with trade
I found that
I was a worthless person to our business
Even though you are the eldest son,
You say that.
Does the eldest son have to take up the family business?
If you don't, our house will collapse
I'm a guy who's suited to be a school teacher
The teacher is not stuck
Business is much more interesting
Shintaro, on the way home from school, you stopped by the bank?
Your wife asked you this morning.
Bu I went to ask for a discount on a bill
It just doesn't feel right
Sometimes it's good to go to the bank but...
A bank is a place to borrow money
I will go there tomorrow
You like helping out like a store
Attending the handover of goods to Chinese.
I like negotiate at customs.
Okei.
Where are you?
What can I do for you?
I found Fumi's underwear in my laundry.
I'm so sorry
Please be careful.
I can't stand being lumped together with hers.
Fusako.
I don't want to force anything on her.
Do it yourself.
Because..
you're a woman too
What's wrong with that?
You like Kei so much.
You always protect her.
Fusako.
Fumie is on good terms with Seizo, so you ar frustrated.
So you take your frustrations out on her.
you're so mean
Just because okie-san is your favorite,
you're not even bringing that up
Everyone in this house is interested in Kei.
I'm jealous of her.
Please stop, I'll be in trouble
I'll take care of the laundry
I'll be more careful from now on
European music is amazing
Right
Japanese music is so poor and primitive that it's not even worth talking about.
Japan needs to become a great power
and catch up with Europe soon
I want to study abroad in Germany after I graduate from music school next year
that's great
It's so fun talking to you
How do you think about Fusako?
She's traditional Japanese women
There's nothing modern.
Unlike you
I'll tell my sister.
Are you going back to China?
Yes.
You had made it into college, but
It's regrettable.
There is nothing more to learn from Japan.
But your father gets angry.
My father is an enemy of China, just like Japan
Enemy?
My father will also take your mother to make money.
She doesn't care what happens to the Chinese people.
The same goes for Japan
I thought that the Japanese would help China for the sake of China's happiness,
but that's not the case
Japan wants to exploit China and get fat on its own
Japan wants to imitate the West and colonize Asia.
Watch out!
Damn it.
He escaped.
Who are you?
What are you planning to do with Son?
That guy is stealing the Japanese government's policies
Are you one of those friends or comrades too?
What if I am?
I will report this to the police
stupid.
Do you think the police can arrest us?
Sho-san
I finally found your wife.
Why do you think?
She's not good enough.
You're not into marriage.
what on earth are you planning?
Tenjin ask us to increase product price.
They've said they're going to raise the price of cotton again.
Again?
Is it really difficult to do business with Chinese.
They're black-hearted.
They are clever.
They're also in business
I'm going for a little walk
Sho-san, Go to Tenjin.
Go to Tenjin?
I'll get the Ministry of Foreign Affairs involved
Sho-san, Please tell Tenjin's lecturer....
I should threaten them and force them to cut down the cotton roots?
Yes, that's right
Sorry, I don't want to do that.
Sho-san, please.
Please go to Tenjin.
because you're popular.
But we have to consider not only our interests, but theirs as well.
Shosan, What I have to do is to protect our business.
The Japanese are a bit arrogant
Don't make fun of Chinese just because we won the war
I'll do it
Even if you say no.
In my position, I have no choice but to do whatever I want
You hate it?
Ask someone else.
It can't be helped
They say that business is going to get increasingly difficult from now on
If you guys are so weak-willed, Shintaro will be unreliable just like he was
and I feel sorry for the administration
If I die, this business will be finished.
Where's  Kei-chan?
She's talking about something with your wife in the tatami room right now
What's that?
I'm really glad that I took you in
The store is clean and the work gets done
I rely on you more than my real children
No way.
When I heard that we were born on the same day of the same month,
I felt like we were not strangers
Thank you very much.
So I wanna talk with you.
Yes.
Yes, you're in high spirits
and  healthy and seems to like working in the store
I'd like to leave this business to you.
Sho-san.
Don't worry.
I'll have you listen with me
Is that so...
It may be strange for me to say this about my own child,
but as a husband,he is not as embarrassing as anyone else's,
However, I feel like there is something lacking on him.
If you could help him as his wife,
we would have two daughters
and many things would happen in the future
I think you will be able to steer the ship well as the eldest son's wife.
What do you think?
If that happens, I can retire with peace of mind,
but I don't know what would have happened to me without your help
I feel it's a shame
that you have to say that so much,
but will you accept it?
But ...Please
I'd like to think about it for a while
Is this something you need to think about?
Well, it's an important part of a woman's life.
Well then, think about it
I have to heat up the bath
Sis.
What's wrong?
I'm going to Tianjin
Instead, I want to quit here.
Now I understand why you guy are always alone.
It's all about Okei,right?
You  must be really hard for you if she become Shintaro's wife
What are you talking about?
I understand.
But this isn't for me to do
Our family tells me to do that.
Please understand that
I'm home.
What happened just now?
You're crying
I'll give this back to you
You are stupid.
That was just a joke
But I don't need it anymore
What's wrong?
Mom.
Are you going to have Kei to marry Shintaro? Why?
Who did you ask?
Anyone is fine, why?
for the sake of the family.
Are you forcing him to marry?
It will also be good for Kei
Or Kei is saying that she does not like?
Mom, I like Kei
Kei likes me
So?
So when I graduate from college, I want to get married with her.
I won't allow that
Kei will become Shintaro's wife and inherit the family business
Mom.
Kei is someone who is desperately needed in this house.
She is the one who must be there to protect the business that Father started
It doesn't matter if Tsutsumi's house collapses
Eiji.
Although he say it's a business In reality, he's making money by using military force
and politics to intimidate people into giving up cotton and soybean meal at low prices
We are getting fat by squeezing oil out of the Chinese
It would be better if one of these collapses were to go under
Eiji.
You want to humiliate your mother and your father?
Are you going to sacrifice Kei for some shameless business?
Are you going to decide Kei's life? I'm against it
Is that so? Do you really hate here that much?
No.
No, there's no choice. Get out of this house
Get out tomorrow
You're not a child either. Try living on your own
Think about how difficult it is to live.
Kei.
I'm leaving from here.
She said something?
If I told her I wanted to marry you
She was angry.
Are you following me or stay here?
Let's get out of here early
I was wrong to forcefully lead you five years ago
Let's go out together and go to China.
Let's Join forces with the Chinese people and fight!
To defeat King and create a new country.
Your wife will allow that to happen
You don't have to worry about her.
Son-kun will be returning soon. Let's go on the same boat
But that wasn't very ungrateful,
so you ended up working as a maid for five years
The repayment has already been made
Sorry, that's not all.
At that time, her picked me up
I don't think you understand how grateful I
am for that.
You know nothing of the poor life.
I know.
I don't think you understand.
Kei.
You hate me?
No.
It's nothing like that
We'll be together
You are stupid.
Or are you scared of China?
Don't worry.
China is more civilized than Japan.
It's better than here.
Well then, I'll meet Son-kun
and decide on a date
Good night.
Ma'am.
What can I do for you?
What you just said..
If you're okay with someone like me,
would you be willing to marry Shintaro?
Yes.
Seriously?
You don't have to concern about Eiji anymore?
No.
Thanks.
Now our house is safe
I'm sure my late father would be pleased
No, please take care of Shintaro for the rest of your life
You promise me?
Yes.
Are you sure?
I'll let Shintaro know right away
No matter how happy he is, Shintaro loves you too
it was good
Good for me
Okei.
What do you think?
I'm getting marry to Seizo.
He likes me over sis.
What do you think?
congratulations.
You made the choice based on your own feelings
Fumiko is happy.
Thanks.
Recently, in the Republic of China,
there has been a fierce protest against Haiti,
with many people claiming that Japan's policy is to colonize
Japanese products were burned in various places.
Anti-Japanese demonstrations, mainly by students, are thriving
If the situation continues as it is, trade between
Japan and China will come to a complete halt,
not only destroying the Japanese economy
but also putting the lives
and property of Japanese people in China in danger
This is the first time our country has been in a position like this since the Sino-Japanese and Russo-Japanese Wars
The things he built as a hero are gone, and the sacrifices he made in the good war
I feel truly sorry for the tens of thousands of people who died in the war
Therefore, there is only one path for our country to take at this time
Whenever our rights are violated in China, we will take countermeasures.
In other words, they are taking a strong stance,
even going so far as to send in troops and go to war
Chiyo-chan, were you in a place like this? You're quiet and alone
Your mom is away every day and you are lonely.
She won't play with me.
I hate my mother.
Oh you hate her?
What's wrong, sister?
If you're going on a blind date, you should be by Inose's side
Inose-san has started playing shogi with your husband
Inose-san, what happened to this?
What happened to Fusako?
I think she will be here soon.
I hear the kid has issues and she's scared or
She is such a family woman.
She’s very interested in children's education
I see.
He's troublesome.
What is your sister's feeling?
Yes, he's a great politician,
but he's a little too old
But I don't think that person would be okay
Well, come quickly
I feel so nervous and anxious,
I feel like my life is being shortened
This is not your first blind date.
If you find annoying,
please go home.
I didn't mean it.
Don't get me wrong.
Please say hello to Inose.
I'm in trouble
Inose-san say he goes home now.
Please stop him.
Okei won't come back yet?
That's irresponsible
She made the arrangements herself.
let's all go and talk to him
here's an urgent telegram
What did Tenjin's store say?
It seems that Chinese’s employees want to quit the store
Why? do they say the salary is low?
They say if someone works at a Japanese store, they're a traitor
Apparently everyone was going to be arrested and beaten up
That's just an excuse
They really want more pay.
In this case, we'll have to rely on the military
Military?
If things continue like this, we won't be able
to do business and our stores will go bankrupt
We need the military to protect us
But if we send troops into the city, it will lead to another war
There's no other way
Because that's the only way
Okei, I hate war.
There's a war going on with your father killed.
The war made you all alone.
and made my legs broken.
It's a business that was started even at such a cost
We have to protect it even in war
However, it is going for a bad that can't forcefully overcome Chinese.
If Eiji hears this, he'll be furious.
For better or worse, we are businessmen
Just say it and make a ton of money
That's good for the country and good for us.
Okei.
You're becoming a more and more scary person
So, please them to increase their salary.
I'll just have to endure it for a while
Hello, is that you?
Inose has left?
What happened to Inose-san?
If that person were to marry Fusako,
it would be a great help to our business.
So please.
I don't know about that kind of politics
If you recommended, then
Why you won't come home early?
You're busy at the store?
but anyway, Seizo-kun, Fumi, and I all tried our best to keep him back.
But Inose-san has gone home
He said it's boring without you.
So in the end it's your fault
I'm sure oKei'll be angry.
Because she wasn't there
Inose-san has gone home .
I don't like being scolded by Kei either.
What's the hell?
But sis.
I'm troublemaker in this house anyway.
Okei want me to go away.
You were also wrong about what happened today
The reason I did shogi was it was
because I wanted to please Inose-san
That's bad.
she must have felt that she had been made fun of.
Would it have been better if I had danced to keep him?
I'm off to home.
He's an asshole.
That guy is just lip service about being European and modern
My marriage was a failure
Why?
He said he would do housework after marriage but he never actually does anything.
Everyone say that Seizo-san is too good for you.
Give me a break.
If Okei hadn't told you
That you were happy
I never married that person
I guess Okei led me on.
Is that so?
I hate her now.
I'm home.
I'm sorry I couldn't make it in time for
Inose-san's return today
There was a big fuss about whether we close the tenjin Shop or not
so you're still angry.
I have no intention of forcing anything on Inose-san.
It's okay to refuse
you
I can't stand you are silent like that
I go to various places to negotiate for the families here.
I know you'll do your best for us
Thank you,
Don't say like that.
I'm incompetent.
I'm no use.
I know about myself.
If you have something to say, please don't hide anything
Nothing.
please tell me.
I can't back down like this
I tell you.
We don't get along
We don't get along?
In fact, there is nothing you do that is flawless.
But women are just good at noticing things
It's not just about working hard
There's something that only women have,
but you don't seem to have it
What is one thing that only women have?
If you don't know what it is, there's no point. It's a waste
No, there's no way
I don't want to be left with just that
My mother told me
to take good care of this house
I am working hard for that.
I just think about you guys.
You decided to be boss here.
and maybe that was more important
to you than becoming my wife
What are you talking about?
By the way
when you married me, you lied yourself?
What are you talking about?
About Eiji.
About Eiji?
You liked Eiji
But you married me.
It's impossible.
Do you like me or not?
You hate me.
Your husband is not me,but this house.
for the past 10 years
You've never loved me like a husband
What a shame.
why won't you break up with me?
Aren't you going to kick me out of here?
Just like Eiji,I love you too
You're a necessary person in this house
If anyone leaves, it's me
You.
Human make a lot of mistakes
It's like doing something just to make a mistake
Once again, this is the path I chose
If I know it's a mistake, I'll try to make it not a mistake
I'm home.
Please give me a souvenir
I'm currently busy
I was busy and forgot.
I'll take you to the zoo next time,
You're always lying.
I hate you.
Get out.
At last, I was hated by you too.
but I'm sure you'll understand me
when you grow up a little more
Good night.
2,000 tons of bean dregs from Goodnight Manchuria
the ship enters Shimonoseki port
The fertilizer is not ready?
It will be shipped early next month.
president, he is an excellent guy.
He'd be a perfect husband for your daughter
He will hold a senior position in the Army in the future.
That's an exaggeration.
He led the war against China
You're young.
I wonder what will happen about war.
It seems that people in the U.S. are opposed to the memory of the war,
but that opposition from other countries won't have any lasting effects
In order for Japan to develop,
it must control China and Manchuria
It's the lifeline of Japan
If this man becomes the president's husband , we will be worthful.
We're in charge of the war, and you  can make a lot of money in China.
I'll give you plenty of support
Hello, it's me.
Okei.
Excuse me
, what happened?
So Eiji came back suddenly.
Eiji?
I get it.
I'm sorry to say this
Can we postpone tonight's meeting until tomorrow?
Why?
I suddenly had an urgent matter.
so it can't be helped.
Thank you very much,
but the seats are reserved for Akasaka,
so I wonder if you've invited some pretty girls.
Yes.
That's a shame you wouldn't come.
I'll go for a cleanse of my soul after a long time
See you.
You're Chie-chan, Okei-san's child
It's like a dream.
Where have you been?
In many places.
in the Kanto region in Nanjing, Beijing, and Shanghai
What were you doing
I've done a lot of different things like that.
You must have had a lot of trouble.
Your dad is at company?
At school.
At school?
He's a Teachers at Yokohama International School
He is a Chinese teacher.
It must be hard to commute to Yokohama from Tokyo
He lives in an apartment in Yokohama
So.
He is separated from my mother.
Why?
I have no idea.
Ask my mom
Auntie Fusako and Auntie Fumie are fine?
I don't know
My aunts and My mom don't get along well.
so neither of them come here very often
I see
you received a call from your mom.
Apparently the matchmaking has been postponed until tomorrow
Excuse me, I have piano lessons
Please come home with me today
Why?
Because Tsutsumi's house is your house
If you are going to separate, it is really me who should move out
Enough already, it's the same old story over and over again
Besides, it's been a while since Eiji has returned home,
so it would be embarrassing for you to be living apart
Did you come here without being an Eiji?
Why?
What do you mean?
I'm sure you wanted to see Eiji.
Don't say about past again
If I'm here I'll just get in the way?
, what do you mean?
Sorry about that, but get it back now
I have some writing to finish tonight.
You don't have laundry?
Chie always come to here to do that.
Chie always come?
She comes over sometimes.
She seems to like you.
You think so?
I guess she hates me
That Chie's marriage proposal I once spoke of
The other party is very enthusiastic about it
You could meet him once?
No, if you think it's good, then you should decide after consulting with Chie.
there's no need for me to step in
I hate soldiers.
You.
Goodbye. Good night
Are you Madam?
Yes.
We're police.
Eiji Tsutsumi is probably be here.
If you hide it, it will be bad
There's something wrong with Eiji?
Japanese sake is good.
It's been a while since I last drank Japanese sake with you like this
It's been 27 years.
27 years or 27 years,china and Japan has changed too.
Japan started a terrible war
It would be a shame for a modern soldier to come here
They don't think about Chinese people at all.
We were different, demons of the Meiji era
We loved China and were willing to die for her
If we wage such a reckless war,
Japan's future will be ruined
The whole world is criticizing Japan
Eiji, why did you come back?
As I get older, I start to miss my hometown
You must have come back to campaign against the war.
Don't hide it.
I'm not that stupid again
I'd love to help you with your work too, but unfortunately
My body doesn't listen to me, and my legs hurt more and more every year
Sometimes I can't walk
Welcome back, Eiji-san
Sis.
It's been a while
Sorry, We had drink.
Come to join us.
There was no alcohol.
Bring us beers.
Yes, I'll bring it right away
I'll have it here.
Here.
Don't disturb me.
When I drink while looking at you,I can taste it well.
You are good at joking.
You have a guest?
maybe they're business partners.
I wonder who the customers are
Eiji-san, how long will you be staying here this time?
I don't think I'll be there for long,
Eiji.
but what business did you have coming back to the mainland this time?
There's no need to tell me anything new
Tell me.
Tell me all your actions
What?
As the wife of the heir to Tsutsum house,
I need to know about the lives of my husband's relatives
What were you doing over there?
What is your purpose in coming back this time?
I don't like to give the same answer twice
Please tell me the truth. Can't you tell me the truth?
I don't see the need for that
Is that so.
It would be a problem if people found out what you did there and what your purpose is when you come back.
I'll leave it to your imagination
I understand, there is no other way
Your customers are waiting
He's waiting in the Western-style room.
Okei.
You meant to say?
I came here thinking I would have to give another reply.
After hearing what you just said, I think my answer was correct
You're such a fool.
You're changed.
You sold me.
He's waiting in the Western-style room?
You came out and I was surprised.
If I don't come here, this family will be in trouble.
That's right
Why catch me?
You are a communist?
You are violating the Peace Preservation Act.
You are sentenced to life imprisonment or death.
You came back to Japan to die.
I want to leave through the garden,I don't want to stand out
What should we do?
Well...
I won't run away or hide.
Eiji.
Uncle.
I'm off now.
Please understand my feelings too
Don't worry, I understand
But Okei
It's no good being tied down like this forever
You're becoming less and less human.
Eiji.
Don't abandon yourself
Humans must live their lives without regrets
Good day.
uncle, say hello to everyone.
Ah.
Okei.
At that time you came from here,I'm leaving from here.
From same spot.
Uncle
Eiji!
Mom.
Where was he taken?
Did you meet him?
What did he do?
I have no idea.
Did you kick him out without knowing?
Right?
It was your mother who did it
After all, he's Dad's real brother.
So you don't think anything of it?
No matter how painful it may be,
there are things in this world that must be done.
I don't understand about your feeling.
Chie.
Your meeting has been postponed until tomorrow.
Please go to the hairdresser in the morning
Of course you'll wear a kimono
Mother
If I married that soldier, would that help the store?
What are you saying?
I only think about you
I don't think so.
I heard it from  Auntie Fusako and Fumi.
There's a hidden agenda behind everything Mom says
Chie.
Mom is such a cold person
What a nasty woman, you're not human.
We're not family anymore
Get out
where are you going?
Yokohama I'm going to live with my dad now
Hold on.
Chie.
Okei.
What are you doing?
I definitely let madam know if something happens
Eiji had a close relationship with a Chinese person.
That's illegal all in Japan
I can't understand
I don't think what I did was wrong
That was the only way to protect this family.
But everyone would leave me.
You too will soon be
No joke.
I will not leave your side.
But I'm starting to hate myself more and more.
It's not your fault
I made you my wife
This Shizu-san is at fault
I want to protect this house as a single woman
No matter how gentle a woman is, she becomes more and more strict
It's not your fault, Okei.
Stay strong.
Showa19
I'm fine with going to war
But when I think about chie and others
I worry and can't sleep at night
I'm going to work at military factory
You can't support a child on that salary
It'll work out somehow
I want to say I'll leave it to me
I haven't had a steady income since I retired from school
Piano teachers are like garbage in this day and age.
I don't even have 100 yen saved up
But I don't have any relatives in the countryside,
so I have no choice but to ask Kei.
I don't want to ask my mother for a favor.
Why don't you just leave your child with your mother
I don't want.
I haven't even notified her about the marriage since I left home
But Mom will be happy
Living alone is lonely.
But I don't like it.
Who're you?
Did you come in without telling me?
I'm the owner here
What?
You.
May I come in?
What's wrong?
I'm really sorry for coming in
She mistook me for a thief
You want me to take care of Chie's child, don't you?
I don't have any right to consult you now,
Don't worry.
That Tsutsumi house is your house
Whatever you want to do,
I have never been against it
That's true, but...
That's fine.
If you are happy with your child and chie
please come and move here with us
I see. Thank you.
What happened?
My heart has been feeling a bit strange lately
When Chie and others return, will you return with them?
To here?
Your room has been left as it was when you left.
I see.
Because you quit school
You don't need to come to Yokohama anymore
That's true...
but if you only eat pitches,
you'll end up becoming a bit of a mess
Here you can find plenty of meat, sugar, and eggs
This coffee is real too
How do you get them?
I got them from the Army.
Will there be soldiers coming in and out of there?
We can only rely on soldiers for our business.
Please come and stay here.
You are already old
It's hard to do it alone
I'm worried that you might get sick.
If something were to happen, I wouldn't be able to face mother.
Mother?
I promised her.
I feel sorry.
And it's embarrassing to the world
It's embarrassing for the boss of the Tsutsumi family to live in an apartment.
Kei.
I won't come back here.
Why? Please wait
Did I bother you?
I don't care if I starve to death
I'll never come to this place again
Please, please come back
I don't want to
Why? Why?
I knew what you thought
How did you know?
You don't really care what happens to me.
But when it comes to being obligated to mother, appearances are important to the world
You.
You're a fine woman who is perfect in whatever you do.
What happened to you
Nothing
I'm fine.
You seem to be in a lot of pain
It's fine, it's fine
Call Mitsu.
Please leave it like this for a bit
I'll call doctor.
it's fine
you can leave it like this
You and I.
I love you.
But you're too great for me.
You have to be strong and stay strong
Don't say anything, just stay still
Just you and me.
You!
Again.
It's been a while since I've had such delicious sake.
Yeah.
It's rare to find such a delicious treat now.
What a great kei.
Please do your best for us old people for the country.
Sister, Brother Shintaro
The doctor said he died of a heart attack
Apparently, he had been living alone for a long time and his body had become very weak
I wonder why okei should have taken better care of him.
She's so cold.
even before he die
Apparently he had a fight with her
and that caused him to have a heart attack
It's like she killed him.
Yeah.
It's her fault.
Please don't speak ill of my mother.
It can't be helped. that's true
The aunties were always saying bad things about my mother
Not only did you receive money for your wedding preparations,
but you also received living expenses every month from her.
but We didn't get it from Okei.
We got it from the family fortune.
our mother increased that fortune.
That's not true.
The company grew thanks to my mother
Whoever did it,Tsutsumi has developed.
Our fathers laid a strong foundation for us
You're ungrateful
What?
I hated my mother too, but I learned
Who made my mother like that?
We made her like that.
We were sloppy.
We were timid.We pushed everything onto our mother.
and acted cool
What about you guys?
You look similar with Okei.
What do you mean?
That's not good for a poor person
Please say it again
Auntie, say it again
Stop it....
aunts say our mom killed our father.
That's true.
Why?
I definitely killed him
I don't know how to apologize, I was a bad wife
I'm sorry,
mother, why are you apologizing?
Mom is a great person, there's no need to apologize
Shut up!
you're still our mom
I don't like you. Please leave your seat
Please leave your seat
I hate seeing these people's faces
Let's go home
What's going on?
This is a telegram that just arrived at the office.
We are screwed up.
This is 4th time.
what happened?
Our 4 ships were sunk by an American submarine today
That is a huge loss
Maybe we'll have to close the store
But there's still some merchandise left in the warehouse in Fukagawa
They were all sold out a long time ago.
so this volume was our last hope
Closing the store?
What will happen to the company's assets?
We will sort them out
I think our stocks will come back
We won't know until we produce it
I think I can afford the monthly living expenses
We can't give it to you.
Would you please leave?
We need to think of a plan quickly
We should have stopped dangerous trade sooner and switched to the military industry,
No matter how much she's good, she's still a woman.
She can't think that far.
She's crazy.
She's been in the cotton trade all her life.
That's the way business was done in the Meiji era.
Even if we sell the office and warehouse, after
paying off the bank debt and retirement benefits,
this house is just left.
If it was destroyed in the war, we can't get insurance money.
It's a shame to close Tsutsumi corp.
I couldn't keep any of the promises I made to my mother
What can I say to apologize?
It's okay
It's a company built on war anyway
It can't be helped.
The Kanto region was destroyed by the war
Warning An air raid warning has been issued for the Kanto region by the Eastern Military District Headquarters
I don't know if they'll come to Tokyo
We're in danger in many ways.
I plan to evacuate Chie and the others to Shinshu.
I have old business partners there.
I think it would be better if it was done as soon as possible
Will you come with us?
No, I'll stay here.
But you can't walk well.
I don't mind dying if I'm too late to escape in an emergency
Don't say that
I don't want to leave your side.
I want to be with you until I die
Okei.
You're Okei.
Eiji..Why you are here?
I'm not a ghost.
I was released from prison five days ago
thanks to the US military
Eiji.
How can I apologize?
I was betraying you
I wouldn't come here if I bear a grudge.
Do you live alone?
How about others?
Everyone else is safe
They were all evacuated, so it was unfortunate that Shosuke  missed to escape
I’m sorry.
He was a good person,
All because of the war.
The house and the warehouse were completely burned down
I have nothing left of what I inherited from my mother
They're all gone
It's ok.
You have suffered your whole life because you
were tied up in tsutsumi house. Now you are free
Live for yourself, not for your country,
your family or your company
What has my whole life been like?
Was it all for nothing?
Okei.
I came to pick you up.
I'm the one who brought you to this house and made you unhappy.
To make up for that, I'll take you out of here and make you happy
Let's get out.
Where are you going from here?
When We lose the war, I have more friends
Now I am wellknown.
So, Okei, do you still love me?
Okay then let's go
I'm going to stay here after all
Why?
Chie and grandchildren come back in the spring.
I need to build something easy by then
Even an old woman like me can be of some use
I can take care for my grandchildren
OKei-san will always be OKei-san
You only think about other people.
I'm sure I'm an idiot
Well, if you ever want to come to me,
you're welcome
Yes, my whole life....
This was decided 40 years ago when I went through the gate.
OKei.
Well then, take care
See you.
THE END.