Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Onna Ga Aishite Nikumu Toki / She Came for Love (1963)
Good morning
The store clerk is the most important person in the store.
you should behave better
I'm sorry
Imai
Please treat the customer at table 3.
take care of the customers in the restaurant
good morning
Sorry I'm late.
The traffic was busy
You look good in Kimono
I think the colors are very flashy
You look so nice
People say business women are not beautiful, but you are not
I won't reward you for praising me
Everyone is here?
Toshiko has not come yet
What's wrong?
she is very punctual
master is out of store.
But he's coming back soon
That shop looks very nice.
but the price is a little high
I think this cafe store is a very convenient place for you.
Let's wait for him inside
Let me see another one
Just take a look
I don't have time.
I have to go for Utsumi party
Utsumi party?
People who were in Utsumi gather there once a month
Is it a bar study group?
Kind of
you might be easy going but customer is so scary
Be careful even if you are a regular customer for 10 years More
For example, if an udon restaurant opens nearby with cheap and delicious food, all customers will go there.
Bar is same
we can look down on our customers.
They are just customers.
I keep talking to myself today
do you want to talk about something?
Do you know Marianne of the Minami?
She said she opened a bar in Ginza, Tokyo.
in Ginza?
What's wrong?
Bars are gorgeous these days
we are number one.
We should not stay quiet.
we want to be more dignified
We are famous in Osaka, so That's why we have guests from Tokyo.
We don't need to open a bar in Tokyo.
If you do that, it means that Ginza is better than Osaka.
Utsumi is Osaka's
We should not have a complex in Tokyo
There are beautiful moms like this in Osaka too.
There is someone in our group who likes Tokyo.
You mean Toshiko?
Although she has lived in Osaka for a long time, she does not use the Osaka dialect.
I hate it
If she doesn't use the Osaka dialect, she'll look smarter
I don't want to work with her
she is so unique.
she has clients
Welcome
Upstairs?
She's coming
Sorry I'm late
Have a seat
were you with a man?
He stood up me
Oh I'm sorry
I can't believe a man would stand up for a beautiful woman like you.
Seriously,you guys should be careful with men
People say a beautiful madam can't be successful
The bar lady is the customer's common property
Guys are easily jealous of bar women
The store loses credibility.
So you be careful with men,Toshiko
Since she came, we only talk about men. You date with anyone?
all my customers are my boyfriends
tell me the secrets
what is the name of your bar chief?
Ecchan?
he is too handsome to be a bartender
someone asked me if he was your boyfriend
Oh I see
Handsome men make customers jealous
But he works hard
Thank you very much
It's been a while
Hi Madam
How are you?
Give him a glass of water.
Welcome
I prefer scotch whiskey.
I prefer Madam here
Thank you very much
You forgot something.
We prefer your shop
Thank you very much
Welcome
were you with a man?
You look scary
It's hard for me to go to a man I like
you are very good at talking
I'll kiss you
Whiskey is ok?
prepare whiskey for him
Ecchan,make a highball
He's calling you
Please turn off that NEON
It's difficult to buy whiskey these days.
you are good at business
business is bad these days
Really?
You look good in this tie
Made in Scotland.
Similar to scotch liquor
I got this from a lady
Being handsome is good.
Don't play with our girls
What's wrong?
Can you come tonight?
I'm bust these days
you are no longer kind.
please give me back my money
I will pay you back later
I'm sorry I have to take care of you
We're used to it
Women's minds don't work like business
Really
he cares about you all the way
Really?
The bar here is always crowded.
we have no chance to talk to you
What's wrong?
you serve your customers too much
Is that bad?
I want to please my customers
I know but
It's not good to seduce men too much
men want to be seduced by women
this is not a restaurant
Right. but I hate doing that
Customers get used to it
This is our store's policy
Madam has no lover?
She's picky.
She does not show her private.
Who support her to open this bar?
She used the money from her divorce and a loan from the bank.
Welcome
A lot of customers
Thank you
Can I sit inside of kitchen?
You are good at kidding
I’ll go around
I'm sorry
He might be her lover
It's suspicious to casually go outside when it's full.
I guess he is her lover
I was sorry I was busy
I worried no one came
Your business is doing great
Did you come today?
I flew in this morning for a meeting at the venue.
I'll go back by last flight
You are always busy
He's Ozaki who works as producer
producer?
He brings actors or singers from overseas
I see
He's young and sometimes in the weekly papers.
I saw the concert poster
Did you see?
It was so great
I was offered a million dollar tie-in by a pharmaceutical company, but I turned it down.
What a waste
I want to work my way.
See you
Take care
Thank you
You should visit her house if you are curious
You can see if man is there or not
I get it. I will drop her off at her house tonight
I've always wanted to look where you live
You are so pervert
It's pervert man look around woman's house
Stop at the crossing
I'll drop you off at your house
Don't worry.
The street is too narrow
Keep driving
You live in big house
I'll serve you a tea
Thanks
Come in
Have a seat
Thanks
Wanna drink brandy?
Just tea is fine
Do you have ashtray?
Sorry, I don't smoke
Here it is
This ashtray is a memento from the opening of the restaurant.
You've got great memory
Because I love you
There's no ashtray so It seems she has no lover
I found out
I didn't know there was nice apartment in Tennoji
This is new apartment
I see
It's single bed
But don't trust yet
Check the razor at bathroom
What are you talking about?
It's nothing
Sorry Lemon is shorted
It's lonely that women live alone
I wanna go to bathroom
In this way
Thanks
Oh brandy
They say adding brandy to tea is bad for you.
Are you sure?
There was no razor
You look weird
Don't be upset
We're here to check if you have lover or not
No way
I gonna left my pajama here
Madam from bar shouldn't make a lover
Why?
Our customers share us
Oh I feel sorry
I won't invite him if I have a lover
I see.
How much is the rent for here?
It's expensive but this is what I need for my work
Just like our company moved to expensive place
Oh it's 1:30 am.
Your wife got angry
Your wife got angry too
Shall we go for drive to Akashi next Sunday?
I'm busy next Sunday
I see
Sorry
Madam
Are you alone?
Yes
Same here
Why you are here?
I like to be outside sometimes.
I was surprised
You remember there was 3 days off in this spring?
I didn't do anything at home and My helper told me I was too lonely woman
So I often come here during day time
I don't like day time neither
Day is long
I don't wanna play golf
I feel like going to Hawaii next month
I envy you.
Our bar won't be busy until autumn
Can I excuse?
Why?
You've just come
I don't feel good
Is it a woman's privilege?
She'll get better as soon as she see her boyfriend
I worry if Nobu find us
Don't worry
He's so strict
Never mind
Welcome
Can I get scotch with water?
Shall I make softer?
You know what I like
Are you busy?
We're fine
Where's Madam?
She's sick these days
I see
Say take care to her
Thanks
You always work.
Do you have wife?
No one wanna marry me
Where's Madam's apartment?
She doesn't tell me
does she shut you up?
No way
Welcome
Never mind.
Say hi to her
Thanks
He looks good
Don't play with him
Why?
He is Madam's ex husband
He?
he looks good and rich.
Why she divorced?
Ask her
She gonna hit me
Welcome
sorry I’m off work
Business won't thrive without you
Don't pay the followers off him
Sorry
How's your health?
Sleeping is harder than being sick
Kitahara was just here
He was staying long?
He left as soon as he saw you weren't here.
Don't talk to him
Welcome
It's been a while
I brought her today
please take a seat in the back
You look good in Kimono
You got better now?
Thanks
this is a very nice shop
are you flattering?
I mean it
This woman has no sense of the interior decoration of the shop.
he likes to speak ill of people
He is very quiet as a member of parliament.
he sits like a doll on TV
he just clap
She likes to speak ill of people more than I do.
Do you guys drink the usual drinks?
I don't know the taste, so I want to drink expensive alcohol
Please prepare two water and water from the old party
Welcome
This diamond tie clip is lovely
this is just a glass ball
It's a  diamond that matches her
I want this diamond too
I want diamonds for earrings
You are funny
Can you buy for me?
diamond earrings are nice
Ok but you should listen to me
you are good at telling jokes.
Don't trust him
Shut up
I think this store is more fun for me than your store.
Welcome
What do you eat?
I wanna eat tuna
is this delicious?
Yes
I want one
Give me more
It tastes good
you should go home and rest
Thanks.
I'm leaving
I'll drop her off
Thanks
I'm Ikuta.
Can you send me a cab?
Tennoji apartment.
You know right?
I wanna sleep more
I worked until 3 am last night
How was your flight?
I was sleeping all the way
I was sleeping
you were snoring
Oh no
What time now?
Don't worry about time?
I don't wanna waste my time
I'm from Shin Nihon TV.
Can I talk to Mr.Shirai who is musical department?
I'm Ozaki
How was the work?
he is a very popular singer in America
I’m not going to discount
So 5 pm
See you
do you work for TV?
I want many people to listen to his music
If there is a deficit, it will make up for it
I always feel sorry
For what?
I lie to my customers.
Everyone think I am single
I always feel sorry for that
It can't be helped.
It's true
You think so?
all the customers are lying too
How's your business?
I'm in trouble
Look at this
The average monthly sales is 1.2 million yen.
you have a tax problem
I'm in trouble
you should set up a company
I got headache
I recommended it when you open the bar
I'm not a bad like you, so I didn't think about such things.
I can help you with your taxes
You?
I have never given you financial assistance
I don't want to receive money like a mistress
We don't have a family register relationship with money
Hi Ozeki
Your friend?
That's right
Don't worry.
No one know you
I'm just wearing clean clothes and acting nice
I'm like a doll in a shop window
You can't do business without sacrificing something
Men's businesses don't care about that, do they?
No way.
We give it a shot
don't be afraid to take risks
I plan to bring Elvis Presley to Japan next year.
no one has ever done
It costs a lot
I plan to bring him to Japan and set a lot of expensive entrance fees.
I am always worried about your business
It deserves.
I want to bring a world-famous singer to Japan.
I'll give it a shot
life is like gambling
what are you thinking about ?
I was thinking of breaking up with you
breaking up?
Seeing you satisfied makes me feel lonely
You feel like you don't need me.
have you ever thought about breaking up?
Never
I stop over thinking
I heard about the sale of a bar in Ginza last night.
would you recommend it to me?
Is it ok if I go to Tokyo?
I think business doesn't have to be in Osaka.
I hate kitahara
I never thought that I would go from Tokyo to Osaka to marry and become a bar madam.
How's Kitahara now?
He visited me last day
I think he wants to marry you again
I have no idea.
He's just a friend now
He is my classmate and a very nice person.
stop talking about him
What if he knows about us?
I met you for the first time when he asked me to talk about his work with you.
It was right after I started working at Utsumi
You worked so hard at that time
That's my way
A lot has happened since then
What if Mr. Kitahara asked for it when he got married, not when he got divorced...
I could marry you
If I had no wife
I wanna marry you
This is the first time I heard about your marriage.
I'm not thinking about marriage so don't worry
I'm not a diplomat like your wife
I don't speak a foreign language
your wife is needed for your job
It might be so
but she doesn't know anything about art
do you know this word?
Please treat the person who comes to the bar and speaks ill of his wife appropriately.
In short,customers like that are trash
You are that kind of person too?
I see you as a woman
I see. I want to have your baby
What the hell?
Women want to have children with the person they love.
But I can't take six months off to have a baby
So don't worry
Time files
when will you return?
I'll board at 4pm
I'll drop you off at Haneda
don't worry.
I don't like it
I'm free on 23rd
Fine
See you
Stupid.
What if someone come?
I don't care
You are bad baby
We're Ozaki production
Good morning
Is that ok?
Don't worry
I got a call from Arai of Nippon Television.
He'll be late
we were having a meeting
All right
We're about to finish it
I heard that the new exchange clerk was his father's subordinate.
I invited him to dinner for business
That's good for us
You wanna join us?
I'll leave it to you
You're meeting with the embassy at 9 o'clock, aren't you?
That's right
I will meet you when my work is finished.
I invite them to a nightclub
I'm going
This drink is good for your health
Why?
You look tired today
You think so?
I knew you were in Utsumi
I worked there as trainee
I wanna go there
have you never been?
It is difficult for Tokyo people to go where Osaka people are.
I don't think so
Everyone who spends money is a customer
I'll show you
Thanks
But it costs a lot
Please spend a lot of money
Nobu..come
I heard that you've been collecting business cards from your customers lately.
It's none of your business
If you quit your job, tell me plainly
Thanks
we are like outsiders.
Madam doesn't greet us
But there are a lot of customers
Welcome
What do you want?
Here's liquor looks expensive
Oh you are here
How're you?
I eat a lot of good food with the public's tax dollars.
how is your business?
We're all right
Not as busy as this bar
I think this bar will be closed soon.
The bar here is overpriced
You talk badly
I like the young sexy women in your bar
Oh Nobu?
I forgot her name but she has nice figure
Shall we leave?
Yeah
Oh Madam is coming
He's our customer. Ichimura
Welcome
you are prosperous in business
Thanks
Can you get out?
I don't want to tell you this but,You guys should not do obscene services
About Nobu?
I want people who used to work at this store to do their jobs correctly.
Sorry, I tell it to her
That's Ok.
I wanna ask you something
where do you get your whiskey from?
From Meiji and Omaki
You do?
Yes me and Ecchan
I think you will make a good purchase, but please don't sell too cheap.
Customers say we are expensive
Mr.Ishi told me about it earlier
he has a foul mouth
Not only him
everyone compares to your bar
There are price quotes in the area.
Sorry
I'm counting on you
Hello?
What's wrong? It's already 1p.m.
I was going to call you
A black agent asked me to rescind the contract.
Oh I'm sorry
I can imagine that you are in a lot of trouble
I'm serious
If the concert cannot be held, there will be a loss of 20 million yen.
Why do you laugh?
I’m laughing at myself.
I thought it was time to say goodbye while I was waiting here
I was telling myself that
We gonna break up?
No no
When I imagine you in trouble, I think you need me
I fly home.
Don't worry. good luck
good morning
Ecchan has not come yet?
well
Are you Toshiko Ikuta?
Yes
I belong to the Shoneza Police Station
What?
I've been looking for you since this morning, but you weren't at the apartment.
Where have you been?
can you come to the police?
we don't want to interfere with business
A bartender named Ejiri also says that
Ecchan too?
I don't understand anything.
is it okay to talk here
you should pay attention to the eyes around you
There was a IBON of shochu
this label is new
Welcome
We close today, sorry
please come another day, sorry
Please turn off the light on the signboard
you guys go home
No no
Please wait here until the investigation is over.
After all, you should go to the police station
I don't mind doing it here
Do you know a man named Hatanaka?
No
I know,right?
Lots of fake whiskey sold by his minions from here.
Look
fake whiskey
He is missing after going to Haneda Airport.
I have nothing to do with that
What?
You were also on the same plane at 2 o'clock this morning.
I wasn't with him
who were you with?
Alone
why should I tell you about my private affairs?
We need to know
we checked with the airline.
I heard that you often fly to Tokyo.
where did you go after haneda airport?
If you don't tell me, you have to go to POLICE
I wasn't with him
who were you with?
An employee here tells us all about it.
Tell us
Even if you keep quiet, I think Madam has already spoken.
Tell us where is Hatanaka?
Oh, you love the Madam?
you pretend not to know.
but we already have proof
who informed you?
Who?
I'm sure someone from Utsumi
you had better talk quickly
Who did you meet before you got off from Haneda Airport and boarded the plane at 4:00?
I was at the beach hotel in Hayama.
who were you with?
Alone
Alone?
I’m not lying
Were you alone before you went to the hotel?
Just check the hotel's phone and we'll find it.
Bar's MADAM sells fake whiskey
You are lying.
Not Hatanaka, but our customer
Who's he?
Ozeki
But he has nothing to do with this
You date with your customer?
Is that bad?
From Sanezaki police
I'm Kurokawa
Ok I get it
What?
He confessed and they were able to locate the killer.
That's good
He'll go back
I see
Sorry to disturb you.
We might ask you to go for the court. Say hello to the Ozaki
You can open your bar
What should we do?
Close the bar today
You guys go home
Excuse me
Pass me the salt
Main suspect in fake whiskey case arrested
She is a disgrace to the UTSUMI Society. Our whiskey is also suspect.
Good morning.
Did you really get permitted from Toshiko?
Ishii also asked me about you.
Anyway work hard
I guess you've had the fake whiskeys
It might be so
I don't think she does not know
It seems she is selling her bar
It's a tough business
Customers were given fake whiskey to drink.
I'm not going to pay for the follow-up payment.
Everyone say that
That's too bad not to pay
We're talking about her bar
She's pity
She's beautiful, but her heart is filthy.
You talk so badly
Sorry
Your bar is always busy
The people who moved out of her bar are not like you people.
You talk so badly
We earn from them a lot
Oh my god
Many businesses are expanding from Osaka to Tokyo
On the contrary, businesses from Tokyo to Osaka will fail.
I think that's the problem
I have no idea
In short, around here, Tokyo style bar is only you
So Local people might envy you
I don't wanna think about it
I wanna ask you about the call girl
I told you not to talk about it
But write what you want.
It makes PR for our bar
It can't be helped.
Sorry to disturb you
Let's go
Who's he?
Nothing
Let's open bar
Yes
Welcome
Thanks
It was urgent business
They demanded discounts on store sales.
So much
Phone call from Ozaki, Tokyo
Hi it's me. I was going to call you
How's the deal?
Can you sell?
How much
3 million, I'll negotiate, but 3.5 million is limited
It's too urgent.
The manager of bar does not wanna sell under 4 million
They are 1st class bar
You need to go to Tokyo
People in Tokyo talks about us?
Tokyo people likes such a bar.
Do you wanna see it?
Leave it to me?
So I can decide?
Don't worry. cheer up.
That's not so you
Are you going out?
I need to talk
Talk me later
You gonna lie again?
I'm not
Now you can't talk about me
What do you mean?
Or something happens?
It's none of your business
I decided not to break up
I haven't said that before
You were shocked
Everyone get shocked to read the article
I didn't see the act, so I gonna trust you
People think we are really husband and wife, OK?
What your wife said about us?
It's not your business
I wanna know about it first
I'm glad you came even though you're busy
I cried when you got off the plane from Itami Airport.
You stupid
I was under a lot of pressure
That's not so you
The customer disappeared like the fire went out
Because of whiskey?
About me
they found out I had a lover
I'm horned
I've been putting up with it, but now I want to quit this job.
birds are singing
you always say different topics when I'm in trouble
I'm glad I came to Kyoto.
I like this slope
This place is the same as when I came here on a school trip.
here's always quiet
Please don't fall when you go up this slope.
Why?
It is said that if you fall here, you will die in three years.
I don't mind dying but I don't want to leave you
It tastes good
It's been a while I relax
I hear the temple bell
here's always quiet
This is all thanks to that incident.
That might have been a good opportunity to leave Osaka.
How's Ginza bar like?
A little smaller than the current bar
The name is Lizo?
Shall I change the name?
Same name chatole is better
People in Tokyo like unusual things.
I'm worried about whether I can work in Ginza.
I know you are confident
Don't make fun of me
Anyway, let's find an apartment in Tokyo
what kind of woman am I to you?
am I your mistress?
do you want to decide your position clearly?
Excuse me
bath ready
Please prepare a taxi to itami
I see
I deposited 3 million yen
I will pay the other party as soon as I go to Tokyo.
The remaining 1 million yen will be returned after the store opens.
when will I see you again?
I don't know yet so far
I was surprised that Ozaki was your lover.
You can go home
You get out them?
It's time to close
Excuse me
please clean up tomorrow
This is bookkeeping
Excuse me
Please go to the police station tomorrow and give this to Ecchan
he likes this sushi
You can go home too
scary mom is waiting for you
I don't care
So wife
She's not my wife
she was taken by my mother.
we live together but it's like another world
If you were like you are now, we wouldn't have divorced.
I was born in an ordinary family.
I knew that if I married into your family, I would have a hard time.
But I married you because I liked you
But you valued your business more than me
I am out of the house now.
I have another job now
I couldn't stand your unhappiness
I did bad to you.
I won't blame to Ozeki
Can we live together again?
I will return to Tokyo this month and open a shop in Ginza.
Did you sell this bar?
You have been deceived by Mr. Ozaki
I love you so much
It's too late
Please don't go to Tokyo and work with me.
I'm thinking of starting a company that makes bottle crowns.
I think this is good business
Will you invest me about 1 million yen?
I know you have money
I bought a store in Ginza, so I have no money.
Good evening
Oh Madam
you're closing the store early
Yes these days
I wanted to go to your shop, but I didn't have a chance to come.
I'll come again
Think about it
Your ex husband?
Did I disturb you?
No no
You got hard time
I heard that you will open a store in Ginza.
I can't live in Osaka anymore
sometimes bad things happen when you do business
When I started my current business, there were times when customers stopped coming due to various difficulties.
now is the time for you.
Stay strong
Thanks
I'm thinking of holding a meeting to console you today.
Mr. Ishii gave the idea
He has a foul mouth, but he is very kind-hearted.
I'm sorry I can't go
Why?
I don't feel like
do you still doubt me?
do you think I reported to the police?
Come in and talk to her
I'm sorry,
I reported the counterfeit whiskey to the police.
When that man deceived me, I thought, but I didn't think it was such a big incident.
Do you get it?
She told my bar staff about it last night.
Please forgive her
sorry I’m late to tell you
Mr.Ishii is playing at a night club now
Shall we go?
Sure
Where have you been?
we weren't supposed to interfere with each other
What the hell?
Ozeki Productions may go bankrupt
I received a letter from his manager by airmail.
He will be performing in Europe, so he won't be able to come to Japan.
Penalty is only $30,000.
It's too cheap
He will pay the penalty and work on better terms.
After all, it was better to work through an agency in New York as my dad said.
Next time I will go to America and speak directly
Damn it.
If he doesn't come, even if I get a penalty, I will lose 10 million yen.
Are you Ikuta?
My name is Miura, who was introduced to you by Mr. OZEKI about Ginza bar
Welcome. come in
I have to catch the train soon.
I just happen to stop by
can I get the money by the end of this month?
Money?
You haven't get it yet?
I gave Mr. Ozaki 3 million yen a week ago.
I see.
I would like to cancel if I don't receive the money today or tomorrow.
Something wrong.
I'll contact you soon
I will wait till tomorrow
Hi
This is Ozaki Pro
Is Ozaki in?
business trip?
what are his plans?
Hold on
A woman is asking the president's business trip schedule.
Who?
From Osaka
Sorry for keeping you waiting
After going to Kobe, he plans to return to Tokyo later today.
Who is it?
I'm glad you stayed home.
I got free time
you live in a very nice apartment.
I think it's very expensive here in Tokyo.
I'm busy with work and haven't looked for your apartment in Tokyo yet.
Never mind.
You have time today?
I have to go back to Tokyo by the end of today
I can't stay till night
I think you were in Kobe
How you know?
I called your office
I heard your wife's voice for the first time
Did you pay that money?
Not yet
Why?
I have to find out before I make a mistake
Oh I see
What's wrong?
Nothing
I got a visa, so I suddenly decided to go to America.
So I stopped by
When?
Next week
They canceled the contract for the concert in Japan.
If I don't negotiate before it's published, I'll be a failure.
I urgently have to go to America and negotiate.
With your wife?
It might be so
She's helpful
What kind of things do you research about bars in Ginza?
I met the owner today, but she's confused.
Who?
Madam called Miura
when did you meet her?
Before I left Haneda Airport, I met her around 10 o'clock this morning.
Are you sure?
Yeah
Why?
She visited me just before
It seems that she has been at Kobe since last night.
She said that if we don't pay by tomorrow, she will sell the shop to someone else.
why did you tell me it was her this morning?
sorry for lying to you
I'm sorry not to tell you honestly
I had to make amends for breaking the contract.
About 16 million advance tickets have already been sold.
Agent found out it
I gave them that 3,000,000 yen for future work.
you should have told me the truth
I thought I could make that money right away
I needed to pay.
But it's okay if I get a penalty
were you going to go to America without leaving me the truth?
I didn't mean that.
I was going to go to Kobe and tell you about it when the problem was solved.
I thought you would understand.
There are many bar properties for sale.
My job is a one-time important job
Don't worry about the money
I didn't know you were that kind of person
I can live without money
I have no problem giving you 3 million yen.
I’m confused you lied to me
This is for my work
You are a business owner, so you should know the importance of money.
do you really think so?
this is how business goes
I understand why you can't divorce your wife
I feel sorry for your wife.
you are using your wife for work
It's none of your business
You’re right
you are me and your wife are stupid
I endured until today
I never thought I would part with you like this
I thought you understood my job
thank you so much for taking care of me
are you going home?
Thank you for what you have done
welcome back.
you've had a hard time
thank you
I'm sorry for worrying you
You were in detention center but you look fine
I didn't take a bath so I took a bath
Today is the last day, so let's have a comfort party for him.
last day?
Yeah last day
here it is
I want to drink
I want to eat sushi
I want to eat tuna
I thought you bought that whiskey thinking it was fake
Me?
No way
I understand you so much
I was crying while eating sushi in the detention center.
take it easy and have a drink
are you guys drinking?
there's no seats
you are still in Kobe.
I will introduce about her
she's my girlfriend.
she's young
take it easy
here it is
I heard you were his ex-wife
I have to tell you I live with him now
See you
What the hell?
thank you
you should stay with her
I'm busy with my boyfriend
what's the a hell that you guys are talking about?
I'm alright
Ozeki
Madam
don't stay here
leave me alone
I want to go die
Good morning
you sleep good
why you are upset?
sorry but can you go home?
forget about our relationship
it was just happening last night
Madam
I’ve always liked you.
I made that incident my own responsibility for you.
I know
I couldn't stand holding you last night
I was so sad last night
you can laugh at me
I could sleep with anyone who comforted me
I couldn't stand
Did you assume that I was Mr. Ozaki?
you are free to think
Madam
I really love you
don't tell me anything
forget what happened last night
Hello? Madam is there?
Unzen in Kyushu
You took long trip
I thought you went back in Osaka
I think your money will be back.
I will start again in Osaka if I were you
I can buy bar in Osaka gain but I worry our reputation
That's the point.
Osaka people are very sympathetic
I think they will forget what happens if you work hard
You can't go halfway.
But I really worry
You made good business in Osaka
But I advise you,
Don't fall in love with your customers
Bar women can't love them.
You can't get money from those who you love
This is your business.
Men are money
You have a guest?
He's my husband
She's ex worker, Toshiko
I'm Toshiko
Nice to meet you
Invite her to our room
How was your walk?
I got good idea
Leftover food can be used for pickles, but leftover whiskey can't be used for anything.
But whiskey has alcohol in it, so I think it's worth using.
I gonna study about it
That's good
I plan to bring together university professors to study it.
It's too hot
I gonna take a bath
Come here,Toshiko
Are you surprised?
I thought you found out
This is who I am, Rie Utsumi
He supported to open my bar
Man and woman usually do that
He's popular money lender
But he is not educated
You can laugh at him
Being Bar madam is stupid
I pretend to be nice in Osaka but I need money to the end
We have to sacrifice something.
We have to win against men
Can I work at Utsumi?
Do you wanna work with me again?
I wanna start over until I settle down
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I will give the money back
I'll get them
I know our relationship is over now
I'll come back in 5 days if everything goes well
We should meet again
I had a hard time.
I didn't tell you I wanted to be your wife
But you were mine in my heart
I thought to myself that all I needed was to have fun.
It was hard to keep it
I can no longer live a lie.
toshiko
Break up with me
THE END