Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Sensei
Onsen Joi / Hot Springs Lady (1964)
Thank you very much for coming.
Welcome.
I'll show you around
Hey.
Dear!
Where is the doctor?
I think he's coming soon.
A customer fainted.
I'll call him.
What's the hell?
She has high blood pressure.
hello, doctor, this is Matsunoe Ryokan
Is there a doctor?
Thank you very much.
Hana-chan, come on.
what happened?
What happened?
Newlywed bride collapses in the bathtub.
So she's naked then
She's totally naked,
hey, where are you going?
Sense is coming.
Madam, the
It's true. he's come here leisurely
Here's fine.
Where's doctor?
I'm checking out.
Come on.
What's the hell?
Come on
Wake up.
Oh no.
Doctor.
This way.
Water.
Thank you so much, doctor
Doctor is here.
Pleases see her.
Have a water.
You are still drinking water.
Let me see.
what are you doing?
Stay away.
It's cold when she's naked
Pleases see her.
Hurry up.
please hurry up
doctor is here.
Don't worry
Don't stay in bath too long.
It's no big deal.
She's the patient.
Oh her.
Calm down
Don't look at it.
Hey you.
Stay strong.
what's wrong with you?
Secchan
Give me another water.
I need to see a doctor too.
Hurry up.
These pills are 3 years old.
I wonder it works.
Medicine for high blood pressure is nothing more than a placebo
But you can't take urgent doctor's visit anymore.
I'm too old.
Telling me to work any more is the same as telling me to die
Don't say that.
We need you.
There's no doctor else in this town
It's none of my business.
Even though it's a hot spring town, there isn't a single doctor here even though there are 70 or 80 people employed here
If you suddenly died at any moment, the local hospital would be in trouble, so it would be a disaster
It might be happening.
Bring dishes for no.8 table.
What about the story we talked about before?
so I asked a friend in Tokyo
I received a postcard from this friend saying he found a substitute and will be coming over in a couple of days
Well, he's not coming
Here's too boring.
Because he hates me.
What are you talking about?
Doctor get paid, so someone will come.
Doctor
Is there a more effective medicine?
Well, why don't you quit smoking?
No I mean..
There's no medicine for that
Your wife is too young.
If you push yourself too hard, you'll end up falling over
There's still a lot of life ahead of me.
Customer number six would like to receive an injection
Another mahjong customer?
Yes, he's been up all night since yesterday and he's lacking vitamins,
Say him if he sleeps, he'll get better right away,
so don't say that, just go and see him
Hey you know who I am?
but at times like this
If only your son Masaki would be here.
He's not to be trusted
He was born as the only son of a doctor, but he hates doctors
doctor, if you keep fighting around forever
You have to made up
We are no longer fighting
He loves bees
He let home and keep them.
But even though he went to medical school,
he was only able to live with bees
I guess he's better than people here
Are you home, doctor?
Whenever I'm here, I stay long.
Sorry I didn't take care of you.
So, Mrs., your husband...
He’s getting older, so please take care of him from now on
customers from union has not come yet?
They hasn't come yet.
Something might be happened about bus
Oh my god.
We need more hands.
Push the bus.
Let's push it together.
I'll try it again.
Please cooperate
Damn it.
It's close.
Sorry
I would like to ask everyone
Please help us.
Please.
I would like to ask all customers to please go outside and help out
It can't be helped.
Let's go.
Well, I guess we'll push this bus and make a leisurely lunch later
Hey wake up.
This person was leaning on me
What?
We haven't arrived yet?
Bus got troubled.
I see. I'll go out.
Oh, I see. sorry
Thank you very much.
Please get on the bus
thank you
Everyone wait, the
condition of the engine is bad.
This happens once in 3 days these days
After all, it's a luxury car for transfers
It's just a showy car.
Our company won't buy it
What's wrong?
What's wrong with your face?
Clean your face.
you're actually quite kind.
I just can't bear to watch you
Are you alone?
The car isn't moving yet.
Sorry
Please wait a little longer
It seems like you're in a hurry
Will I walk?
There must be hot springs.
Why don't you take your time?
Please have some.
Don't be hesitate.
Thank you very much.
Well, I guess I had one too
Excuse me.
The doctor is here?
Yes he's here.
but it's your first visit?
I got pregnant.
Take it.
Take care.
I got pregnant.
Do you wanna see a doctor?
Before that, I have something to discuss with Doctor.
Please,
it looks like a patient is here
Don't pretend you can't hear.
Doctor,please.
She's first visiting.
Hold her wait.
Doctor, it seems like you have another patient
Hold on
Doctor?
What's wrong?
the visit doctor has just arrived
Really?
Apparently, He left Tokyo in this morning.
He must be tried.
doctor, hurry up, doctor,
that's good
Please be polite.
He's not a customer, so this is fine
That's true, but this is not good.
I don't have to change.
Make sure you wear a jacket.
He left Tokyo in this morning.
So now They found a doctor soon.
I thought no one might come.
What kind of doctor was he?
I can't say anything extravagant
I'm sure the doctor is an elderly man who doesn't mind a country bumpkin doctor.
Sorry for keeping wait
I'm Isao shiozuki
Nice to meet you,
Are you the substance doctor?
Please use it.
it's nostalgic and Shota has bad writing.
Long time no see.
Let me introduce Shiotsuki Isao right away.
As you can see, she is a beautiful doctor
doctor
As you can see, she is a beautiful woman, and if I had to mention one flaw,
She hates men.
That's not much.
Please ask her academic history and career history
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
Well, what are you doing, doctor? Anyway,
please come in.
Umm,  Omura and Kosaka
Bring her luggage.
I thought old doctor would come.
I'm just a beginner,
I'm glad you came here.
Please finish your chat and make some tea
please come in.
Make some tea.
I know.
Hurry up.
What about me?
Are you a patient?
You made me wait
Anyway, let's have a look
Please.
even though it's a welcome party, this
is the only thing we can do around here,
the vegetables are very fresh
Our doctor makes everything by hand
I'm more farmer than doctor.
Please have a drink.
She can't drink.
Just little.
He wants to drink.
What's the hell?
Don't drink anymore.
You've already had 3 bottles.
four bottle.
You've drunk four bottles.
Should I take your blood pressure?
You're drunk.
It's okay
Actually I think There's no good substance doctor.
Don't say that.
Old doctor or female doctor
or someone else.
so which one am I?
doctor, let's take a little rest here
I want another one.
you'll get scolded by your wife.
Where's his wife?
His wife passed away more than ten years ago
She worries about his drinking until the day she died
She told me to take care of him.
Don't say bullshit.
Osaka-san, no, no, it's fine
Serve me.
If that's the case, then leave it.
Aren't you my friend?
Stay strong.
Please have some.
Well then, I can not drink.
would you like one?
Me?
Thanks.
When it comes to alcohol, She can't resist it
You know about me so much.
please take care of us
I am working here on and off.
Who?
Shut up!
I wondered who it was, maybe it was a thief, but it was you
Masahiko?
It's gotten pretty cold
so I came to get some clothes,
I told you no to come home
Don't say that.
I don't wanna see him
I thought I would be thin again, but I wanted to see my father's face
Oh?
He's my son,Masahiko.
My face is really funny?
I'm not saying it's weird
As for the level?
It's kind of funny.
What score?
Okay then your face is 20 points
Did you sell my honey?
It's no good, we can't sell it at all
If it's easy to buy as a souvenir.
What are you talking about?
This is good as a souvenir
Yokan and Manju are too common as souvenir
No matter how you say
We can't sell it.
OK, have a drink.
Treat me?
No way
Well, I'm busy for a bit now, so take a bath before that
I took bath.
When?
last month
You're crazy
Let's have fun.
Your friend has visit you.
What a friend
Hey you
We'll have drink.
Why don't you join us?
Really?
You guys should go upstairs
I think one person is fine.
It can't be helped.
Hey you please stay here.
Thanks.
You're awesome.
What's your name?
Don't ask my name.
Why?
She’s cool.
Hime-chan, that's rude
She's Yabuuchi's substance doctor.
Hello?
Nice to meet you.
When we met on the bus,
I never expected that you would be visiting us.
I didn't expect too.
I'm Yabuuchi's son.
Sister.
Where's patient's room?
It's over there.
Actually, I wanna ask you about the patient.
I'll talk to you after
I'm sorry
Doctor is here?
I wonder what happened
Thanks for your hard work.
If you had come a little earlier...
She would have died?
No.
Up until now, she's been sitting on my lap
Now she is finally sleeping soundly
Anyway, let's have a look
Is she here?
She's troublesome.
Is she your daughter?
Oh you are awake?
Well, Lili-chan, she'll see you
She's the patient?
Yes
She can't poo these days
So,
I thinking that maybe if I put her in this hot spring,
she would improve a little,
but that was a big mistake
If that's the case,ask veterinarian.
I don't care if you see her.
That would be a problem for me
Hey, are you going back?
But I'm not veterinarian
But listen to me.
What's the hell?
I don't care if you see her.
so I wonder how many times I have to tell you.
But I'm not veterinarian
Does that mean
You let my daughter die?
No, that is different matter.
What's different?
I'm going to kill this dog?
What's the hell about her.
This is the first time I've ever been insulted like this.
I wish you had made it clear from the beginning that it was the other person's dog
Sorry, that's what we thought
Well, please, she is our regular customer.
Why don't you leave common sense?
Don't get mad.
No
I don't think it's a big deal.
even if it's just over a dog
It's a huge insult.
I wonder what doctors is.
I don't think you need to think so seriously
I don't want to do it at all
Doctor.
She's leaving.
what should we do?
Oh my god. Hey you, go away
Me?
Okamura.
it seems you're in a lot of pain.
That's right.
Whatever happened, Painful rashes on buttocks
There is also a slight fever
Are you a doctor?
Genkichi Okamura, 50 years old, fishmonger. you drink alcohol
Okay, let's take a look
Where to take a look?
Painful rashes?
But that's the place isn't good.
Don't worry.
well...I'm embarrassed.
Let me see.
this is a common tumor
I'm embarrassed.
I can take care of this.
Omura-san, help me
You'll cut it off?
There's no scalpel.
I think there are some.
But this is damaged.
Oh yeah.
This is all we have.
it's fine even if it's just a little cut.
please wait over there for a bit and we'll sterilize it right away
He is here?
Who?
Doctor.
Injection, injection, it's the usual one
Anyway, please showed me
Tell him about that.
Oh boss, why are you showing your butt?
She's a doctor.
I thought she was a nurse.
That's true, she's being cool.
It's just a little prick.
You cut up the fish.
Ok done.
Oh, you don't have to be so arrogant
Because I'm always like that.
Oh, I see. Mimi-san from the nude studio
Don't drink a lot.
I don't drink that much
Wait.
What's the hell?
No
But you are lucky.
For what?
You found good substance doctor.
Is it because of that substitute doctor that we can play Go like this
And she's pretty beautiful too
She's never had this?
Don't worry about that.
If I was younger, I would seduce her.
Welcome home.
Was it cold?
What are you talking about?
You would seduce her?
Yeah, there's no other option than this
Please reconsider.
If I was going to reconsider,
I wouldn't bother coming
But it's three-month-old baby.
Thinking about the abortion.
I don't want baby.
I'm realistic.
If I give birth to a child , I will be no longer Geisha.
But that's a different matter.
I won't ask you again
What do you mean?
I don't need to rely on doctors anymore.
Decided that
There are more doctors than just here
Mamefuku.
God gave you this baby
So before that, think about it once more
I have nothing to do with God.
I became a hot spring geisha
My body is all I need
Hello?
This is Yabuuchi clinic.
Your doctor collapsed
Our doctor collapsed?
Is it true that our doctor collapsed?
What's wrong?
Our doctor collapsed.
Is he dying?
It's not a big deal
Does he have blood pressure?
Acute alcohol toxicity
That means he drank too much
That's why I said.
I know I'll get scolded
Hey, hey, that was the doctor we talked about
Oh she.
I see,
Why you are impressed?
My boss is into her lately and he always talk about her.
Hello?
What's wrong?
She's Kichiya.
Nice to meet you.
Oh Kichiya.
You're so cute
She's doctor.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go
Doctor.
Don't talk about it
Oh, but don't push yourself
I understand.
Is it ok to wake up?
The doctor told you to sleep.
Omura has taken over this month's accounting
How was the Results?
Sales have doubled
The income has almost doubled.
But you know, that's not too big deal.
Why?
It's because of how bad are you.
Shiotsuki is how skilled she is
I see, that may be the case
doctor, why don't you make her your wife?
I think you make a good couple.
It would be silly
if I married someone young like her,
The public would laugh at me.
Don't get me wrong.
I mean,
What do you think about Masahiko's wife?
Oh for Masahiko
It's about time for Masahiko to get married.
Grandma
Masahiko has nothing to do with us.
I remember it well,
so don't say things like that in front of me.
I'm annoyed,
He's better than you.
What?
I am a decent person.
He's totally idiot.
Why she makes Red rice?
We don't have time.
Do I need to put this in?
Oh,
Who is it?
Today is your son's birthday
He's not here.
Why you cook red rice for?
hurry up.
Are you alright?
Don't eat too much at once
By the way
Oh baby?
I wonder if that many folding boxes
Make some rice balls, Bring some water.
What are you doing?
Don't do anything like that.
I don't do that
Your blood pressure is rising again
he's coming.
What do you have?
I'll give everyone one onigiri
It's delicious.
Give me.
It's delicious?
It's delicious.
I know.
it's definitely tasty.
Don't fight.
Enjoy eating.
Get along.
Oh she's coming!
It's 5 days, playing Mahjong.
So, what should I do?
Here it is.
Sorry, please. Thank you
Excuse me.
The doctor is here.
Oh.
Who is patient?
What's wrong?
I switched it off
Are you here to bother us?
I'm not here to watch mahjong.
Because you won't stop.
She's cool.
Let's keep playing.
wait a second.
Why did you guys call me?
we need a doctor when we are collapse.
Why do you want to play mahjong so badly?
We're playing for Naomi.
Naomi?
It's me
They'll propose to me at the same time
I can't help it.
Whoever win, get me.
You get it?
Maybe if Naomi wins,
the three of us will buy her a car
Where's the money for a car?
There's no money.
Do you do thief?
I'll blackmailed my mother.
I cheated my dad out
You make your parents pay for it anyway
In short, yes.
We all depend on our parents.
If parents don't give us money, then they have no value
They Always angry
They don't know the reality
It's usually empty here
Were you not born from such parents?
No one wants them to give birth
stop with that old rant.
What?
You live an unhealthy lifestyle
We are young.
Everyone has had a youthful time
Your parents too
Youth is not a privilege
You ended up getting drunk.
Come, put out your arms
I'll get you an injection to win Mahjong
So everyone, wake up, wake up,
The rice balls are ready?
They are sleeping now.
I gave them a sedative injection.
And if they have any complaints later, please let me know
I apologize for the inconvenience
This is our business so It's hard to decline.
Chiyo
Please come over for a moment. Mamefuku is in trouble.
She drinks a lot
You act like a real husband when you are in a good mood
Are you pretending you don't know now
Don't get me wrong.
I know, I know
I am a bit busy right now
so what do you know?
Although now I am a hot spring geisha
I used to work in Shinbashi a long time ago
I know, I know
I'll discuss that later
Yeah, you crazy idiot
What's the hell?
You bastard!
I'm a bit busy.
What happened?
I'm frustrated.
Here's your water.
The person was mamefuku's husband?
He's mean.
I'm sorry about that
He's a salesman for Belial cosmetics
You need to be careful too
Why did you become Geisha? I'm sorry to ask you.
doctor, I actually wanted to be a nurse,
Oh really?
but We were poor
I didn't get into nursing school.
Sorry to ask you.
It's okay.
But I plan to save up a lot of money and go to school someday
Until then, I'll do my best.
I guess you are nice.
You think so?
This is the best place,
I haven't cleaned this place yet.
Is that so?
show me the photo?
No
Show me.
Oh, it's only kimono person.
Yeah
Your girlfriend?
She may become like that in the future.
It's a long-term story
My girl, Kichiya.
Stay strong.
I love you
I can't stand to hear your story.
Wait a minute
Actually, what can I ask you? I want to tell her how I feel
Is there any way to do that?
You're going to do it yourself
If I could do that, I wouldn't call you.
I'm your best friend
Let me see...
Let's have drink before that.
You're looking at my feet
Here's crowed.
What illness are you suffering from here?
My eyes is messed up.
stupid, She is not an ophthalmologist.
Don't drink alcohol. About an injection,
but it doesn't work that often
I can't make money just by being naked
Thanks.
I caught a fish, so I thought I'd give them some to eat
Just something small.
Are you sick?
My eyes is messed up.
Are you here?
Who? Taihei?
Taihei?
Your illness is still not cured?
So I am here.
Let's have some.
What's this?
This is honey
This is good for your health.
Let's have some.
No way
I'm not a child, so I can't even lick honey
Try it
Well,This looks good.
Drink it
You're very thoughtful
but are you ok?
I'm doctor too.
I know that very well
What are you talking about?
I received such a wonderful fish from Mr. Ume
This is a fine fish, so make some sashimi right away
Honey and sashimi is strange
Did you know?
My ears are fine
Damn it.
I wanna see him.
Where are you guys from?
I'm in trouble with him
What's wrong?
Shut up!
She's busy.
What are you guys all fussing about?
Hey, What are you going to do with us?
I guess we're carrying too much
what I did to you guys?
You've been up all night for 5 days
So I gave you guys a sedative.
That was bad
But if you hadn't it,
you would have gotten really sick
We had been sleeping for 3 days.
It's none of our business.
So, it seems like your fatigue has been relieved
Everyone looks good, don't they?
That's the problem, we don't have the budget,
we can't pay it
This is all your fault, I swear
You have to take responsibility
I have to charge you guys.
What?
You haven't paid me for the consultation.
How can you pay for me?
Please pay.
I'm busy.
Damn it.
so I'll pay for the young people's fee.
I was definitely the one who gave the injection
Here you go
I think that we can't get it from you.
Everything is over.
But that's not enough for me, so please
I see. Then how about we do it like this?
You take our bath, and have a meal.
So We'll take this.
But.
it would be nice.
I think it's better for you to relax  sometimes.
Come to think of it, I haven't had a chance to relax in a hot spring since I came here
I think I'll be bored by night
Please.
I think that's fine.
Oh, right,  can you call a Geisha?
Eh? For you?
Excuse me.
Come in.
Good evening
Are you alone?
You kept quiet.
I'm confused.
I think I'll just ask you.
What?
You know, Are you thinking of marrying?
Marriage?
the union of a man and a woman
What do you think?
I'm confused.
Is that so? I'm having trouble too
But have you ever loved someone before?
I don't really like fat people
Oh yeah, you don't like fat people, so you don't like fat people
He's skinny, so that's ok
What are your hobbies?
My hobbies?
Sports Music Movies and Movies etc
I like Music.
Movies?
Movies...
TV is better?
I don't like both.
Money is better
I can go to school, so
please excuse me.
here it is.
I need this.
Jun?
Yes.
Oh, you're late
Yeah, I couldn't let go for a while .
I tested her.
Have a seat.
Don't worry.
this girl is nice.
I see
Oh, what are you talking about?
Oh, sorry, sorry
Actually, everything I've been testing you.
Actually, he is really in love with you
You don't have to say that in front of her.
He really wants to date you
I took your character test on his behalf
Don't worry about it.
Are you mad?
Well, my business is done
Please talk to each other.
Stay here.
I guess no one will be there when you go home
The bees are waiting for me.
Excuse me.
Sorry, there is a call.
Yes, the doctor is here?
in this room
I've come all the way to this nice
place, but now there's a call, that's weird.
I'm sorry to call you out.
It's okay.
Have a drink
Me?
Didn't you drink?
She brought it to me.
Just one please.
Yeah.
This is good.
Let's have one more
Men are like this tatami rooms,
What kind of things do you talk about with the guys?
There're many things.
For example?
I feel embarrassed
Tell me.
For example, the previous customer...
He was still a good one.
All men do that, right?
I see.
Here it is.
Oh thief!
Help us!
What's wrong?
Be careful.
Why you tired of peeking into other people's rooms?
He seduces her without my permission
But that's a mistake
Yeah.
That is absolutely unforgivable
I'm sorry, please.
In return, I'll listen to whatever you have to say tonight
This is fine, right?
Let's admit it
forgive him.
Yeah,
thank you. So, I'll treat you tonight.
I want Oshiruko.
I want Anmitsu
I want sake
Is it okay?
We won't drink much.
Okay, I will be serving tonight
Hey
Actually, that person has really strange.
He's paying a high education fee, but He sells honey now.
He shouldn't have gone
school from the beginning.
It's a waste.
But life comes with its own problems
There needs to be some waste
It is because of waste that we can do good things in life and it is wonderful
That's right.
So let's have fun.
Yeah!
It can't be helped.
Keep going.
Oh well, it's already twelve o'clock
Yabuki doctor is not here yet?
Not yet.
I'm thirsty.
It would be best if you took a rest
I can't sleep
What's wrong?
Thank you very much.
Take care.
Are you ok?
Good Good.
That's good. Yes, I understand
I'm so happy.
We all drank alcohol
I'm glad that so many geisha danced
doctor, I understand that you like alcohol.
I'm really sorry for being such a nuisance
It's very rare for you to get drunk.
let's drink as much as we can today
Yeah, bring some sake.
After all, waste is necessary in a life.
I studied really well tonight.
Are you ok?
She's fine.
The she tackled.
No no, let's go.
I'm ok.
Leave it to me.
Be careful.
please pick up the pills later
Don't worry about your sick.
See you later
Hey come down!
Everyone is doing well?
Today,Today I'm giving you honey.
Be Quiet!  These are unsold hoeny.
Please come in. I know we are being noisy,
it's such a fun sight that I was just looking at it
It's dirty here.
Here is nursery school?
They are without parents or siblings.
they were particularly poor and orphaned.
Do you take care of them?
No.
This is a government project.
In fact, it is run by a man who sells honey.
so please come in
I'm leaving soon.
I'm making a tea now.
It's about Masahiko,
but he somehow managed to make up with his father?
Well...
Yes, even the relationship between the United States and the Soviet Union is beginning to thaw
I also think it's about time, but they are...
But why you ask me?
It's not a big deal.
But I thought Masahiko had such a good point
That's because I raised him
You are like his mom.
But his father always gets angry at his son.
But he's nice.
He graduated from medical school with honors.
He was highly respected by the female students.
Appearances are not what they seem.
Doctor.
What do you think of a person like Masahiko?
What do you mean?
.
For example, if you had to divide it into likes and dislikes, which would you choose?
Yeah, I don't really dislike him.
Doctor
Look at this.
Is it okay to do something like that?
Yes I am
It's not okay.
Doctor, someone committed suicide.
Suicide?
Now it's okay, it's good now
The amount was small, It was fine
It wasn't serious case.
So there are various reasons why young women commit suicide
this is a special case
She was committing suicide because she can't have a child
You are too happy.
That's what I say. Even if we can't have children,
our love for each other won't change
We can have as many children as we want when we can
That's not true
If you can't have a baby
It means, you lack love as a husband.
I was frustrated by that
You have to sleep quietly
Anyway, she's so emotional
as a husband and a wife,
She wants to have children as proof that.
I don't know how we'll be able to have children
Um, well, you're young so it's okay
So I came here because I heard that this good hot spring for that.
it didn't work?
but it didn't work at all
I feel like I'm getting too tired from taking baths
We sleeps all day and She's finally getting annoyed with me
She says it's my husband's fault.
She was going to die, and finally she took the medicine
Anyway, take care of yourself
You're so cold.
Why?
the problem have not been solved yet?
doctor, please tell me how to have a baby
Don't ask her about that.
After all, that is more God's domain than doctors.
We pray a lot.
I see.
So let me give you this
What's this?
This is female thermometers.
You should rest and take their thermometers from time to time
Just when you got up to this area, It will be good chance.
The conception rate is very high at this time
I didn't know about this.
This is awesome.
However, the responsibility is ultimately on God
Give me one cup.
Oh doctor.
I heard about you.
You were having trouble.
There are people who don't want to have children in the future,
and there are people who want children so badly they're going to die. The world is diverse
doctor, I've decided too
Of course, I'll give a birth.
I've also changed my mind after hearing what you just said,
One tea please.
I'll try to raise him on my own
So you can't take this.
Let's dance.
With you?
You don't feel good ?
I was hit by that couple from earlier
You're getting used to here.
Darling.
The doctor from before was very kind
Why don't you reply?
It was good bath.
Put the slipper off.
I can sleep well tonight.
You are just into sleeping.
We need taking a break.
Oh it's time.
Body temperature increased.
Uh, where?
Oh yeah.
The doctor said that if you get this far, you have a chance
This is our chance.
But it's too soon.
We can't miss this chance!
I'm here to massage...
but did you ask the masseuse?
I didn't expect something like this to happen so suddenly
You are so mean.
See what happens...
Excuse me.
Good morning
Good morning.
I want to give you some juice now.
My head still hurts a little
How about giving her an injection?
It won't work.
At times like this, take a walk
Fortunately, we are closed today
The weather is nice, so let's go for a walk
Walking is also good for high blood pressure.
Maybe I'll show you the source of one of the hot springs?
Thanks.
Do you like this kind of place?
I love this kind of environment
I came out to show you Hot spring source.
Doctor, There is a nursing home where Masahiko works.
I don't know at all.
Please go there.
I don't wanna go.
I don't wanna go either.
You can go there.
I will wait around here.
You are stubborn.
I don't wanna see his face.
Isn't it delicious?
Yeah
It's kinda good.
With a honey tree, some egg yolks,
some garlic and mix it with the queen bee's urine
But it's going to work well, so things will be getting exciting
I see, I'm getting better.
Yes I think so.
It's definitely working.
I'll have this.
Where are you going?
Someone is waiting for me
Oh, you left this.
Thank you.
I'm getting better.
Masahiko-san,
You're good
What for?
You are very good at hypnosis.
Did you just see that?
a cup of honey and egg yolk.
Do you want it?
I'd better not take it, otherwise I'll be in trouble
Actually it works well.
Are you making this?
Oh this?
Indian Jabok is a medicine for high blood pressure.
That's about it
This is for your dad?
I just made it as a test.
You have filial piety.
No way.
What are you doing?
What are you doing too?
Be quiet.
Are you here to see your son?
Don't say stupid things. Who is thinking about him?
Doctor.
This is good for high blood pressure.
Drink it
Bee?
I can't drink it.
You're stubborn.
you are here to see your son.
Be quiet.
You must be tired, doctor
Congratulations!
Read it!
It's from Professor Shiota in Tokyo.
I was pretty sure that your essay was based on the hot spring therapy
Apparently, that was brought up by the professor
So, they really want you to come back to the university,
and I received a letter addressed to you.
Read it.
That's good for you.
I'm glad. Your path has been decided
After all, it's better to study in Tokyo
It's farewell.
It's farewell, let's celebrate.
It's a shame that you've gotten used to it, but there's nothing we can do about it
I'm looking for a new doctor.
Hi, Grandma?
Masahiko is stupid.
Here it is.
Me?
What?
Are you pulling her out?
Is that bad?
I've never heard of such a thing.
Joshi is going to be a geisha's husband
The only thing I'm worried about is money
Maybe this will work.
I've been saving up until now,
Let me see.
It's okay
She has no debt.
I'm just asking for reference
What would you do to pull her out?
Are you guys lesbian?
No, I want Kichiya to quit being a geisha
and go to nursing school
Oh I see.
I'm very happy to hear that.
I feel sorry.
There's nothing to be hesitate.
Doctors make a lot of money.
That's not true.
I will tell my mother right away.
Let's celebrate together tonight for the pre-celebration.
Someone is visiting you.
Oh you called me.
Congratulation.
I heard it from Otani.
I see.
Are you back in Tokyo?
I'm sure my dad will miss you.
He's stubborn, but lonely.
Whatever it is, you should go home.
No, that and this are different
Now, I have a favor to ask of you
What?
Could you please deliver this to my father?
Indian Jabok, for high blood pressure.
I finally made it because it seems to help with high blood pressure
If I bring it, he gets excited again
I'm sure he'll drink it if you bring it
Well, That's all.
We kept fighting, but it was fun.
See you then.
Masahiko-san, Let's dance.
to say goodbye
Can you dance?
Don't make fun of me.
I'm good at it.
Have another one.
Give me a usual one.
Stop messing around and go home.
If you apologize, that will be the end of it
Please do it.
Yes, I really like this place
Returning to Tokyo, I pushed through the fierce competition for survival
It's much better to live here.
So...
I won't go.
Well then, I tell you
I've liked you from the start.
But I'm older.
I don't mind
I'm too strong-willed.
I'll make you a doctor as your father's successor.
I don't mind
Ready?
Once again.
Once again?
Okay,
I'll give you honey.
No no.
Congratulation.
Doctor!
I'd like to ask you a favor
We are closed today.
Woman collapsed in bath again
Oh no...
Then I'll go
I'll go.
But you're dressed like that
You have high blood pressure.
It's ok.
Ok I will take you there.
I sit here
It is like a honeymoon
What a honeymoon.
Are you crying?
Shut up!
Don't call me doctor anymore.
How about me?
You're my husband.
Say it again.
My husband.
THE END