Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Permanent Blue: Midsummer Love / Pamanento Buru: Manatsu no Koi
(1976)
To be or not to be
Thank you, my darling.
Hey! hey!
I didn't think you were still alive
Hold on.
I don't know about that.
Thank you
what's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
If you keep lying there, you'll get heatstroke
Where are you from?
Cheer up
I'll take you home, can you stand?
You can walk, right?
The first inning of the baseball game has ended with the score 3-0.
You must have been hungry.
This is a restaurant owned by someone I know, so please eat as much as you like!
You're not from around here, are you?
Where is this?
Huh?
Who's the hell you are?
This is called Ohama in Imabari.
Did you run away from home?
I hope it's not a suicide attempt or anything.
That surprised me
I thought you were dead.
What's your name?
I don't have a name
What?
Are you being cautious about me?
If you don't want to say it, you don't have to
I'm not interested in that.
Grandma, I don't have any money, so I'll pay for it later.
Hmm, that's fine. I'll get plenty from your Dad
Where are the restrooms?
It's at the back of the room.
Where did she come from?
I don't know
Did you picked her up?
Yap
Ah, a frog's child is not a frog,
but your taste is terrible
You should learn a little from your father
She's not just some beggar-like woman
It's not like that.
I just helped her when she collapsed on the beach
I can't believe it.
I want to eat shaved ice.
Welcome.
It's so hot, I feel like my brain is melting
Oh Konosuke.
You're here.
What are you doing here?
I hear you're taking the entrance exam for Han university.
Who said that?
Man-chan from the police box
I don't know if I'm going to advance my studies or not
Don't hide it from me
We're friends, right?
Let's go
See you later.
What are you going to do from now on?
Do you have a place to stay?
If you like,you can stay with me too,
even though it's dirty, but
it's an inn.
I don't really care either way,
but I don't have any money,
so I don't need that.
You're kind, aren't you?
Kind?
Is that how it is?
Is it far away?
It's about a 20-minute walk from here
can you walk that far?
Then come with me
In return
Could you walk a little further away from me?
Hey,
How are you?
Toyo-san was looking for you,
Since this morning, She haven't seen you.
Where have you been?
On the island.
Island? Are you fighting again?
I went to visit mom's grave.
Alone?
Yes.
visit mom's grave....
See you
oh, oh, you shouldn't walk around town naked, that's a violation
of the minor offenses law, right?
Mr. Kajiki
Please tell Mari-chan
Don't talk about people's privacy so freely
Privacy?
Just say that,okay?
Are you tired?
What's wrong?
What were we talking about?
I was simply stopped and questioned by the police.
What?
I'm considered a bad boy here.
Shall we walk together?
Is that okay?
No one can see us.
No, no, I can't talk about that,
Your dad will scold me.
That will not happen.
My father will obey your orders.
If Toyo-san just says yes,
That's all I need.
Seriously, you are really something else
Without even studying,
You wander around since morning
and end up picking up such a troublesome woman, don't you?
What will you do if she steal the customer's money?
It's not the same as that woman from before, is it?
I think they're the same.
That's not true.
The woman this time is a customer
Customer? Of course, she has money?
Well, of course she has it
If she doesn't have the money, I'll pay for it.
It would be ridiculous
She is sick.
If we let her stay with us for a few days, she will feel better.
so please
Come in.
You don't have to worry
She's just a servant, isn't she?
In a room like this,
it's better than being in a worse place
The futon is in the closet, but the screen door is torn
It would be better to light a mosquito coil
Have a bath before going to bed
Thank you.
Well, good night.
Are you a hippie?
Then I will choose not to ask you anything
Toyo-san lent me this yukata.
Eh?
The yukata and the hand towel
She talks bad but kind.
Good morning,
Dear husband, welcome home
What a sexy umbrella!
From Geisha?
About this girl,
Again, Bon picked her up from somewhere,
and She's dirty and has no money
She looks like a beggar
Bon says to leave her for 2 or 3 days,
but I wish he would consider the person taking care of her.
I hope she won't steals money
Husband
Wouldn't it be good to at least respond?
Mr. Yamaguchi's Tsutomu-kun
has been a bit strange lately
What's going on?
Toyo-san?
Where's Dad?
He went out
He left home
because he has business with the union
What did he say about me?
He said not to use the fishing boat
for customers without permission.
Was that all?
Yeah.
What about that woman?
He said Just leave her
There's a labor shortage,
so just keep her on the payroll
Did that woman agree?
Yeah,
but it will be interesting to see how long it lasts
There's no way a young woman could endure
working as a servant in a place like this
A week or ten days, and at most one month
That girl seems to have some unfortunate circumstances
maybe she was abandoned by a man
Did she run away from the association?
Anyway, the one who brought was you and your dad said to leave her here
so I don't know anything about it
Mr. Yamaguchi's Tsutomu-kun
has been a bit strange lately
What's going on?
Are you serious?
Working at our place
It seems like you're quite the oddball
Well, you can do as you please,
But
This isn't your place, you know
It won't lead to a decent income
Besides, that old hag seems to be planning to boss you around
For now, she's stubborn, nagging, and only looks for faults in others
The reason all three maids here quit was because they were bullied like that,
That old woman was in a surprisingly good mood.
I wanna go.
Give me a cup of water
You are maid here,right?
You're cute.
Hey, why don't you go over there and drink with me?
What are you doing?
It's just a joke, just kidding!
The other party is a customer, you know
He's also a regular from the fishing cooperative
Even if he sexually harasses you, it’s not a good idea to snap at him
There were teeth marks on his shoulder, and it was bleeding.
The organizer ends up to be upset.
Are you listening to me?
How about you respond at least?
You don't even have friendliness
Also, you don't respond to customers
You're slow at setting the table,
You're bad at cleaning, and can't cook
If that's the case, I don't know how much easier it would be for me to do it alone
Oh, Hisago inn's boy
Where are you going ?
with your reference book
to study?
It's tough, isn't it?
Will you drink something cold?
I am treating you.
Come on.
I have something I want to ask
Here it is.
I heard a young person is working at the Hisago inn
Yes.
Who introduced her?
Did your dad bring her?
No
I hear she's cute.
I have no idea.
There's a rumor that she is his mistress
No way.
but it's not like that either
There's no way a beautiful maid would settle in the inn
There's no way that dad would let the prey escape,
so tell me the truth, okay?
Come on.
I'm home.
By the way, Satsuki gave me this
She wants to see you
What about that girl?
She's been lying around,
She's saying she feels nauseous
Honestly, the girls these days are just like that.
Don't be so nagging.
Excuse me.
Yes, yes
Good morning. I've been waiting for you
Please
Thank you for your hard work.
Go home... Riot police... Go
home... Go home...
Riot police...?
Did you feel better?
Thank you, I'm fine now.
The watermelon was delicious
You were sleeping, so I left it quietly
I fed him already
You're a high school student, right?
Is it fun to keep a pet mouse?
There's no way it's fun.
My friend just gave this to me.
The baby mouse has already escaped
I forgot to lock the cage after I fed him
I'm sure by now he has been eaten by a dog or a cat
I'm so sorry.
You were taking care of him, right?
It's okay
I was thinking of throwing him away because it's a hassle
If a living creature escapes, it could be due to negligence,
There is a possibility of earthquakes or fatalities
That's just a superstition
It's not good to make someone
who isn't used to it do this and that,
but if you're going to do it, you need to do it properly.
Oh, Omatsu
It's hot, isn't it?
Thank you very much for the generous delivery this time
I am truly humbled
Well, it's just that my son caused some trouble
But he is a boy after all
Sometimes it's good to have a fight or two,
so come on up and let's have some tea,
Thank you very much.
Well, I have go around, you know
So you came all this way just to say thank you?
If you see a suspicious-looking young person, please contact the police.
There was information that the remnants of that
group seem to be hiding around here in Imabari.
Given your line of work, if you notice any suspicious
young customers, I would like you to contact the police
Is it a man or a woman?
Well, it seems there are both men and women, you know
Don't you know about their appearance?
There hasn't been any communication about that yet
Just be cautious about inns and apartments.
and please take care of this one for me
Thanks for your hard work
come visit me sometimes, Obon
Hey, where did you pick her up?
Huh? That woman.
She was found collapsed in the beach.
If I hadn't done anything, she might have died.
It's too strong
I'm sorry.
I told you, right? You can't just boil barley tea until it's bubbling
Did you water the morning glory?
Honestly, you're useless.
You forget about your work and You've also forgotten the matches for your mosquito coil somewhere.
, and you just take other people's sandals without permission
I want to see your parent's face.
She's  just right for me,
Are you waiting for me today?
No,
Let's go.
I was very surprised that she gave you a break.
That old lady said it wouldn't matter if it was about two hours
What's wrong with her?
You know, Toyo is surprisingly kind when the two of us
She buys me sweet treats that she wouldn't eat herself.
When I was sick, she made sure to give me medicine
She intends to make use of you.
Be careful.
She is a very calculating and nasty person.
And She has good intuition.
She has good intuition?
Oh, it was about three years ago.
when she reported a guest to the police
She said the guest was very strange.
It turns out he was a nationwide wanted criminal,
She did a great job.
Haven't you heard this story?
You should have noticed too
Do you smoke?
Dandan
It's nice to say thank you in this local dialect
Dandan?
Those clothes and sandals look great on you.
Did she buy that for you?
Did someone give it to you,
Who?
From your father.
When?
4,5 days ago maybe.
What do you want to know?
There are various things
You don't have to answer if you don't want to.
I don't know how long you're planning to stay with us
I have no idea.
Do you have nowhere else to go?
What's your name?
I told you I don't have a name
How old are you?
I'm 40 years old
You have some small scars
on your arms and legs,
but what happened?
I was burned by a cigarette
A cigarette burn?
Who did that to you?
A lot of people
This happened a long time ago
You're a college student, right?
I know that
Which college?
What do you want to know about?
I'm just a student preparing for exams
I don't know if I'll become your junior
Are you going to university? Maybe
Maybe
What are you going to do at university?
I don't know
I might participate in student movements?
Do you look down on me?
The police have been looking for you
I can turn you in to the police,
Don't worry. I'm on your side
I'm also feeling frustrated with this world
I won't tell anyone what
we talked about here
You'll understand soon enough
What kind of man I am
Kuro-chan
Where are you going?
I just went for a walk
who is that?
She is our new maid
She's a beautiful person
You think so?
There's no need to run away,
She has to work to do, right?
She's not like a college student?
Why?
Two detectives from the prefectural police are here,saying they must find the extremist criminal
That's ridiculous, she's my grandmother's niece
See you later.
Hold on.
Did you read the letter?
Yes
Why haven't you replied?
I am busy
I have to be preparing for the exam
You're just playing around
I am studying.
Can you lend me a math reference book?
I'll bring it if I feel like it.
You are stupid.
Ah, scary
What did he come here?
Did something happen?
Were you told to get out?
I have something to discuss, come to the back
About what?
You'll find out when you come.
If you stay in this town, you'll get caught
Two detectives from the prefectural police have come,
and they're thoroughly questioning everyone
Don't you think you should escape quickly?
Where to?
Well, the port station is also under surveillance,
so it's very difficult to escape
If you're okay with it, I could take you to a secret hiding place,
It's bit far.
There's a small island about 40 minutes away by boat from here
It's called cat Island
There is the village where my mother was born and her grave
A little further along the cliff on the east side,
there's a small cave
cave?
Oh, that's the one I stumbled upon
when I was in middle school
That's a really nice place.
In summer it's cool and in winter it's warm, It's safe even if typhoons or earthquakes occur there.
I think it might be the hideout of the pirates that used to ravage this area long ago
For now, how about hiding there
and waiting for the commotion to die down?
Are you saying I will be there all alone?
I don't want to be in that house anymore either.
A problem occurred.
I can't see that woman
Bon's room is empty?
I think they ran away from home.
What an idiot
They are ungrateful people.
I cleaned this place the other day.
But It's already overgrown with grass.
When did she pass away?
Eight years ago
when I was in elementary school
My mother's village was just over this mountain,
The cave is there
It's here, no one will find you.
The people on the island don't know either
It's just like when I came with my friends the other day
why not go in? It's cool
Ballpoint pen match or incense
gauze, tissue, and medicine, huh
You're well-prepared
Did you like it?
Yeah,it's interesting
Actually, there's a old well beyond that hill,
and if you run out of food, I'll bring them.
Your family will suspect you?
I sometimes camp outdoors.
Thank you.
Is it really okay to do this?
You're going to regret it
I won't have regrets
I think I've done something worthwhile for the first time in my life
It might seem boring from your perspective,
but don't worry about me
You just relax and take it easy
Dandan (Thank you)
It would feel nice to swim in such a beautiful sea,wouldn't it?
Can you swim?
Well then, let's swim
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm taking a break.
If you just leave quietly, I'll worry about you
Well, you were sleeping so well
Are you drawing water?
We need to start a fire.
What's wrong? Show me
I'm clumsy.
I'm slow.
You were only studying.
I broke a lot of plates at Hisago Ryokan.
They're all hidden under the floor
That old woman will be surprised later.
It's certainly this woman
I thought so.
So She really was hiding out here
and working as a maid, huh?
Where is she now?
She hasn't said anything since yesterday and suddenly disappeared
Did she run away?
What did she do?
She is involved in a murder.
Murderer?
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Do you think about your group?
Tell me about revolution and your ideologies.
Please think about that yourself.
Are you saying I'm not worth talking to?
That might be true
You're a revolutionary,
and I'm just a bad boy
You're a college student and I'm a high school student, you're from the city
and I'm from the countryside
You're a woman and I'm a man,
you're impressive and I'm an idiot!
Good night
I'm going to sleep outside tonight.
Why?
Because I want to.
Do as you please
Go home,riot police
What's wrong?
There is fire on the sea.
The fire is moving far out at sea.
Did you really see it?
that's the will-o'-the-wisp
will-o'-the-wisp of the Heike clan that was killed at Tannoura
Really?
You really saw it,right?
If it's not a will-o'-the-wisp
then it's just the light from night fishing
I like you.
I love you
You love me ?
I love you more than anyone else
You're the first person I've ever met like you
It's true
You're such a pitiful person
You're going to have a terrible time for my sake
please forgive me,
please forgive me
Hello, it's me again,
I am the daughter of the Police officer at a police station, Kajiki mari
You've grown up so much
I thought you were a different person.
What's wrong, Kuro-chan?
Today is a school day.
Did you go somewhere with
that female university student?
I have no idea.
Haven't you heard anything?
There's no need to worry
He'll be back by the new semester
Hey snake!
Where?
It's over there,
no, here!
There
Up!
You tricked me!
The boy is innocent.
Look! A snake! A snake!
You're so kind,
Is your father like that too?
My dad isn't kind at all
He's kind.
Have you ever been treated kindly?
Did something happen with my dad?
He just held my hand.
It was warm and big
Is that all?
He tried to give me money
He said if I was going to run away,
I'd need cash, suggesting that 100,000 yen would be enough
He is a famous playboy.
I don't know how many women he's been with,
whether they're bar girls or overnight guests,
he's just grabbing at anything
He often resorts to underhanded tactics.
There's a certain charm in a man
He used to be a fisherman.
There was a prostitute woman in town before.
My father hit her after she said something mean to her.
There were so many police cars and people, I was really embarrassed.
Why do you speak ill of Dad?
It's like you're treating him as an enemy
Your father is a very hardworking person and is highly respected.
He also paid for the funeral expenses for the person who died at the inn.
I'm sure they're worried about you too
I don't think so.
He's.
That's just how parent is
September is just around the corner
The summer vacation adventures are coming to an end soon
What?
Wouldn't it be better to go home
quietly and study for your exams?
I think a child like you will surely lead a happy life and live a long time
I will not obey your orders.
What's so special about September and October?
I'm serious running away from home
Don't make fun of me!
You're just a lonely person
You just want to go against your dad
You kept mice as pets and picked up women.
You pretend to be a bad boy
Shut up.
I see, so you were just that.
Do you think I'm a punk and are looking down on me?
Do you want to run away from me?
It's not easy
Now that we've come this far, we're in this together until the end
If you try to escape, be prepared to be killed
This is how I do it.
Did it hurt?
Shall we go?
Don't touch me
What's wrong with you?
I feel sick
because I'm pregnant
Of course, it's not your child
It's been like this for a long time
I'm sorry
It's not that I was hiding it.
Ship.
Don't you want to get on that ship
and go somewhere far away?
I don't want
Why not?
If I want to ride,
I can get on anytime
If I ask a sailor I know, they'll let me ride for free anytime
I guess I'm no good
We'll get caught right away
Let's escape
Let's escape together to somewhere far away
Let's live together in a town where no one knows us
I'm going to marry you
I just decided that,
do you understand?
What are you saying?
I'm five years older than you
Do you hate me?
I like you so much
I'm just as much of an adult as you think I am
I'm going back to town tomorrow to load the ship with plenty of food and fuel
Then I'll come to pick you up,
and together we'll leave this island
Since the engine is new, we should be able to go far
away from the island as long as the weather is good
No matter what job I take, I’ll support you
If I work at the shipyard , I should be able to earn good money and rent an apartment to live together
You will give birth to and raise a baby
You...
What I say is childish or ridiculous?
Thank you very much.
But you...
You will surely have a terrible time for my sake
You'll just suffer
I'm a man, so just stay quiet and follow me
Oh, poor thing
Just take a rest.
I'll come back in the evening
What are you doing?
Permanent Blue
the color from August
Let me borrow
Permanent Blue
the color from August
my heart? Huh?
Then.
Make sure to come back, okay?
Yap.
Who?
Oh Bon! Where were you on earth
Where's is my father?
Why are you so into a woman like that?
You're supposed to be the heir of Hisago-ya
I'm asking where my father is!
Bon,
My father is here,right?
Wait.
I have a favor of you
Please just lend me some money without saying anything
I need 100,000 or 50000 yen right away.
I have to go again from now on
I will definitely return it
I will definitely work to pay it back
This is a promise between men.
Don't
If I had known that, I
wouldn't have said anything,
so I'll borrow it
I will definitely return it
Wait a minute
No, go ahead, it's nothing,
just hurry up and go.
Thank you very much!
Please give me shampoo and soap
Welcome!
And do you have a hairbrush and a mirror?
Yes,
and please give me some lipstick
Lipstick? What kind?
I don't care
just hurry up!
Where are you going?
I have something I want to ask,
Can you come with me to the station?
Let's do it tomorrow
It seems like there's
something urgent today.
That won't do, I'm also in a hurry!
Hey, if you run away,
it will be a crime!
If you stay quiet, I won't understand
Where is that woman?
She's a criminal!
Are you okay with being an accomplice?
She's hiding around Imabari, right?
I have no idea.
Tell me the truth.
Where do you plan to take this lipstick and hairbrush?
Bon.
I've been greatly indebted to the owner of the Hisagoya
You're a classmate of our Mari, so I’m going to pardon you.
I won't treat you badly
Huh? Talk to me
If this continues, I have to hand you over to the police detectives tomorrow morning
your dad will end up getting mud on his face by
Think about it as fulfilling your duty as a good citizen.
Did my dad whistleblower on you?
There's no such thing as a whistleblower.
This is the intuition of a 30-year veteran officer
No.
We're having a contest to see who can hold out the longest
Hello?
Yes it's me.
At the third section?
It must be a drunken brawl.
Are there injured people?
that's not good
Alright, I'm going right now
There was a fight in this lousy weather
After finishing , I'll come back right away, so if you run away, I won't forgive you
Should I put on the handcuffs just in case?
Give me your arms.
Stay here.
Dad still hasn't come back, right?
You're hungry, aren't you?
More importantly, Can I go to the bathroom?
I can't hold back anymore.
You're planning to run away?
You think so?
You've really changed
Your gaze, your expression, even the way you talk has changed
You're in love, aren't you?
School starts the day after tomorrow
What are you planning to do?
What about the entrance exam?
I have to go,Mari-chan
I'm not going to help that woman
If I don't go, that woman will die
She has nothing to eat and is sick
If anything happens to her
I’ll never amount to anything as a man.
Will you let me go to the toilet?
It doesn't matter either way
Are you sure?
I thank you.
Did you let him escape?
You are stupid.
Hello, is there Detective Sanada
You've really done something big,
I might get fired because of you
This is Ohama's police station
Thank you for your hard work
Actually, Kyoko Wakabayashi, who is currently
wanted is hiding in a cave on Cat Island,
Yes, that's right.
Yes, the informant will provide a detailed explanation about the location
Talk to him
Hello?
Damn it!
Are you Wakabayashi Kyoko,right?
Shall we have you come with me?
Come on
Hey! What are you doing?
I'm coming out now.
Did you really live alone?
You've got some guts, don't you?
Who told you about that place?
We will ask you for more details about this at the police station.
(Dandan)
Where are you?
Come out!
I've come to pick you up!
Heeeey!
How are you feeling?
Shall we go?
If you keep resting like this, the day will end.
What is it?
Which?
It seems like something is burning over there
It looks like a ship.
Someone is burning an old ship, right?
THE END