Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Year 1940, early summer
Shanghai
What the hell?
I am a state officer.
Something is wrong
You are an enemy
Me?
Don't make a fool of me
Shut your mouth
You leaked confidential military information to the enemy
No way
I know What did you tell
Army permission is required to arrest me
Do you get it?
You should complain in Tokyo
I have no idea why I arrested
Anyway I was sent to Japan main land
Tokyo Military Police
Come in
I don't know at all
You don't know but other side know it
other side?
Yes, The enemy in Chongqing said they bought information from you
What kind of information?
Don't pretend you don't know
I torture you
Say it!
Get up!
The School of Spies 4:
Top Secret Command
Get up!
Mr. Takakura
I want to release you.
Please promise one
Please refrain from making statements that violate national policy in the future
I don't know how I got caught by the Kempeitai.
I haven't violated the law
You guys are in trouble because you can't prosecute me
Please change your mind
He doesn't say anything
Sit down
You should reflect for a while.
You can be in prison for 10 or 20 years if you don't be honest
I have a favor
What?
Please contact Lieutenant Colonel Kusanagi of the Army
I want him to ask you what I am
I will ask him
I wonder what he says
Connect to Lieutenant Colonel Kusanagi
Hello?
I'm Kusanagi
Oh How are you?
Do you know a person named Jiro Shiina?
He is from Nakano School
I see.
He seems to be disappointed with you
Let me talk with him
He wants to talk with you
Hello?
Are you Lieutenant Colonel Kusanagi?
I'm Jiro Shiina
Your traitorous behavior disappoints me.
I had no eyes to see
What?
Hello?
Are you really Lieutenant Colonel Kusanagi?
I don't want to talk to you
Hello?
Are you OK?
They are so terrible
Wipe your body
You are wetting
They are so terrible
They are devils
I'm an old man so they don't hit.
But I've been here for 10 days now
You are a former Foreign Minister, right?
I'm Takakura
That's what I thought
You?
I'm Shiina
Why they put you here?
I have no idea
I don't remember doing anything wrong
same with me
Japan is no longer a law-abiding country
Don't have a conversation
After a week I felt very desperate
I'm trying to find some hidden truth
What's wrong?
I have a chronic illness
I have a pain in my back and lower back
It hurts when the temperature gets cold
I'll massage you
Thanks
How's it?
Roll call!
Roll call is coming
Don't worry
Roll call!
Call a doctor because he has neuralgia
You have to sit upright during the roll call
Bring a little blanket
He's old
Shut up!
You had better not rebel against them
Shiina.
You have an order
You have been demoted from Lieutenant Army to First Class Army
Another 1 week passed
I and Mr. Takakura have become very close to each other.
I want to go to toilet
You be a little patient
I'm old so I can't be patient
You have to go to the bathroom every four hours.
You should wait
I can't wait
This is a physiological desire
Let him go
What?
You're just a guard, right?
You have a responsibility to protect him
He has no choice but to pee here
Is that ok with you?
Get back early
Be quiet
Get out Shiina First Class Army
You will be released
Good for you
Thank you for everything
Thank you for taking care of me
Please take care of yourself
See you again if you have the opportunity
You have been prosecuted
Don't put you in the army because it's dangerous to have someone like you in the army
It's been a while,Jiro
I'm Sanpei.
I came on behalf of my uncle today
You look fine
I thought you were very depressed
Who the hell is he
I decided to have a conversation with him
How's uncle?
He's busy.
Let's go
Please tell me why you came here
Thank you for your hard work.
Come in
I'm sorry
I took such steps to bring you closer to Mr. Takakura
He's your junior
I'm Kariya, a third year student at Nakano School
Mr. Takakura will be released
This case is related to Japanese politics
Late last year we got word that Cat's Eye had infiltrated Japan.
Cat's Eye
Codename of the British Intelligence Agency in Singapore
We couldn't get that information
German intelligence has contacted us
English?
I don't know the race yet
Perhaps they are Japanese.
It turns out that Japan's national policy is leaked to the US and British sides
Information on Japan's measures against China and Europe has leaked
We have to find that cat's eye
I left that assignment to your colleague,Kubota.
He found the identity of Cat's Eye
But he was killed just before reporting to me
He was killed?
Here is a picture of his corpse
He was killed with a pistol.
His notebook was found later
According to his notebook, he said that Takakura's friendship was a problem.
He is a Catholic Father Rogers
He is a correspondent for Mr. haydon of the Canadian News Agency
Mr. Clark, a trader
She is the widow of Baron Asai with foreign connections.
Sakagami of Japan Times
Kubota tried to find Cat's Eye among them
He wrote this at the end of the notebook
An unexpected fact was discovered but I can't conclude it
He found cat's eye
He didn't report to me because he wasn't confident
That was problem
If you should, be sure to report everything to me and die
I get it
Let's meet at the inn here when talking to me
You should not go to the General Staff except in an emergency
The enemy may be among our own people.
A few days later I got a new mission
The mountains of Hakone around here were very quiet
Shall I help you?
thank you very much
I'm Jiro Shiina.
Is Mr.Takakura here?
What can I do for you?
I just happened to be here
Did you make an appointment with him?
Because he said he wanted to see me
Wait a min
Oh
Mr Shiina visited you
Oh you
Thank you for that time
Have a seat
How is your health?
My health is not very good
That's bad
Take it
That place was really terrible
You helped me a lot
He helped you?
Yes he did
thank you very much
Not at all
I was released the day after you were released
I have not been prosecuted
I'm in trouble if an idiot has power
They are insane
They are so bad
Excuse me earlier
What's wrong?
I was suspicious of her
I didn't mean that
Did you get mistaken for the right wing?
They come here every day
Do I look right wing?
We are sensitive
Why don't you ask the police for security?
I asked him but
I don't trust police
What do you do now?
I have free time now
I see
How about you playing here for a couple of days?
The air here is clean and good for your health.
Thank you
This is a quiet and very nice room
How about taking a bath?
Thank you
Shiina-san..well
What?
I have a favor of you
Recently, many right-wing people come to our house.
I am very worried
Do I guard your father?
If you can, I'm very relieved
I wonder if I can
Please by all means
He may refuse
I convince him
I get it
The damage caused by the air raids in London was great, and now the German army is dominant.
However, the power of the British people, led by Prime Minister Churchill, is very strong.
Japanese soldiers don't understand it
You were a soldier
I was fired a soldier
British troops are supported by the United States
I think the spirit of the army is very important
I think British people are very spiritual
You think so?
What do you think?
I think he's right
I think it is impossible to invade other peoples
History show it
Have you seen the Yangtze River?
I don't think the Japanese can invade China if they see that big river
That river has been Chinese for a long time
Forever in the future
I am very concerned about the direction Japan is heading right now.
I have to change the way of Japan
The next evening, a consolation party was held for Mr. Takakura.
British Ambassador and Mrs. Lehman
US Ambassador and Mrs. Carlson
French Ambassador and Mrs. Manuel
They were high-ranking officials of the anti-Axis powers
Among them was Rogers, who Kubota was aiming for.
In addition, there was Mr. Hate, Mr. Clark, and Mr. Takezo Sakagami.
Ladies Asai and others were also coming
Who's he?
He is Mr. Shiina who is my father's bodyguard
He's not police
I get it
He needs a body guard
I'll bring him
Excuse me
He is Mr. Sakagami of Japan Times
I'm Shiina
Thank you for his bodyguard
He's clerk
How do you do?
The guests here are no longer wary of me.
I decided to approach the least cautious of him.
Do you want another glass of wine?
Would you like?
I'm already drunk
She was the least careful.
She was born in Vienna and her dead husband was a diplomat.
She is a woman who knows a lot about the relationship between America and England
Mr. Takakura found a bodyguard who is fluent in foreign languages
Thank you
Do you like dancing?
I like
I heard that all dance halls will be banned
So I should dance before it
It seems that listening to jazz is also prohibited.
It will be a very boring world
Where's Shiina?
Asai's wife got drunk and couldn't drive, so he went to send her
What do you think of him?
What do you mean?
I feel something strange about him
He was a lieutenant in the army
Military personnel who are fluent in foreign languages are a little rare
So what?
For what purpose is he approaching me?
Do you doubt him?
He's good man
Arrived
Would you come to my house?
Don't worry
Do you want water?
It was late yesterday so I stayed at a friend's house
My daughter is still young.
We have a bad reputation from your neighborhood when you are at home
I know
I don't like having a bodyguard
I'm sorry
Not at all
I'm leaving now
Shiina-san
What's wrong with Shiina-san?
What's wrong ?
He left
Why?
That's rude
I have taken care of him a lot
Wait!
Don't chase him
He noticed something and his attitude changed suddenly
He's very cautious
His daughter likes me.
I'll get closer to him again
I think I will take the other way
I am an information clerk
I have disclosed my identity
I did so because I trust you
What do you want to know from me?
You have a close relationship with foreign officials, right?
So?
Do you know the word cat's eye?
Is it a jewel?
It's the code of the British intelligence agency
They infiltrated Japan last fall
Since then, Japan's top secret has leaked to the United States and Britain
I think they are impersonating another person
You have a strong relationship with the United States and the United Kingdom
If I'm Cat's Eye I'll get closer to you
Shut up!
You are rude
Mind your mouth
Do you think my friend has a spy?
I don't mean that
You think because you are a spy, others are too.
I hate spies
They are so mean
Leave here!
You're rude
Shut up!
I'm sorry
Shiina-san
My dad did something rude to you
I couldn't tell him well
He's very frustrated lately
I want you and my dad to work together
I believe you are a great person
I have a favor to ask from you
Can you help me with my work?
Your dad knows some important information so I have to know it
Do you have lover?
I don't have
You are very handsome
Young women like you
I hate young women
They are too childish
What's wrong?
Nothing
I know this man
I was followed by this guy in Shanghai last summer
He's in Tokyo now
You know him?
No
I feel like drinking
Let's go for a drink
What's wrong?
I will reserve a room
Hello.
It's me
There is a man playing the clarinet in a dance hall
I want you to watch him
He is definitely a member of the enemy camp
I get it
Thank you
Turn off the lights and prepare for an air raid
I like dark
What's wrong?
What do you do to me?
This is Muhi.
You smell like Muhi
How did you get this?
It's none of your business
That's my secret
I want to know your secret
The police crackdown is strict now
Can I take a guess?
Who the hell you are?
How did you get this?
I can keep your secret
Trust me
I got it from the German embassy
German
I tell them the information about Takakura and they give me drugs
Now that the world is boring, I want to forget about taking drugs
You get money too?
yes , this is good business
I think so
Do you wanna work with me?
He was a man named Koyanagi and joined the band last October.
He lives in an old apartment and commute by bicycle
There is always a foreign car parked in front of his apartment
I searched for the owner from the car number, but it was a fictitious person
He sometimes goes to the coffee shop
This coffee shop is very long-established
Owner changed 3 years ago
Owner brings coffee to the British Embassy once a week
I checked Koyanagi's locker and found nothing suspicious
Thank you for your work
If he came to Japan last October, it would be the same time as Cat's Eye.
It's very happening
I think he has something to do with them
I'll find out
Did you call me?
Japan's highest secret leaked again
All negotiations between Japan and Germany leaked
It also contains information on national policy.
I’m sorry
What are you doing!
There was a protest from the German embassy
Then we found out.
We lost all face.
We are now fighting England in Europe
I want the Japanese government to cooperate more
Japanese intelligence agencies can't work
You guys don't know anything about Cat's Eye
We cannot have military talks with Japan.
We have two weeks to find the cat's eye.
Sorry for the inconvenience
I think you should be careful of Baroness Asai
What do you mean?
She is a drug addict
She?
I didn't know that
We have face.
We will find Cat's Eye within 2 weeks
I wanted to say that
Do you have any clues?
I only have the clues about Koyanagi
Who's the hell you are?
Shit
Why did you go inside his house?
I wanted to find some clues
What are you going to do?
I'll find out
I mean What do you do with the responsibility for failure?
Please fire me
You're spoiling it for me.
Nakano School has no hierarchical relationship, so there are only orders
If Koyanagi is Cat's Eye, that's a terrible problem.
You are seriously responsible
You get it?
Yes
Write your will.
All you have to do is write a short sentence and sign it
I wrote it
Drink it
Good.
You graduated from Nakano School now
This is just water
I order you again.
Find Koyanagi again
Keep an eye on the owner of that coffee shop
Thank you
Don't cry
I see
There was a party at the Winter Palace when I was the British Ambassador
It was very hot in the summer at that time
I drank too much
There was someone in the bathroom
The British Prime Minister was talking to someone
I thought the man was a spy
However, last fall
I saw the man in Tokyo
I don't know any more
Thank you
This isn't helpful on its own.
My dad won't tell me anything more
You have a hard time looking up your dad, right?
It would be fine with me
He is careful around himself
I would be happy to be of service to you.
I want to see the British spy your dad saw in Tokyo
Does your father write a diary?
Yes
Look at that diary so he can't find it
If the man's information is written, please copy it
I think you will be happy today
What's wrong?
The three countries of the United States, the United Kingdom and France are planning to ask Mr. Takakura to realize peace work with China.
Does the Japanese government know that?
The upper management knows it, but the military does not.
Thanks
Do you have any information about Cat's Eye?
I'm infiltrating the British Embassy and investigating
I want valuable information
I would love to know more about catchers
She will go home
See you
I couldn't find it
He may not come to the coffee shop anymore
Another week has passed
How about Kidnap him?
Do you have proof?
Threaten him
We can't overdo it
I'll give you this
This is the latest weapon made in the laboratory.
Use this just in case
Thanks
Hello?
From  Mrs.Asai
What?
Cat's eye?
I found out
I found it at the British Embassy
I'm sure
So I thought I'd let you know first
I want to see you tonight
Who is cat's eye?
I tell you
Don't be surprised
cat's eye is
Hello?
Madam?
Asai, who knows the true identity of Cat's Eye, was killed by someone
Two days to the deadline
I was in trouble but Misuzu contacted me in sudden
I copied this.
I read out loud
May 11, 1945
Britain will enter the war in earnest
I am interested in Churchill's strategy
I remembered something strange today
He looks just like the person who had a secret conversation with the Prime Minister in London
I still don't know if he is the same person
I don't know any more details
Thank you
Listen directly from your dad
Can I see him?
I try
Who's the hell you are?
By order you die
Dad
Shape up!
Takakura-san
Dad!
Takakura-san, please tell me
Who are the spies I met in the English palace?
He died
Dad!
I'm sorry,Misuzu
I asked him a question before he died
I am a very terrible man
I lost the last clue about catch eyes
I couldn't stay in her sentiment
Two days to the deadline
After leaving Takakura-san's house, I headed to Tokyo
I noticed that an Austin's car was running
Same as the car in front of the apartment
The driver looks just like Koyanagi
I've decided to chase him
The car was running along the coastline
I noticed something strange
The windshield wiper started to move even though it wasn't raining
This was in front of the U.S. military shooting range
Hi
Wait a min
I'm in hurry
Where he's gone?
Keep the change
Thank you
He didn't notice at all
He drove towards the Miura Peninsula
As I suspected, the wipers were rigged with 8 mm filming devices.
Do you remember me?
Don't pretend you don't know
I know you are not Japanese
Who do you work for?
Do it
Hey,Look at this
Stop it!
Who do you work for?
England
Did you get an order from Cat's Eye?
Stop it!
Cat's Eye is
Who is Cat's Eye?
Say it!
I don't know because I only get paid from a reporter
Who's the reporter?
Say it!
That coffee shop master
That coffee shop master is involved
Welcome
I brought the person I introduced to you
I'm Fung Yung Ming
He's Chinese?
He is my senior and graduated from Chongqing school
From Chongqing ?
I was ordered to do a Cat's Eye job
Oh I see
Take it
This man is a Japanese spy
Please introduce me to Cat's Eye
I just know their phone number
But I can't tell you it
I see
I will contact them for the time being
Cat's Eye wants you to do one job
If it succeeds they will meet you
This is a very difficult job
Let me do it
This is the British Government Code book
Take this you visit the German embassy
They buy this book for money
Is this real?
Of course
However, this alone cannot break the code.
You get the trust of them
You search for spy organizations at the German embassy
This is a difficult job
Go to German embassy
Have a seat
You want me to buy something
This is one of the UK's secret documents
How much do you buy?
Is this real?
Of course
How did you get it?
I can't tell
Saimsa,right?
Saimusa?
He is a British spy
You are also a British spy, right?
I'm not
Why do you think so?
Don't pretend you don't know
I know you went to his shop
Our intelligence agency is investigating it
Hands up!
I arrest you
Don't get me wrong.
I went to his shop tonight but
But I came to investigate them
Don't lie. You came to investigate the intelligence department of the German embassy at the request of him
I know that
I can't think of anything other than Saimusa reported him
He and this guy are related
I finally figure out
Can't see the forest for the trees.
You are cat's eye
If you wear German military uniform and have the German flag on, you don't look like a British spy.
This guy is a British spy.
Arrest him
This guy is the British Spy Cat's Eye
Bring him out
Where do you take me?
Let's go to that river
I remembered Kubota being killed in Tama-river
Shiina-san!
I wanna smoke?
Smoke?
It's in my pocket
Are you Ok?
I need a car
Please accompany us.
We have the approval of the German Chancellor
I'm not an ambassador's subordinate
You can't restrain me
We have to contact headquarters
Hey, it's me.
Open it!
Cat's eye!
Stay!
Watch out!
This man is under arrest for espionage!
Don't come closer!
I am here on behalf of Jiro Shiina
I feel sorry
Thank you for coming
I kept this for you from him.
I wrote to her with all my heart.
I have great respect for Mr. Takakura, and I think Japan has lost a very important person.
I am very grateful to her
I wanted her to know the real me.
I will never see her again
As Mr. Takakura feared, Japan has gone down the road to radical war.
I followed the trend and hurried to my next destination.
THE END