Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Run away!
It's dangerous because it collapses!
The School of Spies 2:
Cloud One Command
September 1945
I graduated from Nakano School of the Army
I headed north on the Korean Peninsula towards my new mission, Beijing
Is there Jiro Shiina?
Excuse me
I'm the Jiro Shiina
This is a telegram to you
Thanks
This was a coded message informing me that my mission had changed.
I was to turn back based on the command
KOBE
Was the cargo ship destroyed by a time bomb?
I think so
Look at that.
The accident site is that area
Victims?
All 94 executives died
And A new bomb was on the ship
What is that?
A new type of bomb recently developed by the Army
This was going to be used in the war
Did they aim for the bomb?
I don't know yet
That new bomb was a military secret
It's unlikely that those plans were leaked to the outside world.
So there was a directive to investigate this case
An order came to the school in us and  the local Kobe army
To our school?
To be honest,
I wanted the investigation
Listen
I built Nakano School with my own strong beliefs.
I've worked incredibly hard all year.
Graduates went to the battlefield with their respective missions after graduation
I believe they will be active in the war
Of course it is difficult to expect their results immediately
But I want the results sooner
So I asked the Kobe army and you for that
I want you to prove that the training at Nakano School is correct.
I get it
I will do my best for the honor of the school
I'm glad to hear that
Sugimoto has a little bit of that information
According to his explanation
It seems that my house is prepared around here
Are you the new residence?
Yes
I thought you would come soon
I'm your maid, Tame.
Thank you
Are you Jiro Shiina?
Where did you move from?
From Tokyo
How old are you?
I'm 24
Were you in the army?
You look strong
I was at 1st camp
Oh the 1st camp
What's your job?
I am a product of Toa Institute of Economic Research
Institute of Economic Research?
About that?
What do you mean?
Don't pretend you don't know
Left wing
No way,
I am an employee of a government agency
I see
Toa Institute of Economic Research
My place of work was on the campus of the university
This was a great place to contact Mr. Sugimoto, who is already investigating.
Mr. Sugimoto did not appear for some reason
I went to the wharf
The time bomb should have been set up here
Get ready!
Get in!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Nothing special
Come with me!
Stay here
You are the next
Come
What they asked you about?
They say there are spies in us
Spy?
I was told I wouldn't return tonight if I didn't say the name of the suspicious person
They are like Yakuza
Sit down
Tell me your Name and profession
I'm Jiro Shiina
What's your job
I work in the army
Don't make fun of me
I won't hit you
Your hairstyle is not a second lieutenant
You can find out if you look up my background
That's interesting
Ok, I'll look into you
Be ready for anything.
Shiina
Hinata
I'm Captain Yamaoka
I'm sorry to bother you
Forget this case
Sure
I'm going.
If you need any help please contact me
Please be careful not to disturb me in our work
You were in trouble
I'm sorry I was out
I was too busy
Were you busy?
I was doing various investigations
I had a news
keppei unit seems to have set up a time bomb
They made various plans
Suspicious are workers working in groups
The night watchman who patrols in the middle of the night is suspicious
I see
I want to investigate inside
I'm marking one person
Who?
Ichiro Motokawa
He's 38 years old, single
From the next day I followed Mr. Motokawa
He went home as soon as the night guard work was over
He eats at a nearby dining room at noon
He goes to the public bath at 2 pm
He is living a regular life like this
A day
Excuse me
I'm home
He met a geisha woman.
It's unnatural
She is the most popular in that place
Is she local?
She seems to have moved half a year ago
She was born in Niigata.
She's moved a lot
I just heard the information at a nearby tobacco shop
Her identity is being investigated at Nakano School
I hear they're not busy at school.
By the way,
Will you go out with me tomorrow?
According to what I hear, unconfirmed radio waves are being transmitted from Kobe.
That's a spy's wireless contact
The starting point seems to be 1 km square around here.
I think we should check the site
Ok,let's go
Ok, then see you
Otokawa-san
I hear you have a sister
a sister?
I have no sister
It's strange.
You were with a young woman the other day.
So you have a girlfriend
No way
Who told that?
I'm just kidding
Because you are single
I had a terrible experience with women
Really?
Tell me about that
No way.
I don't want to remember it
I will back to work
He may make suspicious gestures during the patrol
I've set up two patrols, starting tonight.
See what he will do
By the way, the site is around here
There is a small park a little further ahead.
It is easier to understand from there
The left is the city.
The right is Yamamoto Street
Anyway let's walk around there
Oh. Are you Miyoshi?
Oh,Sasaki
It's been a long time.
How are you?
She's my wife, Kuniko
Pleased to meet you
I'm Shiina
He was my classmate
You've changed your work?
Yes
You look fine
I've been busy.
I heard you are in the army now
Now I'm working at the Toa Institute of Economic Research
I heard you joined Tomitsu company
But I was immediately sent to China as a correspondent
I wanted to tell the Japanese people about the situation of the war
Now I'm a representative in Shanghai
Do you have any good articles for us?
Let me think
The articles we write are too serious
He's busy so please stop talking anymore
Sorry, I didn't notice you are with him
Anyway think about it
Our office is in an easy to find location.
There are various outsourced jobs
I have to do a lot of work these days
See you then
He's a college friend but has nothing to do with me now
There are many foreigners' houses around here.
There may be a wireless antenna in some house
They may be pretending to be a Japanese house
Many people in the upper class like foreign countries.
Is he a Christian?
The man talking to that priest
He is the master of the cafeteria when Motokawa always goes out for lunch
Despite heavy security measures, another artillery transport ship is bombed and sunk.
Was there a new bomb on that ship?
That ship was supposed to be 2nd
This damage is the second time
Spies are definitely aiming for new bombs
Where did the information that even we didn't know leak from?
I have no idea
I thought I'd taken every precaution.
I took them all
Army soldiers investigated the workers
I went to a public bath by the way
Mr. motokawa did not come on time
I don't know why
She's late to come
Don't be so rush
We've been waiting for an hour but never come
She's a disciplined woman. I'm sure he'll come.
Excuse me
I'm sorry I'm late
We were waiting for you
Were you busy?
I'm sorry
I got out on the way
Because you are popular
It ’s hard because you ’re a popular person.
Recently I'm busy even on holidays
She will become an increasingly popular geisha
Really?
I'll introduce you
Pleased to meet you
Stop it
You're not sexy enough for me.
Don't spit out rough words
I don't care.
Soldiers are not here
Don't be so proud
What?
They can't catch me.
I'll give them punishment
If I'm a soldier, it's easy to win a war
See?
I'm sorry but I have to go
Oh too soon
Let's take our time next time.
Really?
Yes for sure
Excuse me
Thank you
Don't say bad things about the soldiers in front of her
Why?
She is a professional geisha of the head soldier
Her husband?
No, but She has something to do with them
What are you doing, Motokawa!
This is the time bomb he used
He hid this in the attic of his hideout.
I failed to catch him.
Did you find out about this bomb?
We will experiment with explosive power soon
First of all
About this
This is pretending to be here and actually it works
Here the two substances are mixed
This pours sulfuric acid through the spout
So connect the two together
Then sulfuric acid will move here
This bomb will now explode
Therefore Explosion time can be adjusted by the thickness of this copper plate
We experimented with different copper plate thicknesses
We’re ready for the experiment
I'm going now
Fire!
It ’s a tremendous destructive power.
It's a pity that he made him self-destruct
Stop it
Hey you
You made such a mistake because you tried to take credit for yourself
I don't know what kind of education you got at Nakano School but what can you do?
You're gonna be sorry.
We still have a clue to a woman named Umeka
We have no choice but to investigate her
First, get the evidence firmly
Step by step
Let's find out about her anyway
Follow her and grab the evidence
Shiina-san
This is a telegram to you
Thank you
The telegram was a report from Nakano school about Umeka
She was born in Niigata, and moved around
I got all the information about her
She and her right arm have tattoos
This is the name of her childhood friend
I see
It seems that your mother is hospitalized
In Aichi
From here you can go overnight
You should visit her
I understand your feelings, but I have something to do
Where did you born?
I was born in Niigata
So your skin is so clear
Thanks
You don't have a Niigata dialect
I speak Kansai dialect now
I have lived in Kansai for a long time
You've had a hard time
Yes really
I haven't had a family since I was a kid
I see
You will surely have a future
You think so?
Shall I do Palmistry?
Do you know?
I'm a palmist
You are kidding
You are the chief engineer of the Army, right?
Let me see your palm.
That's my hobby
She didn't have an callous for a shamisen in her hand.
How's my hand?
How can I say
No!
Sorry, I was just excited
No way
You have a tattoo
Who's man's name?
He died in the war
Really?
I'm sorry
He was my childhood friend and we were orphans
Who received his remains?
Eh?
You?
No, I was in Otsu
But why you ask me that?
If you received his remains, because you are like his wife.
You're like a widow.
You are kidding
I'm just a Geisha girl
Don't worry
Next day. I visited Sugimoto at Akashiya inn
Umeka lives there
It's a best place to check her
She was in Otsu?
According to Kubota,
She moved Kanazawa to somewhere
She moved to Otsu maybe
I should ask Kubota to investigate it
I'll go to Otsu
You ask Kubota to investigate the guy who died in the war
I'll follow Umeka
How do you like living here?
Not bad, but a little boring
I'll contact you when I'm back from Otsu
Take care
There wasn't much information about her
Finally...
Oh Umeka works as a Geisha in Kobe
What's wrong?
I thought she was already married
married?
She had a childhood friend, Takashi Saito, who died in the war.
She got married to another person
Yes
I got a call from someone who was with Mr. Saito on the battlefield
After that, Umeka suddenly left home.
It's been about a month since then.
She said she would get married suddenly
So Umeka backed?
No. she didn't
Her marriage partner is a customer when she was in Kanazawa
She told me not to ask her detailed words.
But she politely greeted me
We all said she looked happy.
When was it?
It was about 3 months before I started this business
It was around August last year
Excuse me.
I'm Sakai from the design department
Please
It's too late
I forgot to lock
I am responsible
That's too bad
Please come in
Sorry
Hey
Wait
Go
Did you get the documents?
Yes
I immediately contacted my home country after hearing from Mr. Sasaki.
It was bad not to tell you about Tadashi Saito in China
But it can't helped
He is still alive since he became our POW
I want to ask you about a guy called Shiina
He is a classmate of Mr. Sasaki's college days and now works at the Towa Institute of Economic Research.
But according to him, he is always out of the Institute
He may be a detective
The Army's been doing a lot of investigating since that ship exploded.
So be careful about him
I know
I can't reveal myself to him until the mission is over.
Ok, so let's move on the test
This material was also provided by Tadashi Saito, so there is no doubt that it is certain.
Have you taken this test in your country?
No
This is a truth serum.
Hitting this will put you in a hypnotic state
No matter how much you put up with it, you won't lie
If you pass this test, you can be completely Umeka
OK?
Umeka, your lover is
Tadashi Saito
He died last year
Where is his spirit?
The village mayor in the countryside accepted
This is a picture of  Umeka that I got in Otsu
Please take a look at it
If this is a fake, they look very similar.
Shall someone read from Otsu and listen to the story?
I was thinking about that
I got new information from Nakano school
Maybe that's proof
Why did your boyfriend's mother die?
I was working in Tsuruga at that time
I went to visit her
Did she transfuse?
She did a lot
Her blood type was O
It seems that it was the least blood type
I took turns with Mr. Tadashi and gave blood
So your blood type is O type, isn't it?
Yes
Give me a glass
Send this by express delivery
How about the document?
He is the man caught at Yokohama Port today
This is a picture of a new battleship in Kobe Port.
The factory in Kobe is under our control
We caught a spy who stole this photo
Let us form a research team
Use local people for private research.
I'm home
Takashi looks like a spy
What? Sakai?
Sorry I made you wait
I'm her husband, Sasaki
What kind of relationship do you have with Mr. Sakai?
Well...
I was introduced to him by the design manager of a Japanese ship
I come home late for work.
I asked him to guard the house
Because he had a good reputation
I see
I've heard from my wife
I think something is wrong
We have proof
He is denying
There is also testimony that he was in and out in the middle of the night
in the middle of the night?
When was it?
Do you have any idea?
Nothing
If you don't be honest, you will be suspected
Actually it was the other night
Tell me what you know,Sakai
I'm not spy
Don't pretend you don't know
I hit you
I didn't do anything.
I stole the drawing on my own
The drawing was written by me
Don't make excuses
Trust me
Please trust me
I'll bring someone
Call him
Oh,Sasaki-san
Help me
Sakai-kun
You did something bad
I should have held you back
That night I went to the bathroom around 11:30
And I looked through the window
You went out
I thought you went for a walk for a change
No way
You gave me sleeping pills that night
Don't make a lie
I'm in trouble
What were you doing?
Let me go!
Hi Shiina-san
Thanks for your work
Thanks to you, the damage was kept to a minimum
Mr. Sasaki seems to have been on good terms with the upper class.
If We couldn't catch him, I think the damage would have been great
Did he confess?
He doesn't confess easily
I want to ask you something
I want you to convince him because he is your college friend
If he cooperates with us
We're not going to execute him.
What do you think of this?
Western countries are desperately trying to protect the colonized nations
Soviet and China are the enemies of the world
It is a shame for the Japanese to give them national secrets
I'm not being paid off.
What did you say?
I'm here on Captain Yamaoka's orders.
I got permission to talk with him
You and he only?
You're not trying to get him away?
I'm in the next room so Contact me when you're done
When I met you the other day
I falsified my identity
same with me
I never thought my college friends would have this kind of relationship.
Listen to me
You don't want to die, right?
It might be so
I want to know your background
Then you'll be fine for life.
What do you think?
I decline
Are you willing to leave your small child to die?
It's not your business
This is a matter of my belief
I'm talking as your friend
Are you going to change your mind?
You should change your mind
Why?
I grabbed your proof
Then I'm honored
Let's call that colonel.
Anyway
It's hard to be with you
It seems that friendship had no effect on selling countries
Thank you
I want to say something to you
Take care of your life
Ensign Shiina.
There is a letter for you
Thank you
Finally I got a strong clue
We authenticated the saliva on her cigarette butt.
Umeka had an a-type blood type instead of an O-type
She is a fake
I'm so upset now
Can you give me a fire?
Sasaki!
He's dead. Put him in the car
I was surprised
Nishida
We will be punished at the conference in Tokyo
at the conference in Tokyo
I decided to look forward to the meeting
As I thought
Something important will be said at this meeting.
Umeka knew it
She must be active at the night
That's fine
We were tired of Sasaki
I'm sorry
You don't have to worry so much
I will go back to Kobe and work hard
Take a rest
Good night
I've been waiting for you
Have you found a new lover?
No way,
I've been so busy
So there was no banquet.
I don't care about your boss
I only like you
Didn't you sleep with my boss?
I'll get angry
You mist know Your boss is too serious
I see
I was his assistant.
Now I can sleep with you
But it's exciting
I happen to be in Tokyo today
You are also a strange person
Let's have a bath
Sure
Come later
Come now
I'll go soon
Let's try to develop this as soon as possible.
It will take about an hour to start it now
Yes
Shiina
You go to see your mom
to my Mother?
Your mother seems to be in critical condition
You must see her
Go ahead, don't worry about us.
No, I won't go
Why?
Why you don't go?
I'm not Jiro Miyoshi anymore
You told me to put my personal feelings aside.
Since then, I've been to try to be Jiro Shiina
Then I'm him now
I have no parents
Let's move on,Kubota
Shall I help you?
How's her?
I'm preparing for a blood transfusion, but the person hasn't come yet
Please take my blood
I'm taking a little too much of your blood
Don't worry about me
I can't let her die
Please do it now
You've dropped something
Oh thank you
You believe this is a sneak peek by Umeka?
That's right
Immediately after you took a bath that night
Don't sat bullshit
Are you going to trap me?
I thought of you and brought it directly like this
Ok come with me.
I'll bring her too
Did I take this photo?
He said that
What if I take this photo?
You can earn money if you sell this to a spy
It might be so
But, Nishida-san
Do you think I'm the one who does this for money?
I'm sad
I never do such a terrible thing
That's too bad
You believe what he says
Hey, Shiina
This is the trap you made
Why did you say that?
I've heard that
Nakano School has a sneaky education
You used very terrible means
Then I'll ask her
Umeka
You are fake Umeka
You are a fake of the real Umeka from Otsu.
You and she have different blood types
Umeka
You guys killed the real Umeka in Otsu
Why you wanted to be her?
You're still telling me you don't know these pictures?
Tell me
Say something
I have nothing to say
You admit that you are a traitor?
Yes, if I'm Japanese
But I'm not Japanese
I am a patriot who likes my country
I am one of the warriors who will protect my country from Japanese aggression.
Then you stole the information about that new bomb?
You've been fooling me all the time
Humans without beliefs are always stupid
A human without a belief in protecting freedom and peace
What? what happened?
So Umeka's true identity has been exposed.
There was something wrong
I don't think the Japanese will find her true identity
But anyway I'll contact her
We are investigating this church for violating the National Security Act
This is a holy church.
You can do whatever you want
But what if there is no evidence?
In that case I will take responsibility
You'll take responsibility?
God does not forgive all mistakes
Go ahead!
Ready!
Look at that!
What happened?
Nothing happened
You have violated the sacred church,Yamaoka-san
I'll protest the Japanese government
Is that OK?
I get it.
I also take responsibility in the worst case
I will follow your response.
Go back!
Wait!
Can you pass me the key?
Key?
I don't have it.
I've lost it
What's this?
God does not allow suicide
Catch that dog!
Japan Shipbuilding Kobe Factory
Completed proportion
Set in 5 pm
A time bomb is set in the center of this factory
The range is around here
Citizens have already evacuated
Explosion time is 5 pm
Just in case,
Complete the mission by 4:50 pm
So there is 30 minutes left
Start the mission
Yes
Call off the search.
Evacuate the area now.
Hey!
Come on, Everyone
Everyone is here?
Isn't Shiina still back?
No
What?
Shiina-san, it ’s the time of the explosion. Please come back soon.
Come back!
Mr. Shiina,Come back soon
He faked the antenna into a bomb.
This criminal plan by a spy ring
All were arrested because the names of the spy officials were written on the radio.
The mission under the Cloud No. 1 order is over
I was ordered to appear at the General Staff
Kusanami Lieutenant Colonel
Shiina
Thanks to you, Nakano School's reputation has risen.
I got a telegram from Kubota
You took care of my mother on my behalf
Thank you very much
Not at all
But
Mother is important to humans
I said no personal feelings are necessary for a spy.
You accomplished it
Thank you,Shiina
Are you going to the General Staff?
Yes
I'll give you only one piece of information
You are promoted to lieutenant
I'd like to know more about my assignment.
Please tell me
I can't tell
No personal feelings are necessary for a spy.
Shiina
As I told you before
Wherever you go, take care of your own life.
Keep up the good work and stay alive.
See you
Yes
I'm leaving
The end