Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
School of Spies 5 (Final Episode of Series):
The Night Before The War
(Old Title: War Broke Out Last Night)
November 1941
Japan was in a stalemate due to the war on mainland China
I left Japan, which wasn't working at the US-Japan talks
I was headed to Hong Kong for a top secret mission.
Were you followed?
Maybe it’s the minion of the B agency.
There are US and British intelligence agencies operating in Hong Kong
They are marking the Japanese here because the US-Japan negotiations are not going well
He's coming
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll introduce him
He is Isomura from the Hong Kong branch of Yamato Bussan
He is a navy intelligence officer
He is Mr. Shiina I explained to you
I'm Shiina.
Nice to meet you
Have a seat
I got him to collect a lot of information for you
I want to help him
He is Lieutenant Colonel Dalek, who is stationed in Murray this time.
He chairs the next meeting
He will stay in Room 443 of the Plaza Hotel by 3 days
He reserves the innermost room on the 4th floor
Your room is room 424.
There is an emergency staircase nearby just in case
American and British staff gathered here for 5 days from November 5th
Asian Defense Liaison Conference to be held in Hong Kong
The next day I went to the Stand Plaza Hotel
My mission is to steal the confidential information that will be decided at this meeting.
Hi
I brought Masako, the daughter of the branch manager
She is the grandson of Dr. Okada
She is Masako's friend actress Ichinose
Good evening.
Nice to meet you
I'm Shiina
What do you want to drink?
I'll have wine
I want to dance
I'm afraid
Let's dance,Akiko
Serve us a wine
They are very good fiancées
Are they engaged?
They are best friends since college
You didn't know?
He didn't tell me
They seem to decide the date of the wedding
Let's have a festive party with four people in the near future
We should tease them
What a nice view
When will you return to japan?
I really want to stay for about a week, but our office doesn't have the money
If you stay at a hotel exclusively for Japanese people, you can stay for twice as many days with the same budget.
I wanted to stay longer if I knew I could meet you
Our wine is here
Mr.Dyke comes at this time every night at 8 pm
Isomura was closely investigating his behavior
I had to act for 30 minutes he was there
That day I stayed at the Plaza Hotel
The next day he left the room at 8 pm, as expected
On the rock
One more on the rock
Check please
I need to go to front desk
My bad
I will be back soon
I'm sorry
I don't drink anymore
Your Japanese is so good
I worked at a embassy in Japan three years ago
I miss Japanese women
I get it
Good night
He is kind
I did something bad to him
Let's invite Akiko tomorrow night and celebrate together
Shiina is a really kind person
Shall we go home soon?
If it's late, the branch manager will get angry
You are too serious
It's OK
I want to dance more
Ok just one more
I'm sorry
It's OK
What's wrong?
I will take you to a hospital!
He seems to have lost consciousness
Are you Shiina Jiro?
What is your status?
I am a member of Toa Research and Culture Research Institute
Don't tell a lie
I don't
You're a Japanese spy
No way
I'm not
You're not
Let you tell the truth
Tell the truth
No way
What is your status?
I am a member of Toa Research and Culture Research Institute
Tell the truth
I'm not spy
Nazis are using this medicine
This works well
There is no doubt that Shiina left the hotel this morning
Yes
I gave him the film.
He has to go here by 10 o'clock
Come in
Shiina Jiro
You're a Japanese spy
Spy?
Yes
You're a Japanese spy
I'm not
You are.
You entered Dalek's room
What did you do there?
Where did I enter?
Room 443
You entered Dalek's room
Here's not hotel
Where's here?
I want to get out of here
Tell me what you are thinking now
About Akiko
Akiko?
I want to see her again
Didn't you enter his room?
Hello?
Yes, Please wait
Is Isomura there?
There is a problem. I’ll put you through to My sister.
I'm Akiko.
I happened to see a foreigner taking Mr. Shiina to a Western-style building.
Really?
Where did it happen?
Here
If I don't come back after 5 minutes please contact the police
I get it
Let's go
Shiina!
Isomura!
On November 14th, I received an emergency return order from Lieutenant Colonel Kusanagi.
I headed directly from Yokohama Port to the Army General Staff Headquarters
You stole a lot of information in Hong Kong
The reason I brought you back to Japan was because of a big problem
What do you mean?
There was a meeting in Kyushu on the day you went to Hong Kong
Japan's national policy was decided at the meeting
No war will occur if US-Japan negotiations are agreed by December 1st
If the US-Japan negotiations do not agree, a war may occur
Is that secret leaked?
Actually, I found that from that film you got from Hong Kong.
from that film?
They learned that the deadline for US-Japan negotiations was December 1st.
It can be assumed that they will further act as information spies.
I want you to find that leak route
Prime Minister Tojo attended the meeting with 14 people.
I looked up those 14 people or they weren't suspicious
But half of them are very patriots
I felt that there was something with Dr. Ohara, who has something to do with senior military personnel.
What?Dr. Ohara?
He is in the hospital now but can visit for 30 minutes
Did you look up his list of visitors?
No one is suspicious so far, but I'm trying to find out
I get it.
Have a drink
Good evening
Hi,
Serve them
I think I'll work on you guys tonight.
She's Kogiku
Here it is
Don't be wary of her.
She is also a graduate of Nakano School
She is the only woman I trust
I'm Kogiku.
Nice to meet you
Her husband helped me to build Nakano School
But he died on the way
I was asked by her to cooperate with us
So she is in charge of this position
I see.
I'm Jiro Shiina, a first-year student
I'm Sankichi Kariya, his junior
Let's continue the previous story.
Did you find out about Mr. Ohara's family and servants?
His wife died of tuberculosis 5 years ago
Currently there is a maid who has been a nurse for over 30 years.
There is one man studying law
3 have a guarantor
He had only one daughter
She is now the wife of Yamato Bussan Hong Kong branch manager
I met her for the first time in Hong Kong
I see.
You also searched for a marriage partner
She has a fiancé
Isomura from the Navy.
What a shame
(Japanese navy vs army joke as he belongs to the army side)
I know him
You know?
There was a welcome party for military personnel who returned from Hong Kong about 5 days ago.
If I remember correctly. His name was Isomura Captain...
I don't think Mr. Ohara will leak information, but please investigate just in case.
Fortunately Masako returned Day before yesterday
With Akiko too
She came back without deciding where to work
She is staying at Ohara's house now
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'll visit her now
Masako
Oh
I learned from Mr. Isomura that you have returned to Japan
I'm happy to see you again
He was convened by the Imperial Japanese Navy General Staff because he was familiar with the Southern situation.
Good for him
I will meet him next Saturday
Do you draw a picture of a flower
There is something black on your face
I'm embarrassed
Who is he?
He is Mr. Oyamada of the Imperial Japanese Navy General Staff.
He sometime visit my grand father
I see
Can you go out with me today?
I want to surprise you
What's that?
that's a secret
Sis
Hi, Akiko.
Thank you for everything in Hong Kong.
Long time no see
I went to the Toa Institute when I came back to Japan to meet you
But You were absent
I'm part-time so I'm not in the lab
She was looking for ways to meet you
I'm embarrassed
Hi Masako
Mizuike sensei
I'm going to see your work
Hello?
I'm Mizuike
I'm on my way to the museum too
This coffee reminds me of Hong Kong
I think there will be more opportunities to drink coffee
When did you come to shanghai?
I went there this spring
At that time I draw that picture.
Do you know shanghai well?
I came on a business trip last year
Are you a military person?
I'm not.
We are working to get people to understand the oriental culture
I see
What are you drawing now?
Gozen meeting
Gozen meeting?
The government asked me to do the job
I want to express it in my own way
It seems to be difficult
Yes,
I am moved by the hearts of women
I want to make a picture of you
No way
According to a survey he lives in an atelier.
His wife is french
Currently he is ill and hospitalized
It’s the same as the nurse at Mr. Ohara ’s house.
We should investigate Mr. Ohara's house more
This is a plan view of Mr. Ohara's house.
Let's examine his range of action again
How about the female relationship of the painter?
He's play boy
Does he play?
Yes
He was there when I was with Kusanagi-san
Really?
Please
Be careful because she is a woman
Churchill says Britain will enter the war within an hour if Japan and the United States fight.
I see
The Navy's ship preparing for the war with the United States left secretly yesterday
It is impossible for the US-Japan negotiations to be concluded by December 1st
Pay attention to how it will be a war
It's weird
Really.
She is so pure
If she doesn't like it, she refuses everything
Why she invites me?
It's very strange
Perhaps she is interested in your painting
She wanted to see you so much
She is your great fan
Good evening
Then see you
I thought I couldn't meet because you look busy.
You have time today, right?
I will entertain you with Masako
But I don't have enough time
Masako-san hasn't finished drawing the picture yet.?
Please put the flower out
Is Mr. Mizuike the other day her painting teacher?
She was taught by him before going to Hong Kong
Her mother and Mr. Mizuike are acquainted
Does he come here often?
He does not come lately
I see
I prepare tea
Thanks
I wonder if I'll look at her picture
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting
Since there are many customers, Mr. Ohara is busy
I don't know if he's sick or something
Thank you for your distribution next week.
Thanks
No reaction
I should have done something if she was snooping
I don't think she had a chance
Thanks.
Please contact them to expand his range of activities
Japan-US negotiations virtually broke down
Government meeting was held on November 29
The enemy espionage we have marked has gradually escalated.
I've always been concerned about you
Have you finished your work yet?
I have not finished all
I will take you wherever you like today
Your home
My home?
I'm hungry
Would you like to dine at a hotel in Akasaka?
You don't like?
I want to cook you something
To me?
I am confident in cooking
OK let's go!
We can share this if you like
Really?
about 100g
Thank you
I will contact them that I can't go to work today
Follow that car
Hello?
Oh Kogiku
To his home?
Did something strange happen?
He brought coffee beans?
I care about it
Anyway take care
Sorry for keeping you waiting
Thank you for calling
I heard you will get a job from today
I work at St. Joseph Hospital
Mizuike's wife is also hospitalized there.
Really?
The world is small
Who introduced you to the job?
The director of the hospital when I was in Hong Kong introduced me
I want to celebrate you tonight
It ’s very quiet and calming here.
Isn't it cold?
I drank alcohol so my body is warm
Do you wanna drink little more?
No thanks
I won't drink too
I hear you can drink very much
I get sleepy if I drink too much
How is Mr. Ohara's health?How is Mr. Ohara's health?
He got better
He always has a long conversation even when customers come
Can you trust that nurse?
I have no idea but she care him very well
Why do you think so?
Nothing
I think Masako's bride is very cute
Do you want to get married?
I sometimes think of it
I sometimes feel lonely to be alone in a world like this
I often go abroad for work.
I always think it's important to be with someone I can trust
I'm tired from time to time
Sometimes I think of something else even with you
I'm trying to find out the secret of that nurse from you
Why do you suddenly say that ?
Actually, I don't belong to Toa Institute
I can't tell you further detail
So you were looking into her
In addition to that nurse, Mr. Mizuike is also investigating.
I'm investigating the organization behind them
Can you forgive me?
I'm glad you told me the truth
Hello? Yes, I'm SHiina
Ok. I'll get back soon
I have an urgent need, so I'm going home
This is who I am
Will you meet me again?
I wish I had a calmer world
I may not be able to meet you anymore
I'm really happy that you have fulfilled your promise in Hong Kong
Akiko
I love you
As you said, the realization of the Greater East Asia Co-prosperity Area is near.
If today's meeting decides, Japan will attack the U.S.
The Army is ready.
The Navy is also ready
It seems that the war is about to begin
Hello
I'll give you coffee
Real coffee?
Sure
Sensei
Mr. Mizuike gave coffee beans to a foreigner living next door?
The man is a doctor in the St. Joseph Hospital
The owner of the pharmacy is Bunichi Minami.
Coffee shop master is Koji Minami
They are from South Korea
How about such an information route?
Nurse Kazuecatches some information From the story of a customer who visited Mr. Ohara's house
She then fakes a drug order and gives it to the apothecary, Mr. Minami.
He then gives it to his brother
Put it in a coffee bag and give it to that foreigner
I see.
Everything is related to St. Joseph Hospital
I will go to Mr. Mizuike
Mr. Tanaka is currently watching him
Kogiku is in danger
What's wrong?
I have an appointment.
I need to go
I will send you if you return
I cook and wait for you
Thanks
Hey. What are you doing?
Say it
Who asked you to do it?
Who the hell you are?
I can kill you
I don't care if you kill me
Don't be strong
Hello?
I'm Mizuike
Did you forget the promised time?
I'm sorry, I forgot something.
Come here right away
I will go immediately after organizing the room
Damn it
Follow him
Are you OK,Kogiku
Shiina-san
Fukuzawa no...
Kogiku-san
I can have this at that location in less than 30 minutes.
What?
Mizuike was died?
I can have this at that location in less than 30 minutes.
I thought that if Akiko Ichinose was a spy, there would be some action.
I'm surprised they killed their fellow Mizuike.
They seems to be in a hurry.
I heard from Mr. Kusanagi that Japan and the United States will have a war at today's conference.
The number of cryptocurrency stores of spy organizations suddenly increased
It's only a matter of time before this secret is leaked
The base of the spy organization is around here on the map
If the code is sent again, the location will be known for sure.
What if it was the last confidential information about the war between Japan and the United States?
It is not good to rely on the enemy's radio wave transmission
Now let us go to St. Joseph Hospital to find out
They are run by foreigners so we can't move until we find evidence
Just in case
Do we leave this problem alone?
I will invite Akiko again or
She'll use the next means.
maybe
Hi, Isomura-san
Hello, I'm Isomura.
How are you,Akiko?
Masako?
Where is the hospital?
I will go to Minato Hospital in Yokohama soon
Please transfer to Ms. Ohara
She is out now
Hello
From whom?
Nothing
You are Mr. Isomura
Where is Masako's hospital room?
She was taken to St. Joseph Hospital because she couldn't operate here
St. Joseph ?
I'll take you there
Shiina-san
I have something to do with you
What's wrong?
Isomura is missing
Really?
He was called to come to a hospital in Yokohama because I was injured
I see
What's wrong with him?
He was in the Imperial Japanese Navy General Staff as a Navy officer
He seems to have been involved with an enemy spy
Really?
Akiko Ichinose kidnapped him
I can't believe it
She is a member of the spy
I wanted you to call her
I can't believe who she is
Where is the nurse, Kazue?
I think she's in the room
Mr. Isomura is in a dangerous state.
You should wait here
Ogawa is chasing her because the nurse ran away
Please contact the military command urgently
Yamamoto. please
Please
10 am.
Where was he taken out?
Take this
I'm waiting for you at the lock behind the hospital.
Akiko
Thanks for coming
What did you do about Isomura
You can meet him if I get in my car
You are Japanese but why do you pass information to the enemy?
I'm not Japanese.
I love my homeland
It can't be helped but I thank you
Don't chase me anymore
See you
Go
At that time, the Navy was heading for Pearl Harbor in Hawaii.
The warship was running around 40 ° north latitude
How was it?
I got a photo of alien registration
From hospital officials
Hello?
Oh Shiina
I now have a photo of a hospital official
Please come to Keihin National Highway with it
See you
Hurry up
This is a picture that KOGIKU found at Mizuike's house.
I checked mine against the photo on the alien registration.
He's the x-ray technician, Mr. Steiny.
Yes he is
Something is strange.
Check by device
He's foreigner
Who is he?
He is an outpatient and is not registered as an alien
I remember,
He threatened me in Hong Kong P agency man
P agency?
He is now at St. Joseph Hospital
We're heading to the hospital
Contact the Kenpeitai
Is the report complete?
This Amobarbital is more powerful than the one used for Mr. Shiina in Hong Kong.
He is from the Nakano School of the Army
The Cloud 15 Directive etc. are all his achievements
Recently the drug was caught by him
We'll take him down.
Akiko
Get ready
This drug works soon
You will speak sensitive information without your consciousness
We will report it to America
Japan can't do anything
We are homeland freed from Japanese colonies
We'll be free
Where is the Japanese Navy riot police now?
Tell me where they are
Where?
Tell me
Chishima
Single crown bay
Single crown bay?
Are they there now?
They are now in the northeastern Pacific
Where are they heading?
To Hawaii
To Hawaii?
Pearl Harbor
When?
What time
December
8th
Is that true?
Send this information immediately
We will leave after sending the information
I was fired by a man who followed me.
Japanese intelligence will be here
Please contact your home country as soon as possible
I caught a strong radio wave from this direction
Let's investigate this hospital
Contact me to turn off the main power of this hospital
Kariya
Investigate this hospital
I will investigate this hospital
Get on work
Send information as soon as possible
I will talk about the situation later.
Turn off the main power
I can't do that because it's during surgery
Please
I can't do that for another hour
It seems that the power cannot be turned off during surgery now.
What should we do?
Get jamming from your car
I get it
But I can only give it for 10 minutes
10 mins, ok hurry up
There is no problem
We should hurry up
4 mins left
Go in
Nothing problem
Wait
Shiina-san
You guys wait here
We will arrest you for espionage!
Stay down
We don't have time
Send it quickly.
Isomura
All of the spy cells that attempted to transmit information to the country at 1:00 a.m. on December 4 were killed.
At 6 a.m. on December 8, the Japanese were at war with the Americans in the Western Pacific.
Oyamda leader visited me at that day
will
Hiroshi Isomura
He committed suicide.
Confessions were demanded of him by enemy operatives.
I get it.
But Are you aware that military secrets were tapped by the Ohara house?
I don't want to talk with you anymore
Force majeure is not allowed for military personnel.
He was sent to the front lines of the war.
We, the Japanese, launched a surprise attack on the Malay Peninsula at 11:50 on the 8th.
We're getting results.
Japan will be in difficult situation
We too must reconsider the mission of the Nakano School.
With the start of the war on December 8, Japan expanded its front to the Pacific Ocean
Japan will fight against the United States and Britain as enemies
We have taken on a harsh fate.
I could not imagine my next mission
THE END