Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Hey!
What's wrong?
Damn it!
The School of Spies 3:
Dragon Three Command
I am Colonel Hidaka.
The colonel left the interior on a special military plane with special orders.
He arrived there on time
He was on his way to Shanghai when he came under terrorist attack.
He died in battle along with the warriors who greeted him.
You know who the terrorist group is?
We haven't known yet
What is the license plate number of the terror group's small truck?
It was abandoned, so Japanese soldiers investigated.
This is the car that was stolen from the site on the day of the incident.
This is a plan to commit the perfect crime.
They are pretty tough.
But there is one clue.
The clues are the bullets and shell casings that shot the tires.
This this morsel
That's right.
It is a military machine gun of 7.63mm in length.
One of them is familiar with this gun.
This is the one dollar coin found in the terror group's car.
There is a number 078 on the back of the coin, which I think means
something.
This is a copy of the coin I made because I thought it would be useful
Model rifle mark and $ 1 silver coin
I hope this gives you some clues.
This terrorist organization is certain to have something to do with spy organizations
In short,It must have been a special mission to kill Mr. Hidaka.
Actually,Shiina
Between you and me
We want to quickly resolve the long-term war with mainland China
This is absolutely necessary for us Japan's future
There are those on the Chongqing side who are interested in a peace treaty.
Mr. Hidaka was dispatched to discuss with each other
Mr. Hidaka gathered information in Shanghai and went to Hong Kong
There he was to hold preliminary talks on peace negotiations.
In short,The terrorist attack was to obstruct the preliminary stairs, right?
Some people are not happy that Japan and China make peace
They must have interfered to do that
Moreover
There is no doubt that it was the Shanghai military authorities who leaked this information.
Shanghai's secretariat says it will investigate the case thoroughly
But We have to send another one for peace negotiations
We decided to investigate this in our own research
Shiina
I need to ask you
Do your best for peace in Japan and Asia
I ask you
Yes
If you succeeded in peace negotiations with the Chongqing side
You first-year students, as well as your juniors, will play an active role in the liberation of Asia.
This is the hope I made this Nakano School
Sugimoto already sent to Nanking
You can contact him
By the way
This is the equipment developed at Noborito's laboratory
I think this helps you
The afternoon of the third day I was already in Shanghai
Since 1845
There was a river between colonies such as the United States and France and Japanese colonies
I was staying at a Japanese-owned hotel there
I was transferred to military headquarters.
I, Jiro Shiina, arrived today after receiving orders to arrive.
What do you dress?
What?
When you talk to us, you should wear your military uniform.
Mr.Fuwaki, I'm sorry to say this but
We, Nakano School graduates, do not have military uniforms
What?
I don't know what's in Kusanagi's mind
Listen
This is different from the mainland
Go to a special agency
I was ordered to be assigned to a special agency
The secretariat was in a quiet part of the French colony
The organization here was called Tsujii organization
Let's get down to business
Do you have any information about the incident in which Colonel Hidaka was attacked?
We are investigating where the information leaked
We haven't got a clue yet
Currently suspicious...
This person,Zhang
I hear he is very pro-Japanese.
He belongs to the Ochoumei
He is involved in these peace talks.
HQ Sasaki was always in contact with him
In short, he knew the information about Hidaka
He knew it
But his private life was being monitored secretly by us all the time
We were tapping all his phones
We absolutely knew if he behaved suspiciously
How about his family?
His wife and children lived in Hong Kong
There's only a maid and a cook in his house
There is no information that the maid who goes shopping every day has contacted someone
This cook has never left the house
In other words, Zhang himself is suspicious.
But I don't think he's a spy
I first checked his house
And went to town
Stop it
It's none of your business
Run away
Zhang had a daily routine
He and the announcer appeal to the public about peace in Asia
It was a job to appear on a promotional program
I decided to follow the announcer
There is a phone call for you
To me?
From who?
I don't know
Hello?
I'm Sugimoto
I'm next to you
Oh Sugimoto
I was also surprised at first
I know you're in shanghai but I never knew I'd meet here
When did you come here from Nanking?
1 hour ago
Look at floor and listen
There is a woman wearing China dress
That long hair one?
Yes she is called Chou Meili
I was following her actions in Nanjing
There is something secret around her
She is here today for something
Who's the man?
I've never seen him before
Oh, she's going out
Then, good luck
Ah!
I'm sorry
Tips
Please
Ladies and gentlemen
I'm the manager
Someone used a fake number to gain entry here.
So we must conform your membership
Please corporate with us
Right
Thank you.
You
Alright
Thank you.
Your membership
Alright
Thank you.
Your membership
Alright
Thank you.
Your membership please
Find 078!
He's there!
Catch him
Hurry up!
It means I think the woman Sugimoto chased from Nanjing has something to do with Hidaka's case.
Yes that's my guess
This is a hidden photo taken at the gambling hall
He's stainer
You know him?
He is a German trader
Mr. Sasaki of the headquarters is taking care of the request for the Triple Alliance of Japan, Germany and Italy.
Is he a pro-Japanese foreigner?
Yes kind of
He has lived in Japan before and sometimes brings important information
But I don't know this foreigner
Oh yeah
There is one person who is familiar with Shanghai and Nanjing
He is Kawazoe who is Kempeitai Second Lieutenant
I've told you before
He is Shiina Lieutenant from Tokyo
Nice to meet you
What can I do for you?
Do you know these guys?
I don't know
I sent the pictures of these two people to Nakano School and asked them to investigate.
We decided to keep an eye on Steiner and Kowa broadcast
Oh
Thank you for the other day
I was in hurry so I didn't ask you your name
Is this yours?
Oh
I thought I lost it
I liked this
Thanks for everything
Are you waiting for someone in Kowa broadcast?
So you are working here?
I'm typist here
I'm Akiko Hayashi
She is my friend, Kinden.
She's like my sister
Let's have a dinner if you like
Thank you
See you
Please come with us if you like
Thanks,
But she have to go somewhere
I see.
Then see you
Brandy
Are you here for work?
I came here looking for novel material
Wow, what kind?
About spy
I thought there was a clue here
Have you been here long?
About 3 yrs
How about your parents?
They are died
My father died in shanghai
My mother died when I was 3 years old
She dies in here too?
No.
We returned to my mother's hometown after my father died
My mother committed suicide in Yokohama
Your mother committed suicide?
I found out about it later from my grandmother.
Is the person in the picture your mother?
Yes
You're amazing to come to Shanghai alone
I feel sad when I'm in Japan
Do you know Zhang Zi Yuan?
He' brought me here
He was very close to my dad. so he is happy to look after me
That's good for you
And Kinden is here too
She's also no parents.
We are like sister
I see
At that time, a top secret telegram was sent to the headquarters.
I was informed that a second messenger would come from Tokyo for peace negotiations.
I see, so?
I want you to cooperate again
What do you mean?
Don't pretend you don't know. Mr.Zhang
I thank you for the recent attack on Colonel Hidaka
Many people in the mainland do not want to negotiate peace.
Mr.Sasaki.
You misunderstand something
As I told you before. I have nothing to do with the terrorism case
Then let's leave it at that
But You're a member of the Ouchoumei, so you know what happens if Japan and China enter into peace talks.
I get it.
Pretend you can't hear
The 2nd messenger,Mr. Kihara, Mr. Sayama, and influential people in the private sector
They will arrive at the airport by special plane at 8 o'clock tomorrow morning
Depart for Hong Kong 30 minutes after the plane refuels
I live here.
Thank you
Good night
Kinden!
What happened?
Damn it!
Kinden! Kinden!
Akiko sister
Kinden!
Sou's stick
stick?
Who shot you?
Kinden! Kinden!
Kinden!
The right is the ammunition of the Hidaka incident and the left is the ammunition of the KINDEN incident.
Compare the marks of these two pistols
It's same
It means The pistols used in these two cases are the 7.6 meter Mauser pistols.
In other words, it ’s the same criminal offense.
And moreover Kinden said before she died about KOWA Broadcasting Sou Announcer
Let's investigate it
At 8:41, I was informed that a special military aircraft had crash landed due to an engine failure.
Really?
Where?
According to the telegram, it's around here
Near the Raikochi?
That is the base of the communist army
Yes
That's strange
Why the engine broke down?
I have no idea but Perhaps someone set out on the plane after making adjustments at the airfield.
Is it sabotage?
Tsujii lieutenant
Yes
Please take Zhang Zi Yuan now
I interrogate him on suspicion of being a Communist spy
Mr,Zhang.
I got information that you are being targeted by a secret society in Chongqing
I'm being targeted?
Please go out with us
I will guide you to a safe place
Let's examine his house carefully
What happened?
Sasaki-san
I need to ask you something
Mr.Zhang
When did you become a Communist spy?
What do you mean?
You made a special military plane crash land at a Chinese Communist base
Don't pretend you don't know
You are a traitor
Please refrain from words
You tricked me into taking me here
You misunderstand something
Do you think I'm a spy?
I was asked to investigate you
But Akiko
You'll be free if you like
No thanks
You like to be with Shiina
Shiina?
Pending.
Take her out
Ah
I've heard something from Kawazoe
Shiina lieutenant is you
Hsu, the cook, eavesdropped on the secret meeting with this microphone.
He hid the note in his CHOU WEI's stick and outside and he
contacted
Who's the other side
I think it's the announcer's SOU who meets with him daily.
Um
Manager,
Your care is ready
Are you going out?
An emergency meeting begins at the command center.
I would like to interrogate her too.
Ok leave it to you
fully confess something
Stop it
Let me hit him
I'm in charge of this
In charge?
Who ordered you?
I was authorized by the head of the agency.
I will to interrogate him from now on
Leave it to me
Are you OK?
I know that you do not speak out in violence.
But you've been caught by us
I think Your mates doubt you
Our work is ruthless with each other.
Do you have your family?
It is predicted that the crash landing incident and the Hidaka incident were committed by the same person.
Moreover, these two men are necessary for peace negotiations.
The General Staff is doing everything in their power to get them out.
chief of staff
I think we should take down
That's right
Are you going to ignore the wishes of the General Staff?
If we attack them, Ensign Kihara will be killed.
It is best to send a special agent to rescue them.
I don't agree with you
Why?
It's impossible to send there
Take our time and we'll be fine.
But prolonged exposure can be dangerous.
Therefore, We should take down them
OK let's decide the date
Rescue operation by special operations personnel will last for 10 days starting today.
7 days ... 8 days are enough
OK.
We should think who can be the rescue them
I want to recommend that person
That's what I thought
How did you get the note that HUS puts in this stick?
Mr. Zhang always puts his stick in a locker when he comes to the broadcasting station.
I get out before I enter the studio.
Kinden was killed yesterday because she happened to see it
I feel sorry for her
Who killed her?
I don't know
Why?
I always just contact them at a fixed place and at a fixed time
Is that place a nightclub gambling place?
Is that gambling place your place?
No.
That gambling place was just used for contact
Where's your base?
Somewhere in Kyodo-sokai
Are you hiding it?
No
I like your personality
So I tell you everything I know.
Tell me the name of 3 people
I don't know these 2 guys
This is Wu wu song I'm always in contact with
Wu wu song
Where is he now?
He's not in Shanghai now
He said he was going to Raikoji yesterday
Raikoji ?
Chief is calling you
Will I be that special officer?
I know you are investigating Colonel Hidaka's case
But Mr.Sasaki asked me to recommend you
Can you?
Sure
I obey orders
I see
How many subordinates do you need?
I need no one
Instead, I would like you to call Mr. Sugimoto in Nanjing.
Sugimoto?
It ’s your classmate at Nakano School.
I see
This is hard work
If you don't like it, please decline
I don't care
Don't worry
I'm chasing that woman in Nanjing.
Because I think she has something to do with the obstruction of peace work
Let's give God to the waves of trouble
It's like the school song of Nakano School.
By the way, How's Zhang Zi Yuan?
He was released
Except for the chef Zhang and the announcer So, they were released earlier.
I see
I can see how Zhang Zi Yuan could be targeted by the enemy, but I can't imagine him being a spy for the enemy.
That's good news
Oh you are Chou meili
You are terrible
You left me in Nanjing and disappeared
Well..I didn't mean that
Long time no see.
You have your boyfriend here?
I get angry with you
I was looking for you when I went to Shanghai to meet you.
I can't forget about you
Really
The next morning me and Sugimoto went to RAIKOJI posing as local residents.
I knew this was a difficult job
I was very worried about the existence of Mr. Wu who left Shanghai first.
Go ahead
Thanks
Hey!
Wait!
Show me your belongings
You are deaf
Ok go ahead
go ahead
Have you seen this guy?
I think he went to Lai gang tsuen
I haven't seen him
I see.
Thanks
Wait.
Are you Japanese?
No way
Don't tell a lie.
Japanese move their hands when washing their face
Come!
Wait!
What's wrong with this guy?
He's a murderer, but have you seen him?
I've never seen him if he is not local
That person should stand out
Thanks
Do you ask me?
Foe what?
I knew from the beginning that you were the one with the problem
Me?
5 yuan is OK.
I'll catch you for murder
murder?
Thanks
Put your hands up
Who are you?
I know you are Japanese spy
Approve it?
Who told you about me?
Say it
Meili
Oh, He thinks I'm a spy
I don't mean that
My job is to investigate outsiders.
Thanks
Excuse me
It can't be helped
How did you find here?
I've wanted to see you
Meili
You tricked me
How dare you are
Chinese girl never love you
Don't get me wrong
I hurriedly arrived at Raikoji on the morning of the third day
Wait
We're special officer from Shanghai
I'm a leader,Chen
What's your name?
Wu wu song
Was he on the Shanghai branch roster?
Give me your pistol?
Japanese POWs tomorrow
You guys will send back tomorrow
You take care of him
Please
Thanks
Is it strange to you?
Thanks.
I want to see the face of a prisoner
Ok. come with me
What time do you go to bed?
The bell rings at 9 o'clock
Show him the guy
Sure
He seems to be a Japanese spy
We caught him hiding during the day
You are Japanese devil!
Don't spit because he's an important person
Lucky
During the turn-off time
Boss
I'm Wu wu song
Are you Wu wu song?
Let him meet
Shiina!
There's no key
I'll manage it.
Anyway get in the car
Sugimoto!
Watch out!
What's wrong?
Gasoline has run out
We should go on foot from here
Are you OK.Sugimoto?
Are you OK?
What's wrong?
This is a minefield
It can't be helped.
Please follow me one by one
I'll be the top, Shiina
I'm not afraid to die
Survive no matter what
Did you forget Kusanagi's words?
You get it?
Don't shoot.
Catch them!
Don't let them go.
You
What's wrong?
Sugimoto?
Shiina.
I'll leave the left to you
Sugimoto?
Let's move on
Anyone there?
We reached the front of our allies just before the end of the given deadline
Tomorrow afternoon in Shanghai...
Hello?
Oh is that zhang?
What can I do for you?
I'm just back from the go
There was something strange in my pocket
Eh?
Is it written as Buddhahood?
Yes. it means I go to die
Do I have any idea?
I think a woman was following me
You're being targeted by the enemy, aren't you?
Actually yes
I want to talk to you about that
Eh? I want to see you in person
Hello?
Mr.Zhang?
Mr.Zhang's assassination was also due to a 7.63 mm Mauser pistol.
Do you know anything about Mr.Zhang these days?
Yes
It was a week ago
I was told to get a job at a Steiner company
Steiner company?
Yes
He was disappointed to be suspected of being a spy by the Japanese Army
He was planning to set up a company himself
Then?
I joined the company there as a secretary
And the day before his death
I was asked by him to collect Steiner company transaction slips
Do you have The copy of transaction slips?
Yes
Here it is
Let me see
This looks like a trading telegram, but it appears to be a code.
a code?
What does it mean?
I have no idea now
But if we have a code book, it's okay
Where is the Steiner Company Safe?
It's in the president's office
The key?
the president has it
Always?
No
When he goes to work, he puts it in the top drawer of his desk
Do I have a chance to look up the safe?
I have an idea
But it's difficult
When?
Tomorrow noon
The president always applies for a visit by noon and meets the customer in the afternoon.
That time is your chance
I'm waiting for tomorrow noon
Please let me know when you ready
Sure
But please be careful
You are being followed in the same way as Mr. zhang
I'll give you this
This looks like a fountain pen, but if you press here it will become a pistol
There is a poison here that will surely die within 3 minutes
I'm sorry
I'm stainer
Meili took the bait?
Ok I get it
The rifle mark of this ammunition was the same Mauser
I see
Colonel Hidaka, KINDEN, and
SOU, SOU announcer, JOU the cook, and Mr. Chang and you, all of you are the same person.
Moreover I noticed later
This was in my pocket before I knew it
This is...
I think MEILI CHOU put this in.
This is letter for you
Thank you
This letter was information about the Steiner company from Nakano School
According to this letter
Steiner has lived in Yokohama as a trader since 1910
Then he lived with a Japanese woman
During World War I in 1915
He was suspected of being a spy and fled abroad
He seems to be the same person as Mr. Hans Berger
Hello?
Yes he's here
Phone call for you
Hello?
I'm Shiina
The call was from Akiko Hayashi
Mr. Steiner seems to have a visitor at 4:30 pm today
Just in case,Please escape from here
The key is in this drawer
Set the intercom.
If you hear voices, run away immediately.
Be safe
Boss is here?
No.
He has visitors at reception room now
I see
All right,sir.
I'll see you
Bye
Mr.Steiner?
Please escape now
What are you doing,Akiko?
I know the reason you've come here
What did you do while I was not here?
Who did you contact with at noon?
Freeze
Put your hands up
You dirty, basted
Get in now!
Watch out,Shiina!
Who's her?
She's my mom
What her name is?
Shino Hayashi
Shino
Where's she now?
She's passed away
She's passed away?
You are Hans Belgel
So I tell you
She committed suicide because you doubted her as spy
Because of you, the world suspected her of being a spy.
I still love her
I was just standing up for what I believe in.
You are Steiner belgel
I'll give you this
Order No. 13: My mission is over.
From that day on, I never heard anything about peace talks again.
Not only that...
It was because of the General Staff's plan to negotiate a peace deal.
I have been summoned by the General Staff this time.
I will train them when I get to the interior.
We must band together.
RAIKOJI is occupied.
Lt. Kusanagi from Tokyo and I went there.
Rest in piece, Sugimoto
I must say sorry to you
The peace process you opposed was forced upon you by the Army.
How Japan will happen later?
The war will grow.
War will expand from mainland China to the South China Sea and then to the Pacific Ocean.
We must make up our mind
We must shape our future.
I remember what Sugimoto said.
God please give me freedom.
THE END