Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Sasameyuki / The Makioka Sisters (1959)
Hello, Sis.
Where's your mom?
She's at home.
I brought a gift
Hello.
Akan-chan, are you going somewhere? Yes
I bought tickets to the concert
My brother is waiting for me at the Osaka office
Do you use that belt?
You also used that belt during the piano concert other day.
Yes.
I was sitting next to you and your belt looked very tight.
Really?
Please turn off the radio
Yeah this is bad.
No?
No.
I'll show you my good one.
I want a souvenir
Please stay in this house tonight.
I get it. You have homework
Yes.
That's what I thought.
So, just play around and write it properly
I'll show you later.
Try this.
Try this?
Hold on.
This is no good either.
I get it.
This is too new.
Really?
Try this.
Is this ok?
This doesn't feel tight at all
This belt is old and very easy to use.
I see.
You should use your brain a little
Yeah.
It's already this late.
I've already given our workers over to my workplace
I'm not ready.
I will thank you later
Hehe, I know everything, and if you don't have any pocket money, I'll lend it to you
That's a lie.
Kan-chan.
Have you been dating Keibon lately?
Keibon?
Why do you say such things?
Thank you for waiting.
It's really late.
Sorry.
I get it.
Please come home soon
Wait, I have something to say.
Don't forget any souvenirs
Despite all my efforts to tighten your belt, the concert was unfortunately canceled.
But I can't help it
Due to work reasons,
I think your sister at home is having a very hard time.
Are you okay without being at home?
She said she'd do everything herself
She won't let me help her with anything.
That's so her.
Be careful.
Nakan-chan.
I have to go to Tokyo with the main family?
You don't like?
I don't want to go
I can't get along with my brothers.
I feel like the water in Tokyo just doesn't seem to suit my tastes
But if no one goes
I think your sister feels lonely.
That's true, but if I end up being a nuisance to anyone,
I want you to be a nuisance to you.
I'll also take care of Etsuko-chan
Eventually, I will be able to earn money like Koi-san
So please.
I would be grateful if Yukiko-chan could stay here
Well then, please
But more importantly, why don't you take a blind date?
There is a very good marriage proposal.
about Jinba-san?
You knew it.
It's been four years since the first person I met had that happen
And this is a good offer.
You might like him.
So please think about it
but I know how Nakan-chan feels
I'm really happy about it but...
I know how you feel too.
Yuko-chan, everyone really want you to find happiness as soon as possible
I'm not telling you to forget about your past.
so please give it some thought
I will.
Good.
Anyway, I'm going to the main house now to check on your sister
I've already made the kimono, so it's nice to see her
Oh she's here.
Hello
you're bringing something so big.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Welcome.
Hello.
Oh you are here.
There're many stuff here.
You seems to be doing fine.
I thought you'd be crying like crazy
Ah, I'm so tense while I'm doing this,
but I think that once I get to Tokyo I'll relax and start crying
This is Suzuri.
I remember my dad making me buy this.
Is that right?
It cost hundreds of yen in those days
Because my dad loved expensive stuff.
He was like that.
So his Business was going badly.
He was complaint about the world.
Are you taking these to Tokyo?
No, I'm thinking of selling them.
Why?
If I take such a luxury item, It doesn't fit into my life from now on.
What a fool! This smells like my dad.
It's ridiculous and the smell alone is not enough to make me eat
Since you are decided to go to Tokyo, you have changed yourself.
What do you mean?
You've always said that hearts are precious.
I said that, but now it's important to eat,
You might be right.
This is my favorite.
I'll give it to you, take good care of it.
What else.
I want something more.
You're greedy.
Here's album.
Wow, a rare award came out
Sister, Look, this is our mother. She was beautiful woman.
This is Koi-san,right?
Oh yeah.
At this time, she was bothering everyone because she didn't want to be photographed
There's Yoko-chan.
I was when she graduated from school
She looked nice too.
I thought she would be the happiest.
was our dad smiling like this?
I wonder what New Year's holiday it was
When we first put it out in the store.
It was really flashy.
I can still see it now, sis
Sis.
I didn't imagine that Kyoka moved out of Osaka
The rumor of destroying here and
building a new building is really, sister?
It's up to the person who bought it
We could sold this house,
We were able to pay off the debts our father had when he was in business,
and we moved back home to Tokyo
That's true, but
You know what.
We must be strangers who have come to adopt.
We went out of business because of it.
I thought that studying to become a banker
was the way to protect the Makioka family
Honestly, I don't think that much
I've heard that before but
Then you should be more than happy for us to go to Tokyo.
Yuko-chan and Koi thought I ruined this main house.
You think too much.
Sis, what's that? That's Yoko's kimono
What a nice.
My dad did it for me that I just want to be able to get married anytime
He was so unhappy man.
He was nice at first time.
Yukiko-chan liked that person too
We promised to go see a movie together and Yoko-chan is waiting for us
On the way to the restaurant, his car crashed into track.
Human life is a fleeting thing.
Don't talk about him anymore.
But that was already four years ago
I think Yukiko-chan's big emotional wounds are gradually healing
And what more.
What?
Actually, Yoko-chan has a marriage proposal right now.
Really?
I'll look into it a bit more and let you know the details
Yuko-chan, let me take care of this.
But I feel sorry for Teinosuke.
You don't have to worry about him.
Yeah.
but I'll ask to what our family says
Dad is back.
This place is very messy.
Welcome back.
Oh you are here.
Don't play there.
The date for your trip to Tokyo has been decided?
I was forced something from main office.
I won't be able to visit koi's exhibition.
Sorry.
Ah, I forgot about the souvenirs. Ah, leave them all here.
The souvenirs are coming soon
I wonder what's this.
Sweets or toys?
Open it.
Here it is.
Give it to me
Koi?
Oh, Mary.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
This woman, Mary, works at an American trading company in Motomachi
Her Japanese is very good.
Everyone,I become Koi-san's student and become an artist.
Thank you in advance.
She speaks Kansai dialect.
The person who taught her Japanese is from Osaka
That's right.
She's Yamamura-style's Osho.
The dancer?
Yeah.
I wonder if I want to be your student
Do you mind?
OK OK
You look fun.
Please excuse me for a moment
Thanks for your hard work.
Let's go to Noda,Keibon.
Are you going to make a pamphlet?
Yes, I want one in front of the venue too
You're working so hard.
Good luck
Go get the credit properly.
Let me see.
Is he Okahata's Keibon?
He's a son of a jewelry store owner in Shinsaibashi.
They used to run away together,
Holding their hands?
Of course.
It was widely reported in the newspapers, and both houses were chased
Nakan chan's are coming soon.
I see. I have to go home soon
This is a celebrate the exhibition.
Handbag?
Open that handbag
There's a brooch inside
That's so sweet.
It costs a lot.
I know
Thank you for your hard work.
Nakan-chan, He's Keibon
Really?
Welcome.
Oh, I saw Jinba-san just now
I made a promise here
He's waiting for you at the cafe
I'm going to go for a bit.
Let's play with dolls together.
Hello, how is it going for a while?
Have you looked into it yourself since then?
Yes, he us the president of Kansai Electric Railway
He has a good reputation at his workplace
Everything was exactly as you told
Isn't it time to go on a blind date?
I did, but I had to ask permission from my home base
I'm sorry to say this but
I feel sorry for Yukiko if the main family is being so strict
That's just as you say
Anyway,they are urging you to hurry up
The president of Kansai Electric Railway has been very helpful to us
So please.
I guess that's right
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll report the statistics on Yukiko though.
The problem with the Koi and Keibon is troubling
Koi-san's work is quite complicated
There are things that ordinary people don't understand,
I agree
I was worried so I thought I'd ask her about it
She's at short apartment.
Yeah yeah yeah
Well, actually, I didn't tell you this,
but Keibon has been telling me to go
to the office recently about the business
No, he took the items from the store
her mother has to clean up after.
I've heard the rumors he gave birth to a child with a girl from a cabaret club.
Does koi know that?
Koi?
Don't come.
I'm on the phone.
I can't wait
Wait.
You must be tired today.
Not really
I promised our students that we'd go out for dinner once we narrowed down the venue
I see.
I mean, I'll just ask you straight out
Koi-san, when did you start dating Keibon again?
What's that?
Did you see us?
Yes
I want you to explain it to me in a way that I can understand today
Both Teinosuke-san and I have responsibilities to the main family
It's our responsibility to give you this job.
I don't think it'll be a big deal
Why?
I wonder if that was last fall
When the first exhibition was held
That's right
at that time he came and bought the best work.
After that, we started going out together
, but
Of course, we only meet occasionally,
if we have a strange relationship,
I don't think he'd be in an exhibition.
I'm not a child anymore, unlike before
I want you to trust me on that point,
but if our family finds out, we won't be able to face them.
I am responsible for it.
What a fool
What's so stupid about that?
I wonder how much of  shame it would have been
when Koi-san and Keibon had just appeared in the newspaper at that time
If those two were to become rumor in the world today,
we'll be in trouble again.
We are genuinely in a relationship.
And main house is in Tokyo.
How they notice us?
Koi-san
Nakan-chan, don't worry about us.
Maybe Yuko-chan will have an arranged marriage meeting
Then it's with Nomura-san?
That's why you have to be also very careful about Keibon.
I know, I won't do anything to make you worry,
Are you sure?
I'll go home.
You're stupid.
What if she found you?
She couldn't go home easily, so I squatted down against the window and cried.
You are stupid.
Yukiko will have a blind date?
Yep, it seems so.
With whom?
He's rich and elegant.
I see.
He's like me
I can't compare it to you.
You are stupid.
Am I so bad?
Yeah.
You're saying what you want to say
But I'm really glad that you're willing to go on a blind date
What?
I can't marry someone unless you marry someone.
Of course
The main house is old, but even now they still keep the order
Are you starting another job?
I want to do that
I am against it
Why?
I  can't make a living by making dolls.
Why are you against me having a job?
You can't get a share of your property
Wives shouldn't work.
You’re sweet.
No matter how much money you have, you spend it
Oh gosh.
You're currently enjoying the luxury of your mother's savings,
but what will you do if something happens to her?
That's true, my brother is not on my side,
See?
so you're just going to keep quiet and watch what I do
I get it.
Please look happier.
Sorry,
I think that if it was Nomura-san, he'd do
whatever you said and do what you wanted
Please feel free to go.
Put more lip stick.
Why?
It's better.
You think so?
Thank you for coming.
Welcome.
hello.
What's that?
This is where I finish it off
Here?
Studio
Can I enter?
Please come in.
This is not an American style photo studio at all.
You think so?
The sign in front of this house is very old.
Keibon helped me.
You were well looked after by him.
But you shouldn't follow him completely.
but he's a great help to me
Oh? I know
How long have you been to America?
for six years
Whereabouts you were?
I studied photography in Los Angeles
You didn't even graduate from middle school.
Is that right?
Yeah.
My family was really poor
You must have been hard.
I made money in America by washing dishes and working as a hotel bellboy.
Did you do it on your own?
I rely only on my own strength
I see, This is strong arm.
if you touched my arm,
I'd feel like I was being shocked by electricity
Don't say bullshit.
the tea is ready
Thank you very much.
I came to ask you a favor
What?
I would like a copy of the photo from the doll exhibition the other day.
That's my job so it's no problem.
Were you at work?
Yes I was.
It's a Rokko hotel.
Yes.
She is currently having a matchmaking session at this hotel.
Sorry...Nomura..
what is your main job?
I work in the inheritance department.
That is a very interesting job
Well, half of what he does is just a hobby
The president of Kansai Electric Railway Company is providing for his livelihood.
I get it.
Of course, everyone at Kyoka's place
You guys listen to Western music, right?
Yes, this person plays the piano.
I have recently started playing the koto again
That's because my youngest sister is a dancer in the Yamamura.
so I have many opportunities to become familiar with the koto.
Oh Yamamura's?
She dances well
She occasionally holds recitals.
I can’t believe it.
It's strange that that's not the case
No, but that's not common sense
That's a problem
Who would say something like that?
I hadn't thought of that
Hello, are you Nomura-san?
not? No, I wasn't expecting it.
I’m sorry.
I started talking to myself again.
Hi.
What?
please go home
Forgive me....
The most important thing is hidden for him.
He has such a silly habit.
It's kind of charming
You met your husband today?
Who told you?
Oharu told me.
If I get married,
Etsuko will be in trouble
Why?
Who check my homework?
No way! I'm in trouble.
I don't get married.
I'm glad.
Ask Oharu put your kimono in the right place
Yes, yeah
I'll take care of it later.
I'm sad.
Why?
There are better matchmaking stories out there.
I mean...
Once I've finished this today, I have to go to Tokyo
You should have just taken it a little slower
I will send them a letter.
Really?
I'm glad.
I feel better now
Do it in the garden
Let's practice the piano
You shouldn't say unnecessary things to children.
Sorry.
Do you have anything to drink?
No
Please go to the greengrocer and buy it.
Yukiko, it seems like things didn't go well.
Oharu told you that?
Etsuko said that
everyone's so talkative
If it's that person, it doesn't matter.
hurry up
Also, Yukiko couldn't forget the first person
Yes, that's true, but...
she'd better forget about it quickly.
Anyway, I hope she can be happy for at least one day
You really care about her.
Of course.
She should find a good husband.
It's important to have a happy home.
You want fires?
There.
I want to eat oranges
You haven't finished studying yet.
My sister asked me to bring it.
I didn't say that.
You said it
It can't be helped.
She looks fine so you needn't worry.
It seems that a typhoon has landed
It seems the TV is broken.
I am worried about the typhoon.
Hello? Hello?
The phone is not working.
Watch out.
Oh you
What's wrong?
Where's Koi?
She goes to school
The weather is very bad.
Window.
Take this.
I worry about Koi
Is she ok?
You should go home early.
so be careful.
I'll go and pick her up
There's no point in you going.
Koi!
Itakura!
I'm home.
Koi!
What's wrong?
Itakura rescued her
Itakura rescued her?
There was a landslide
I see.
Where's Itakura?
So Mr. Itakura handed her to me and then went home,
Are you alright?
In the blink of an eye, the ceiling was crushed
The principal and I were hiding between the pillars.
but I couldn't breathe and the water was rising
But why Itakura was there?
Itakura risk his life to save me.
What did you do with that dress?
I stopped by his house and borrowed this kimono from his sister
That's right, but I'm glad you were helped.
I can't believe I'm alive
It's like a dream
It's good.
Why did you hold my hand?
Well..
Do you love me?
Yes.
Why you didn't propose marriage?
You have Keibon.
Why do you care about him?
I won't be able to go to your house
Ko-san will be abandoned by your family
So how is that possible?
I think people around the public will say bad things about us.
Are you scared of it?
It can't be helped.
I am waiting for you
Hug me.
You look surprised.
Not really.
Is it inconvenient for you to meet me?
You are lying.
Your face show it.
I wanna talk with you.
Do you see Koi these days?
I have nothing to do with her.
You were shocked when you saw my face just now
What's wrong?
What were you doing with koi?
I was asked to take some
pictures of dolls.
You're stupid.
She recently stopped making dolls.
You are lying.
Don't see her anymore.
Why?
Why don't you ask your heart?
Get lost.
Who?
Oh Keibon.
We didn't promise
Where did you take this?
Why?
Who took this?
It's none of your business.
I knew Itakura took it.
So what?
What have you been doing with him lately?
What?
He has been with many women and borrowed money from them.
Your life will end if you get involved with him.
What are you talking about?
I am having someone research him.
During that typhoon
He risked his life to save Koi-san. I just thought that was not a normal thing
Honestly, what have you done to me?
What?
Go home.
I hate seeing your face
stop going out with him.
Please.
He saved my life.
Go home.
I apologize if what I said was clear
I can't live without you.
Please.
I'm sure you understand this
You can cry
I feel like crying,
Keibon
I don't know what Itakura think
But as I can see, He just came back from America and it's really interesting.
It's very convenient because he takes care of everything
why don't I use him?
He is happy to do so.
I see.
You are thinking well.
Are you feeling jealous or something?
Well then, give this to you.
This is awesome.
The lens was broken, it was my brother's favorite camera
It can't be helped.
Customer?
Koi.
I'm back, but I've decided to do dressmaker's store as you told me.
I see.
I do not want to be a financial burden to you.
Would you like to use your wedding deposit, which your family of origin has entrusted to you?
I intend to use the money to negotiate with them.
I wrote a letter to Keanchan in Tokyo
I don't like the brother of the main family
I asked her in Tokyo for a favor.
Is that so?
No, what happened?
I did break.
Koi.
What?
What's wrong?
That finger was in my mom's shop.
I know it was from Keibon.
Yes.
You are not clear on your relationship with him.
I guess you are still loving him.
Itakura.
I can't stand your relationship with KEIBON.
I thought that if Koike-san wanted to be happy, I would work hard.
Itakura.
Forgive me....
I wanna be happy with you.
No need for these luxuries.
Koi.
Is it too late for the autumn leaves to change color?
I remember walking to the waterfall every year under the beautiful autumn leaves
Everyone here is doing well,
but our life is not so easy
because we depend on my brother's monthly salary
I have talked to my sister many times about how I want to find a job
Not only will they not take it up,
I want you to get married quickly and be happy
I feel sorry for my dad and my brother scolded me
Did you read this too?
She only writes about herself and doesn't write about the important things
The important thing is
It's about money?
Yes.I asked her to negotiate with the main house
She didn't, I didn't think she was that kind of person
But..
No.
I'm going to Tokyo
I'm going to go there tonight because of that money.
Koi.
Sis.
Well then, I can just reply to Koisan exactly like that
I showed my husband the letter and asked him twice,
but he replied same.
There is no money in Koisan's name
I see.
Well, I'm thinking about when she'll get married,
for any reason
There is no money in Koisan's name
I get it.
but my family is against she open dressmaker.
They want her to study dolls and dance.
But does your brother have the right to restrict her freedom?
I guess there's no.
where is she waiting?
In Gaien.
She came all the way to Tokyo.
Why she's there?
I asked her to do that.
If she come directly here
She meet her brother again, something terrible will happen
Mom.
Hold on.
Be quiet.
Yuko-chan, please bring Koi-san after you settled down.
I want to see her.
I'll tell her so
I'm waiting
Please
You have any money in my name?
That's right. I was thinking of asking my brother
but my sister told me to stop doing that
The truth is,your life is getting tough
So why would you lie and try to cover it up like that?
I don't think so.
I really need that money to open a dressmaker.
What are you doing all of a sudden?
I promised to marry Itakura.
With Itakura?
so do you think I am weird?
I don't think that's the case
He helped my life.
But.
He's pure man.
But he has a strong body.
He has the courage to jump into the fire when the time comes
He has the passion.
But what about Keibon?
You know what?
I realized that education has no worth.
Someone who enjoys the luxury of tasting their mother.
People who have the ability to struggle and survive on their own are much better
I think it's right.
But I wonder if it will affect your marriage if I get married him?
Why should my fate be affected by something like that?
I'm sure that happiness will come to me soon
Yeah.
This is the first time I've said this to you.
Thank you very much.
Are you confident that you'll be happy if you marry Itakura-san?
Well then, please talk to your brother right away
I'll support you too
Go to a nearby place from here
She probably eat her meals outside, right?
Koi?
Yes.
Yeah.
it can't be helped if she didn't.
I want her to sleep in the same futon with you.
Thank for coming.
How are you doing?
The telegram came soon after Yuko left.
from Osaka?
Itakura-san is in critical condition.
Itakura-san's sis told her.
What happened?
Calm down.
I have to go back in Osaka.
Koi.
Hold on.
What happened to him?
He said his ears hurt.
Please tell main house about Itakura.
Koi.
If so, you will surely be happy
I'll ask my brother about the money again.
I'll tell you later.
Thank you very much.
Over there.
I'm Makioka.
Itakura-san's parents has arrived.
I see. So how is the patient?
acute otitis media
He got a fungus in his leg during surgery.
It's serious now.
No, why did it happened...
Thanks for coming.
Are you alright?
it hurts!
It hurts.
Koi.
The director of this clinic is telling me to
operate on the painful part of his leg again
Can you perform the surgery?
Yes.
But his parents are from the countryside, they know nothing.
They said he was killed.
It's better to have surgery,
please tell them.
They will also listen to what important people have to say
Am I like that?
I'll try my best to tell them.
I'll try to tell them while I can.
I guess he's in the middle of surgency right now
Yes.
I was choked up by the phone call from Koi-san
That's what I thought, so what kind of disease is this?
I don't know the details, but it's not like something harmful
If so,He needs to have one leg amputated.
He needs to have one leg amputated?
What are you going to do if he'd saved?
Just thinking about it makes my head hurt.
Sachiko
Actually, deep down
you wish Ita would die, right?
Ah, that's right
Humans are despicable.
Yoneyan.
Koi-san.
Are you alright?
It feels like a dream.
It does not hurts.
What happened with My leg?
I'm glad.
Where did everyone go?
There are resting over there.
I see.
I'm sorry for worrying you so much
What are you talking about?
I'll work as soon as I get out of the hospital
I'll do it too.
Koi-san.
No matter how poor or hardship I'm in,
I have the courage to fight it,
but it's hard to make Koi-san endure that
That alone is the most painful thing
I am planning to be reborn for you.
I tried my best.
Koi-san.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
If anything happened to you, I was going to die.
I'm relieved.
I know it was hard for you.
I for one am glad to get out of the main house.
I see.
But what they say?
About Koi's money.
They said they didn't have that kind of money after all
I just got a call from Koi-san.
From Koi?
Itakura-san has just passed away.
Itakura-san has just passed away?
Koi-san.
What did you come here for?
What do you mean?
I was working with him for long.
I'm also a Blood type A-type
I thought that maybe blood transfusions would be useful
But it was too late.
I thought you'd be happy.
Why me?
I'm not like that.
Itakura ended up like this
Don't die without telling me.
You are stupid.
What a big rock.
This is awesome.
My parents are being taken by Koi-san to see the sights of Osaka
So I thought I'd take this opportunity to let you know
Please come in.
Is it important?
Actually, before that brother died...
Mr. Itakura?
Yes
At that time, Koi-san wasn't there
but my brother said that Yukiko would bring the money from Tokyo soon
Me?
Yes.
Taking the money from the main family.
My brother said happily that it must be a lot of money.
No, not at all
My brother was trying to somehow get money out of Koi-san,
and that's what he did
Well then, Mr. Itakura cheated Koi-san.
I don't want to say this coming from his sister
It's so painful to see that Koi-san has
been kind to us since my brother died.
But my brother is already dead
Please forgive him.
Oh you have a visitor.
The customer is Itakura-san's sister.
Can you see it?
Yes.
Wanna see?
Thank you.
Be careful
so Itakura was such a bad guy?
Koi was deceived.
I don't want to feel like that.
but he was after money
Koi-san was so serious, I want to believe in Koi-san.
but Itakura wanted the money
I think the only person who can provide that money must have been Koisan
Why?
Itakura must have loved Koi-san.
You think so?
That's right, that's what I thought.
I guess I'll just have to keep this story to koi-san.
Yeah.
She might get upset.
What does brother say?
He talked about my blind date again?
That's right.
He's trying his best to make up for it.
That's a pretty good.
Here's very good.
Is this your first time here?
I don't have any business in places like this,
but these days, every company seems to be using these places for some reason
I'm not very good at that kind of meeting,
but does your company have something going on?
I don't come to the place like here.
Today is special day for me.
Your meal is ready.
Let's start
Let's go.
Fukusaburo Hashidera
His biography. Doctor of Medicine
Executive Director, TOWA Pharmaceuticals
What do you think about him?
I don't understand him even if I've seen him once or twice
Yukiko never says anything, but
she always says that she decides for herself whether something is good or bad
Who?
Ennosuke brother.
I see.
He's a bit eccentric
But I think he's the best candidate so far
That's true
He does look similar to him
Your first man.
Help my homework.
Where?
Don't you understand this?
Just think for yourself
I have no idea.
I'll check it later.
Nakan-chan
It seems Koi-san go back home late since I've came here.
It was before that
And She become messy.
Be careful.
No, Keibon.
Do you feel pain?
did you drink too much?
Did you make me drink too much?
Yes, have some water.
Go home,Keibon.
Why
You're mean.
there are good things about you.
Thank you for being so kind to me at Itakura's funeral.
please stop talking about him.
You were burned to death.
Why?
My brother disinheritanceed with me
Your brother disinheritanceed with you.
it's been 35 days since my mother died
I got fired from the store.
I see.
You're miserable too.
What on earth are you planning to do from now on?
Hello,This is Kakioka.
I did it
Don't read at that again
Look at this.
This is the reason why we ended up like this
Hashidera is calling you.
Hashidewa?
Where's the wife?
She came all the way to the post office
No, she's not home
Hashidera-san wants to talk with you.
Me?
Sorry to have kept you waiting
I apologize for being rude someday
Thank you very much for taking me up on your offer
Who?
Hashidera-san
What did he say?
He said Hanging out in Shinsaibashi tomorrow evening
and have dinner together.
Isn't that great?
I wanna go.
There's nowhere for my kids to go
That's the same restaurant as that time
When I heard that
I was scared that the same thing would happen again,
You are stupid.
He knows nothing about you from way back when
But
you promised to go, right?
Why did you go on a blind date with me when that had happened?
It was inevitable.
It was inevitable?
Nakan takes care of me a lot.
So what about today?
I have no idea.
But if I did that, I would have declined today
I wanna be happy too.
Thanks for saying so.
I invited you here without knowing that it was a restaurant with such memories
It's natural for me to be declined, but you come
So I guess I can have a lot of hope
By the way, I have a girl at my home.
She's the only sister's child
She lost her parents early, so I took her in
I think that girl is very cute
Even if you came to my house
To be honest, I might love her more than you
You love children
Yes.
if you do that, there's nothing to worry about
I'm an experts at children.
I'm a big hit with the kids.
I've known that for some time.so I was completely at ease
What were you relieved about?
I was relieved about absolutely everything
And I think you know my assets and income
I studied in Germany for a long time
I knew one German woman,
What else?
but I thought there were more.
That's all.
Actually, you look very similar to a person.
I mean not your looks.
Is that how you feel.
It's an honor.
Touch net.
Big sister, yeah, I'm sad
Why?
Are you really going to get married this time?
Who will see your homework if I'm not here?
Well, I'll get my mom to look at it
I see
but　you really have to study more
and do it yourself
Yes.
Don't tell what Oharu said about the marriage.
I won't say it.
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Yukiko?
What for ?
Nothing.
Yukiko?
She was away just before.
Yes, it seems that Yukiko-chan is into Hashiriya.
She has been waiting for you to call her.
She's really lively.
But it's bad.
Bring me tea and  so we can chat at leisure
I wanna eat sweets.
Ask Oharu.
Oharu.
I wanna eat sweets.
Thank you very much.
You know what?
The matchmaker called the office today.
He said he wanted to cancel this matchmaking.
Why did he suddenly say that?
Hoshidera-san likes Yukiko a lot.
The reason he refused was Koi.
She has been on good terms with a man since Itakura-san passed away.
I guess she seems to be living a bad life
It turned out that she had a sister like that.
Is that true?
I don't know the detail.
My face was turning red.
I was embarrassed.
Is koi really such a bad woman?
The engagement was ruined because of her.
This is such a stupid thing
I don't know what to do.
I'm lonely or sad?, I need to get a clearer picture of my feelings
Say I'm not here.
That's what I said
Please just say something nice and don't let him in
She's here.
But
You are a liar.
You keep missing our plans after this
You think so?
I was disowned
Is it the end of money, the end of ties?
What a stupid.
You talk like a gangster.
So you are like what?
I have no idea.
You're just whore.
Who is the guy you've been hanging out with lately?
Who is that guy called Miyoshi.
Go home.
I don't want to see your face.
I won't go home.
I'll leave then
Welcome home
customer?
Baya from Okuhata is here.
He still think the same about koi.
so please make her for his wife.
After all, Bonbon and Koi have such a long-standing relationship that it was even featured in the newspapers
What would happen to him if koi-san abandon him now?
She's Baya at Keibon's house.
Are you Yukiko?
Nice to meet you.
Koi-san is causing so much trouble for Keibon about money?
Yes, I didn’t say anything like that
But there is no way to do that
This is what I received when he put on your fur coat last winter
And this was when he was making something called Afternoon
In fact, he brought a lot of items from the store for you.
That being said, I am in no way betraying Koi-san
I feel bad.
He did a lot for Koi.
so please, please, please take care of it
I have to go.
Oharu.
Where's her?
Koi.
Have a drink.
Keibo's Baya just visited us.
Oharu told me.
I had a fight with Keibon and we broke up cleanly
If you're going to break up, then break up
You have to make amends.
it's not like that
He followed me around forever,
I was so annoying.
But Keibon have been causing a lot of financial trouble
That's ridiculous and it's definitely not true
Seriously?
I've been doing my own thing.
You know I was saving money too
People don't think that way.
There's no job for Keibon.
I was thinking that if I had to support Keibon, I would
Well, I'd like to ask
Wasn't the fur coat you got last winter made by KEIBON?
I was selling a rose-patterned haori and a kimono that fit into a vertical frame,and bought it.
but the old lady at Keibon said, "I paid for that."
She showed me the receipt.
That afternoon dress was like that too.
I don't want you to believe what she says.
I want to trust Uchika and Ko-san, but
The Baya has solid evidence
If that's the case, then
Well, how about you show me some real evidence?
She said she remembers the ring, the brooch, everything.
He was disowned
Apparently, she said he was the cause of the problem when he took out the jewels from the store
That's not fair
She said that.
Koi-san
The thing I want to say most about all of this is,
Why didn't you clearly break up with Keibon while you were dating Itakura-san?
People might think that you took money from KEIBON and supported ITAKURA.
That's something you do in night business.
You just used him
Now he is no longer be of any use.
You say such horrible things to him
why can't you reply?
I'm going to Tokyo again soon, but I'll just say this
Until now, I only wish your happiness.
It would be ridiculous to think that a
woman can find true happiness that way
You doesn't understand my feelings
Why?
The doctor will come soon
Yukiko says she won't return to Tokyo and will take care of you.
I'm sorry
I know about my health
Maybe three or four mouth.
Keibon's baby?
If so
Miyoshi's baby.
He is a bartender.
You're going to have his baby?
I want to have a baby if I can.
Take care of yourself.
Who will tell koi that she has an ectopic pregnancy?
Yukiko said she would let him know herself.
In ectopic pregnancies, the baby is often unhealthy.
On the contrary, the doctor said that her body is also damaged.
Kian
You haven't slept since last night
You don't have to worry about that
I’m sorry.
You've become completely weak-hearted.
I'm sure you hate me.
Why?
For my sake
Hashidara did a lot to me.
That's enough.
But
Let's talk after you get better.
Hold my hand tightly
Yoneyan.
Yoneyan means Itakura.
Is she dreaming of Itakura?
As expected, the person she like the most is Itakura-san
I think that's pretty clear
Honestly,
She'll die because of Itakura-san.
Why you say like that?
She is having surgery today
Don't wake her up
Dawn is almost here
I feel like I can forgive anything what Koi-san did.
I think Koi-san just tried her best
To grab the second happiness.
To grab the second happiness?
For her,The first happiness has died.
About Itakura?
She worked hard to grab the second happiness.
I guess She's become unable to distinguish between good and bad things
It's no wonder
She was naive by nature.
Yukiko.
You turned down a marriage proposal with Mr. Hashidera for the sake of KOI.
It was not for her.
A marriage proposal that will be ruined because of her
I have no regrets at all.
I want to marry someone who genuinely loves me.
Is that really true?
Why?
I've always wondered about that.
That's funny.
I was relieved to hear that, but when I see what Koi-san do
I sometimes wonder if we're real sisters.
Don't say anything stupid.
I don't know what koi-san do.
I was glad Koi-san was saved.
At least her life was saved.
But the child was dead.
That may not have been my child.
Can you go to by Tobacco for me?
I'm not going to threaten her.
Are you going to marry her to the bartender?
We'll discuss it together someday.
He was a sailor.
I don't know what kind of man he is
Yes, I have given that much thought
Ah, I really can't break up with the person I've been with for so long
But.
You already knew everything
These days, I'm struggling to even afford my own money
Koi has put up a lot of my money.
Well, I think I've already returned all the various items
How much money is that?
How much would you give it from you?
I am very short of money right now
Excuse me.
Hello?
Oh it's you.
I got a letter from Tokyo
I had some business to attend to, so I'm sorry
My sister is coming here next month.
So I decided to have Yukiko-chan stay here until then
Miyoshi.
Here isn't cheap.
Someone really wanted to meet you.
Who is this?
I'm Miyoshi.
I'm the sister of Taeko
Why you came here?
I wanted to meet you.
For what?
Did you come to say that you are against me marrying the Taeko?
If so, what would you do?
I don't care.
I have a responsibility to her as a man.
No matter what anyone says, I will bring her to me.
If you do that, it's not like that kind of business
Are you saying you'd like to help pay for her wedding?
I'll turn down.
What I want is her, not money.
This is a place where people like you come,
so why don't you go home?
What do you see all the time?
Big sister, Makioka's house is gone
and a building like this is going to stand in its place
Seriously
the neighborhood has completely changed too.
I'm disappointed that the town has changed.
Is everything alright for you?
I'm not saying it's alright
I feel like I cry.
That house was sold
The house now belongs to the buyer.
Do you care about anything?
I thought you would be the one to start crying
I had a hard time after going to Tokyo. I can't remembered the past.
Come on, let's go home.
Are you really going,Koi-san?
My sister from Tokyo is coming
I don't wanna see her.
I'll have to see you again someday, but I can't do it right now
I don't wanna see her now.
Please return this to Keibon.
I lost one of them.
This is a real pearl.
Do you think I am really stupid?
Why?
Since I met Mr. Itakura, I have understood who I should love.
But I couldn't forget about luxury.
I was confused, but I was using Keibon to manipulate money.
I feel sorry for Keibon.
If you notice that much, Keibon will forgive you.
What happened to Miyoshi today?
He's back in Ashiya and waiting for me.
He said he'd like to go find a room with me.
Room?
He said he wanted to do that.
I see.
Koi-san, you really like Miyoshi, don't you?
Why do you ask that?
I'm sure if you are with Miyoshi
You'd be able to endure any hardship.
You're thinking of renting out the room
If you do it, you have to make a decision
Do you doubt us?
I won't tell you what to say though
But How good is the other person...
Can you stand living in poverty?
You can't do that
What?
but he came out and did something wrong
I'm a dirty woman dating a bad man like bartender.
Koi
I think you despise me but I have my own way of life
From now on, leave me alone
You don't know my feelings
Koi.
why do you say things like that?
I met Miyoshi.
I wouldn't do something like that! Honestly if I don't care you.
Really?
my sister in the main family was against you.
I will convince your sister
My mom came back with her aunt from Tokyo
so I'll be there soon
Well then, Koi-san, please wait a moment
After all, Koi-san was born at the youngest age in a family of only women
When she was little, she had a pitch black face
She was called a dirty kid and wasn't loved very much
So, she don't have to like bartenders
Welcome.
Hello?
you look fine
I'm just strong.
I guess you're doing your homework,
I'll take a look at it.
Give me the stick.
Thanks.
Did you tell your sister about KOI and Miyoshi?
I was just talking about that
I feel sorry for myself too.
Why?
No matter how much freedom you say you have,
After all, We need the right man for our home.
We care about public opinion.
You are too happy.
She has no more choices.
I don't know what kind of person he is.
Do you know the man
He's not rich but he's very manly.
I think she'll be happy with him.
Yukiko-chan, I agree with this idea.
Really?
She is against it.
The most important thing is personality.
I think our family agree this idea.
Family background, lineage, and fortune are all gone
Thanks,Sis.
But you worry about Koi-san a lot.
When will you be happy?
I'm still happy, and I have that feeling in my hearts.
You can't tell it from the outside.
Yeah but....
Don't worry.
I'll find my happiness for myself,
I'll bring Koi-san.
Koi-san?
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
I can't find Koi-san.
She told me that she met Miyoshi at the station.
I'm going.
Hold on.
I'm talking about money Koi-san wants.
That is actually what we are keeping
I used it when my child was sick.
That's fine.
Hold on.
Say this to Koi-san.
Please tell her that I will pay for your wedding.
She's coming.
Your sisters in Tokyo have agreed to your marriage.
Ok?
If you find a room, please come back right away.
We congratulate you.
Ok?
Yukiko was on time?
Sis.
Come to think of it, it seems my way of thinking is the oldest among my siblings
It's like there's a disembodied something stuck somewhere in my head forever
Yeah.
Sachiko-chan doesn't have any troubles,
You think so?
I'm sorry.
Sister, It's snowing.
Really.
THE END.