Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Ninja in a Business Suit
Oh my god
Isomura Industrial Research Institute
Good morning,everyone
You guys worked all night
I'm back from Osaka now
welcome back
The work of this survey is very difficult, isn't it?
We are doing a demand survey on the fan popularity list
If we talk about fans in winter, people won't be interested in them.
Each manufacturer is now taking measures for summer products
We do our best to investigate and get only a profit of 30,000 yen
This is an unprofitable business
Only big companies make money
But we are subcontractors of big companies
Oh yeah,
How was your job in Osaka?
Did you get the money?
This is 100,000 yen.
This is a severance payment.
It seems that a research company has also been established in Osaka.
So they don't need us anymore
I get paid, right?
You can pay the loan
We'd be happy to get some money for the severance payment..
That company is cold to us
If a big research company is established in Tokyo, we may go bankrupt
I may be dismissed
Our president is a sucker for big business.
Watch the phone
I'm sorry
I'll answer
Hello?
This is Isomura Industrial Research Institute
What? Isomura is our president
Oh...Yes
I see.
I'll go there right now
What's wrong?
What's wrong with our president?
He died in a car accident
He died ?
Where?
At Nakasen-street
He was hit by a car
Call his daughter now,Furukawa
I don't think she's at home
Let's find out where his daughter might be.
Verification please
He's your father, right?
President
Are you sure he is Shohei Isomura?
I'm sorry
These are his belongings.
What's this?
It was in his jacket pocket
It may have come in by chance
It ’s a dead leaf, is n’t it?
This is a leaf of Shiiki
I thought I'd throw it away, but I took it
Can you keep it?
We keep this?
Yes,I want to check this dead leaf
So please keep it as proof
keep it as proof?
Yes,please
Please tell us a little more about the situation of the accident
According to the driver, he suddenly jumped out in front of the car.
But I think this is his excuse
We've referred the driver for manslaughter.
He was also a speeding over 10km
I don't think this is a simple accidental death
I think it's a little strange that he dies in a car accident
What do you mean?
For example, he may have been taken sleeping pills and taken out in front of the car
Of course we also examined the inside of his stomach
There were no sleeping pills or alcohol in his stomach
There was only a little food left in his stomach
His body seems to have been a little weak
Anyway don't think too much
The president was very happy to go home
Why was he walking alone in that place?
He was walking alone on such a distant road in the middle of the rain.
I can't understand why he walked that way
About The dead leaves in his coat
It seems that trees will die due to exhaust gas near the factory that makes TVs.
Maybe he was in a TV factory
But there is no TV factory in that place
We will stop producing science TVs, right?
It was officially decided at yesterday's meeting
The new TV we are releasing is called AH4
This TV is still in production and must be kept secret
As a means to do that
We tell the business industry that our new product is a 16 in flat-screen TV.
Keep secret until you are ready for mass production
Hello? It's me
Oh you
What?
Ok, good
What's wrong? Machida
I was contacted by a subordinate who was spying on Shindai Electric.
Mr.Tsumura
What?
Check that flowerpot.
Does it belong to our company?
No,This is a borrow from the outside
They come to replace once a week
This is a microphone
This is a small dynamic microphone
Why was this in a flowerpot?
What do you mean?
All our conversations are recorded
This is a product of Shingai Electric
There is a spy
I think it's a bad spy.
If I'm a spy I use the new radio
Anyway I will investigate this gardening company
And
I use this the other way around
You'll use?
We'll leave a recording of the lie conversation.
We will start mass production of 16-inch flat-screen TVs next year
That's good
From now on, 14-in TVs will be replaced by 16-in TVs.
16 in TV information is still a secret in the industry, isn't it?
If they have a female spy,they'll know
That's enough
Good job,Kaneko
I gave money to a gardening company and put it on the bottom of the flowerpot.
16 in flat-screen TV is fine
If it is the same product, we outperform them in terms of capital and productivity.
But we mustn't let our guard down.
Find out until you have a solid confirmation
OK?
Yes
Japan's economy is being gobbled up by foreign capital.
This is the conclusion
Even if it is a pure domestic product, We have to use foreign parts.
The future of the Japanese economy is also difficult.
Mr. Kazuo Kato, an economic commentator, visited us this morning.
We visited the house of Moriichi, a professor at the Doctor of Economics University.
We talked to him about the future of the Japanese economy
I didn't notice that the front door was open
Actually, I opened the front door when the TV sound came out
And I listened to the sound of the TV for a while
You are awesome.
You're doing my best even if your father dies
I'm trying hard to work hard and forget about misery
I’m here to pick you up.
Actually I got a cab so I feel it's better if someone go together
The current TV program will continue for a long time, so please do your best
This is the bill
Here are the rent and food expenses
What can we do?
What do you mean?
Please extend the payment well
You know that this company doesn't have a job, right?
I wonder if I will be freelance
freelance?
I'm going to be independent.
I want to do a bigger job than being used as an employee
See our president?
He was killed to get a job
He did a lot to us
Hey,Hinuma
You think too much.
It has no confirmation
I'm sure he was killed
I want to know what he's been looking into.
I don't want to waste his death
We are just regular employees
So for big companies it doesn't matter if any of us die
But I don't like it
If a big company wants to take advantage of us, we have to be strong
I take as much money as possible from big companies
Companies are trying to steal each other's trade secrets
They are trying to survive by all means
We interrupt there
Come here, Hinuma-san and Endo-san
What's wrong?
There is a big news
Come on, Endo-san
We are like mice
What's wrong?
She is my lover Takako Kume, a telephone operator of Sanesu Electric.
Tell them yesterday's story
Sanesu Electric will release a new TV called AH4 next year
AH4?
What kind of tv is it
I just listened to the manager's phone
I don't know for sure.
But it seems to be a revolutionary new product
Is that all?
Remember that story more.
I'll love you tonight
AH4
Let's go together
I want to go to Kumagaya
Go with me?
I would like to find out what the president tell Shinkai Denki.
If I go to Kumagaya, I think there are some clues
Sorry for the inconvenience
This is natural because it is for the president
I'm Akiko
So Akiko-san
You also had a lot of trouble
Please relax for a while
How about moving from Tokyo?
I can't. because I have to work
This area is noisy these days unlike in the past
By the way,When the president came here, did you notice any changes in him?
About my brother?
Let me see
Nothing in particular
It was just a little weird when he return
What happened?
There was just a TV survey that day
TV?
What did they come to investigate
They asked us What do you want for your second TV?
They brought a paper
So I answered the survey.
I had a brother, and that became a problem.
My brother is an expert, so I've entrusted him with the investigation.
My brother looked at the paper and had a troubled face
He came home with the paper
I couldn't find that paper among his belongings for sure
What question was written on the paper?
I'm too dumb to remember a few things.
The paper was immediately collected by the investigator.
Information on the size of the TV was written on that paper
They told me to check my favorite TV
Which one did you check
I checked 4 inch TV
4 inch TV?
4 inch TV is like this size
This is a TV that is too small so I checked this because it is interesting
Thanks
There was a TV that could be removed in the car
I checked that
It's cool we can watch TV in the car
It's the worst if I watch TV and have a traffic accident
I knew what he was investigating
A manufacturer is trying to develop a micro TV
He cough this information
If I look this up, I'll know.
You can also see why he died
Thank you very much for thinking about my father
But he died
I think he can finally sleep because he was so busy
Can you leave him alone?
I will not forgive anyone who lives without guilt.
I need to find out why he dead
I can't forgive them
Anyway I'll return to Tokyo
And then we'll have a meeting to figure out what to do.
Hi I want to eat Ramen
No,
I have a lot of bills
How much?
He is hungry.
Order ramen for him
I paid for the train so I don't have any money anymore.
so Please
You can be good wife
I'm disgusted with this life
Ok.let's go for eating
I'll pay in cash
Let's eat
Is it a 4-inch small TV that can be attached to a car?
Is it possible to develop?
The president happened to get the survey form and let the company know.
Someone who knew it killed him?
Maybe
But do they kill people to get the survey form?
The president may have found the factory
There was a leaf in his pocket that was dead from the exhaust gas
But there is no clue
For that matter, let's find out the connection between Han-chan's girlfriend's new TV and this Kumagai.
Why don't you use that to blackmail 3S Electric?
But everything is just speculation.
That much information is not enough
If my intuition is right, I will make a lot of profits
Let's do it without fear of failure.
This is 3S electric
I’m Machida
Nice to meet you
Take your seat
What can I do for you?
I heard that your new product in the industry is a 16-inch flat-screen TV
Oh I see
In fact
Someone said your new product is different
Oh I see
Go ahead
Your new product is an ultra-compact TV that can be used in a car, right?
Oh I see
I'll be frank with you.
If you don't buy this information we're going to sell this information
For example, to Chugai electric
That's fine
So?
So what?
Do you buy?
No
Such an ultra-small TV cannot be made with the current Japanese technology.
Your engineers are very good
I think no one will buy it even if we sell it
Other electronics companies are not stupid
we're negotiating with you because it's technically possible
You sure?
Let me listen
Talk about it for our technology improvement
I can't say that easily
So up to you
I have a meeting so excuse me for this
People like you sometimes visit me
But I didn't have time to talk to them
Wait a min
Please contact me if you want to hear the continuation of the story
We look forward
Please hand over your business card to the secretary
Isn't it difficult to develop an ultra-small TV?
We have to bet on it.
We haven't heard from 3S Denki since then.
Is there a company that needs such a TV even though the market is so small?
Development of a new refrigerator in 1963
No research work comes in
We should have subcontracted for the company like our president did.
Who are you guys?
Why you are here?
Is this an industrial research office?
Yes, and you?
We just came here to say hello
say hello?
What the hell
Stop it
Who are you guys?
We just came here to play
We wanted you to see this hunting gun
We just hit a little,
Stay down
Are you ok,Hinuma?
Damn it
The police these days understand us well
I can say that I went out of control when I was playing with a hunting gun
All you have to do is ask me if I'll pay for it myself, or if I'll serve a year in jail for injury.
I will get bail by the way
Who did you ask?
Listen
You guys should quit this job
This world is not so easy.
Listen
You guys should quit this job
You understand?
We understand
I just have to quit my job, right?
That's right.
I'm okay if you understand
Can I smoke?
This is not in the subway.
Smoke as much as you want
Everyone will go home
They hit us.
Damn it
Everything goes wrong
Listen
This is 3S electric's reply
They want us to keep our mouths shut.
In short,
The information on the micro TV was true
My intuition seems to be right
Let's look behind them
We'll definitely find someone who is using them
The answer is this cigarette lighter.
This is a cigarette lighter camera
I've made up my mind.
If we're quiet, they'll just use us.
I'm angry at companies that use sneaky means
They use Yakuza
If we identify them, we will get a lot of rewards.
Hey, Hinuma
I found out what they were
He is a former yakuza named Fukai
Recently he has been hired by Taiyo research company, Uehara.
Taiyo research company?
I haven't investigated this company yet
It's a one-year-old company
I still don't know which company is affiliated
Let's go to the company immediately
But I don't think they say anything when they get in there
We'll have to stake it out for a while.
Can I borrow your friend’s car,Han-Chan?
Can you ask your friend?
He is trying make a call
Oh to noodle shop
Are you Sakashita noodle?
This is Taiyo search
I want a order a noodle
He is stingy
Don't say bullish
I'll switch with you.
Wait. Fukaya is coming
Now we have proof that they attacked us.
Oh shit!
He found us?
Never mind
He originally has that kind of eyes
I'll switch with you.
If he goes somewhere, ask you to go
I and Han-Chan try to kidnap Uehara and threaten him
Oh my god
What's wrong?
The soba shop really brought the soba
Mr. Hinuma's telepathy is wonderful.
Hey,Hinuma,Handa!
Uehara will go out
Uehara-san
You are Mr. Uehara of the Taiyo Research Center,right?
Who are you guys?
We are here to pick up you
Pick up me?
Who ask?
A company
I can't say any more.
This is urgent
Please get in the car
Who are you?
Why did you come in without permission?
Where is Uehara?
My boss?
He's just gone out
Oh I'm sorry
Who are you?
I'm Yasuoka from 3S electric
Oh you are from 3S
I was very sorry
Can I wait for him here?
Sure
I'll make a tea for you
Here it is
Thanks
Oh shit
I forgot....
Eh?
I'm out of cigarettes
I have some
Please
I like cigarettes with a filter
I'll buy it for you
Oh, thanks
Here it is
High light or hope,right?
Yes
TV penetration survey card
Please wait a moment
Get off of me
Why did you guys bring me here?
Do you have any idea if we are person from Isomura Industrial Research Institute?
It seems you know something
What the hell
Don't pretend you don't know
I also investigated your relationship with the yakuza Fukai
I also took a picture of where you give him money
Be honest.
What the hell
The attack on our office was probably ordered by the 3S Corporation.
Say it
Hit you if you don't say
No
So why you did it?
The fewer peers, the better.
Forgive me
I will get along with you guys
Don't cheat
Who asked you? 3S right?
Say it
I can not breathe.
Get off of me
I'm a 3S electricity research company
Your company had a beef with 3S Electric, so I helped them out.
I was willing to help them
This is the perfect place to blackmail you.
No one hear us
Confess more
Your company was asked by 3S in Kumagaya to investigate,right?
President Isomura of our company saw the survey form and learned that 3S Electric will develop a new ultra-compact TV.
He found the factory
The president tried to inform Chugai Electric of the information
You knew it and killed him
You pushed him in front of the running truck
I don't know about him
I just did a survey
I don't know anymore
Trust me
Say it
I know you can't say you killed a person
Don't you want to die?
Where is the factory?
I don't know
Say it!
It's true that 3S Electric is making ultra-compact TVs, isn't it?
It's no use asking me that
I forgive you for this today.
But prove your crime and make sure you are arrested
Let's go
I feel really stuck.
A person named Hinuma is chasing me
They have threatened me
Damn it
By the Hinuma?
He also noticed that I killed Isomura
we're in danger.
It's none of my business
Give me a break
I killed Isomura for your company
It was my failure for Isomura to learn about my Kumagaya investigation.
If other companies know the results of that survey, you will be in great trouble.
I didn't ask you killed him
It's your business
Then I have an idea too
Calm down
I'll check on his movements.
He seems to know the daughter of Mr. Isomura who died
Now we know for sure that 3S Electric is developing an ultra compact TV.
Let's go directly to the factory and find out the secret of the product
And let's talk to 3S Electric
Let's check the factory
But one of their four factories
Maybe there is a secret factory
Maybe it's in the neighborhood of the president's parents' house
However, there is no such factory in Kumagaya
Let's do this
You should look for a parts drafting manufacturer
If it's a micro-TV, there should be a lot of parts on order.
The delivery destination is their secret factory
And another one
Find out their engineers
Probably a lot of engineers are working for this product
They may be in the factory
That might be in captivity
Ok, I'll do it with Handa
I'll find whoever killed the president.
I'm sure we'll find the people at the big corporations who ordered it.
Leave the rest work to you
Let's do it tomorrow morning,Han-Chan
Endo-san
Can I borrow some money?
I feel like drinking a little
only you?
Never mind
I give you
I'll have it
Are you going to date with someone?
Don't say bullshit
Please use the electric blanket of Chugai Electric
World-famous Chugai Electric
Chugai Electric
Who is it?
I'm hinuma
Sorry I'm drunk
What time is it now?
it's still 8 pm,
Please come in
Thank you
I'm here to talk with you something
Your dad was looking up information about 3S electricity
3S's?
He died on the way to inform Chugai Denki of the information
Perhaps he was killed by the pressure of 3S Electric
Did you find the evidence?
Still treated as a traffic accident
But I will definitely find the culprit
To achieve this, I will definitely find a factory for ultra-small TVs.
Don't push yourself too hard
I worry about you
I'm very worried because you are so serious
You take good care of yourself
Akiko-san
I also want to live a life in peace
You will understand me someday
Behind every great product there is a black shadow.
Your father is the victim
I don't mind being called a poisonous mouse
They are dirty than me
They are willing to kill people for the benefit of the company
I can't forgive them
Then
I'm going home
See you
We make glass for CRTs in 3S electric
But such small TV glasses haven't been ordered by them
I see
It is said that it is difficult to produce CRT glass in-house.
Ordinary glass is fine as long as the quantity is about the prototype.
So it's conceivable that a manufacturer could make CRT glass in their own factory.
Yes,they can do it if you make a small facility
Certainly there was a patent application for a television transistor this spring
Who applied for it?
Mr. Matsushima, a semiconductor expert
Lecturer at Toyo Institute of Technology
Is it an individual, not a company?
Yes
But
Is this an individual study?
This is a very advanced content, isn't it?
maybe
For example, is it possible that some company is pretending to be an individual?
The content and design of the invention are necessary for the application procedure, right?
maybe
Can I see it?
The intelligence agencies of each manufacturer always ask us
They come up with a lot of money and we get very upset.
If we cooperate with them, Japanese companies will only make a mess.
Does it make sense?
Mr.Matsushima is in USA now
He went there around the beginning of January.
To USA?
Is there anyone doing the same research as him?
Do you know?
Yes,Taskahata,
He is an engineer in 3S electric
3S's?
Where is he living?
Ok, wait a min
Here is his resume
Thanks
May I ask you something?
What?
Is the person living across the street a 3S electric person?
Yes he is the engineer
He is now in usa for research
To USA?
Yes he's gone around January
He left his newly-married wife
That's too bad
Her wife is a person who doesn't go out much
But she goes out early on Sunday morning and comes back late at night
Sunday,right?
Thanks
Let's go
He is Takahata
The engineer is actually confined under the excuse of traveling to the United States
I see
If we follow him, you'll know the location of the secret factory.
I think it'll work fine
The trade secrets of large companies can be understood thanks to the young couple.
No one can beat humanity, can they?
Thank you Mr. and Mrs. Takahata
Humans are wonderful!
Let's go
Are you jealous?
I want to meet more comfortably
They probably stay out
What should we do?
We'll stay out too
Do you have enough money?
Of course not
Your watch is made in Switzerland, isn't it?
I need to say good bye to my watch
If I put it in a pawn shop in Kumagaya, I can't easily come to pick it up
We'll come often
Let's go
Is this the secret factory of 3S?
It doesn't look like that
That's it
The president had that dead leaf
It must be here
The leaves are dead, right?
This is due to the chlorine produced for semiconductor manufacturing
Can you hear something?
What?
I hear strange sounds
Yes I can hear
It's like the sound of water
It ’s the sound of cleaning to make semiconductors.
So must be here
Here they are making a micro TV
Ok Let's check it out
How can we go inside?
Let's go back today
We should make a plan and come here again
Do you worry about Hinuma?
What?
What does he do lately?
I don't know well but he is checking around about 3S electric
Oh 3S's
As an employee of Chugai Electric, I'm curious about that information.
What exactly is that information?
It seems to be the secret of a micro TV
He always does dangerous things
He may go to the 3S factory
Oh I get it
I want to help him but
Let me know if something happen on him
I want to help him
According to the story of Isomura's daughter,Hinuma is checking around about 3S electric
Of course, the security of the factory is strict.
Please cooperate with me too
Our purpose is corporate defense
First, keep them away from the factory.
Even if they find a factory, it is difficult to enter the factory.
So you must absolutely prevent them from entering.
I scoured the fire department and the electric company to get a floor plan of this plant.
I see. Well, so We will be fire station staff
Can you do it well?
Leave it to me
I'm good at making certificates since I was a student
I made a graduation certificate and even a salary statement
I helped many people
I'm glad this talent of mine is being put to use.
Good job
It was information that 3 S electric is making a 16-inch TV but
It seems that there is no such thing even if we check the parts factory
Maybe they are developing another product
Soga-kun
Do you have any information for that?
I'm collecting that information but..
The information on the 16-inch TV we are developing has already become public.
What the hell is this?
It ’s better to steal than to be stolen.
There may be industrial spy in our company
Our department is checking to see if the spy is there
We got the proof at the end
Proof?
Was there a spy here?
I think you only have serious employees
The spy is in this room
Because there was a flaw in our defense measures.
This is my fault, I'm sorry
Now I announce who the spy is
Hashizume-kun
What?
You announce here as a 3S Electric Spy
Am I spy?
What the hell?
Don't pretend you don't know
There are many suspicious points lately, so I asked Kaneko to investigate them.
I found out about your relationship with Mr. Machida of 3S.
Needless to explain
This is the proof
Here's a picture of when you met him secretly
Ms.isomura
He is Nakaoka from Chugai electric
He will be in charge of the show on behalf of Mr. Hashizume
I'm Nakaoka
I'm Isomura
I didn't know you were in charge
Mr. Hashizume was fired from the company today
Why?
This is just between you and me,
Spy?
He was a industrial spy
I was also surprised
Which company's
I hear it's 3s electric's
How many cigarettes do you smoke a day?
I'm asking you
That's depend on day
I don't care about the number of cigarettes when I'm thinking
You smoke too much
I haven't charged you for cigarettes
I have no money to lend to you
Is Hinuma here?
What's wrong with him?
Where is he now?
He is in Kumagaya
He went looking for a 3S factory
When has he left?
This morning
There is a problem
What's wrong with him?
I told Mr. Hashizume about him
Because I thought he is an employee of Chugai Electric
I didn't know He is 3s's spy
What? Hashizume is a spy?
I heard it today
If he is a spy, all of Hinuma's actions are known to be 3S.
It's very dangerous for him to go to the 3S Factory
We are from the Kumagaya Fire Department
We came for a temporary inspection
Is this real?
Yes
Thanks for your work
Please put this on your chest
Thanks
Hello?
I'll show you around
Don’t worry about us
We finally found it
It's a very small TV
That is 4 in TV for sure
This has just been replaced
Thanks for telling me
Who is the duo in the coat?
They are from the fire department
They're here for a temporary inspection.
Did you confirm their identity?
They had an ID card
Please contact the fire department
Yes
But...
An emergency security order has been issued from the head office
Yes
What siren is this?
The news that a spy has infiltrated
Then see you
Thank you
Hey! Catch them
Run away!
Wait!
Let's escape to the back
Take this and run away
Run straight here
There is a gate
Come on!
Wait!
Close the gate
Run away!
Who are you?
Hey, say something
I'm looking up
He seems to have escaped well
Shout up
Who are you spying for?
I will talk after meeting the factory manager
We will dispose of you
If you do,You may be fired
In addition you will be arrested by the police
Are you the factory manager?
Who are you?
I'm Takashi Hinuma
I'm from Isomura Industrial Research Institute
That's what I thought
I know you are here
I was waiting for you
Really?
Then it's easy to talk about.
Well, that's the problem with my people running away.
It's enough to catch you alone
Crimes of trespassing
Injury charges and obstruction of business
Your sins are many.
But it's not easy
We hold the secret of this factory
He can tell that information to Chugai Electric
We can sell it at high price
But I am the only person who can stop him
Let's deal?
What are you doing?
I'll talk to Mr. Machida directly.
You also need his instructions
Please connect to the Tokyo head office
Hi, I'm Machida
What? Hinuma?
Hi,machida-san?
It's been a whole
Now I am in your factory manager's office and looked around the site
And
What?
Did you take the photo?
Do you buy the film?
I'll make the price
Includes President Isomura's incense fee
If you don't buy, there are many people who want to buy
Come to the headquarters tomorrow.
at 7 pm
We can talk there
Good.
I'm looking forward to seeing you
I'm in captivity now
Change the phone to the factory manager
Talk to him
I've failed.
The security system of the factory has been tightened.
How much does he demand?
I'll meet him tomorrow
But before that, we have to decide the policy of the company
How complete is the AH 4-inch TV?
Up to now, 100 units have been made
It will be released 4 months in advance, so we will increase production capacity by then.
Eventually 2000 units will be in stock
If you can't release it, we have to make it public.
If we do that, other companies will imitate it.
Other companies may know the structure of ultra-small TVs and enter the production system
Then the market will be confused
If they do so, we will not be able to sell the AH 4-inch TV exclusively.
All our efforts will be in vain.
Either buy it at his asking price or make it public.
There are two choices
If we buy from him, it doesn't mean our secrets won't leak to other companies.
Hello?
Oh Hinuma
Did you succeed?
That's good.
I worried about you
Akiko-san is here
She also worried about you
Let me get her on the phone.
Hello?
Akiko-san?
Mr. Hashizume was a spy for 3S?
I see
No worry.
I've got their secret.
Maybe we'll find out who killed your father.
I definitely want this
Don't push yourself too hard
Yes
He wants to talk with you
Hashizume?
We'll find out his address
OK,
Leave it to me
Good
You were valuable because you were at Chugai Electric.
You were fired as a spy.
You are no use anymore
Machida-san
I've been working hard for 3 S so far
I was an employee of Chugai Electric, and I worked for the 3Ss.
Do you understand my miserable feelings?
You were originally an employee of Chugai Electric.
As for your espionage, I settled for money.
The company hires people who can help the company develop
No need for worthless spies anymore.
The relationship with you will be cut off in the future
This is a natural decision
You'll be working for another company.
Damn it
Treat me like trash and I will surely make you regret it.
I will reveal all the secrets of this company
Can you send him out?
Give him some money
Are you Hashizume-san,right?
Who are you?
I'm from this company
I have a favor to ask of you.
It's not big deal
I want you to call Mr. Uehara of Taiyo Research
To Mr. Uehara?
Yes To Mr. Uehara
It's a simple requirement
I want you to call him up.
If you refuse, you will be guilty of murder.
I quit spying
I hate being arrested
I promise to meet him at 1 o'clock
Yes..but
He's in trouble if he doesn't meet me
What's happening?
There will be a press conference from now on
There will be a press conference?
Look at this,everyone
This is 3S Electric's new 4 in TV
This is a great product
How much is the price?
Is this a self-confident work?
Oh It's not expensive
So you can buy
What are you doing?
There was a traffic jam
This design is pretty good
Sit down
I respect your efforts
But
The secret you grabbed is no longer worth it
Please take a look at our products slowly
I just want to tell you this
Our original plan is
The plan was to secure inventory quantities and monopolize the market.
But we had a press conference today
I think other companies will develop the same product
So our market is monopolized for only 6 months
But in the meantime we will sell as much as possible
For at least 10 months, we will dominate the market for 4-inch small TVs.
I just want to tell you this
Please congratulate us
congratulation
I just want to tell you this
See you
Come in
What's wrong?
I got a call from Mr. Hashizume.
You want us to come here
Did I call you?
I didn't.
Something is wrong
machida-san
Are you going to fire us like Hashizume?
I rewarded you for sure
We announced 4 in TV
Our business is over.
What do you want?
We also have an idea if you dismiss us
We announce that We have killed Isomura at your order
Isomura?
Do whatever you want
There is no evidence that I did
I don't know if he was killed or not
If the police are involved, you're in more trouble, right?
We are not afraid of it
Isomura found out 3S Electric's development of a small TV.
He pushed Isomura in front of the truck
And I ordered him that
But if we are arrested you will be called by the police as a witness
I will announce everything
You are in trouble, right?
We don't care if we get arrested
But you are also responsible
We'll get you involved.
I get it
Will you become an temporary employee of our company at 400,000 a month?
Please say so from the beginning
Machida-san
I have one more thing I want you to buy
What?
It's thanks to your company's wireless microphones that we know who killed President Isomura.
Don't say bullshit
Where did you hide the microphone?
I recorded all your conversations
Isomura found out 3S Electric's development of a small TV.
He pushed Isomura in front of the truck
And I ordered him that
But if we are arrested you will be called by the police as a witness
I will announce everything
You are in trouble, right?
Industrial espionage is not just your specialty
It wouldn't be strange if there was one spy in this company.
How much you want?
Hey! How much you want?
I don't want to sell this
Don't try to solve everything with money!
This dead leaf is the dead leaf that was in your factory
President Isomura had the same dead leaves
It is kept at the police station in Kumagaya
President Isomura was imprisoned in your factory and killed
Police investigate the background
Moreover
Hashizume you fired
He appears in the police as an important person
Mr. Machida of 3S Electric is said to have been dismissed.
He was fired
I think President Isomura will be a little pleased with this.
But it's a little complicated.
Here is your tea
Machida also worked hard for the company and was finally dismissed
I feel sorry for him
By the way, what will happen to us in the future?
We have to work for living
Let's talk about work when Hinuma returns
Hinuma-san
I'm sure my dad is grateful to you
I don't think I've been helpful.
I felt like I was facing a big company
What will you do from now on?
I'm thinking of going to Kansai
To Kansai?
Now is the age of wireless
Car phone is one of them
I heard a rumor that a company in Kansai will develop it
So
You don't change anything
Would you like to investigate a wireless company this time?
No, it isn't.
Not a spy activity from another company
It ’s a survey that surveys consumers and helps the company.
I would like to do such an economic survey
I'm sure my colleagues will cooperate
That's cool.
Would you like to change the name of the company and start again?
Isomura Industrial Research Institute is uncool name
I will not change the name of the company for the president
You are a very old-fashioned person
We need an old-fashioned man in this era
I may also be an old-fashioned woman
I think I'll go to Kansai with you.
Akiko-san
I'll pick you up
Surely
Until then, you should be doing TV commercials for Isomura Industrial Research Institute on TV.
Special price, please.
The end