Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Kagoshima
Hey wake up
Wake up
I'm sorry you're tired, but I need you to fly to Amami Oshima again.
What did you just say?
What?
If you're sorry, don't ask me to do it.
It's hot
This is an urgent job and the pay is high.
I don't want money
But it comes with something special
What?
I'm sorry, sir.
What's going on?
Is someone hurt?
go to the island and ask her
Please
I hate women who smell like medicine
Ok let's go
Escape from Zero Visibility / Zero Escape Visibility (1963)
(Shikai Zero no Dasshutsu)
That day was the hottest on record according to weather station reports.
I got back from the Genkai Sea fish finder at one o'clock in the afternoon.
Excuse me
I'm tired.
I wish you'd shut up.
I'm tired too.
I was in the hospital, finally out of surgery, and they ordered me to go to Amami Oshima right away.
You know how I feel.
I flew to the Genkai Sea in the morning, and when I finally got home...
I'm your companion now
What's the hell
But I'm going because it's important.
For The kids.
I'm not into kids
I hope you're not too good with airplanes.
use this bag
i hate flying
You'd rather use a boat
I have to be at the island hospital by 4:00 p.m.
It's 2pm
An hour and a half at most.
We'll be there soon
Do you feel safe?
what do you do with that pistol?
Use this to kill sharks when they fall into the ocean
You fall into the ocean?
Please keep this if you are worried.
This is sky island
From where?
That island's team
That island's team?
an emergency has occurred
please land immediately
Wind speed 65M.
the runway is short
So please be careful
I'm so unlucky today
is something wrong?
They are calling us
How much time do you have?
I'm sure it's just another medical emergency.
I was dropped off the other day carrying an appendectomy patient.
Is there a doctor on the island?
There's a small fishing village on the cape.That's all
We'll land on
We landed on
It's an emergency, so please come immediately.
I get it
Please tell me the detail
It's an emergency, so please come immediately.
I get it
Come with me.
There is an air conditioner and it is cool
I'll be waiting.
What's that?
It's a live vaccine for infantile paralysis.
vaccine?
That's why I'm in such a hurry.
I have to be there by 4:00.
If I'm not there by 4:00, the dry ice will melt.
Why didn't you just say so?
I'll be back soon
Please.
Thanks for your help.
We've been waiting for you
Who are you?
I'm sure you are not working here
What's wrong?
You'll know if you come
Senior
What's wrong?
what happened to the plane that crashed?
Don't touch them or I'll shoot you
What's the hell about this?
It's easy to tell if you're kidding or not.
Are you alright too?
There are only men here, so men will attack you.
They are crazy. don't get involved with them
If you give me a plane, I will spare your lives.
Me and airplane?
They crash landed, so they used you to escape from here.
There is a small fishing village on the cape.There is a site back of them
did you fly alone?
Yeah
It's ok if I give you the plane but What about the pilot?
Sorry
I've got about 2,500 hours on the plane.
That plane doesn't often fly if it's not for me.
I have no idea
I like that kind of plane
You sure?
Get the plane now
This is still a joke.
I'm not ordinally guy
You turned me mad
I saw someone
Damn it
What's wrong?
How about there?
We don't have enough gas to get where we're going.
gas ?
I don't know how far you're going, but it's enough to get you to Okinawa.
I looked upstairs, but gasoline is nowhere to be found.
What are we gonna do?
If we don't have enough, we'll just replenish it.
Is there anything else out of the ordinary?
It's too late for that if you miss them
I like the plane
And this
do you like women stuff?
Hurry up and get some gas.
this is not an airport
How could you not have stored it?
We don't have it
This island would have also served as an evacuation airport.
How could an evacuated plane fly over without gas?
We don't have it
If in doubt, check the airport.
Are you sure?
If in doubt, check it
You can't refuel immediately.
It was still landed on the cape due to the typhoon.
How long does it take?
It takes 40 minutes round trip by car
Guide me
What if I say no?
I'll kill you in a raw
I'll give you the guide
Yoshimoto
I've been bitching and moaning about the mundane nature of my job day in and day out, but I never thought it would be this exciting.
Bring us the car
no wireless
There was hand pottery on top
hand pottery ?
For short distances it is enough
you do bad things we kill you
I'm still single.
I don't wanna die
What about the gasoline?
We're going to the Cape to get it.
I'll take you there now. You wait in the car.
This kind of problem happened because of you
Look,The chartered plane crashed
We found a new plane, but I'm running out of gas
we may escape from here next year
Stop drinking
I'm an errand boy
All you want is a drink and a girl, and you're in.
You found that
Stay alert.
Call me if you see anything out of the ordinary.
I haven't smelled a woman in two months and she has a Pistol, I'm mad.
Please continue with your duties as usual.
But no radio calls or phone calls from the outside
Do as I say.
What if I don't?
What the hell are you doing this for?
Why don't you mind your own business You should be thinking about taking me down.
person with bad leg
What's the hell?
If you call me person with bad leg, I will never forgive you.
There are some things people don't want you to touch.
Don't tell me anymore
What's the one thing you don't want people to touch?
That's what I'm more interested in.
Who take the phone?
Answer any questions you have.
The answer is "all clear.
I understand English.
Hello?
This is Sasarito site
About a direct flight to Amami Oshima?
It went through about 20 minutes ago.
Everything is fine.
I will contact you as soon as I have more information.
I get it
From where?
Kagoshima.
They're worried they haven't heard from the plane.
We are always quick to exchange information
We'd be quicker to refill our tanks with gas.
This is Tokyo BM
Where are you calling this?
Hong Kong or Saigon or somewhere.
She's smart
You falling love?
It seems she is not yours
What the hell is that girl?
Are you into her?
I go crazy if I don't talk about something.
I like to talk a lot
We all get the short end of the stick once in a while.
So don't do bad things
what experience have you had?
It's none of your business
I'm on the brink of having my precious plane taken away from me.
I have a right to know who you are.
I see. So It's the one who revealed it.
Untie them,
They can't run and hide!
you don't want to die,right?
Don't do anything unnecessary.
Counterfeit money.
How could you tell?
Take the time to appreciate it.
This is kind of art
So you are an artist?
Yes,It's funny how some places charge more for this counterfeit money than the real thing.
That's ridiculous.
The small countries of Southeast Asia that are now struggling with uprisings
Wars aren't fought with guns and machine guns alone.
They use these counterfeit bills to tear apart the other country's economy.
These counterfeit bills cost more than the real thing.
I see.
The Japanese Army used to distribute them during the war.
That was called B-bill
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
As long as there's a war on, our business will thrive.
You are smart
Yes She is
Stop
Her father used to make copies with a sophisticated printing press.
He was hired by a special agency of a certain country during the Korean War to print a lot of counterfeit money for a lot of money.
The war was over, he never came home.
He knew their secret so he was killed
Use your brains while you're alive, man.
So you're a woman and you're waving a gun?
It's too good to be true.
Give me
I want women!
He did it again
Never mind
Watch out,Emi
I'm going to check the front.
Guns?
Don't worry.
There was a messenger pigeon up there.
messenger pidgeon?
Did you kill him?
You sure?
I don't wanna kill bird
But you like to kill people
Don't worry about the pigeons.
I don't think he works well
You are too sweet
Stop it
Stay strong. we are working
Work on your own
All is your fault
Stop here
Keep driving
There's a women
So what?
I don't want to miss it
We can't afford to do it
What's the hell?
Stop here
He's passed out.
We'll get him after
Wait
Are you alright?
You are member of site?
This is serious injure, what happened?
Who you are?
I flew in.
I heard about the site, called the police, and I was hooked.
But there's no house around here
Bad guys are trying to break into the site. They're trying to steal your plane.
Is the pilot man okay?
He'll be in danger
They're all armed with handguns, so you'd better stay away from them.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
The dry ice is melting a lot
I was going to go to SITE because I heard they have air conditioning.
Stop it
You tricked me
I'm just kidding, sorry
You shouldn't do anything you're not used to doing.
I'll shoot you
There is a safety device.
This is how you shoot when you hit a person
Stay away!
Help me
It's hot.
What are they doing out there?
Hi Sasorijima site, this is Kagoshima Agent
Reporting on a regular basis.
What should we do?
Where you going?
This is Reporting on a regular basis.
Flip the switch.
If you don't report it, it'll look suspicious.
This is Sasorijima site, Reporting on a regular basis please
Northeast wind 30 knots
atmospheric pressure 1600 millibars
temperature 34
Kumamoto cloud cover
We're getting ready
1122 millibars
Just reporting please
We were doing a typhoon observation.
We are not supposed to contact them unless they ask for a weather report.
Amami Oshima will be prioritized first.
Nothing to worry about.
It's Squall.
It's heavy
I worry about Runway
You need my help?
I have a good idea
They worry about runway
And pigeon.
He will go up to feed him
You know what?
There's one woman
That woman will definitely be on watch.
You divert her attention
Or I'll do that
Don't run away
What are you talking about?
I was surprised last year when there was a typhoon.
Wind speeds of 60 meters per hour.
we were blown away by the wind
You could fly to the sky
No more boats, no more rice.
We had to go to the Cape in the storm to buy food.
I'd end up licking dried bonito flakes and drinking the water.
I was like a cat
I see.
Is this what you guys do for a living?
You're bored out of your mind.
It's what keeps us pilots flying.
You have no idea how much we appreciate it.
I feel sorry for you.
Not seeing a woman for a year or two.
Just like you.
You're not into me
I'm sorry but...
You love pidgeon more?
Bad news.
This runway won't jump up if it gets any wetter.
Right?
i go to feed the pigeons
I'm not letting you out.
Hold on
I'm gonna go check on the run-up to the airfield.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take a record.
Hey
You?
I'm going to bathroom
Don't move or I'll shoot you
You
You lied to me about being alone.
I knew
You knew?
I heard you on the radio.
Then why you came?
I was wondering about the vaccine
vaccine ?
Paralysis has struck again?
I heard this place has air conditioning.
So you've prepared yourself.
I don't care what happens to me, please protect the vaccine.
Stay strong
You were trapped
One of your guys is out cold out there.
Who?
Tell me
A big guy.
His head was bleeding.
he was alone?
Yes
How about the car?
I have no idea
Damn it
I’ll go check
no need for that
If there's something wrong, they'll call us with the hand pottery.
They were just arguing
How about Daimon?
We don't need him anymore
I see
What the hell is that?
I hope you didn't put anything suspicious in there.
It's dry ice.
It's got live vaccine in it.
Touch it and you'll get scalded.
Childhood paralysis.
I see, anyway come with me
You'll be over
You tripped me
You're just realizing that now?
I won't forgive you
Just bring it on
Come on!
did the volcano erupt?
That was a gasoline explosion.
what the hell do they do?
This is Sasorijima Island site
Criminals have infiltrated and paralyzed the functionality of the site.
Please help us
This is Sasorijima Island site
What the hell?
Can you handle them by yourself?
I'll take care of it.
Why don't you take her with you?
Perhaps he's injured.
so we should take her
Come !
She's tried
Don't pretend you are good
She decides if she goes or not.
But you're still human.
Yes I am
Tell me
I'd go
you have to protect her with your life
It's none of my business
I need rescue
This is Sasorijima Island site
Criminals have infiltrated and paralyzed the functionality of the site.
I need rescue
This is Sasorijima Island site
I'm informing you
Criminals have infiltrated and paralyzed the functionality of the site.
The longer you wait, the more likely it is that this radio will be used to call the plane.
And your plan's not gonna work.
I don't think that radio will work
Criminals have infiltrated and paralyzed the functionality of the site.
I need rescue
It's boring to be alone?
I know what you're thinking right now.
Let you guess.
You're gonna find an opening and you're gonna take me out
No
I'm thinking about the goldfish.
Even though he's grown up, it's hot and he's about to die
Forget about me
It's easy to shoot you guys
We're bare-knuckled.
We won't die
You're the best.
I'm not supposed to say anything if I'm not good enough.
So I pay attention on you
You got a nice body.
You like it?
I may have seduced you
because you were always with that ugly man
I was just kidding
you are a coward
I'm asking about the scar on your neck.
it is his medal
it is his medal?
Stop saying it
When He had just become a pilot..
He was flying a plane to Shikoku with a load of passengers.
He crash-landed at sea in bad weather.
He ejected the passengers.
But he got a lot of scars for it.
You are brave
His mother told me to stay out of the dangerous business when she saw the scars.
He thought so for a while, too.
But then he changed his mind.
He saved the lives of three passengers.
A pilot with a pretty body is not a real pilot.
A scar is the medal of honor of Pilot Rock.
I've tried to value human life ever since.
That's why I'm a coward.
It's easy enough not to beat the shit out of one of you.
But try losing one of these lives.
You're young and you're a hard worker
That's why I don't know how you feel.
When your father died, why didn't you want to take over the fine business of copying on a printing press?
Why did you print counterfeit money?
When people are in pain, they can either be trained or they can be crushed.
Why were you crushed?
are you going to preach to me even though it's hot
I wonder if the air conditioning is on.
Air conditioning is for machines.
It's over 35 degrees in the human quarters.
This is no place for ladies.
We're always in our underwear.
Even when it wasn't hot, I wanted to strip naked.
i won't forgive you
I know you are a coward
Give it a shot
It's hot and this may have broken
Don't look down on me
I become stronger because the scars increase
Be careful
This is kyowa ship
Relief communication intercepted.
My goldfish died.
he  went down easy.
You're no better than the goldfish.
Maybe it's you who's the goldfish.
What are you going to do?
I'll bury the goldfish in the soil
it's my responsibility to do it
I'm not letting you out of here.
What should I do then?
Flush it down the toilet.
You are so mean
There's a PISTOL in the first aid kit.
Turn off the lights when you get a chance.
Phone call
You know right?
Hello? Hello?
This is Sasorijima Island site
Did a fishing boat intercept the rescue transmission?
It is something wrong
No communication is sent from here
Don't move
Don't move or kill them
Intercepted a rescue message in the Southern Sea.
Please check the status
I was surprised when she got a pistol
Where's the Pistol?
I threw that thing away.
Don't tell a lie
How about Mikami?
He was burned by a gasoline blowout.
How about Yoshimoto?
I can't find him.
No wonder he's dead, that young man.
All you had to do was pick her up.
But she's fuckable
Say it again.
I'll beat you
It's none of your business
you can't get any woman
This is no time to be fighting amongst yourselves.
It's time to get mad.
No matter how much you squirm, you'll never get gasoline or a pilot.
You said the more wounds I take, the stronger I get.
I think a scratch like that would be enough to fly a plane.
my shoulder hurts because of you
What's more important, your shoulder or your heart?
I see, But what about gasoline?
I thought you said it would last all the way to Okinawa.
I'll take care of the rest.
we will endure a little
What about the vaccine?
I need to get it to them.
I'm sorry, but we are  not going to Amami.
You'll just give up.
You people don't have a soul.
Right now in Amami, little kids and their mothers are waiting like crazy for this vaccine.
Every minute or second we delay, the more children will get sick.
You are crippled too, aren't you?
I think you know how children feel
do you know why i have bad leg?
Caused by infantile paralysis
that was very painful
Why did you do this ?
When I was a kid, they didn't have vaccines.
What does that matter?
I just want the world to know how I was painfil
If you use that vaccine, the children will get well soon.
That could be fine
you are heart numb
It could be
but who made me that?
These are rich people living in the lap of luxury.
who are humming and driving and bouncing off the muddy water
i want to make them sick
you're crazy since you were born
It could be
Hello,Poilot
I'm looking for a marine near the 101st.
It seems to have been contacted
A rescue plane is heading here.
What should you do?
I am searching for SOS at sea
please let me know if you have any information
The rescue message is a false alarm
Are you sure?
Please check it
I'm sure The rescue message is a false alarm
I get it
Please ask why it is false
all is well on our side
can you hear me, pilot
Landing is invalid due to runway problems
I will contact you soon, so please wait there for a while.
We have to go now
We are going
How many people?
4 people include you
4?
I can't
You sure?
With that gasoline, we're gonna have to make it to Okinawa. Two at the most.
If you lie to me, I'll kill you.
I ain't lying.
I don't want to crash in the ocean either.
Me and one other one will have to draw lots.
What should we do?
You tricked me
I'll take the money and Yumi
You can't betray your own people and expect to be saved.
Shut up
Me and he can do anything
He was a fool who believed a lie.
What do you mean?
Well, one less person, anyway.
I'm gonna check the plane.
I don't know what he's doing.
Let's go anyway.
Just deliver this.
What's wrong?
Strange, we won't go to Amami
What's this?
You lied.
Get away
I'll shoot you
Shoot me
If I die, you'll never get off this island.
Gasolin is fine
Come here
Is this OK?
What about vaccines?
You're so desperate to be dead to vaccines, aren't you?
Azuma
She broke the radar.
Are you alright?
Where's him?
I killed him
Give me the postol
Let me handle this
Are you ok?
That's a blind spot. You can't hit it.
You're the only one left.
I don't want to kill her.
Put your pistol down
I'll kill all
Stop it
I won't
I'll kill all of you
Stop shooting
I can keep shooting
I can kill you and the nurse
Don't kill me
My bad
I can't seduce you anymore.
No worry. You won't die
Take care f this
Electeic is off
You guys go to hell
Asaka
Yoshimoto
I'm glad you are alive
How's him
He's alright
Hold on
Are you altight?
This is Kagoshima police.
A rescue team including two doctors will arrive in 20 minutes.
Please let us know the extent of the damage there.
It's 3:30 , Let's go now
There's still time to deliver the vaccine.
But
The doctor will be here soon.
Don't worry about us. Just get the vaccine to them.
See you
Take care
See you again
Let's go
Have a safe trip
If you feel sick, just use this.
It's okay.
I'm kind of starting to like flying.
THE END