Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Omiya and I again risked our lives to escape from the army.
New soldier gangster
Hoodlum Soldiers Return (#3)
Hoodlum Soldier Deserts Again
They are!
What happened?
Gasoline is gone
Let's go
To where?
Let's go as far as we can go
We are walking the same route all the time
Don't worry.
China is so wide
Hey , they are No 8 army
Damn it
That's not a statue
Strange
Japan army?
It will be difficult if you are caught by the Japanese army. Let's run away
Who are you?
Are you soldiers?
We are Arita top soldier and another
We went to lookout but got out of the army on the way
Which team?
4242 team
What?
They moved to the front this morning
Oh right
What did you say?
You guys went in the opposite direction
Why you dress like that?
China no 8 team attacked us on the way
Were you caught by them?
Yes
Stupid?
Are you really Japan army?
Ah
Who you are?
I'm Omiya first grade solider
You look like a rock
It's innate.
You guys are like garbage but we take care of you
Join our team
Reply!
Thank you very much
Chief
We have a connection with the army
One way to escape the Kenpeitai is to join the army.
Can't see the forest for the trees
We have been sneaking into the army for a while
This team was a very tough team called Hayabusa
We trained hard every day
Leaders trained their troops hard every day
Put your head down!
Do you get it?
I"m talking to you
What the hell?
Wake up!
Wake up, Omiya
I know
That's ridiculous.
I'm sleeping
I don't want to train
I will be Renpeikyu 9 for a while
Renpeikyu?
That's good idea
Hey guys!
Wake up!
What the hell you are?
We're sick
What?
I have a stomachache
I may be the cecum
cecum?
How about you?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with him?
He got mental illness
He's been crazy since last night
Ok.
Take a rest
Good job
Good acting
I miss women and drinking
Here's so bad
Usually we can drink alcohol or stay overnight after training
It ’s good to watch the training while sleeping.
Hot!
Hey guys.
Sit on your knees.
Right now!
You got sick because you didn't train
I'll treat you now
It's hard but good effect
Line up!
Hit them one by one
I'll show you first
You are the first
Are you ready?
You're cheeky
Fuck you!
You bastard!
Beat him!
Yes!
Next
Get out!
Fuck you!
Damn it
Omiya!
You bastard!
Fuck you!
What's wrong with team 3?
All team 3 units are normal
Stupid! Why normal?
It's the first time that the entire army has become sick
Everyone except me and Omiya can't move
I feel boring
Don't be extravagant.
I'll take a bath
We're sick.
Don't get too carried away.
You are the cecum, but I'm just crazy
Right?
I'll take a bath
Omiya
This team?
Yes they are
They all attacked the psychotic soldier.
Where is the psychotic soldier now?
He's taking a bath now
He's taking a bath now?
His name?
He's Omiya first grade solider
He is Kisaburo Omiya?
Yes he is
I have a stomachache so I'm going to the bathroom
OK
He has a mate called Arita
He's gone to bathroom now
What?
Omiya.
There's a problem
What's wrong?
Kenpei has come
Oh my god
Don't go back
Why?
Hurry up,Omiya
He left this
This is his underwear
Is he naked?
Where has they gone to?
Don't catch a cold!
Omiya and I took a train to Tianjin
Don't touch!
I'm starving
Chief
Don't call me chief
How can I call you?
Well..call me Arita-san
Arita-san?
It seems you are different person
How about Big boss?
Big boss?
It seems I got promotion
That's fine
What?
We need to earn money
I was thinking about it
But
Do you want to thief?
How?
From there?
Thief from the army
The army has a lot of supplies
Lots of stuff to steal.
But how can we steel?
Anyway we should go inside
There are guards there
Big boss
Chief
Let's ask that guard
that guard?
The guards here are nothing but rogues.
You're right
He has no motivation to work
Leave it to me
Go away
Thank you for your work
Are you Japanese?
We're walking around
Whereabouts Japanese are you from?
I'm from Osaka
Oh you're from Kansai
I'm Omiya.
He's Arita
I see
I'm Bungo
Bungo?
That's funny name
It can't be helped
Could you give me a cigarette?
OK
Here
Thank you
Do you have a light?
You demand too much
Do you have any interesting stories?
How long do you work ?
I have been working for about 4 years and half.
I'm only thinking about women right now
Are you still in the first grade after working in the army for four and a half years?
I was about to promote
You were hated by the boss
It's none of your business
I want to ask you a favor
Ask me
The chief officer has come
There's no problem
Who are they?
We are performers
performers?
I wanted to show the soldiers our performance
You too?
He plays the shamisen.
But He sold it
He can't do anything
Show me
I will
Ready
Good performance
Ok I'll ask our boss
Follow me
Line up
Hide your pistol
I like the song
Ok.Do their physical examination for the time being
Yes
OK
What's this?
You have a big cock
There's no problem
OK.
Call solders
Let's listen to their song
It tastes good
Big boss.
We broke through the first barrier
Art will help you
Thanks to you
But from now is the problem
No worries.
Leave it to me
Let's go
Hey
Thanks for your work
Your performance was very good
Thank you
The leader loved his song
These are the reward
This is good sake
There is a lot of sake, rice and sugar here
This is a treasure trove
So I volunteered to come here.
This is better than being in a unit
Which unit?
64 unit
I don't have to go to war if I'm here
It ’s very difficult to be in the unit, is n’t it?
But there are a lot of things that go over my head here.
For what?
Boss only think about themselves
He wears a high-class cloak even in the summer
He hides supplies under the cloak
He hides supplies and takes them out
Line up!
Some people load them on trucks and carry out supplies.
The bosses make money by selling it to the townspeople
Our bosses are so bad that I hate to obey their orders
You think so?
You're right
In other words, you don't know if you take out supplies from here.
Yeah, no one know
I say you are not performers
You're solders
I know everything
I know the soldiers right away
Did you escape from Army?
Kind of
What the hell you are doing?
Can I ask you a favor?
For what?
I also want to make money
We can share the profit
I thought I could work with you when you first came
Leave it to me
Who's there!
Oh you.
What's this?
You bastard
What!
You want to go to die?
Or let us go?
If so, I'll give you some profit
Shall we kill him first?
Do you want some profits?
Or you want us to kill you?
Tell me!
Ok I get it.
I'll let you go
You sure?
Yes
Profits
What?
Come get it tomorrow afternoon
You are like a thief
Big boss.
Is he OK?
I know he wants profits
He's so cheeky
Let's make this the last time we steal.
We can try more
That's so risky
Don't get carried away
I'll give him this much
That's too much
It's better to give some more
OK?
Not only sugar but Let's steel some tobacco
I'm here to get the share
Good. so now we are same criminal
Only this?
You're not satisfied?
I want 10 times more
You are greedy for money.
If they find this, I could be court-martialed.
So I want more
I can't give you anymore
OK
I'll show you what will happen if you don't give me more
OK show me
I've asked my subordinate to come here
I'll arrest you if you obey me
Choose you give me more or you are arrested
What the hell?
You can do whatever you want
What did you do?
They are
You have stolen valuable military supplies.
I hand you over to the kenpeitai
kenpeitai?
That's ok
What?
I have a lot to talk to them
We are not the only ones to divert valuable military supplies
All the people here are habitual offenders.
Shut up!
I have the proof
I think you should look into this team
You are bastard!
Fuck you!
Stop it,Omiya!
Stop it
I'll beat you if you hand me over
Why?
Kenpeitai is not here.
They are too far
I'll forget this.
soldiers keep their word.
Instead of it,get out from here now
Damn it
Show them how strong the military is.
Get up!
Damn it
I know what's going on
What?
You say soldiers keep their word.
Wait!
I'll make your mouth close
See you
What's wrong with your pistol?
I have it
Don't worry
Let's go for play for the first time in long time
I have money
Let's go
Omiya!
Stop it!
What's wrong?
I want to cry
You can cry
Don't you feel sad?
I feel fun
I like to cry
None of the people here came to mainland China of their own volition.
We can't go back to Japan
I feel like crying to listen to the Japanese song
Big boss,
You think too much
Let;s make it over
Give me Sake
Wait
You shouldn't drink too much
Lunch is always full.
It's good you earn so much
Thanks
Leader is busy today.
Call women right now
Sure
You shouldn't drink.
Let's choose our woman
Do whatever you want
Ok I do
Choose me
Ok I'll choose you
I've changed my mind
Excuse me
Come with me
Where are you going to?
I'm sorry.
Please lend her
The leader of Kenpeitai has come
Kenpei?
I can't go against them
They are same guest like me
We're very sorry
Only for a short time
Instead, invite you to an interesting place
Do you like this?
Can you do this?
I'm good at gambling
I won!
I bet
Damn it
Omiya
What are you going to do?
Shall we help you?
Thanks
I'll put this on.
Play it
You guys spent last night drinking, a woman and my money
But we have no money now
Are you guys not going to pay?
I don't mean that
We'll work and pay you back
What work?
We'll do anything
I get it.
The daily allowance is very low
You mean?
1 day 0.3 yuan with 3 meals
That's ok
How about you?
We have no choice
It's better to be in army
What's wrong with you?
After you left and I came to gamble
Then I lost
You are miserable
Have you been working here for a long time?
I have been working here for 4 years
I went to Shanghai first then Beijing and Tenjin
But I have been working here longest
I thought I would go back to Japan when I first saved money
I have increased my debt and gave up on returning to Japan
So I decided to forget about it
Yummy
How much do you work for?
1 day 0.3 yen
You're stupid.
You were deceived by him too
He takes people with money to the gambling hall and cheats them.
Is it cheating?
It's kind of
Is that true?
Well
What're you doing?
Customers has come
See you
Wash more thoroughly.
Still has some stains.
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Does it taste bad?
I didn't expect to eat here
If you are fooled by him, everyone will be like this
Remi
OK
Thanks
I'll give you mine too
I'll give you half
What's wrong?
We skip meals if there are no more than 10 customers a day
He's so greedy for money
You are better than us.
You'll have all meals
I can't accept
I feel like being crazy
I want to revenge to him
Be careful
They have something to do with Kenpeitai
All the money taken from you go to the Kenpeitai.
Let's do something
I'm so upset
You are very patient
We don’t have pistol now
Please forgive me
I have an idea.
Would you like to run away together?
Run away?
Everyone escapes from here
That's interesting.
What do you think?
I can't walk anymore.
Let's take a rest
I am walking all night
You have no guts
I have never walked like this
Ok let's take a rest
Don't look
We dissolve here
We dissolve here?
It's enough to get here.
You're free now
We have come to rely on you.
What should we do from now on?
You are responsible
I can't take responsibility for you
What should we do from now on?
I told you you are free
You are responsible
We can't do anything if we break up in this field
That's true
I'll get back
Wait.
To where?
I have no choice but back there
You can't
How can I live?
We can't live without prostitution
We can only do that
That's right.
Omiya.
What should we do?
Would you like to run a comfort station with them?
comfort station?
For government
is that good?
If you run, we will do our best to work
I can't!
Why?
I don't want to be the manege
What are you talking about?
Don't pretend you are great
You can only do if you want.
Why?
I take another action
Just you can help us.
you can help us.
Why you don't want?
I hate it
That's good business
Have you ever done that?
I have never done it.
But Working with women seems to be fun
We work hard so don't worry about money
You are good for managers because you are kind to women
Big boss
Omiya.
Just you do
I'll leave
It can't be helped
We can't
Everyone go back
You said you'll start the business
That's right
Big boss can't do so I can't do
You're so selfish
I know you want to do
Big boss can't do so I can't do
Everyone go back
I can't
Omiya
I lost.
Let's do!
What should I do with this?
Is  this OK?
Good
I think around here
Here!
Wait!
Please pay the money first
I didn't know there was a comfort station here
Oh you!
Long time no see
How did you know here?
I happened to hear about you.
Here is so good
We've build with the money
Please come sometime
Let's go
Hanako
Thanks for your work
Yoshiko
Yes
Thanks for your work
Boss
Leader!
You've opened comfort station here
You're thief
Return the stolen item
I was waiting for you
You manage these women in debt
Now they are making a lot of money
It's none of your business
You bastard!
Stop it
Break here!
Big boss
What's wrong?
Ryugu attacked here?
That dude
Wait
He says he wants to fight one-on-one with you
They are waiting in the warehouse at 8 o'clock tomorrow morning
I accept it
I'll beat them
I'm ready for it
But they have a pistol
I don't care
Stop it
I can't forgive them
This is my order
But omiya wore a new kimono the next day and went to the promised place
I was worried and followed him
That's not what you promised.
I thought you were alone
Quarrel always changes
Who's this guy?
I can't tell
Big boss
You are two too
It has been changed
Ok Let's fight!
I won't die if shot
You bastard
Are you a soldier?
you are a soldier
What are you guys doing?
We do nothing
I heard the shot
I just tried it
You sure?
Trust me
Yes
Don't fire your pistol for nothing.
That's strange
I wonder if it was such a play
But then they didn't get revenge
Women also worked hard and peaceful days continued
How about this
All the customers who come here can aim for Momoko
I know she's nice
She's not only beautiful but also plays nice
You guys found a good woman
Momoko is one in 10,000 women
She's nice so much?
I have a lot of experience with women
It's the first time I've met such a beautiful woman
How good is she?
You will never be able to forget her.
I won
Your turn
Momoko is one in 10,000 women
Omiya
Eh?
Do you love momoko?
Is it bad?
It's bad
Why?
Because other women are jealous.
We will be unable to manage them
If you like women, go to another comfort station
If you want to marry her, fine.
marry her?
No way
Then forget about her
You are sometime like school teacher
Omiya
All the girls look cute when we live together
We are like family
It saddens me to think of their fate.
Soldiers are enshrined at Yasukuni Shrine if they die
They don't get a grave built for them when they die.
They are used until their bodies become puffy
I feel sorry for them
He's easy to get sleep
What?
What's wrong?
Oh why I'm here?
Don't pretend you don't know
You entered from there
I knew you'd come
I like you
What?
Advance payment
It does not need
This is rule
I loved you from the beginning
I know, but give me money
You're mean
I don't feel good without money
Go to take the money
You're stupid
I like you too
Great
Oh my god
I'm falling in love
Good night,Momoko
Good night
Omiya
As big boss says, you should marry
But I can't marry
you should marry.
I'm jealous of you but it can't be helped
If you don't get married, we won't have control here.
What do you think,Momoko
I'm a woman, I can marry him.
We don't have to be a couple
If you don't get married I won't see you anymore
You're mean
Omiya
You should
How do we get married?
How?
Call the pastors and priest and swear to get married in front of them
How should I say?
Say Treat her as a wife forever
forever?
It's okay for a month or a year for me
There is no such wedding
I have no relationship with pastors or priests
I know a ex Buddhist monk.
Ex Buddhist monk?
Shall I bring him in?
That's good
No way
Wedding is not for money
So
Anything is fine, so prepare appropriately
I still think you should prepare something proper.
You are an annoying person.
Just marry him in a good mood.
I have never prepared a wedding
What kind of sutra should I read?
I have no idea.
Anything is fine
Let's go
But Bun-san
Bun-san?
Mr.Bungo,
I have only read funeral sutras.
They never know what you read
that's bad for them.
Wait
So let's get started
OK
Then we will start the wedding now
The groom should hold the bride's hand
You make her a wife
Do you swear to love her forever?
I'll do my best
From now on I will read the sutra
In the meantime, have a drink.
It was a very strange wedding
It was a wedding that mixed Buddhism, Shintoism, and Christianity.
After they left, Bungo and Big Boss returned to the room with a woman.
I suddenly felt lonely for some reason
What's wrong?
The wedding is over
Let's drink
Where's your wife?
She's there
Did you have quarrel?
No
I don't want you to be alone
So I didn't want to get married
I will always be with you
Is that OK?
Omiya
You and I are totally different
Sometimes I have the same idea with you
But mostly you and I think differently.
I feel sometime it's better to separate with you
But you already know my mind.
I don't know the detail but I really know how you feel
So you know?
Arita leader
I'll support you forever
Don't pretend you are great
I'm sorry
Let's drink together
You should get wife too
No way.
I feel annoy
You asked me to get marry
Don't complain.
Kenpei has come
Kenpei ?
What Can I do for you?
You are Arita leader and Omiya first grade
Are you going to arrest us?
I won't.
I can arrest you anytime
So Why you are here?
I will look into you guys.
I know you are runaway soldiers
You'll look into for nothing
I can arrest you anytime
Are you threatening us?
You are making good profits
Let me see inside
I hate him
He's here for something
He'll deal with us
We can beat him
He's active kenpei
Was there party?
He got marry
Married?
That's good to hear
Who's his wife
Momoko
Momoko? the woman was in Ryugu?
Do you know her?
I don't like you
Don't hide your pistol
I know what's on your mind
I don't plan to fight with you
Let's have a drink together
Omiya! your wife is waiting
You should go home
Oh Aoyagi
Long time no see
Are you Kenpei support leader now?
Yes
You?
I'm still first grade
Why you have come here?
It's none of your business
Being Kenpei is easy,right?
I can resign Kenpei anytime.
It's like homeless
There are no good people in KENPEI.
I'll go home
Why?
I'm upset
Hey Aoyagi,
I know your secret
Secret?
He killed a woman and a soldier
See you again
Get home safe
You too!
What's wrong?
Let's pee
I won't
Ok let's go home
Hey
I want to drink more.
Buy some sake
Let's go home
Where are you going?
I'll buy some
Do you have money?
Take care
leave it to me
Gunshots!
Bungo was shot!!!
He was buried as a war dead man.
We had our own funeral separately.
At that day Aoyagi came here for some reason
Hey, too long
Ok, I'll stop
Please burn incense in order.
You know that?
He was saying like that..but he was died
I need to talk with you
What?
I looked in you
I need to talk with you about it.
Let's change place
Come to backyard later
I'll wait there
Big boss
What did he say?
He's left
He's left?
I know he shot Bungo
Did you see his attitude?
He came to the funeral.
We were fooled by him
Bungo might be upset
Don't be upset
I have no choice but angry
You're a coward.
I'll talk to him
Wait
Listen, We have no evidence that he killed Bungo
And he knew we are run away solider
So I need to talk with him
It's not good
Actually I have promised to talk with him
He plan to deal something as I thought
He might kill you
If you come, It might be happen
Big boss, Here is not Japan
Killing people is easy.
He has a pistol
He killed Bungo in the mid night
Leave it to me
I have my own way
I need to support you
You!
You can't trust me?
You stay here.
This is my order
You have your wife
You should think of her
I'm glad you stay here
But I know you'll go
Don't worry about me
Please go
What do you want to talk to me?
I looked in you
You run away 3 times, and stole supplies
Besides that, there were some
Why you don't arrest me?
You want to be arrested?
I don't think so
Being comfort women station manager is much fun
I also feel fun.
I won't get promotion even if I arrest you
No one know about you so far
I'm the only person who know it
If you want to buy this information, I can sell
But it costs a lot. Because For your life.
How much?
5000yen per person, with Omiya, it becomes 100000yen
I don't have such a money
Make it if you don't have
I will arrest you if you can't
That dude
I'll kill you
Bullshit!
I fire a pistol better than you
Line up!
Damn it!
You!
I'll train you!
We're very tough
Remember it!
This is for nothing!
Say the truth
You bastard!
KENPEITAI's torture was intense.
Every day this torture would kill us both.
Wait
You give up?
I want to talk with your boss
What?
Can you untie us?
I can't
Say it
You've had your fill of torture, haven't you?
Can you release me?
What?
We did nothing but run away
Two run away solders have nothing to do with your promotion.
It's safer for you to release us now
Shut your mouth!
Listen
If you court-martial us, I will expose you for opening a gambling house near the Ryuguu comfort station.
You'll be over if we expose it
Shut your mouth!
I won't afraid of it
I'll also talk about your subordinate Aoyagi
He killed Bungo first grade solider.
He used to kill a woman and a solider
And you will be held accountable for it.
Would you still court-martial us?
Tell me
Is that all you want to say?
I'll teach you how Kenpei is strong
Aoyagi
Yes
We will not court martial them.
Release them tonight
Yes
You're so stupid
You should have dealed with me.
You will be killed
Are you killing us?
You'll be released
as dead body
You...
Are you human being?
A court-martial will condemn you all to death.
We'll cut the process
Give me your hands.
I'll unlock you
You bustard
Omiya
Line up!
Put your pistols out
You bustard
You said You 'll teach you how Kenpei is strong
I 'll teach you how Kisaburo Omiya is strong
Get out in front
Yes
Stand up
Are you Senior soldier?
Bring it on
What the hell
Next
Who's next
You
I want to talk to you
want to talk?
Yes
Next
Omiya!
Is it a grenade?
I'll beat you
You bustard
Come on
I will beat you!
Catch them!
Omiya!
We did it
Omiya,You are so...
You want to say I'm so stupid
Well, where shall we go from now on?
THE END