Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
You will kill me?
You can't kill me.
You are my mistress.
Ma'am.
Good evening.
It's awfully cold.
Hamano?
Your wife in in trouble.
Please come quickly.
Come quickly!
Where's he now?
He's on business trip to Kyushu.
Did you tell him?
I telegramed.
Mr. Munekata, president of the Jonan Bar Association.
Right?
Where were you?
I was at cooking school at 8:30.
Cooking school.
I saw her dead body when I backed.
What time was it?
Just before 10pm.
You were out 8:30-10:00.
Before you left, did you notice anything unusual?
For example, a stranger visited her.
Or someone wandering around?
I just saw Hamano before I left.
Hamano?
Hey.
Mr.Munekata took care of me.
I'm Lawyer Hamano who was working with him.
He's Munekata's co-worker.
Ok come in.
So you lived with them for about three years before you left the office.
Then you know a lot about the family situation, etc.
Did your wife have any enemies?
As far as I know..
I understand you arrived here at about 8:20 this evening.
Yes.
What did she sound like then?
I heard she was absent because of a cold.
So I went to visit her.
What time did you get home?
8...
I'd be very grateful if you could tell me the exact time.
I can't tell you every minute.
That's about right.
Manager!
We arrested!
What?
We arrested the criminal!
Shiro to Kuro / Pressure of Guilt (1963)
Oh Munekata's wife was killed..
Come on,Dad.
Can't you get up 10 or 20 minutes earlier?
Can't you at least read the paper?
Here's your meal.
The wife I know was murdered.
Who?
MUNEKATA, abolitionist of the death penalty
He's the president of the Jonan Bar Association.
I saw the news on TV.
When are you going to have your surgery?
Hemorrhoid surgery.
I'm too busy.
That's what you're afraid of.
You are big guy but You are coward.
I'm going.
Watch out the traffic.
Are you going to the office?
Good morning.
Mr. Terauchi from MITI called me last night.
You decided?
March 3rd, 6:00 p.m. at the Hotel Tokyo.
Fee is 1000yen.
You are stingy.
We can go to Atami and Hakone for our Alumni Association.
Atami and Hakone are boring.
It's Saturday, and I'm going out with the director.
What's the hell about the director.
You'll just have a business meeting.
Well, he's the Construction Chief.
That's good.
Stay inside.
Move inside.
I'm getting off next.
Next stop,Kasumigaseki.
Good morning.
This is beautiful like you.
Thank you very much.
Let's go to a movie together sometime.
Movie?
Skating is cool these days.
I can't do skating.
Well..
The witnesses are Yoshida and Kubota.
Shall we invite them?
Room 313.
He's here.
Managing director is calling you.
How's it going? Have you made up your mind?
What?
Hemorrhoid surgery.
I drink too much.
Don't worry too much about your wife.
I'm a matchmaker myself, so I have a bit of responsibility.
By the way, I have something for you.
I heard that Munakata-san's wife was young and beautiful.
That's what the papers said.
It's a very flashy case.
But the Metropolitan Police Department did a good job with the speedy arrest.
Is HIRAO in charge of group 6?
Oh you know him.
We are old friends.
He's a little stubborn and hard-headed.
But he's a hard worker.
The incident occurred at approximately 9:40 p.m. on January 17, 1963
Mrs. YASUE, 37 years old, was strangled to death and robbed of money and goods at the residence of Harumasa MUNAKATA,
a lawyer at 2-13, Government 2-chome, Nakameguro, Meguro-ku, Tokyo.
You had no idea how much cash she had?
She always carries a handbag...
And the necklace, was it pearl?
Yes.
You remember the color and shape" of the ring and watch, don't you?
Numerous fingerprints were collected from the jewelry box and other items.
However, no fingerprints were found on the red waistband used in the murder.
The murderer's route of entry and escape was through the front door of the house, which was left unlocked.
The situation at the time of the arrest of the murderer, Detective 43 found a man who was acting suspiciously.
Don't move.
Earrings and Rings
Ring.
Necklaces
That's a fancy case.
It's rather easy to deduce.
Okay.
Okay. Let's do it.
Bring Wakita.
You must be Shokichi Wakita.
What's your date of birth?
November 22nd, 1931.
Where is your legal domicile?
Azatomitsu, Koko no Mura, Shimohira-gun, Iwate Prefecture, Japan
Address?
No fixed address.
You have a criminal record.
Six years and nine months in prison, along with one count of theft and robbery.
I guess you could say I've been living in prison since I was 20.
By the way.
Mr. Prosecutor.
I've told the police everything I know.
I may have robbed, but I didn't kill her.
That ain't what I did.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
When did you come from Kyushu?
First JAL flight this morning.
I never thought I'd leave my wife's funeral twice in my life.
There's a lawlessness in this world.
I'd kill him if I saw him in front of me.
Then it was 8:30 when you left Asahimachi Daikokuya House, right?
I don't have a watch, but that's about right.
How much money did you have then?
About 200 yen.
You took the Yamanote line from the south exit and arrived at Meguro station around 9:00, right?
That's about right.
I walked around for about half an hour.
Apparently, there was something oddly unpopular about the place.
The door was not locked?
She was dead?
Yeah, with a red waistband around her neck.
That's a bit of a surprise.
But I couldn't call 110, so...
So I got to work.
She was already dead when you walked in, right?
Oh, yeah.
Bullshit.
A little too childish for the work of a four-time felon, don't you think?
That might work in the real world, but it won't work here.
Mr. Hamano.
So the woman was dead.
With a red waistband around her neck.
She was alive.
She was alive?
The woman was sleeping soundly on bed.
Yesterday and the day before, she was dead.
You told me She was alive today.
The D.A. won't believe me if she's dead.
I don't blame him.
What do you want?
I wanna know what you did.
I told you that.
Well, if it's exactly what you did, you're a little naive, aren't you?
Why?
How many days has it been since you sat in that chair?
Five days.
You told me The first day and the next, the woman was dead.
But since yesterday, she's been lying alive on the bed.
Who can trust you?
Wakita..if she was died..
Why did you steal there?
I told you she was alive.
Why she didn't wake up?
She was completely sleeping?
She was dead from the moment you walked in the room.
Or she was sleeping peacefully while you were working, either way, it doesn't make sense.
Then what the hell was going on with the woman when you walked in?
Wakita.
I heard you didn't sleep well.
The D.A. is going to be on me every single day.
By the way, you got a new defense attorney.
Court-appointed, right?
No.
He's the husband of the wife you killed.
He's a famous abolitionist lawyer in Japan.
There are some strange people in this world.
You arrived at Meguro station at about 9 PM?
You bought cigarettes from a tobacconist, walked out of the shopping district to a residential area.
You spent a half an hour going around the residential area looking for a place to break into.
You arrived at the Munekatas' house at about 9:30 or 9:40.
I'm gonna need you to be more specific from now on.
So the front door was unlocked?
Mr. D.A., how many times do you have to ask me the same thing?
Well, I guess that's as far as anyone's going to go with that.
I'm in bad mood today.
I got a letter from my mom in the country yesterday.
She wrote some strange things.
She said I should tell the truth and serve my sins gracefully.
She thought I killed her.
D.A.
I don't care if I get the death penalty for a robbery followed by a murder.
I'd be in prison for 10 years for robbery alone.
I'm not gonna do ten years in this body, or even five more in prison.
I was thinking about that when I got Mom's letter.
I couldn't sleep last night.
D.A.
I know you don't trust me.
I was born in the middle of nowhere.
There are only three houses among the mountains and fields
It's like a cattle pen, but it's all there.
Behind our house is a wood.
That's where my dead dad and brother are buried.
It's very quiet.
It's so peaceful.
Birds come here all the time.
I used to catch them with a net when I was a kid.
I can't wait to get in there and stretch my legs.
I don't like being in jail, but it's hard enough having the D.A. chastise me every day.
I don't know what else to do.
D.A.
I'm gonna tell you the truth right now.
I'm the one who killed your wife.
As I told you above... Masayoshi Wakita, 28, was questioned. He confessed this afternoon that he was responsible for the murder.
Next, at the JMA...
I'm so relieved.
Because I don't like the idea that we'll never figure out who did it.
Right?
What's wrong?
I know exactly how you feel.
She was like family to you... a little too young, a little too beautiful.
She was like a mother to you.
She was killed..
Cheer up.
And the culprit clearly confessed, so it's settled.
The case is now closed.
Thank you very much.
One more sake.
Long time no see.
I've been busy at work.
You are great.
Don't be bossy.
Hey, treat me nice.
You know?
Mr. Wakita.
The case was closed easily.
Not so easily.
Everything is dead.
That's what it feels like when a weight is lifted off my shoulders.
hey, what are you doing?
Long time no see.
Hi. Hi.
Hi, I'm sorry it took me so long to get here last night.
I'm sorry to ask so late at night.
Have a seat.
I heard Wakita confessed.
So you are here.
If that's the case, we'll We're formally charging him with robbery-homicide.
We'll have him formally charged with robbery-homicide in a couple of days.
Wakita's confession... is it credible?
credible?
This case will never move.
I'm the one who wants to know.
What kind of expert testimony and evidence will you use in your defense?
No matter what happens, he'll get the death penalty.
I'm Munakata, and I've been retained to represent you.
This is Hamano, who is helping me with your case.
I'm going to go ahead and decline, but I'm not aware that I've been asked to represent you yet.
I've been calling for the abolition of the death penalty for 40 years.
I have my reasons.
First, killing is unacceptable from a humanitarian point of view.
Second, trials are often wrong.
It's a human thing to do.
There are cases in which a wrong trial takes place, and it is only after the execution that we find out about it.
Therefore, the state sometimes commits murder by mistake.
I see.
You say you're willing to cleanly forgive me for killing your wife.
Isn't that what you're saying?
To be honest with you, I hate you.
I hate you.
But I need to be able to truly forgive you.
Because  if not, I've been lying to all kinds of people for 40 years.
I get it.
You want to work for yourself.
Ok go ahead.
As for the upcoming case, the fact that you got in one day of someone else's life and stole their stuff can't be moved.
They have all the physical evidence they need.
But for the murder, there's no physical evidence.
It's kind of circumstantial.
They have your own confession that you killed her.
We will do our very best to make your guilt as light as possible.
So don't hide anything from us, just be honest and tell us the truth.
Did you in fact kill someone?
Or did you confess to such a fact, but only under the guiding or intimidating interrogation of a police officer or prosecutor?
Or was there something else going on that you had to tell me?
There's nothing going on.
You killed her?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Cut it out.
You're just like the prosecutor.
He's like you killed!
When you're interrogated so persistently, even if I didn't do it.
I can't help it.
You know?
So.
The D.A..
I did it.
I told you.
It doesn't matter.
I did it.
I read it.
Thanks.
It's a lot easier for a trial prosecutor when the investigating prosecutor does all this.
In this case, the case itself is clear.
It's a skill to express it in the right sentences.
You messed up a lot at first.
It's better to get used to it than to learn it.
It's been 10 years since I work here.
Bonus please!
The 10-year player's?
The case of the defendant, Wakita, for robbery and murder is now before the court.
Defendant Wakita, please stand.
At approximately 9:30 or 9:40 p.m. on the same day, you broke into the Munekata residence at 1213, 2-chome, Nakameguro, Meguro-ku, Tokyo, with the intent to commit a burglary, and ransacked the house for money and entered Mrs. Munekata's bedroom.
When Mrs. Yasue 37 years old blamed you for the murder,you immediately had the urge to kill her.
You tied her up with a red waistband her found on the spot.
You killed by asphyxiation to death.
You stole the omega watch, market value 60,000 yen
Pearl necklace with sapphire ring with a market value of 150,000 yen
Pearl ring with diamonds, market value ¥20,000, earrings with diamonds, market value ¥70,000
and 48,000 yen in cash in a handbag.
Penalty: Article 240 of the Penal Code
First of all, this case is a kind of indiscriminate murder.
This is a senseless murder.
Killing a person simply because she was seen.
It is as easy to take a precious human life as if you were twisting it out of an insect.
And while committing the crime, the defendant shows no remorse.
I see.
Defendant Wakita has four prior convictions.
Prosecutors say that a person with a criminal record like this would commit a crime like this with impunity.
However, if the maximum sentence is imposed simply because a person has a criminal record,
there will remain a major humanitarian problem.
Even ex-convicts have human rights.
That's enough.
You're so horny.
You're out of your mind.
It's like you've changed.
Ever since that incident... and not just you.
Munakata-san is too.
Munakata-san is the worst.
He's defending a trial like that, and the people involved will always remember the bad things.
Unless there's another culprit.
No matter how much effort you and Munakata-san put in, Wakita won't be saved.
Or maybe you can help Wakita with your defense skills.
You have the confidence to lighten his sentence?
I don't need you telling me how to do my job.
It's time for you to get ready.
Are you going home?
One more bar!
Get out of my way!
Hamano.
Do You Know the Minister of Construction?
Let's go.
I'm off to home.
You are bad.
Welcome.
Please sit Minister of Construction.
What's the hell?
What do you drink?
Let's save money
Suntory Old.
And you?
Water with whiskey.
Brandy fro Miyamoto.
It's unusual you came here.
He's minister.
He's just constructor.
And you?
I won't tell about my job.
He's scary.
He would change his mind for money.
He's nasty.
Are you police or something?
No no.
Tokyo District Public Prosecutor's Office
I'm Miyamoto of the Miyamoto Gumi
President.
The world today is afraid of ordinary people.
Just the other day... you saw it in the newspaper, didn't you?
The murder of a beautiful lawyer's wife.
He worked on that case and put one of his own on death row.
What's wrong?
You work on that case with Mr. Munakata, don't you?
This is Hamano, the lawyer.
From the Jonan Bar Association.
I see.
So that case..
Excuse me, are you single, Mr. Hamano?
If so, you'd better watch out for this guy.
He's even playing matchmaker.
Hamano's our general counsel, and I invited him to a party today.
He is very supportive of our company.
I introduced him a woman.
First of all, congratulations.
No, no, unfortunately.
Just at the last minute, the other party suddenly starts acting strangely.
So he's still single.
Are you into him?
Really?
I heard this time the murderer didn't want to confess.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It could be.
The details of this case are clear.
The only question is whether or not he'll confess.
I guess that's the way it is.
Mr. Munakata and you are worse off this time.
It's hard to defend even in layman's terms.
No, no, not really.
Lawyers have ideas.
for example... If you can't move the crime, there's a lot you can do.
I see.
Do you have physical evidence that he killed his wife?
I was told the only question is whether he confessed or not.
Physical evidence is more important than confession, first and foremost.
Hamano.
As for Mr. Takahara and I,
we've done all the work we can do at the trial.
You know that?
You think so?
As an investigative prosecutor, you did all you could.
Stop talking it.
You've believed from the start that Wakita was the real culprit?
There's plenty of physical evidence against Wakita as a robber.
But there is no evidence as a murder.
You decided from the beginning that he was a murderer.
You forced him to confess.
Is that the attitude of a prosecutor in pursuit of the truth?
Do you think there's real murder?
You think you know that?
Stop talking it.
Let's have fun.
Bring alcohols.
Why don't you think about your body a little bit?
I don't care if it hurts or bleeds.
Who you were  with?
It's none of your business.
He's really cheeky.
What's wrong?
It's none of your business.
Water.
We don't see any questions, and of course we wouldn't ask for a supplemental investigation.
The case is clear.
Could you be a little more objective?
What?
The robbery is fine.
But for the murder, there are too many preconceived notions that Wakita is the murderer.
I don't think everything is fine.
What's the matter, Ochiai?
Are you saying then that there is someone else besides Wakita who is the real culprit?
I don't mean that.
Why are you coming back to this now?
The first investigation was the matter.
The problem is that we've been investigating everything on the assumption that Wakita committed the murder.
Yano!
I'd like you to stop making a mess of things now.
There's no end to the questions we can ask.
I know how you feel.
There's something that's been bothering me.
Why are you coming back to this now?
Speaking of trendy mystery novels, there are other culprits.
There are two.
Hamano and his mistress.
This mystery novel would be if this Wakita guy didn't appear at all from the beginning, though.
Come to think of it, why did Hamano go out of his way to visit people's homes?
In the middle of the night.
He kept saying there was no physical evidence of the murder.
Maybe he knows something special that no one else knows.
Ochiai.
He might say something about that special circumstance at trial.
If that happens, we're in big trouble.
Let's start all over again with a clean slate.
But it's too late now to do that.
But...
You look serious.
I've got some thinking to do.
You can't just think about it.
You have to act.
You can't just think this way and that way.
You got that sponsor, too.
Who?
He's Akemi's husband.
He's Akemi's husband?
Don't be disappointed.
How old do you think she is?
She's 35.
Light.
he can't survive on her own.
That's why she have to cheat on him.
You know?
I see.
So good luck with that.
We can't take a deposition against a lawyer.
Unless we have a warrant for our arrest.
I wonder what would happen if we took that statement instead of the report then.
Is it the same as this?
It's too late.
Why?
It's not like it was a year or two ago.
But...
Nothing you can't remember, right?
At that time..
Let me see.
Oh.
Yeah, when I asked him what time he got home.
What?
I was a little concerned.
But then we caught the guy and I forgot about it.
I'm sure he was just thinking about it.
Yes his attitude..
That was right after the incident, wasn't it?
But I wasn't concerned about that.
We'll do a supplemental investigation.
I think this case is all clear.
But..
But if you're not convinced yourself, go for it.
But I doubt that the supplementary investigation will turn up a completely unexpected culprit.
Wakita's trial for robbery and murder is proceeding apace.
If another culprit turns up, it would be a stain on both the police and the police agency.
On that point, I'm sure Wakita is the culprit.
This supplemental investigation will clarify some of the ambiguities and uncertainties, and we hope to be convinced by the current indictment.
That's how we see it.
Go for it.
Have you made up your mind yet?
Hemorrhoid surgery.
Tokyo has the best facilities.
I hear the next scheduled transfer is quite significant.
I hear you're going to be the chief of detectives in Hiroshima.
It's quite a bold move.
Good luck with your last job here.
Yes.
First of all, there's the death of the wife.
I'm sure someone killed her.
Then who killed her?
There was no motive for her murder?
It is also possible to hold a grudge against another person due to borrowing money.
Let's do a background check on her.
Your report says she remarried.
She was widowed from her previous husband, and she remarried in 1954 to a Munakata.
What was the reason for the marriage?
She's the daughter of a very wealthy family.
He worked on her father's property rights issue, and that was the beginning of their relationship.
I see.
Munakata must be quite old by now?
He's 63?
She was 37..
She's been married once before.
It's not inconceivable that she's had other relationships.
You think so?
I see.
Come to think of it.
Come to think of it?
Nothing.
Of course it's possible.
Let's think about Hamano next.
His attitude is strange.
He knows something.
So to find out what he knows.
There's no way to start from scratch by looking at his behavior and condition before..
and after the crime, his relationship with Munakata, and more.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
You've been looking a little better lately.
It's all about time.
Every bad thing will fade and disappear with time.
The best thing you can do is get this trial over with.
I asked around about the Mrs. at various stores.
But there were not strange things.
I believed she only love his husband.
Let's see about the Hamano.
What happened to his marriage proposal that broke down with the matchmaker, the president of Miyamoto Construction??
All we know is that she's the daughter of the manager of Nitto Kasei in Marunouchi.
That's all we need to know.
But you see, there are a total of 23 department heads at Nitto Kasei.
According to the family register.
12 daughters of marriageable age.
So you're going to have 12 or 20 people check each and every one of them.
That's a lot of work for us.
We are not a detective.
We are busy, and the chief's is not into about the case.
Ok.
We'll handle this case.
Excuse me, but didn't you have a marriage proposal last year?
With Hamano.
No.
Thank you very much.
In other words, why did Mr. Hamano and this marriage proposal suddenly break off? That's all there is to it.
I understand why you don't want to talk about it.
It's not something that would cause you any trouble.
Oh my god.
As I said before, it was just a small matter.
We didn't want you to come all the way to the Metropolitan Police Department for something like this.
I got a letter.
You got a letter?
From Mr. Hamano?
No.
From someone I don't know at all.
I couldn't bear to see the person who was about to marry Mr. Ichiro Hamano, so I took the liberty of writing to you.
I don't know what kind of publicity Mr. Hamano, the matchmaker or the person himself, is talking about, but I know Mr. Hamano's past.
He has had a girlfriend since he was a student, and the relationship continues to this day, making it very difficult to resolve.
I am sorry to hear of your unhappiness at the thought of marrying such a man.
Please accept my sincere apologies.
I will not mention my name for various reasons.
The name is totally fictitious.
I also checked the address.
Postmark's in Nihonbashi.
Someone's interfering with Hamano's marriage.
Why would anyone want to interfere?
This letter would've been better if it was Mrs. Munakata.
It's impossible.
It's easy work for us if so.
It could happen.
Look at this.
What's this?
Mrs. Munekata sent this manuscript to Weekly Woman magazine.
It's a continuation from a little over a year ago.
It's a kind of travel guide.
My home town.
I was hoping you could do a handwriting analysis for me.
This would be great clue.
Yeah.
This character "marriage" is an attempt to force the handwriting to look different. She's trying to make it different.
The stroke order is exactly the same.
Are you sure it's the same person?
There's no doubt about it.
Unexpected things often happen.
Unexpected things often happen....but
I'm surprised.
But now we have a pretty good idea of what happened.
Thanks.
I'm sure she's doing something to harass Muramatsu's daughter as well.
This is a completely unexpected turn of events.
I think we've reached a certain point in the investigation.
It's going to be tricky.
We have to be very careful.
If it turns out later that she's not guilty  at all, it'll mean that the prosecutor's office has created a hell of a scandal.
I know.
And moreover.
I don't think that's possible.
If she is the real culprit...
What does that mean?
It would be a stain on the D.A.'s office.
I'm telling you this because it's between you and me.
But it's also a personal matter for you.
You're gonna lose a lifetime.
How many times have you confessed to Wakita's murder?
8th.
The newspaper would say this.
Prosecutor's coercive interrogation of Wakita with no physical evidence
Whether he's guilty or not, We made him say so.
But I still suspect him.
The trial's on 14th, less than a week from now.
Yeah. Well, we can't delay the investigation.
Get in touch with the D.A. and see what we can come up with as soon as possible.
There're a lot.
Do you know how many inns and hotels there are in Sendagaya?
And besides, Shibuya, Shinjuku, Gotanda...
I'm so frustrated.
Well, let's do something about it!
What about Muramatsu Yuki?
No, no, no, that can wait.
We'll have to corroborate the evidence against Mrs. and Hamano.
I'm counting on you.
At this rate, it's going to take a time.
We need more times.
Because the day after tomorrow is the final argument.
But please.
I extended the investigation once at your request the other day.
The trial director agrees with me.
I think this supplemental investigation is going to end up being a waste of your time and effort.
I hope that's the case, somehow.
Excuse me but.
I was wondering if you had received a letter similar to this one?
Not at all.
Really?
Who wrote this terrible letter?
I was surprised.
I'm asking you again...
Have you ever received one of these before?
Not at all.
Anything else?
I'm sorry.
And, , as I asked you to do at the beginning, don not tell anyone.
That's not going to happen.
I know this is just a harassing slander.
If this were true, even our marriage would be in a bit of trouble.
There is nothing untrue about this.
We can imagine who wrote it.
I feel sorry for Hamano.
Can you vouch for me?
Of course.
Then I won't tell anyone.
It would make both of us uncomfortable.
Excuse me.
Thanks
It is clear from the above evidence that
its brutality, its cumulative criminality, and its negative impact on society.
Based on the above three guidelines, I sentence the defendant in this case, Masayoshi Wakita, to death.
Thanks for coming.
Where shall we talk?
I'll take you somewhere.
I'm sorry, sir, but I'll have this cleaned up in no time.
It's ok like that.
I've got a business meeting alone with him for the next two hours.
Can I get you something to drink?
After we're done talking.
Yes, sir.
If you need me, please press the bell.
Wakita's case is finally down to just the verdict.
Yes, it is.
As I told you on the phone.
I have my own opinion about the case.
I've explained them to you. I'd like to hear your opinion.
Go ahead.
You know Fujiya Ryokan on Kamidori in Shibuya, right?
Since last February, you have been going there two or three times a month.
Mrs. Munakata, who passed away, accompanied you there.
This is based on the testimony of the Fujiya Ryokan's maid.
Then there is TOKIWA HOUSE near Sendagaya station.
You know this one too.
Three or four years ago, you often visited there with her, but not since last year.
This is based on the testimony of the Tokiwa house's maid.
Taken together, there was a physical relationship between you and Mrs. Munakata for several years.
I hope you acknowledge this fact.
Ochiai.
Here's not police.
Yes, this is not the prosecutor's office or the police.
This is a private discussion between us.
But isn't this a bit much for a private discussion?
Then I'll have a warrant prepared for your arrest, and we'll discuss it in my office, taking notes.
Is that better?
Then I have your permission to continue.
Since last fall, you've been in talks to marry a woman named Fusako Ooi.
Mrs. Munakata's defamatory letter unilaterally broke off your marriage.
I have Mrs. Munakata's letter from that time.
Not only Fusako Ooi, but a few years ago there was an incident similar to this with Yoshiko Kondo, with whom you had been dating since you were a student.
I have no doubt about this either.
Next, please tell me specifically about your actions on January 17, the day of the incident.
You left your apartment at approximately 8:00 a.m.
From 10:00 a.m., you attended the 4th trial of your case at the Tokyo District Court, Courtroom No. 7.
It ended at 11:30 a.m.
Now, would you please recall what you were doing between 11:30 and 8:20 at night when you went to the Munakata home?
It was about three months ago.
However, this was the day of the murder of Mrs. Munakata, a very serious incident.
Naturally, you have many memories of it, and I am sure it will not be too difficult for you to recall it.
If it is difficult for you to say so, let me say it for you.
You met with Mr. Yuki Muramatsu that afternoon or evening.
Hello?
We had a long meeting after the trial.
What's wrong?
Read this.
Who's her?
Do you know her?
Why are you silent?
Ms. Muramatsu is denying everything.
But if she would come to the Prosecutor's Office and sit at my desk.
I'm sure we can clear this up.
Am I wrong?
What did you do when Yuki-san showed you Mrs. Munekata's letter, and you felt intense disappointment and anger?
Anyway, you arrive at the Munakata house at 8:20 p.m.
The maid left to reserve food about 10 minutes later at 8:30 p.m.
So it was just you and Mrs. Munakata alone in the Munakata house.
What went on in the Munakata house?
I have proof of everything up to this point.
But I can honestly say that there is nothing certain about the future.
And no matter what kind of investigation we do in the future, it will probably turn up nothing.
It's just my eternal conjecture that this is what happened.
When the maid left, you scolded her vehemently.
She objected.
Naturally, a fierce struggle ensued between the two of you, during which you lost your temper.
You wrapped your wife's neck with the red waistband and killed her.
And a little after 9:10, you left.
Here's what I'm thinking.
I'd like to know your opinion whether I'm wrong or not.
One word is all I ask.
I'd like to know if I'm missing the point, or if it's more accurate than I thought.
What do you think?
My relationship with her is complicated.
But I didn't kill her.
I see.
That's enough.
I still believe that the culprit is Wakita.
I'm sorry for asking so many rude questions.
But...
I have one more question, just to be sure.
About this case...
You acted in a way that aroused certain suspicions in me and Mr. Hirao.
This is an undeniable fact.
Actually, not only Hirao-kun and I, but there is one other person who suspects you.
That's Muramatsu Yuki-san.
When I met Ms. Muramatsu I frankly showed her the letter Mrs. Muramatsu had sent to Ms. Fusako Ooi.
However, Ms. Muramatsu was not that surprised.
I was astonished.
It says terrible things about the man she's  going to marry.
However, Ms. Muramatsu was not that surprised.
However, she didn't show much of an emotional response to it.
This means, of course, that she has seen this same letter before.
Perhaps Ms. Muramatsu thought that the owner of this letter could be none other than Mrs. Munakata.
I suspect that she made such an assumption right after the incident.
Think back carefully.
What has Ms. Muramatsu said to you since the incident?
I don't know how the word she used.
But the meaning is a necessary question that perhaps you are not the culprit.
At other times, for example, even if you are the culprit, someone else has already been clearly identified as the culprit.
Don't dwell on it.
I think that's what she meant.
She's beautiful and clever.
No, too clever.
Anyway, I, Hirao-kun, Muramatsu-san, and myself had our own reasons for suspecting you.
Why did you act in a way that arouses the suspicions of these three people?
It's just a feeling of regret from your special relationship with the ladies, that's all.
Or is there some other reason?
If there was, what would it be? I'd like you to explain yourself.
Normally, whatever special relationship you had with her, she's dead, and that's okay.
I'm talking about a hypothetical.
Even if you had killed her, we already know who else would have done it.
It is natural for humans today to hide it.
but you couldn't do it.
This is not just a matter of guilt, but I still think it's a matter of human conscience.
Your conscience made you do it.
Please swear on your conscience again, please say it one more time.
You've been troubled by your special relationship with her, and you've done things that have aroused suspicion in others.
But you had nothing to do with the murder, only with the killing.
I won't ask you again.
Just one word ok.
I don't care what your motives are. I would never think of you as a murderer, no matter what the motive.
I can't believe it.
And if I'm wrong about this...
Wakita cannot be given the death penalty even if he has a criminal record.
Ochiai.
Wakita wasn't the one who killed her.
I'm the one who killed her.
It's too late.
It's all about the aftermath.
I'll take responsibility for the accusations and accusations against the DA's office.
But as for you personally, you'll have to think about that yourself from now on.
The pursuit of truth is a difficult thing.
Frankly speaking, I think there is a problem with the attitude of the prosecutor in charge.
I think that once a prosecutor's office makes a decision, they tend to have a mentality that they are going to stick to that decision forever.
But I think the problem lies in the strength of the spirit of pursuit of the truth.
I think this Prosecutor Ochiai's attitude is admirable in that respect.
You've always had a penchant for strange things, even as a student.
Oxtails.
If you ask Kikuya, he'll bring you some.
You have to eat something.
You never know what you're going to get when you open it.
I thought I was in for a hell of a lot of pain and terrible criticism.
I was like PR for the D.A.'s office.
The world has changed, hasn't it?
The pursuit of truth is more important than the fear of making a mistake on the job.
My ideas are out of date.
Maybe I was a little too clever.
No way.
us to appear on their Saturday show, "Visit This Person".
I see.
What's the motive?
You've done a supplemental investigation.
First of all, the time of Mrs.'s death, which means the time of the crime.
The real murderer had a guilty conscience and was ready to confess.
I think Hamano is very admirable.
All he had to do was say he didn't know anything.
All would be fine.
Yeah.
Wakita is just like that. He's saying he did it on his own.
Good Morning.
This is awesome.
I saw you on TV.
You did?
My wife was impressed by how open and friendly you were.
You were like a celebrity.
You know, on TV, everyone wears makeup.
I hope it wasn't too weird.
It was so great.
Come in.
This is express mail.
Takigami, Monbetsu-gun, Hokkaido
Koichi Ishikawa
I don't know him.
Koichi Ishikawa..
I would like to express my deepest respect for the work you are doing day and night in pursuit of the truth.
Today I saw you on TV.
I guess everyone watches TV, I'm afraid I can't do anything bad
Seeing you on TV, I have the utmost respect for your hard work and efforts.
By the way, I used to be a great admirer of Mr. Munakata......
Are you Koichi Ishikawa?
I'm Ochiai from the Public Prosecutor's Office.
Thank you for coming all the way from afar.
You said in your letter that you had a relationship with Munekata.
Four or five years ago my brother was involved with him in a fraud case.
He helped us a lot.
Since then, every time I come to Tokyo, I visit him with a gift to thank him for his kindness.
So?
So I arrived in Tokyo on January 15th.
I was also on a business trip for my company
I had a lot of things to do.
I couln't visit him.
I called him before I left just to say hello.
You did that from the inn?
Yes.
What inn is it called?
Yamashiro inn.
You first called at 9:00.?
That's right.
Would you excuse me for a moment?
That's the correct time?
Customer number 10 is calling.
And the phone was busy?
I tried every minute or two, but it was busy.
It was so strange.
I thought maybe their phone was malfunctioning, so I called the station.
What time did you call the telephone station?
Let me see.
At that time, you said that the only way to get to the train was from there, 20 minutes away.
Yeah, it wasn't closer to 9:30.
What did the telephone station say?
I'll look into it. Please wait a moment.
It wasn't more than two or three minutes.
I noted that the receiver was off the other end of the line.
The receiver was off the other end of the line?
So I wonder who picked up the phone on the other end.
So you called again?
I tried calling.
But this time, instead of being busy, I get a call signal, but no one answers the phone.
If the receiver is disconnected, we'll send a signal.
Look at this.
That's where the other person answer.
We give him a warning.
So in the case of 4611, when the signal was given, someone on the other end answered, right?
Yes.
What did it sound like?
It was a woman.
It was a woman?
Did the woman say anything?
Just a word.
What did she say?
I'm sorry.
Between 9:26 and 9:28.
The woman responded to your attention.
That's Mrs. Munekata, isn't it?
Here?
Yes.
I see.
What time did you see Mr. Hamano?
About 9:10.
How do you remember the time so precisely?
Because I came home in a hurry to watch the 9:15 oriental featherweight title on TV.
When I put my car in the back storage and came out of the store, the news was still on the previous program, not a commercial.
It's absolutely impossible for something once completely dead to have come up for air.
But people often mistake the fainting state for death.
At first glance, they look almost dead.
Does it last for 20 or 30 minutes?
Normally, it would be more like 30 or 40 minutes.
So Mrs. Munakata was in a coma until 9:27, 8:00.
So she was alive, at least until then.
From Meguro to his apartment in Sugamo.
Then the maid found Mrs. Munekata's corpse at about 10:05.
I get it.
That's why.
I don't know why the lawyer said all those strange things, but it's just gibberish.
I understand now.
But that lawyer's an idiot.
I told him I did it myself, so he should keep quiet.
It's none of your business.
Wakita!
I'm the only one who could do it.
If I talked about the phone call... I'd get yelled at for being an idiot.
You!
Listen,
That room was the only bright one.
I pushed the door open.
I was crazy about it. I was jumping at her, but...
I got a phone call that I didn't expect.
And I jumped on her.
I don't know about the first she said "I'm sorry" on the phone.
I came in after she put the receiver back on the phone.
I've done a lot of rough stuff in my day.
But this is the first time I've killed someone.
Are you in pain?
But I'm glad you did.
Doctor cut off your hemorrhoids while you are here.
You were always complaining about your hemorrhoids hurting every day.
Cheer up.
It's just that when they looked into it, they found one new fact after another.
It's not your fault.
You don't have to worry about your transfer.
No one thinks you're the kind of person who'll make it to the attorney general's office.
You.
Hamano.
Come in.
This is something small.
This is from him.
I'll get out.
Come in.
I have to go squeeze some apples.
I'll be right out.
Don't worry.
Have a seat.
When did you make bail?
13th.
The day before yesterday.
What are you going to do now?
I'm going back to my home.
Are you in pain?
How is Mr. Munakata?
I heard he went home from the hospital and he's getting better.
I've heard a little bit about you.
Are you suddenly transferred to Kushiro this time?
It's too far from Tokyo.
How's Yuki Muramatsu?
Did you see her after that?
No.
She left for France.
France?
She's a fine young lady, isn't she?
I bet she thought to herself as she flew out of Haneda like that.
There are two stupid men in Japan.
Ochiai.
I see.
You and I are both idiots.
But you know what, I'm fine with stupid.
Ochiai.
Take care.
Take care of yourself too.
Lawyer Hamano commits suicide at a inn in Kofu.
THE END