Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
A wind and woman?
Aiko Takano is also at a turning point?
I don't feel like she's making any progress.
I understand How she has the impatience of trying to somehow break out of her shell, but...
This may be her limit.
Still, She's not losing her popularity.
Her paintings are for rich people's homes and hotels.
The decoration of a rich person's reception room or a hotel lobby is something I can't imagine
The color has lost its depth and the spirit has become delicious
Also,she's so beautiful and friendly.
Welcome.
congratulations!
Thanks.
Please take your time.
Thank you in advance.
That's the son of the picture dealer who deal her paints.
It's really popular!
My dad is happy too.
I'm sure he'll come to greet you someday.
He does not need.
We've already sold five paints.
At this rate we might all be sold.
Is he Yatabe?
He had been standing in front of that painting for a while now.
I think I managed to finish just one of the pictures.
Welcome.
Hi.
Can you review this?
I am a complete amateur so I can't.
Anything fine with me.
please help me with my studies
I see..well...
Well...this paint is..
The instinct of a woman who continues to seek eternal happiness.
I guess I could say something like that.
Is that really what I draw?
Of course, this is just my personal opinion.
It's probably not what you think, but...
It would be rude to say something like this but.
The real you is probably lonely and very unhappy.
That's what I feel.
Me?
I have only bought three paints from you so far.
That's the feeling you get in my paints?
Well..I was sorry to say that.
Hello.
Welcome.
I'll be off now.
Thank you for coming.
There's crowed.
It's all thanks to you.
No way.
You did a great promoting on your magazine.
Thank you.
Congratulations on everything.
Where will you be shooting for next month's gravure issue?
Here's fine.
I wonder what it is that will save me from my loneliness and misery
Shojo Jutai (1966)
Aiko.
I've dated many women, but there's never been one like you
What does that mean?
In many ways.
That's silly.
I read your novels these days.
Aiko.
Could you please draw for my portfolio?
Why are you saying that?
Your paint made my magazine a best seller for 3 months.
It was 7 years ago,right?
Back then, everything in front of me was shining gold.
Is it pink now?
Stop it.
It's dark now.
I've even lost sight of myself
Yourself?
It's better to lose sight of such things.
It was a waste after all.
I thought maybe if I met you I might find a way out
Shall we go too?
No.
What's going on?
I don't care, it's fine
Leave it here
I guess how much I could drink.
You met him for that,right?
I got sick of it
Why do you say that so suddenly?
I suddenly got tired of it
I guess you hate me.
That may be true.
Aiko, you seems to be pretty drunk.
A woman's life is short
In that short time, I want to know what makes a man attractive
I guess I'm  greedy.
Am I really hitting a dead end
I can't paint anymore?
I've been looking you
Welcome.
When I went to your house in Tokyo
the maid said she didn't know where to go
How did you know about here?
My guess.
I thought maybe you were going back to your hometown
Are you here for your magazine project?
and I'd like to take some photos for you, This is my work called "a painter going to his hometown".
Besides me, who else?
Kita,  Onishi, and  Kurita.
You're the only woman
That would be an honor.
Would you please come us?
You're so sneaky.
Anyway, let's go home
What a nice garden.
I didn't think you'd be so rich.
The land around here was liberated after the war?
Almost all the fields are gone, and only that mountain remains.
It's hard to take care of trees.
Those hinoki cypress trees?
Is cypress expensive?
Apparently a 100 year old Hinoki tree costs 1 million yen!
1 million yen? for 1?
1 million yen...
Your house is built on this incredible wealth
You think so?
Yeah.
I'm saying big but
I believe I will be of some help to your growth.
I really understand about you more than anyone else.
I was able to prepare a meal for you.
Thank you for the meal.
Are you so full ?
I can't eat any more
Never, this Murakami-san is the one who proposed marriage to me
What do you think?
You're a perfect couple.
Rest room is outside of the room.
Thank you so much.
Where is she sleeping?
Are you still awake?
I was wondering what was going on because I could hear people talking
Come here.
It's terrible to come all the way here and make you sleep alone.
What's wrong?
I've been waiting for long time.
Murakami-san, shall we get married?
Is it true that I will give you our house and our mountain.
Are you sure?
In return, you have to live here and look after our property.
What are you going to do?
And of course I'll be in Tokyo as usual
Because if I stay in a place like this I won't be able to paint
You don't like it.
I don't mind.
But you will be in Tokyo with another guy, I worry about that.
I don't know what will be happening.
Good night.
Hold on.
Baya will be here.
Good morning
Please wash your face.
Thank you, Aiko-san is not awake yet?
She left this morning.
She left?
I have been told that everything she said last night was a joke
It's been so long since I've been able to pain.
Why can't I paint anymore?
It's not burning.
what's wrong?
I can't do anything.
Anyway, please accept this from your father
If I don't, my dad will get angry with me.
You are from a wealthy family,
so no matter how much I tell my father that money is no good, he doesn't understand
No, even if I knew
We don't want someone else to take your painting away from you.
I'm honored.
He thinks I'm a money making bird.
I don't mean that.
Would you like to go to Yokohama?
I found a Chinese restaurant that is a little dirty but very good
You're in a bad mood What's wrong with you today?
Yeah.
Go home.Go home.
I am here to consult with you.
What is this?
About my work.
I'm in trouble.
Can I help you with any issues related to art?
Please, as you said before, I am lonely
To be honest, I haven't been able to paint recently
You can't?
I guess I hit a wall.
I can no longer paint.
Teacher, what should I do?
Takano
I am a doctor
I can only find a disease.
The paintings that you have bought of me so far are my favorites
So I feel like you know me,
so please tell me what to do
As I have said many times
I am a snob who has nothing to do with art.
I say this as a snob
You have to marry.
A woman will first marry the man she loves
Next, I'll give birth to that man's child
I think giving birth to a child is the most wonderful and important thing for a woman
I don't just want to get married
Why?
I feel like if I get into the confines of marriage,
I will become even more useless
What does that mean?
I'm afraid of being tied down mentally.
That's not good.
I can't get married.
I have no choice but to say anything.
Come in.
Please come in.
Thank you for your support
I have been discharged from the hospital
Thank you very much for everything.
I'm glad.
She's sleeping well.
Aren't you happy?
You're her mother now.
She's so cute.
I didn't think it would be this cute.
Right? Right?
Please take good care of her.
Of course, we'll do my best
Can a woman's happiness of getting married and having children go hand in hand with her career?
I don't know.
Hello?
It's been ages.
What's wrong?
Sorry I scared you.
Suddenly I wanted to see your face.
I'm so happy. Sorry
Come in.
it's been years since you last saw me
It's still small and dirty,
but it's great.
Don't flatter me.
Where's your husband?
My husband is still at work
Oh I see.
I remember that Kei-chan is in kindergarten?
Yeah.
He's taking a nap now.
I see.
You look happy.
You think so?
I might be happy in a different way than you are
Do you draw pictures?
but I don't have any amazing talent like Aiko
Well, I'm just doing it as a hobby,
but it's no good.
This is for Kei-chan
I'd never seen you knitting before.
After Kei-chan was born
I just naturally started to like doing this kind of thing.
It's strange
What's wrong?
It's nothing like that.
You look a little pale,
Are you tired from working too hard?
It's nothing really.
That's fine, but let me make some tea
It's not a particularly good painting, , but there's something about it that draws me in
I wonder what it is that attracts me so much.
The tea is ready
Is he till asleep?
I am weird after all
Why?
I didn't you buy a souvenir for Kei-chan.
If I were a normal woman, I would notice it.
What are you talking about?
That's so you,Aiko.
I'm a strange woman after all
Something is needed.
I've never felt a purpose in life as a woman.
Mom.
Did you get up?
I've never felt envious of someone before,
but today I wonder why I'm so envious of her.
Hello Kei-chan
Say hello.
Hello.
Say hello to your husband.
Kei-chan.
I didn't know anything about it
Do you like cars?
Yes.
Let's go for a ride together.
You're lucky.
What do you want to do when you grow up?
I'll draw pictures like mom.
Do you like to draw?
I want to see Kei-chan's work.
This is Mommy.
If I could have a child, I might be reborn
You were surprised to receive such a telegram so suddenly, weren't you?"
Yes I was.
Sorry, You've only written " come here"
I’m sorry.
I suddenly wanted to see you.
I think you tired.
Are you alright?
I'm thinking about having a baby.
Well, you suddenly said something like that
Please don't make me too surprise.
Do you support me?
I've been waiting it for the past six years
So, is the person who will become your husband Mr. Murakami from the other day?
No.
that is someone I don't know
Someone I don't know either
Please speak clearly.
Who is your husband?
Do you know about Artificial insemination?
I can have a child without a husband
That's not good idea.
I really want to have children, but I don't want to get married
So...
What are you talking about?
You are the daughter of the Takano family.
That's not good you would give birth to a child without husband.
I thought that only you would understand my feelings,
but that was impossible.
Well, that's fine. Take a bath.
Kiyo-san, give her a towel.
I really want a child that is just mine
Just mine.
There are two ways to have my own child artificial insemination
First, AIH and second, AID
First of all, AIH is when the recipient's husband's sperm are used
In many cases, artificial insemination is performed
because the husband's sperm are extremely weak
Therefore, even if ovulation dates are measured perfectly,
the chances of success are low
In contrast, AID is a method of using someone else's excellent work
that meets all the requirements,
and the probability of success is extremely high
Okay, any question?
Whatever the reason, donors and recipients
must never tell each other who they are?
Of course, when it comes to artificially inseminated children,
various difficult legal issues can arise,
such as issues of inheritance rights
When did artificial insemination start in Japan?
It's been 20 years already, and there must have been about
4,000 children born as a result of it.
Okay, any question?
That' all for today.
Satoru-kun and Ozu-kun, please stay.
There's another operation today, so I'm counting on you
Yes.
Are you alright?
Do you want to take an artificial insemination?
because I wanted to have a child
So please.
I was surprised.
Although it is called artificial insemination,
there are various conditions for receiving it
First, you need to have the couple come together
and confirm their consent
That's because, unlike blood transfusions,
it creates a human being and sends him out into the world
For the sake of the child's life,
you must be extremely careful.
In my case?
You don't meet the conditions.
Sorry.
Umemura is here.
operating room is ready?
Yes.
I have an operation coming up, see you.
Satoru?
Is today's person beautiful?
I'll tell Dr.Yatabe.
Apparently She was female artist, Takano Aiko.
Yes.
She came to see a doctor?
She knows Dr.yatabe.
I see.
Will you go to watch a movie this coming Saturday?
I'll buy the ticket.
I'm busy with my study.
That's neurotic.
Are you not interested in whose body your sperm will enter?
No.
Generally speaking, artificial insemination itself is a human emotion
It's just a mechanical thing that ignores everything
But...
It bothers me that a woman I don't know is making my baby.
Even if we could find out who it was, it wouldn't do us any good
If she's a beautiful woman, that's fine, but if she's a woman
but if she's a ugly woman
That will only lead to hopeless self-loathing
Don't say that
You shouldn't take it so seriously.
We both passed strict requirements and were selected by Professor Yatabe.
It has to do with our paths.
Why is this not okay?
No, it's not okay
If you want children, you have no choice but to get married
What time does the conference start?
Dr.
No matter how many times you say, my answer is always the same
Please keep this a secret between you and me
If you do that, what do you think will happen to the child?
Are you saying that I slept with a guy and got pregnant?
That's right.
I don't care.
No matter what people say, I want my own child
I will do whatever it takes to protect my child's happiness.
Please.
That's no good.
I'm sorry for calling you here
Don't worry.
I often come here to watch fireworks to relax.
Dr.
Are you still not giving up?
If I continue like this, I will be ruined
Why?
I have no hope of recovery other than giving birth to a child.
Something as simple as giving birth to a child makes me a real woman
That's our only hope of getting the painting back
But having a child doesn't necessarily mean
the way will open up.
I know that.
Even if we can't return to the world of art, I think I can still live purely
Please.
I'm in trouble.
Dr.
That's fine.
Come tomorrow at 3 o'clock
Thank you for waiting
Is the person today beautiful?
You're always thinking about that
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
I decided to quit.
You decided to quit?
Even if I upset Professor Yatabe, I can't take it anymore
Don't lose your temper
However, for me, it means that my biggest rival will take a step forward
Don't get serious.
You haven't done it?
Is she Takano?
Why are you so worried about Takano-san?
I'm big fan of her.
fan?
I've loved her paintings since I was in high school
What a strange person you are.
What's wrong with her?
She's single, so there's no way she's pregnant
But apparently she wants kids.
Is she here for artificial insemination?
I don't know.
I'm sure you know.
She is here for artificial insemination after all
No?
I don't know, so hurry up
Ok.
Just to be clear,
the donors were selected to be two healthy people
with normal blood sugar levels and clear minds
We do not know which sperm was used.
Please be aware that you will never know who the provider is,
Please rest for one more hour.
When will we know the results?
It will be clear after a month.
I can have child of my own in a month.
I can have child of my own.
I was surprised
What happened?
I was waiting for you .
I have something to say
I honestly don't know about that story.
Anyway, please come
Do you really love me?
Yes.
I'm glad.
someone might come.
Let's go backyard.
May I ask you something?
What?
I wonder which one was used today.
I guess that's what it was about
Please, which one was used, mine or Satoru's?
If I knew that, I'd be satisfied
There's no way you could know that.
Please remember that.
Didn't you see the damage to the B sedge?
Well then, mine was used?
No, I can't say that.
You.
You wanted to know about it so You did this,didn't you?
Don't get me wrong.
If only you knew that, you'd be satisfied
Of course
Are you sure?
Yes.
Can I believe you?
Yeah.
Yours was used.
Hug me.
I can't wait for the next 15 days. Sorry
I’m sorry.
What's the hell?
Please draw soon.
My dad is getting irritated.
Gofu is there?
Do you have any sugars?
I have some.
Is this modern art magazine?
Are you interested in modern art or something?
There was someone I knew on magazine
Wanna come to have a tea?
I'll see you later.
Dr.
I should probably say congratulations
There is nothing in particular to note
I don't know anything about the father either.
Thank you
Take care.
I look very beautiful today.
Beautiful, like a cleansed soul.
A child of God, I may have been reborn.
Hello.
You came early..
I got a sudden call so I rushed over
I think it would be better to tell you this.
What can I do for you?
I am having a baby.
Please don't tease me.
It's true.
My baby?
Well then,  what you'd do if it is your child?
I'm getting married
But It's not your child
So, after all, Hosokawa's?
He's such a worthless novelist.
No either.
Who's?
No, he's anybody's child
This is no time for jokes
What on earth are you planning to do by causing
a stupid scandal at such a critical time?
What are you going to do?
What's wrong?
I've been working with you for four years.
Aren't you being a bit harsh towards me?
But you should have paid it back
Who is the real father?
I don't know .
You don't know?
You don't know whose child it is, but is that okay?
But it's my child.
He's my only child.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I didn't think you were that kind of girl
I'll despise you.
That's fine. Well then,
goodbye.
What are you talking about?
Sorry.
Hi, It's Hosokawa.
Oh you.
It's been a while, what happened to you?
What?
I'm having a baby.
Really?
That's good for you.
It's up to you.
I will not force you to abort your baby.
Don't worry.
He's not your child.
Well then, Hosokawa-san, goodbye and write a good novel
Hey, hey Aiko.
what a strange woman.
What's wrong with you?
Aiko Takano's works are all old works.
I asked her to paint but...
but she couldn't make it
She's here.
hello. Thank you for coming.
You look little losing your weighting.
By the way, your face looks pale.
I'm sorry I haven't been able to draw much
so I've only been working on my old work
Please take your time.
Please.
Come with me,Tajima.
Hey, you know, I just had a baby
Is it my child?
Please keep it a secret from my father
I have to consider aborting it.
How much you need?
Don't worry.
He's not your baby.
Is that true?
Yes.
Who is Dad?
God
God?
That's terrible.
Murakami's?
or Hosokawa-san?
I’m sorry.
It's fine
His growth is going well.
Thank you very much.
Do you really have no regrets at all?
Not at all.
The vague feeling I had before has completely cleared up
And now I feel very important to myself
That's good. Your artwork is progressing well
So, I have your own ideas,
but I can't decide on the composition.
But I will definitely finish it by the time of the exhibition
You are a strong-minded person. Please show me your work if you finish it
I'll invite you.
Oh?
Are you student in the Faculty of Medicine here?
No, I am a student of the Faculty of Literature.
I  have a bit of a cold.
You have quite a few clippings of me
I am a fan of you.
why you ran away other day?
I'm sorry.
I'm suddenly feeling a bit off
Are you going to see a doctor now?
No I've done it.
So for a little while, can you stay with me?
I want to go for a drive with you
Sure.
Sato-san, I have a request
I'll do anything I can
Be my model
Model?
I really need a model for my next artwork.
If it's okay with me, I'd be happy.
Thank you.
But can I do it?
It has to be you.
Now try standing up
Can you turn to the side?
Please raise both hands and lower your right hand.
Yes,that's it.
Can I talk?
Okay, but don't move
You've certainly never drawn about a man, have you?
Yeah, it's the first time for me
What kind of painting is it?
I can't tell you until it's finished.
Why?
I can't.
I want to see it.
Don't move.
Why did you choose someone like me as a model?
I just can't understand it.
You're naive, and strong.
Anyway, you are wonderful.
Satoru-san is popular with girls, right?
Why do you ask that?
I want to know more about you.
Why?
I can't help it.
Is that bad?
It's not bad but..
Don't move.
Well...
What?
Would it be okay if I visited you from time to time after the work is completed?
Of course, are you tired?
Let's take a little rest
Yes.
I want to see it.
Not yet.
I think it was the first time I met you
It was at Tajima Gallery.
No, I met you once before.
I wonder where it was.
in the hospital corridor.
Are you really a literature major?
Yes I am.
When I'm doing this,
I feel like I've known Sato-san for a long time
So when will it be completed?
I don't know
Are you getting tired of it?
No way.
Now I am happy to have someone draw for me.
When I hear people say that it makes me happy,
I want to say that I want to draw more and more
You must be tired after working all day today. Let's stop here
No, I'm fine with it
I don't mind standing up until the morning without sleeping
If you say we'll stay together till the morning, I won't be able to keep it up
What's the matter?
I'm busy
Are you busy with her model?
if you don't need me, I'll go home.
Wait.
We haven't finished talking yet.
It wasn't you who was used by Takano-san
It was Satoru-san's.
What are you saying now?
You clearly stated at the time
that the damaged pipe was used
You were so crazy about it.
I thought you would be happy if I said that.
I can't believe it.
You're trying to get revenge on me?
but you don't deserve it.
I was wrong, I may have used you
But that doesn't mean there wasn't love
It's true that I loved you
You may not understand what I'm saying now,
but please at least hear me.
It was after I heard from you that mine was used
I couldn't even understand started happening.
but It was used by Satoru's.
I wonder what will happen to your love
Please don't say such cruel things, tell me the truth.
Ozu, I never had any hope of becoming your wife.
But I can't stand being used by you.
At first, I thought I would confess what I did to Yasaka-sensei and Takano-san and get revenge on you
But when I think about it, it seems foolish to perish with you
That's why I called you
Whatever you want to do is up to you,
but at the very least, you'll have to give up on Takano-san
Well then, goodbye.
students, students, wake up
Stop it. It's my child,
it's my child.
help me.
Help me.
help me
Ozu? Takano is calling you.
What happened Satoru?
You know there aren't many days left until the exhibition
I'm going
Yes, I'll be there right away
It wasn't yours who used it then
That's a lie
That's a lie!
What's wrong Satoru-san?
What on earth happened today?
Are you tired?
I'm alright.
Excuse me.
I told you not to come in while I was working
But Hosokawa is here.
Hey.
what are you doing here?
I came to visit you because you're pregnant.
I guess it's true after all.
I'm at work. Please go home
Well, don't say that,
I'm the kid's father
Are you still saying that? I want to have children
So I did the artificial insemination. It has nothing to do with you
No, definitely He's my child.
Go home
No.
Anyway, please go home
Don't get in the way of my work.
Work?
You just draw nonsense.
What kind of work is that?
Go home
I don't wanna see your face anymore.
What?
What's the hell who you are?
I'm sorry
That's fine.
Thank you.
Satoru-san, This is not good idea.
Look at this.
Title is Virgin Conception.
She got pregnant as a virgin
The father is a young man
He is her ideal man.
So she looks very happy.
With this work, I want to express that young women today have lost sight of their ideal.
Not my child, not my child.
That's dirty.
Virgin Conception?
It is much better in previous drawings.
It's dirty, everyone is dirty
What are you talking about?
Would you be happy to give birth to anyone's child?
Tell me.
What are you going to do with me?
Stop it....
It's unfortunate, but it was unavoidable
This may have been God's providence
It may seem cruel, but I think this was better for you
Next time, I will take care of you as you give birth to your child in the natural way
Cheer up.
As soon as the hospital room is ready
I'll take you there.
Please turn off the lights.
This may have been God's providence
I feel sorry for Takano-san, but I'm glad she had an abortion.
I'm sorry.
please forgive me
She scared me.
What a strange person.
She couldn't paint that much
How did she manage to get out of it?
I never expected her to bounce back so well.
So thank you very much.
Thanks.
Congratulations.
You're doing a great job, I really respect you
Thank you for coming all the way
No matter what you put down, I come right away
Being a model isn't a good feeling when the paint is completed
Well, I don't like violence
Please go there, Takano.
Excuse me.
I heard that your fertilizer.
What is it?
It's a manure.
What do you mean?
You know? that woman...
She gives out sweet nectar to attract men.
And she makes that man into fertilizer.
She's a woman like that.
This is awesome.
Is that so? Thank you
What a good mood!
The victims are pitiful.
You probably won't understand now
Once I was her fertilizer
I couldn't really believe it though.
You should be careful.
It's fine as long as your fertilizer is working
But once it's not working, she easily discard you.
I can't stand to see an innocent young man like you get hurt
Look.
She seems triumphant.
Are you upset?
Well, if you don't like my advice, you'll be her fertilizer for the rest of your life
Damn it.
I'm not fertilizer.
What are you going to do?
What are you doing?
Stop it....
Are you alright?
Why did you do this?
Satoru!
THE END