Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Excuse me
you get up early in the morning
You too
Yeah
Next stop is Hiroshima
Are you getting off?
Thanks for last night
Not at all, it's just beer
I wonder where's your bar
i gave you my business card
Oh yeah
If you come to Hakata, please come and see me.
Let's drink together in Nakatsu
i drink more than you
your back is very nice
Thanks
See you
Excuse me
To New Hiroshima Hotel
Sono yo wa wasurenai (1962)
(A Night to Remember / Hiroshima Heartache)
Welcome
I'm Kamiya from Weekly Journal
Your room is ready
Please fill in this form
The dining room will open in 10 minutes
Hello?
Chugoku TV ?
Oh you, I've just arrived
I hear you called me earlier
I've been working all night.
A new video system was developed
Did you come here to cover the atomic bombing?
What? you came here for that?
It's kind of..
Atomic Bomb Memorial Day is held once a year, and today marks 17 years since the day the atomic bomb was dropped.
That's boring report
The reporter seems to be having a hard time finding a story.
I know how you feel
Kusanari? Yes I have it
Let's have a drink together after a long time
I'll contact you later
See you
It's been 17 years since the atomic bomb was dropped.
Let's make it quick
Please come in
There are few visitors
There are usually few visitors.
However, many visitors come every year before the anniversary of the atomic bombing.
Do people from Hiroshima come here?
No one come
don't they want to remember it?
I have no idea
The number of hospitalized patients at this hospital from January to today is 117.
13 of them had leukemia.
18 had liver damage
9 patients with cataracts
Surgical disease 12 Hypertension 8
And other 12
Are there any special medical conditions that exist after the war
I don't know what the future holds, but so far it's fine
There is a report on the effects of radioactivity
In other words, the atomic bomb is genetically related.
That's right.
However, it is not clinically proven yet.
So it means
The issue of atomic bomb disease is very political
University professor Asahina is researching the genetics of the atomic bomb
Here's the report
can you introduce him to me?
I’ll call him.
Why don't you see him tomorrow?
do you want to see the hospital room?
Yes please
Excuse us
Can I take a photo of you?
Go ahead
How do you feel?
It's hot
You got tanned, and look fine
I was in Tottori for practical training until yesterday.
It was fun
I shot like this
Excuse us
Please
Japan's army has changed
Humans used to take the place of bombs.
I joined not army but self defense force
It's same
You eat a lot. You'll be fine
Oh yeah, there use to be 500000 members
You guys used to meet once a month.
We used to share our common feeling
But now w don't have to do that
So Are there any effects of the A-bomb now?
I can't say there's no effect but I have no idea
Can I see your member list if you don't mind?
Excuse me but is here Fusako Tamura's home?
I'm the Fusako
Hello
well..I'm this person
I heard about you at Kusanabe party
Oh, you wanna ask me about atomic bomb, come in
Come in
Thanks
It's hot. please take off your jacket
Don't worry
Enjoy your tea
When did you visit him?
This morning
It's hot here,right?
This is me
This
At the time I hated having my picture taken. They gave me candy and took my picture.
You don't care now?
No matter how much I hate it, this aftereffect will never go away.
Oh yeah
This is a photo I took at a roundtable meeting of survivors the year before last.
And this
That's enough
I wanna ask you one thing
Tell me
This might be rude
Ask me anything you like
I wanna ask you about your scar
How can I say..I was wondering if you are happy or not
Every News paper reporter ask me same
Oops
I know it's better not to have this
But It can't be helped
Sometimes even healthy people die in car accidents.
I see
Please enjoy your tea
Thank you very much
Shall I go outside if you take a photo of me?
Don't worry
It's really hot
Sorry to have kept you wait
An American newspaper said Hiroshima was in the business of atomic bombs.
The Americans might think I am doing business here.
But I don't mean to that
There are people who don't know or have forgotten the atomic bomb.
That’s bad
I want to help them understand the horror of the atomic bombing.
For that I am willing to take criticism.
Look at that
That A-Bomb Dome has endured 17 years of rain and wind.
As long as people see my body and know the horror of the atomic bomb, I'm happy.
Do you get it?
I get it
i want to forget the atomic bomb
But you're fired with the aftereffects of the atomic bomb.
Can you see?
You don't care?
I’m still young I’m enjoying my life
do you enjoy life?
Yes I do
do you want to get married?
Why you ask me?
What if you love anyone?
I have my boyfriend
What are you doing?
did you finish talking to her?
I may marry him next month
Someone was sitting at the entrance when the atomic bomb was dropped
There's only her and her shadow left
The surface of the houses around here melted with heat of over 5000 degrees.
This place is 280 M away from the hypocenter.
now there's nothing left
Hey kamiya!
I'm here
Hi
I sent ticket for you
Thank you very much
Don't stand up!
I’m sorry
Hit the ball hard!
How's going on your work?
Did you go to Kusanabe party?
It wasn't going well
He's bad
Not you but him
What are you doing?
Damn it
she is a talent in our theater company
I'm Etsuko, nice to meet you
Today's Hiroshima has changed.
Do you know about Atomic bomb?
I don't know.
i was not born
Children who do not know about the atomic bomb are growing up
People who talk about the atomic bomb now are very strange.
I know
I don't care no one concern about it
There're many bars
There are many branches of various companies in Hiroshima.
You mean?
The more companies, the more bars
How about here
Welcome
did you come from narita airport?
Yeah
It seems that the baseball game was interesting today
Hiroshima Toyo Carp is very strong when they have home game
That's funny
you are much more beautiful than before
Thank you very much
You got a boyfriend?
How do you know?
Love makes a woman beautiful
If you want to be beautiful, you should fall in love
No one loves me unfortunately
How about me?
No way
Why?
Because...
How dare you
What do you drink?
Give me a beer anyway
Do you like night life in Hiroshima?
Why don't you change seat?
Let's change
She's the Madam
You know him?
Yeah I met him today
Is he regular customer?
I don't think so
He's here to watch Madam
What are you guys talking about?
You are one of them
Call her
Kimi
Welcome
She is so beautiful
As far as I know, She is the most beautiful woman in Hiroshima
you are so pretentious
Look,Only ugly women are here
Oops, Sorry
Let's drink together
Let's toast
Thanks for everthing
Welcome
It's been a age
He is a reporter named Kamiya of the Weekly Journal.
he is a college classmate
Nice to meet you
Have a seat
Do you wanna drink?
Thank you very much
Give us more
will you introduce me to her?
please introduce yourself
You're mean
I'm Yoshiko Tada
Are you a member of a theater group?
You know of me?
I saw you on TV
I'm glad
you don't make a fool of me
I was so sorry
Excuse me
Sensei,Excuse me
They are strange
Don't get jealous
i like to speculate
Excuse me
Sounds like you had the deepest conversation
Don't get us wrong
Welcome
Come here
I heard you came from Tokyo
i arrived this morning
Do you come here often?
This is my first visit
Thank you very much
Are you bored here?
i just got here so i don't know yet
17 years after the atomic bomb was dropped, he thought that there would be some kind of evidence again, so he is interviewing here.
I see
There is no other way than to interview the atomic bomb survivors in the materials of the Atomic Bomb Museum or in the hospital.
Let's enjoy alcohol without talking about work
Yeah
beer is not alcohol
Bring me whiskey on the rock
Give me high ball
Give me Jin beer
You're so drunk
I'm alright
Where's Madam?
Mama
this is a present for you
I give you
Don't be shy
Oh my god
I'm sorry
What the hell?
I'm sorry.
Let's go
He's so bad
Pass me the towel
Clean here
I'm sorry.
I'm alright
When he gets drunk, he behaves badly
Mama
I'm busy
I was sorry
What the hell?
Let's go
What's wrong?
Let's go out
I'm busy
Please listen to me
What's that?
Who's he?
he looks like a journalist from some magazine
He's chasing her
He is still young
He wants her money
What do you mean?
You are still kid
Let's go out
Go home
Check please
We are going
They are leaving
Thank you very much
We'll pay later
We were sorry
Don't get upset
It's ok
Will you come here again
Yeah
Please visit us again
See you
To ABCC Hijiyama
abcc Atomic Bomb Cure Association does not provide treatment
They are funded by the U.S. Defense Department and monitor healers on a long-term basis.
They learned the relief method for combatants at the time of the atomic bombing.
They are also doing genetic research on radioactivity
abcc does not treat
Good timing,let's take that taxi
Oh
Hi
Oh you
Thanks for last night
Same here
I'll leave first
See you
To station
Take care
Are you alright?
Were you in ABCC?
I'm just here to collect the money.
The scenery from here is wonderful
Yeah
Hiroshima has changed
That's right
Did you finish your work?
It's hard
I know it's hard
Did you find something?
As far as I can see, the Atomic Bomb Museum and DOME have no pride in the atomic bombing.
It's been 17 years
Were you in Hiroshima at that time?
Why you ask me?
Well..nothing
Where is Kusunoki city?
I think it's on the north side of the castle
It seems that there is a mother of a baby with six fingers
I plan to go see her after abcc
what are you going to do looking for that person?
I'm a journalist, so I'd like to make sure
It's cruel
This is my work
what do you do to make sure?
It's a journalist's job to report new medical conditions after 17 years
I have to visit somewhere, see you
Hold on
Excuse me. May I ask you something?
I'm looking for Yamada around here
Yamada?
That Yamada
she moved a while ago
To where?
I have no idea.
Do you know?
Well...Kuniko Yamada is divorced from Yuji Yamada
divorced ?
She back to Kuniko Seto now
Kuniko Seto?
I know her
She worked for only two months, so I'm not sure.
Sugata might know about her
They were good friend
Can I see her?
She is absent now
she said she was going to the sea
Come on
Where's my order?
What did you say?
I'm cooking it now
Don't watch TV and make it quickly
Please make the customer's curry quickly
there are no customers
Saturday always like this
Welcome.
Are you alone?
Mama was here just before
She's not here?
She has something to do.
You're unlucky
Where is she gone?
I have no idea
Do you know?
No
I will go back to Tokyo tomorrow night
This bar is closed on Sundays?
Can you extend your stay by one day?
I can't
Say hi to her
To whom? Mama?
you love her without me knowing
Don't get me wrong
Hi, We are Aki, yes he is here
From Kikuta
She always disappears every Saturday
What?
no one knows where she's going
i think she is with that man
Who?
It's the man who poured alcohol on you
Oh that guy.
I can't believe
How old is she?
Why?
is she married?
I have no idea.
she said she wasn't married
let's drink a lot tonight
No way.
I am very tired from walking around all day today.
Are you disappointed because you don't have a girlfriend?
alcohol takes away your tier
Thank you for waiting
You don't work today?
I will go to work late today
Did you find a baby with six fingers?
I have a hard time finding his mother
I have bad luck
don't be disappointed.
It's so hard to find what kind of things now
If you think Hiroshima has a problem, I think you have a problem yourself.
Since we came all the way here, why don't we go to Miyajima tomorrow?
I can go with you
Oh yeah
What's wrong?
Drink more
Hello? Yes connect me
Editorial office?
I'm Kamiya, where's desk?
I'm Kamiya,
I have covered a lot of ground, but I can't do this project, so can we cancel it?
I know I know but
There is nothing left in Hiroshima today.
this project is too old fashion
I get it
I'll go back tomorrow’s train
See you
Hello?
A stranger is sleeping in my bed. Please come
Excuse me
I took shower and she was sleeping
It seems door was unlocked
Excuse me
Hello?
She got wrong room. her room is 317
I'll call her friend
She is troublesome
Help me
Damn it
Good night
This is tip for you
Thank you very much
I’ll clean your bed
It's ok
Good night
Hello? Oh you
That baby is in Akitsu
What? Akitsu?
I've never been there.
The town is famous for Sake
My friend there told me
You were disappointed so I helped you
I'm sure
Well..The baby was died
She was dead
A year ago she died of pneumonia.
Where's her mom?
I wanna see Kuniko
Why you wanna see her?
I want to ask her something
What you will ask her?
I won't give you trouble
You reporter?
Go home
You're sick.
Stay in bed
Stop it
You ask about babies for fun.
I don't mean that
So Why you are here?
Don't give her trouble anymore
You're sick.
Stay in bed
I'm sorry.
You came here all the way
Hi
Why you are here?
I wasted time
For what?
You're strange
You stayed here last night?
I can't do anything bad.
Why you are here too?
I'm here for finding the baby
She was dead so I can't do anything now
I see
Where are you going?
Shall I guide you?
You're good at kidding
So you can go alone
To where?
My hotel
I will bother you
It's ok
It's strange
For what?
Because
You get me wrong
You can come with me
Here
Come in
Take off your jacket
Take off your tie
Take off your shirts too
I can't
It's ok
Excuse me
You're sweaty
Oh yeah
I know you smoke
Thank you very much
The owner here is my friend.
I come here every weekend
Here it is
you don't have to hide it
No one believes me when I tell the truth
I'm too lazy to explain every time
Welcome
Sorry I'm like this
It's ok. It's summer
Please make yourself at home
She's owner
Thanks for coming
He's kamiya
I met you at Hijiyama yesterday
you haven't had lunch yet?
Shall I order Sushi?
Yeah
Please order
Please make yourself at home
bring me a bigger towel
Ok that's better
Don't worry
why was she there?
ABCC?
is she an atomic bomb survivor?
Yes but it's not serious
She's your classmate
So you were in Hiroshima at the time
You should take a rest
i bring a pillow
Don't worry
Please make yourself at home
That's not so you
Why?
you are a journalist
i have nothing to do with the job now
Please
You serve me a lot
You should take a rest
I feel good
You are so sweaty
Shall I prepare the bed?
Don't worry
Please make yourself at home
Please order Sushi
I will order
i look sick
you are curious sick
It's cold
I have no idea what kind of person you are
Same here
I want to know more about you
what your life is like in your past and now
because you are a journalist?
please don't mislead me
I really wanna know
It's better if we don't know anything about each other
I'm happy now
i won't be happy anytime soon
you are greedy
It could be
But I don't want to leave without anyone knowing
I have to go back to Tokyo tomorrow
It's a pity that we became good friends
So
I want
If you go back to Tokyo, you will be busy with work.
Why you say that?
Stop it
Are you alright?
Please lay down
you are anemic.
I’ll get some medicine
I'm alright
Don't worry
I was sorry
You bully me
I worried
Stop here
In front of the hotel
I'll send you
Don't worry
Take care
Good night
Welcome back
we have booked your train ticket
Thank you very much
Good night
Can I reserve a ticket for the train at 9 o'clock tomorrow night?
Asakaze train?
I think it's too late
I'm in trouble
Excuse me
I'll give you this if you like
Are you alright?
You don't need ?
I'm alright
He's so kind
I'm going now
Good morning
Mama
You're here
You're cold
What can I do for you?
Again?
I borrowed money from a friend, but I spent it all.
Please help me
It can't be helped
Good morning
I'm going out for dinner
How much you need?
50000yen is enough
Good morning.
Sorry I'm late
Good morning
Thank you very much.
Let's have drink together
I'm busy tonight
Go away
Good morning
Good night
It's been a age
Madam is here?
Yes, please come in
Welcome
have a seat
Excuse me
Didn't you go back to Tokyo?
Are you alright?
Why didn't you go back to Tokyo?
I thought I'd go home without seeing you, but I changed my mind.
Can you go out?
After work, ok
Welcome
Where's Kaneko?
Over there
you were waiting for me?
Excuse me
Do you want another beer?
Serve him beer
Excuse me
What's wrong?
you borrowed money from that woman?
Yeah
You're kidding
It's true
i won't be stupid
why don't you trust me?
Give me water
What's wrong?
You go home
Ok I'll wait for you
Bye
Why you upset?
you don't have to worry about her
You didn't care about me so I played with her a little
you are always busy
I was lonely
Mom
What are you talking about?
I was so worried about you because you don't have parents
So
don't rely me too much
You go home
What's the hell?
Get away
I am one of the customers
you are nagging her
one of the customers?
You are new here
You just act cool
What? you act cool
Stop it
He look me down
What's wrong?
What's the hell?
Stop it
You go home
What's the hell?
Who are you guys?
Mind your mouth
What's the hell?
You hit me
Go outside
Stop it
Calm down
You go home
Are you alright?
I'm alright
you are bothering me
You go home
Sorry, we will just drink
You're too bad
I was sorry
What's wrong?
It's nothing
Where's Kamiya?
He's just left
Welcome
Welcome back
Kamiya-san
What's wrong?
I need to talk with you
Me?
Thank you
Where have you been?
I was waiting for long time
i was drinking in some bars
I'm here to say sorry
I'm alright
shall we take a walk outside?
I’m going to change clothes
what kind of relationship does that man have with you?
Nothing
I have seen them stay together in a hotel
i happened to see it
He's play boy
I have nothing to do with him now
What do you mean?
a lot happens in my job
But he was always lonely
that's why he depends on me
So you are...
We were drunk so I don't remember anything..so we slept together
You are lonely too
Kind of
You were too lonely
i understand your feelings
Akiko?
you have a very pure heart
now i know about it
i feel like i understand you
You are lonely
I want to help you if you want
I really wanna help you
Excuse me
What are you doing?
Put your hand out
What's this?
Hold it
The stone is at the bottom of the river at high tide
At low tide the stone appears
The tide was ebb at the time of the atomic bombing
Is this the effect of the atomic bomb?
There are many stones like this in Hiroshima.
This is Hiroshima stone
why did you give me this stone?
Please make yourself at home
If you have any business, please ring the bell over there.
It's quiet here so we can talk
why are you interested in me?
because i like you.
That's all
Have a seat.
Wanna drink?
do you doubt me?
Because of my job, it may be unavoidable
do you think all men are playboys?
No
What do you mean?
I really love you
You hate me?
You know how I feel
So?
I'm sure you'll regret it
i will never regret
Hold on
you don't understand me
It's none of my business
Hold on
Open the door
I was a student at that time
I lived in the suburbs of Hiroshima and was hit by the atomic bomb on my way to a temple.
Then I feel very insecure about my health
I’m always so insecure about myself
I don't want female happiness
After I graduated, my parents died and I started working at a company.
I also worked as a housekeeper
and now I’m doing this job
many men seduce me
I'm a woman, so I want to rely on men sometime
but my body won't let it
men see my body and run away.
I’m worried of it
Now you know how I am
I’m like a stone in Hiroshima
No one sees the stones at the bottom of the river because people see the blue sky during the day and the neon lights at night.
you get it?
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
See you
Don't go
You can't go home
Let me go
Stay here
No matter how is your body. I love you all the way
I love you
I can't believe it
Let's get married.
I will protect you
I will heel your disease
We can't
I can't believe it
I can't believe
You can't?
Not you but...
Akiko
Let's get married.
No..
We can't get married
Stay strong
I want to help you
You'll regret
Stay strong
I wanna make you happy
You'll regret
I love you all the way.
Your unhappy is my unhappy
Your happiness is my happiness
Let's go to Tokyo with me tonight.
This is our best way
Can you?
I won't leave from you
If you are sick and dying, use my love as a springboard to live the rest of your life.
I will willing to support you
Can you?
Thanks. I will buy a ticket for you at the station
You sure to come?
Yes
You gonna get married?
I think you know about yourself very much
So I'm here to consult you
I can't say no.. and I can't recommend
I always tell you about your health
I don't know what's going on your health
I can't against to you
Sudden increase in white blood cells may occur
But this is your happiness..so I can't say anything as a doctor
Kamiya
Thanks for waiting
I thought you wouldn’t come
Excuse me
One entrance ticket
What?
I've bought your ticket
Where's your baggage?
I don't have
no?
Let's go
Akiko
What happened?
I'll say good bye here
Why?
I can't go after all
We have time.
Let's talk
You worry about your health?
No
why did you suddenly change your mind?
Let me think more
I need to think
Think?
You just follow me, ok
This memory is enough for me
I was happy
Anyway, we're splitting here today
I won't leave
I won't give up, so please wait until I come to pick you up
I'm sure to pick you up
i will come here again to pick you up
Trust me
See you
Kamiya
Do you have data on coal mine turnover?
I have not prepared for that yet
Please prepare it
Kikuta,Phone call
Take this
Hello? I'm Kikuta
Oh Kamiya
Are you alright?
I'm alright
Bar?
Which?
bar Aki?
Madam?
She doesn't come to work these days.
I think she went to play somewhere
I haven't seen her lately
let's meet again then
I'm busy so I can't check her
I'm busy
Come here if you love her
Hello?
Welcome
there is an empty seat in the back
Here's fine
It's been a age
Drink this?
Welcome
when did you come here?
I've just arrived
He's Kamiya
He is a reporter for a weekly journal in Tokyo.
Nice to meet you
Did Akiko leave this bar?
She's died
When?
2 months ago.
You didn't know?
she died suddenly
Yeah
she put up with her illness
i didn't notice that
She was nice person
Are you alright?
I'm alright
i was resting,sorry
You didn't know...
Since when has her illness been bad?
We were in the habit of not talking to each other about our illness.
I thought it was pointless to talk about illness
we tried to forget it
I can't believe she died suddenly
In the hospital?
She collapsed in her apartment on her way to work
She pushed herself too hard
she was dead when i went there
We promised that when we die, we won't show it to anyone.
A few of us attended her funeral.
It was too lonely
But I think it was what she wanted
She's been here for the past three months, reading your letter.
she looked very happy
I should have come earlier
she never intended to see you again
Why?
If she is going to meet you, I think she went to Tokyo to see you.
The last night she spent with you in Hiroshima was her last.
she ended her life that day
We live as if we don't know when we will die
I think it's really miraculous that we meet someone we've given our hearts to.
it's so dreamy
I'm so glad she finally had a happy day.
I think like that
THE END