Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
We don't have much time, so we'll move on.
The first point
There is a clause that
says the use of nuclear
weapons is necessary for
the defense of Japan in No.11
In this clause, Japan says
Nuclear weapons can be brought in if necessary in the future.
And No12 has the same record.
The second point
About overseas XXX issue
About the region of the mercenaries,
The item whether it is necessary for the operation.
Japan's territory, territorial waters, airspace, and surrounding areas.
We have no choice but to deploy troops overseas.
We've declared it a virtual enemy.
But Isn't it too extreme?
I think there is this criticism
This is a small case we don't use.
But There's something behind this case.
I feel like that
Ok OK don't misunderstand me!
I know how you feel
I know but you should be patient
What? Yes that's it
OK, leave it to you
Hey Ken-san. He doesn't feel guilty about his corruption.
Their parents are very black-hearted.
They're as thick-skinned as the animal rhinoceros.
I have no idea
They are very upset
They have a very short temper.
It's like a little volcano
Hello? this is Social Affairs.
But chief...
Do you feel something strange?
What?
It's hard to break out of a Omura's prison camp.
That's true
Then we should investigate it?
To where?
I'll see what I can find out.
The Omura station said they had no new information.
But we can try
If we're going to do this, we should call in a
specialist.
But Travel expenses will apply.
Suga-Chan,Let's have a drink later
He'll be caught anyway.
But...
Another article on the Japanese conspiracy?
No way
You tend to make for interesting posts these
days.
What will you do,chief?
What?
Never mind
Your work is valuable to us.
What can I do for you?
Reporters these days are unmotivated.
No budget for business travel, they say.
A friend of mine, a union president, put it this
way.
The democratic forces are in the newspapers....
Hey,Gon-Chan
I'll go anyway
To where?
To Omura
Leave the rest work to you
What about travel expenses?
I borrowed it in advance.
Chuo Shimbun Social Affairs Department
I never give up on a case once I'm involved.
What happened if I didn't work for this at this
time.....
This case has gone unsolved.
Mr. Lee was a student at Seoul National
University, a leader of the student movement.
Last year, there was a demonstration
against the Park administration in South Korea.
He was arrested and imprisoned for that demonstration.
But he escaped from prison at the end of last year.
He's been arrested in the past.
Yes
The South Korean government did emergency procedures, but he's still in the
underworld.
And, the 3rd of this month
He smuggled herself to Japan.
He wishes to stay in Japan.
If extradited to Korea, she will be sentenced to
death.
So he escaped and arrived in Japan.
He's on a mission to unite North and
South Korea with Koreans living in Japan.
He speaks Japanese?
He is fluent in Japanese
He said she learn from his father.
He was in Japan for long
So her father takes care of him in Japan
Her father's friend called Kim Yojitsu do Korean
restaurant business in Tokyo
Kim Yojitsu?
Is there any connection between him and the
others?
The police came by once to check it out.
What the police name?
Well...
Well...Uzaki
He is a MPD's SABURO UZAKI
Uzaki?
I haven't heard the name before
I know most of the police's name
Has the head agency contacted you in advance?
No
But I checked his police license card
No problem
Thank you
I will be in main office so let me know when you
finished
He came in the morning of the day he escaped.
I doubt the police
His police license card was real
But you should contact to head police office
about it
I see
Call them
Anyway he escaped that night,right?
He made his escape an hour before night roll
call.
He stole his pistol
But The ball of the pistol was safe.
What the hell!
Uwaaaah!
Move
Right away!
Do it!
OK go
What are you doing? go right now
That driver reported to the police next day
That's why we were late.
Do you have a specific time for carrying
groceries?
Yes 8 pm
So So his escape plan was premeditated?
But He had no contact with the outside world.
Chief! There was no police exist called Uzaki
I was very nervous
He placed his pistol on my side.
Go right now
Did you know where you were going all along?
Yes, he told me the in front of post office in
Higashi head city
Drive fast! Drive fast!
Don't report to police if you don't want to be
killed
Get lost now
What kind of the car?
It was Chevrolet
It was night, so I could see clearly but I'm
sure It was Chevrolet
Yes, I'm sure
There's something at the bottom of this case.
I returned to Tokyo convinced.
Welcome
Thank you for everything
Mr.Kim, can you see this carefully again?
Doesn't he look like your best friend?
He might look a little like him.
Is he really Lee's son?
He didn't come to visit you?
The police have investigated and know it properly
Because the Japanese police are very good
Japanese police trust me
The dish is ready
OK
No 2 table please
But
This young man only knows you in Japan
Hey reporter
He's made a premeditated escape, hasn't he?
Does he tell Japanese officials where he is going?
But what if he really visits you?
I will report to police
There is no choice
The Japanese government is cold towards Koreans.
It also gets in the way of my business
If he comes please let me know before telling the police
I won't make it worse.
I think I can't do it
If he comes
Dishes
OK
Hi
Oh welcome back, how was it?
I'm sorry
You don't have to apologize
It's been hard enough without you.
It was worth the trip.
Really?
For sure
Chief!
There is an editorial meeting
Please talk about this
There are various topics
Then we will work on this
Chief!
How was it?
Our director objected
Our director objected?
Does that mean it's not news?
He said he wanted more reliable data
OK, then I'll work on it
This job has been terminated.
What?
That's what we decided.
No way, wait!
Suga-Chan,It's no use talking to him
Didn't you check Omura's case?
I did it
It's strange
What?
The police aren't moving at all with that
It's like the case has been resolved
So Was Lee arrested?
He was not arrested by Japanese police
So Us army arrested him?
No
So why do Japanese police do nothing?
I think America is involved
They are going to deal with the US-Japan agreement
There's a reason for that.
Damn it
Against the Vietnam War!
U.S. forces get out of Japan!
You have a hard time
How are you?
1 + 1 = not necessarily 2
Do you study philosophy?
I thought you'd been dumped by a woman.
I've been dumped by you all year.
You have never seduced me
Madam?
He is calling you
Yes
Welcome
Please give me whiskey sour
Sure
Another cup
Yes
Do you know her?
The Madam....
Ah
Please call Madam for me
Madam
Thank you very much
What's wrong?
She wants to talk with you
Do you know her?
Kind of
What can I do for you?
Can I work here?
Do you talk about that suddenly?
I have to know your identity
My identity..I'm alone
What work you did?
I worked at a night club
Whereabouts?
Newzabra in Yokohama
You worked in a famous place
Why did you quit your job?
Because I was tempted by American soldiers.
Are you really alone?
I think you are with someone
I can't hire if I have a husband
She doesn't have
I see
I trust you if you know him
what is your name?
I'm Shigeko Noriyama
Please work from tomorrow
Thank you
Please take care of her
Thanks to you
I'm glad I could help you
Let's really get to know each other.
Here's to celebrating your employment!
Chasing her rather than chasing the criminal
I felt like that for a moment
Do you know Uzaki?
It's been a week
Where is here?
Here is not Tokyo
I can hear the sound of the waves, but is here near the sea?
Sorry I can't talk with you
Hi,
Do you enjoy the meal?
Uzaki-san.
You said you'd protect me, but I'm not free.
Here is locked
When can I go out here?
Don't be extravagant.
Eat the meal
What will you do with me?
Of course We want you to work something later
OK,Uzaki
Mr.Lee.
What we want you to do is not difficult
We want you to join a North Korean organization in Japan
A North Korean organization in Japan?
Yes,
They have a strong unity
We can't easily get inside them
You are against the Japan-Korea talks., so I think they trust you
They are also against the Japan-Korea talks
You want me to be spy?
Not a spy but Freedom warrior.
Fight totalitarianism
Who are you?
I am on South Korean side.
I am your friend
Please trust us
But
Don't complain.
We helped you when you were in the camps.
So what do you think?
Ok?
I refuse
You are a patriot of the Republic of Korea
You are against communism,right?
Of course?
Home country is one.
I can't betray my country
I love the whole Korean mass
Oh my god
It can't helped we send you back to Korea if you refuse it
Do you threaten?
We gave you two choices
You cooperate with us or You will either be deported to Korea and sentenced to death.
Damn it!
You deceived me
Don't be mad
I should be sentenced to death
Anyway listen to me
We will give you many rewards if you cooperate with us.
Japanese police will not chase you if we guarantee
You can live as much as you like in Japan
You can marry a young Japanese woman
That makes you happier
You think so?
What do you throw away instead of that happiness
Your hysterical nationalist parents?
There are only things that don't rot
At least it's not life-threatening.
Can you think again
I refuse
You don't have to die because you're still young
Damn it!
Hey
Do you want to offend me
Fuck you
There's nothing you can do.
You're just gonna get hurt.
Wipe your nose, it's bleeding.
I'll give you time so think again
There is no need
I admire your conviction,Mr.Lee
Please enjoy your meal while listening to the
music
Put the music on.
You told me I am like a dog, but not it's your
turn
I never lose
Hey Sally?
The visit of the Korean Foreign Minister to Japan
is on schedule, so our plans are also on schedule.
OK?
I get it
You'll get hurt later.
I still smell like sea
smell like sea?
A sea
Cold and rough sea
I was about to go to Singapore at that time
I was a plotter in the Army.
I was removed from the family register.
I was an imaginary person named Yuichi Fukushima.
To find out about the local anti-Japanese overseas Chinese and their backgrounds.
It was The end of December in 1944.
The ship was sunk shortly after leaving Keelung.
Don't do it
I'll go home
Wait
I have something serious to say.
I have no time, say it
You were too heavy
Sorry for that
Is that your serious saying?
You are tired
Or you think of another things
What the hell?
It's not your business
Hey, can you stop over tonight?
I'll stop over whenever I like
Please listen to me
Please
I don't like it
Can I have your baby?
What?
I want our baby
Your baby
What the hell
Don't act like stupid
I don't want baby
You don't have to be father
You just allow me to birth him/her
I won't allow
What if I did it on my own?
I dump you
I might kill you
to me?
I know you can't kill me
You will ask me to commit suicide
It might be so
You have become to hate me
When I said I love you?
That's not fair
I hate women who are pregnant.
You are cold
You are lair
I'm not
I don't tell a lie much
You are mean
I sometime think so
Who are you on the earth?
I am my shadow in front of you
I'm the lightest shadow.
Get an abortion now.
If you give birth, I will want to kill that
baby.
The baby looks like me
Japan is sex haven
American troops are coming by plane for that
Because there is no god here
Do it right away
There's been another strange incident.
Give me money!
Get out of here!
There was a demonstration against the
visit of the Korean Foreign Minister to Japan.
If they participate in this, they will be paid a per
Diem.
A vagrant was hired.
They used the name of a North Korean organization in
Japan.
People of North Korean descent in Japan are
vicious.
This was a clear provocation.
I hear this was a plan to suppress the North Korean community in
Japan.
I think so
I wonder if this is a plan of South Korean descent in
Japan.
But It was the Japanese who were promoting it.
Not a vagrant in Sanya, of course.
They are not right-wing partner neither
I get it
Please send us again
Hey!
There is a big new from Kyoto
They are advertising to kill Koreans who oppose the Japan-Korea
talks.
They says this propaganda is a hoax on the part of the North
Koreans.
This is too good timing
Visit of Korean Foreign Minister to Japan for Japan-Korea
Talks
Sanya, Kyoto
This is too good timing
This is the work of a third-party conspiracy.
This is the work of a spy?
The Security Treaty employment contract includes a spy employment
contract.
Japanese educated in espionage are protected as intelligence
agents from being followed, investigated, and arrested.
It's stipulated that they can't be caught red-handed and
investigated.
We can't be sure what the spies are doing.
We can
Uzaki who is the Omura Camp Escape Case
If we can track down that fake cop.
Let me take another look at the Omura case.
It's not good
Gon-Chan, let's have a drink tonight
I have to see my wife tonight
You came here early tonight
Because I am lonely
Everyone looks lonely too
We're in a serious recession.
Hi,Madam, you are lovely as usual
You will charge me?
The economy is bad this year.
I agree with your philosophy.
My philosophy?
Something like 1 + 1 = not necessarily 2...
Oh that's it
You are my no.1 student
Let's drink together!
Welcome
She is fine
Give me another glass
You can't go home if you drink too much
I don't mind
I will be with you tonight
With me?
Yes, I found nice Sushi restaurant
We can have sushi and drink there and then....
That's all
OK?
It can't helped
Then I will send you home
How is it?
Sounds good
Welcome
Give me Tennessee
Thanks for coming
Tennessee
I haven't got another glass
I'm sorry
Why you work here without asking me?
I want to think while working
Think what?
You've given up that stupid idea, haven't you?
I'll never see you unless you give up the idea
I get it
Please listen to me after work
I'm done talking about it.
Can we go home together tonight?
I would never sleep with a pregnant woman.
You are mean
I'll come here again
Excuse me
Are you Imura?
You are still boy
I found out you as soon as I enter
It's been a long time to see you
I heard you got into military school.
What do you do now?
I work a reporter
I know
Then you should come to see me
I don't need to see you
You are too bad
Let's have drink tonight
OK?
Give us Tennessee
Yes
Do you come here often?
Yes I am regular customer
I can pay by check and choose the girl I want.
Do you know each other?
He is one of the bad friends
Don't say that.
It's been a long time to see you
He and I grew up together and used to hang out a lot.
I don't think we were good friend
I just did your opponent
Whatever. anyway let's have a toast
He's had this attitude since he was a child.
He was so poor and he was upset with it
Even to me, his closest friend, he didn't show his deepest feelings.
It's because My house may have been rich and happy
You asked me what do I do
I am Intelligence
It's high-level
I see
I have important information now
This will be a great article
Do you want it?
What kind of information is it?
Information about the Northeast Asian Military Alliance
What?
I want it
How much?
I don't want money
You don't want?
But I want information on the left wing from your company
This is a dark deal between you and me
I don't need any other words
Or we maybe fired
He is doing something dangerous
He is spy, yes he looks like spy
It's as if we're both spies.
Well....It's human nature
It's a kind of human desire.
Well..I can't
You can't?
Yeah
Can't you give out information on the left wing?
Kind of
Then I'll give you this woman.
She is pregnant with my baby
But I will dispose of it in the near future
I'll give you this woman so please give me that information
What the hell you are
This is a business
And I think you are into her
Shame on you!
What's wrong, Sugawa-san.
Don't be upset
Please introduce me
I'm leaving now.
I will call you later
So think about it
No...
You should think about it
You'll get greedy.
How bad he is
What's wrong with her?
That man forgot the cigarette case
Let's go for drive
Thank you
You hoped to go with them,right?
I just wanted to get in the way
Did you disappoint?
You are mean
I see, then good bye
Wait wait!
Do you want to play with me tonight?
Forget it
You don't like me so much?
You are stupid
You smell good
Your smell stimulates me like the sea
Are you a sailor?
I'm unemployed person
Here is your dish
I still don't understand why I felt that way
I seem to have been drawn to a strong force
And it's been that way ever since.
What kind of life does he have?
He's unemployed but rich
I've been dating for 2 years but I don't know
He doesn't say anything about the past or the present
He won't even tell me where he lives.
Well..how do you contact him?
I just wait he comes
That's sad
Drink it
Here is your dish
I'm surprised you're okay with that.
I'm not Okay.
I worry always
I am very anxious
He always has a pistol
Isn't he killing someone?
I have a feeling so
You think too much but....
You had better break up with him
Why?
Because it only makes you miserable
But I can't
It was like the wind was blowing in my head
I felt like I was looking into a deep edge
A spy is working in this midnight Tokyo
Day and night, its spies stir the fires of war.
This dog is very healthy.
Just keeping this dog will use my monthly salary
Don't be afraid
He's scary on the outside, but kind on the inside.
Just like me
I heard you have many friends in Korea
I have an old student there
and An acquaintance of the Korean Army's staff era is now a bureaucrat
It seems that you cooperated with the formation of the South Korean economic inspection team this time.
Do you also do business in Korea?
I'm too old for it
I was just asked by the government and the business world
Strengthening South Korea's economy can counter communism
This is the mission of Japan and the United States
You were at During the Pacific War..
It's not the Pacific War but Greater East Asia War
You have opposed the US military
So do you misunderstand me?
My belief is just one
I fight the enemy thoroughly and trust my allies
You know what,America used to be our greatest enemy, but now it's our greatest ally.
By the way
Asian Youth Comrade Association you are teaching
It is rumored that he has been distributing leaflets against the Japan-Korea talks in Yamaya.
Shout up!
Will the Chuo Shimbun publish such a lie article?
I just want to confirm the facts
Shout up!
It's easy to see if the truth is true
Youth Comrade Association cannot oppose the Japan-Korea talks
Why Big Newspapers Hire Reporters Like You
I'm sorry
Are you a visitor?
He is a reporter for the central newspaper
There is nothing I can talk about
Can I ask you one more?
Uzaki and Imura comes here?
I don't know
I don't know because various people come here.
I don't know Uzaki and Imura
I see, thank you very much
What can I do for you?
The boss is waiting at gold club
I'm not good at golf.
Is it an urgent matter?
As you know, the situation in Vietnam is not good.
Anti-American momentum increases and China becomes more and more advantageous
So we need some new ideas to promote Korean morale
We want to talk about that
The reporter mentioned earlier linked the case of Sanya with the Asian Youth Comrade Association.
That will be no problem
Uzaki and Imura are your people, right?
I don't know them
Please stop the music
Do you cooperate with us?
Yes
Please stop the music
Good,you cooperate with us
Stop the music
You're a pain in the ass.
Why are you crying?
Wash your face
Mr.Lee,
Your life will change from today
Listen,
You will be an excellent member of North Korean descent in Japan
You will earn their trust and eventually become an executive.
This is interesting business
Change your cloth,
Let's go
Where are we going?
He is a board member of the Chamber of Commerce and is a new North Korean sect.
You will be his friend
I owe you this
After escaping from Omura camp, say that you earned from a day labor job
Uzaki-san
Tell me what you are.
You just have to work according to my instructions
You don't need to know anything else
I was arrested as a spy for the Japanese army when they lost the war.
But I was hired by the American CIC without any punishment
I didn't care.
It was like a new master came
I had a fake name, a fake adviser.
It was very suitable for me
My destiny is very stupid
Please laugh out loud
That restaurant.
The man is sitting at the cash register
I'm coming with this car so wait for the timing
OK
Welcome
Beer!
Come here
Would you like beers?
Turn yourself in to the police.
And hope to be repatriated to North Korea.
Maybe the Japanese government will send you back to North Korea
I'm sure the North Koreans will warmly welcome you
Mr.Kim, I'll tell the truth
I'm being monitored by a spy agency
I came here at their command
I see
One kalbi.
Please help me
Please calm down
The enemy may be pretending to be a guest
Trust me
I can't betray my country
There is only one motherland.
I have fought for North-South unification
I'm not willing to give up that belief.
I don't betray my country
Two Dishes please
His dish is ready
I get it
I'll be killed
ok
Pretend you're in on it.
I'm told to contact them tomorrow
Tomorrow
Get back
Take this and go to the Osaka branch
There is a person named Sai
You tell the truth to him
Here is money
They may be watching outside.
Get out of the second floor
You can go out to the railroad track from there
It's safe to go over there
You can pick up a car there
I'll never forget what you did for me.
Take care
Help me!
They are murder!
What the hell?
I did what you ordered
You bullshit!
I've bugged everything.
Hi,please wait
Oh Sugawa-san
Were you waiting for Imura?
Please come in
Are you sick?
I'm Ok
You are absent from the bar
How is Imura?
He has not come here since then
Never?
Do you want a cup of tea?
Black tea or coffee or whiskey?
I knew you were going to have a baby.
I'm against it.
I know it's not my business
He needs me
Even if we can't live together
He was so poor as a child that he developed that
personality.
I'm his classmate so I understand how he feels
He was more capable, more human, than I was.
You are very kind
Bring him back to his old self.
I can't
I don't have that kind of power.
I can almost always tell what he does for a
living.
What?
He is a spy
He's part of a larger spy ring.
He's doing something very scary.
I feel scary, What should I do then?
You should run away
From him?
Yes, run away right now
Even if you can't break up with him
You should run away
I will help you
Sugawa-san
Don't laugh
I really love you
You should have locked the door
I was going to see you
Don't tell a lie
Trust me
I've been looking for you about that deal.
You haven't had an abortion yet?
I hate women who get pregnant.
You shouldn't say it in front of him
I think you're jealous of me.
What? What did you say?
I quit the deal
You were the first to say it.
A deal can only be made with even strength.
You and me, it's just my loss.
I don't need you anymore.
Go home right away
You are not the only informant.
Wait!
What do you mean by that?
I'm an employee of a large newspaper
company. I know a lot of secret information.
And I know you are related with Sanya and Kyoto
case
What?
He was definitely upset.
I'm fine with small deals.
I will withhold any information that could be used against
you.
in exchange for it, I want to know about the Uzaki
I don't know how much he know.
I don't know such a person
He's the fake police captain in the Omura prison camp escape
case.
You know him,right?
Go home!
Get in touch with me later
What's wrong?
Your belly is too big.
I give you this
Kill yourself using it
I don't want.
Why you don't kill me?
Shoot me! Shoot me!  It's better if you kill me!
You're interfering with my work.
(In the Osaka Branch of the Korean Association of
Japan)
You are Mr.Lee
Yes
This letter says you'll explain it to me.
So please tell me
Yes
I was a student at Seoul National University,
and I led the June 3rd demonstration.
What you will do to me?
We don't need two Lee Kishuns
We will change your face
In short,You are not Li from now on.
I don't like it!
No!
Whose face do you want him to be?
Hey,Whose face do you want him to be?
Make him look nothing like him.
Keiichi Taguchi, Night High School Student
If your senses are correct, the case will be
solved.
Oh stop here please
Thanks for today
I'm always happy to help, if that's okay with
you.
Thanks
I was on this road that night, as usual.
It was around 10:30, because I didn't want to
make any stops on my way home from school.
10:30
Here it is
I heard screams in here.
I hided here
He said someone kills him?
Yes
He was like help me! I will be killed!
Why you didn't report to police?
I was going to
But there was nothing in the news paper so
But I am curious.
You let us know
Yes
Thanks
Was he this man?
Can't you remember?
It's hard to remember
I couldn't see much because the headlights of the car were
backlit.
I see
About the guy you saw in the driving seat
Yes
Please tell me the man's face in as much detail as possible
I saw the man's face for a moment as he switched back
His face looked a little cold.
Do you know if I show you his picture?
Well....maybe
The car was a foreign car?
That's right, it was Chevrolet
I also saw a few car plates.
Did the Lee kishun come?
I didn't tell you but he came
Did he come?
But soon I kicked him out.
I didn't want to have a relationship with him
I gave him money and got him out
When was it?
It was the day before yesterday
Where he has gone?
Well....I don't know
You are cold
There is no choice.
I have a business here
Let sleeping dogs lie.
Right?
Yes
Did you call me?
Where are you going out lately in the afternoon?
I heard you had a crush on a woman in a bar.
I reported to the director
I heard you investigate Lee kishun case
That case is left to the head office
If you can't do this job, please show us why.
For example, there was external pressure
Don't exaggerate
You're fighting a fantasy that you've created in your head.
I'm not
Unreal things are happening in this Japan
What is that?
For example, the abduction case
Such things are done in Japan, a country governed by law.
We can't overlook it.
Does it have anything to do with Lee kishun?
Yes
There are various problems on the surface
But Lee's escape case,A fake detective named Uzaki who helped with him
Abduction case using Chevrolet
And There is a man involved in the Japan-Korea issue
Assumptions are dangerous.
Don't worry
I'll meet that man tonight
I get clues to these cases from the man
So let me do this job
It will be solved in a little more
I will work on this
If you don't allow me, I'll move to another company.
Wait. that's risky!
His photo?
There's not a single picture of him.
I see
I was angry when I told him to take a picture together
He is weird
Well....
Thank you very much
Wait
What's wrong with him?
Will you use his pic?
Nothing special
Do you want to see him without telling me?
No
Don't do that please
I worry about you
Then will you leave him?
Let me think about it
Let's make this deal simple.
You called me
What do you want?
Tell me all the information about our organization that you know
What is the reward?
I don't know Uzaki
Can I meet your boss?
Do you want to meet my boss?
Who is your boss?
He will not be a public security boss or a cabinet politician
Is he CIA?
Or
Is he a more secret espionage person?
What if you meet my boss?
I want to know the purpose of your espionage
I want to know why you can work freely in Japan
I can't accept your offer
I'll buy your information
Give me a break
I am a newspaper reporter
I am a Japanese newspaper reporter
I want readers to know about your espionage
Don't think about buying with money
I don't want to lose
How can I trade my life for yours when you won't risk yours?
Do you afraid?
You are lying
You are stupid
You have no courage
You are pretending to be strong
You don't understand how I feel
Do you regret?
Are you suffering from what you are doing?
Shout up!
How about our deal?
You sell or not
I say this as an old friend.
You will eventually be killed.
This is the fate of espionage
Now is the time for you to quit this job.
This is the only way you save your life
Wait
Getting out of the organization can be difficult
But the more time that passes, the more difficult it becomes.
Before it's too late
This is my destiny I chose.
Don't order me
Do you understand our friendship?
I get it
You wanted to make a deal because of friendship?
Don't make me laugh
You are a third-rate newspaper
I hate people like you
I never see you
Imura!
Run away,Gon-Chan
Dangerous!
Ok We got it
Did the ship sink?
Where did this come from?
Don't touch it
You can find out if you look up his belongings
Ok I'll find out
Is it a beast?
It is not a beast
What is this?
This is some code
What is that?
This is used to break the code
He is a spy
What is this?
(Drifting corpse of North Korean agent found)
Look
Finished?
OK
Thank you for your time
Has anyone ever performed an autopsy on this person?
Yes
I want to meet him
Sasaki doctor,
He is from news paper agent
Hello
Sorry to disturb you
What can I do for you?
What is the cause of death of that corpse?
I thought he drowned, but he froze to death.
he froze to death?
Yes
It's summer now
It's strange
His blood distribution was abnormal
All his organs were growing
The blood in his heart was higher only to the left
This is a characteristic of freezing death
I see
Do humans change their faces when they die?
The face changes a little.
Do you have anything to do with that corpse?
I think he is this guy
So I've come here from Tokyo
I was disappointed because it was completely different
Who is he?
A man I look for
Thank you very much
Not at all
Do you have a photo of his death?
Yes
His face is not the same person, but we can check his
fingerprints.
It's the same fingerprint.
He is Lee Kishun for sure
But why the different faces?
Oh..They changed it
Welcome
Lee Kishun was dead
What?
Is that really?
Yes
I checked yesterday.
I can't believe it
Why?
It's impossible
Look.
He is Lee Kishun
He is not.
He was not in Niigata
You misunderstand it
I checked his fingerprint.
Are you sure?
Mr.Kim.
You know something. Please tell me
Kishun is in Osaka
He is at his friend's house
He'll let me know if something happen
He is not Lee Kishun
He is a fake
Mr.Kim.
He was killed
Welcome
A spy is trying to get into our organization.
The area around the Osaka branch is filled with their hidden cameras.
I see
To them, our organization looks like a North Korean guerrilla force.
It's misunderstanding
We are only uniting to increase the authority of Koreans in Japan.
Spies always assume war.
They are creating public opinion with their
paranoia.
This is how spy works at present
He went to Niigta? For what?
Can we talk it in front of him?
He knows everything, don't worry
Spy knew Lee Kishun came to Osaka
He feels scary so we tried him back to North
Korea
It is the day the ship is going to sail.
I figured Spy didn't know yet.
What? it's a problem
They are going to infiltrate the North Koreans with
fakes.
Lee Kishun
Are you really Lee Kishun?
Of course I am
Thank you for coming to see me off
He looks like Lee Kishun but he is not.
His voice is different
Is he fake?
Who are you?
I haven't met you in my life
He run away!
Catch him!
Call doctor!
We killed Lee Kishun's fake
But It's very costly to our organization.
It's all your fault
You stupid.
I was just asked to kill Lee Kishun
I have nothing to do with his fake
You think so?
You failed to break him out of the Omura camp and take him in to KIM.
You killed Lee Kishun and You've infiltrated Osaka with his fake.
You think you've succeeded, but someone plucked it out of the air.
Who is it?
Your best friend, Yasuo Sugawa
Sugawa....
Our boss doesn't trust you
We hired you because we heard you were good at what you do.
But our boss doubt you
Let me see boss,Peter
No
Please. I want to explain it
Can you?
I know you often meet with Sugawa lately
Have you notice us?
Did you watch me?
Our boss doesn't trust anyone
This is the rule of Spy activity
Our boss is misunderstanding me
Let me see boss,Peter
Or At least, you understand me
I tried to get information on North Korea from
him.
That's why I see him often
But on the contrary, he's taken our information.
He knows everything what we are doing
Please order what I have to do
You should find the answer on your own
Do I have to kill Sugawa?
He's a reporter for a major newspaper.
I'll manage it anyway
I'm sure I kill him
OK, Make sure you succeed.
Otherwise, you will be in danger.
You understand?
Is that western house?
Could you bring him to our company,Mr.Kim?
It's not safe for two people.
No worry.
I'm just covering them.
But....
Leave it to us.
We will run away if we are in danger
But....
It's even more dangerous to wait here.
Hello? We are from central newspaper
Hello? We are from newspaper
Strange
Let's go backdoor
Hello? We are from central newspaper
Gon-Chan
What is this?
This is a lipstick
This is foreign one
A woman
Careful!
Anyone there
What should we do?
Let's go
Anyone there?
We are from newspaper
Careful!
I'm Ok
We almost caught the spy agency.
They got away just fine.
Don't let you down
Our Director's consulting with the Head Director.
I'm a good photographer.
Taguchi and the people at the Omura camp confirmed that he was
Imura.
I see. Spy is like him
Let me see
He looks good man
Sugawa-kun
Come here
Bring charges against Imura.
What?
Our Head Director said that
Our Head Director said that?
He'd like to help you with your work.
It's little late...
Sugawa?
Wait a min.
Phone call for you
From your girl
Hello? This is Sugawa
Yes, what?
What happened about Imura?
He never come to see you?
Yes but he called me just before
I asked him to come here
He said he will call me later
I'm sorry to disturb you
Hello? Hello?
Please come here right away
OK, I'll go there right away!
Imura said he will break up with her
He is important to us
And she looks panicking
I must take care of it
Hey,wait
Wait,Sugawa
I'll go with you.
You are on their target
No worry.
Let me go alone
What's wrong with you?
Take your seat
What you will do to me?
You
I'll kill you
Stop doing it!
You shout, I pull the trigger.
You said you'll have to talk wit him
Yes...final talk
Why? Because we found out your base?
You know too much of us
Write a suicide note.
You commit suicide because you have trouble
working.
Stop doing it!
Write it!
Do you think I follow you?
If you don't write, I'll kill her too and make it look like a suicide
pact.
Write it if you want to save her
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine
You think you win but you lost
If you bring her into this, you will suffer for the rest of your
life.
She is the only woman who love you in the world
Write it!
Don't push me
I'm a news paper reporter.
It's my job to write.
Let me write slowly
You should give up
There's only one thing I regret.
What is it?
The person I met last will be my best old friend
But He's totally bad guy
You spies are not brave. you are afraid of the world
You don't have spirits
You can't love anyone
Even yourself
The rats are better than you.
But a rat is not a person.
Shout up
You don't like to listen?
Has your heart been broken?
You're stalling for time?
I will wait another 5 mins.
I won't wait anymore
Some people commit suicide without writing a suicide note.
Stop it.
Drop the gun.
Don't do anything stupid.
This is the gun you have me before for my
suicide
Don't move.
Otherwise I shoot him
I'll shoot you if you shoot him
Don't do overdo ,Shigeko-san
Never mind.
I will commit suicide after I shoot him
Wait...
I've always thought about dying with this gun.
so I don't care if I die
I'd be miserable if I lived.
I'd be happier to die with you.
Drop the gun
You are fine now. Leave it to me, and you run
away
You run away, I need to talk with him
That's not good
You are going to...
Stop it!
Shigeko...
Shigeko-san
You can no longer return to the spy agency.
You have no way to live but to return to our
world.
To live? for what?
Wait, Imura!
Imura
Sugawa
Do you see me, Imura?
I can smell the sea.
All has been finished at that time
All leads to the spy agency are now gone.
It was a quick end.
But I'll never give up
The world is moving more and more violently.
I'm in hurry
The united action against the Vietnam War and against the Japan-Korea talks
is
Organizers announced 65,000 people.
The atmosphere in the hall is more heightened than
expected.
The first demonstration team left Hibiya Park at 8:00
a.m.
Thank you, I'll be there soon
I'll go the meeting
Representative Oka's press conference will begin at
9:00.
Thank you
You're having a hard time with your current
problem.
200 Students Clash in Front of US Embassy
The activities of the spy agencies will
intensify.
I will expose them for what they are.
The guys who killed Lee Kishun and others
I'll find out them
Ok I get it, hello?
And then
The END