Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
The difference in height is 11cm so
If he is careless, as you can see
It's like it's coming from above
He lost his balance
In that case, you know
It's his best chance to attack
His right hand struck cleanly
bang-bang!
Are you in?
I'm here
We're missing a member
What do you think?
He is coming here later
Until then, okay?
I haven't done that in a while
Take it for me
Hey master,Another sucker has arrived from Osaka
Tong! Here is it!
I don't know if you're a sucker or a wolf
You're terrible. You're playing with him
Hahahaha
Hey you, If you lost,you pay on your won
Oh dear,Don't be so heartless
You can't just do that
That's how you fooled me the other day
In the world of competition, husband and wife are irrelevant
But you all have one wallet
Hi
Let me join in
You saw our card right?
Hey Misaki!
Hello guest
I will play mah-jongg game
Misaki
Takei-san's father got bald head
But He's been nagging me all day
For what?
You should learn a little from him
I wonder it works or not
Welcome us
We are playing mahjong
Get it!
I've got good cards
You're very strong
You
Wanna play?
You play,Mai
Can you change seat, Asai-san
I'll make coffee
I'll make coffee for you, so you carry on playing
I'm sorry but It's all in the kitchen
How is your business, Asai-san?
Not so bad
This is Maruyama trading company
Is Kitagawa section chief in?
I'm Asai
Oh, Are you Kitagawa-san?
What's the executive director's thinking?
Ah?
Yes
You think it's too early?
Can you do it now? You have the authority
You're using a lot of those now, aren't you?
So, Thank you in advance
See you then
Hey you
What?
You have a wife, and you cheated on me
Who said that to you?
I know all now
Did you talk to the people down there?
A woman has come to see you from Kyoto
You cheated me well
I didn't mean to that
Everyone was laughing downstairs. They said I was stupid.
You can't live in this day and age if you worry about what people say about you
Come here
What is your wife like?
Don't worry, We will divorce
Since when you are being with her?
She's the daughter of the family that took care of me when I was in school
She'd been to music school
You can't simply leave a woman like that.
The daughter of a benefactor...
I've repaid him well
I helped him out of a failed business venture
Where is she living?
She lives in Kasaoka where is outside of Okayama
You are also from there
I will leave her
I feel bad that you're splitting up for me
Because you said you are cheated
I don't want to be that wife
Hello?
Are you Kojima?
I guess we work well with Maruyama trading company
Chief's urging me to do it
I will go there later
You go back?
I must go for our business
Give me my shirt
You come here to sleep with me
Car salesmen are
to find an opening for them
When the new car sells, I'll buy you the one you like
You worry about your wife as I thought
How long are you saying
Your wife is very jealous
I will be back day after tomorrow
Hi Yuki
It's late
You're very easygoing, aren't you?
When did you come?
Just now
Hey you
Get up,Maki is here
You don't have to wake him up
He is sleeping all day
Oh, welcome
I'm sorry to disturb you
Please come in
Yes
How are you going with?
I'm thinking of separete with Asai
Why is that?
I don't want to live like that
I will go out
Make yourself at home
I'm sorry to bother you
Never mind
He goes in and out of sleep
There are no good jobs around here at all
There is no work?
He sells this, you know what is this?
This seems good
It's a fake painting of a famous person
This looks real
He's a fall guy, selling fakes
He is idiot
But you are with him long
What do you like about him?
There is no good or bad. No choice
That's about it
I envy you
You live in a big house and don't have to worry about money
Kind of
It's all thanks to him.
You should be thanking him
It's boring to be bored every day waiting for a man
My body becomes loose
I feel enjoyble when I was working
Hey master
Good evening
It's been a whole
You are with Yuki
How's your business going?
Not so bad
I'm having trouble with our most popular one quitting the store
No customers at all
Hi Master, Look this
ha
There is a stain like this.
Is this going to cost me 3,000 yen?
Take it off if you don't like
Oh...but
Oh...
She doesn't do her job, and all she does is complain
Excuse me
I hate this place. I think I'd rather live in Nio-san
I'm back
You are late.Asai-san is here
I see
This is suvenior for you
Thank you
I'm back
Where have you been?
I thought you have left from me
Hey
You're going to spill beer
I won't let you go home tonight
Mmmm..
Hey stop it
What wrong with you?
Hey
I see. I'm surprised
How could you sleep with him for 16 hours?
Whenever I see my husband , it makes me want a drink.
I guess I feel like into Asai step by step
I guess that's fine
But It's the crime of having driven his wife away.
Hi, come in
Hello, I'm Asai's wife
Hello, How are you? Sorry I am dressed down
You leave
Yes
It's been a whole, Please come in
My husband comes here often?
He did come in half a month ago, but not at all recently
Oh..She's a neighbor. Don't worry about it
Excuse me
Well, you want to leave some massages for Asai-san?
No, that's ok. Sorry to disturb you
Oh I see
I saw your wife's face clearly
She must not know you're here
Women are animalistic
Her sixth sense
It maybe so
You are away from your home for 4 days. You should go home sometime
You're so selfish.
Because you won't let go
I would consider you and your wife together
We should move out here
The people downstairs are noisy and the environment is bad
Right
The only woman who isn't your true love
Drive carefully. It's for sale
I know
Good night
Welcome back home
I'm so tired
The bath is ready
I won't take, I feel I got cold
It seems you are very busy
Make a tea for me
What are you doing hiding from me?
I did nothing, I was away for work in Nagoya
How can you tell such a story?
Well then, that is ok
You don't need to escape
I'll take a bath
You just told me you won't take a bath
I've changed my mind
I've put up with poverty for too long
I've been trying so hard to help you
You're going to say that until you die
I think I've paid my debt to your house well
Well....Don't be self-serving in your logic.
You gave it back or you didn't give it back
You're going to shirk your responsibility
You told my father you wanted me
You asked for it seriously
You're a human being, and you've done this to me
Stop it
You took me away from our home and you married him
I hate that attitude of yours
All is your falut
You are so mean
Where are you going?
Do not be crazy
You are the crazy
Where are you going?
I will chase you forever
Let go! I will go home
You don't have to go home
You can go wherever you want
I will get after you
Your wife is hysterical
She act crazy, she is like that whenever I go home
Men are selfish. You made her that way
You made her that way
I know a lawyer, and I'll get him to intervene
Who is it?
Oh Ayako, Welcome here
Hey you ,Ayako who is our cousin is here
He is Asai
Welcome
Please come in
You have grown a lot
Did you finish high school?
I graduated high school last year
Come in
So both of you are fine?
Yes
Your yonger brother and sister too?
I have six siblings
My brother has been nagging me lately
I heard your grandmother had a bent back
Yes
She is fine
Hey you, our grandmom is 68 years old
She has a long life
Wanna eat toast?
You haven't had breakfast yet, right?
No, I had breakfast on train
I will go to Urawa today.
My errands will be over soon
Let's go to an eel restaurant
That sounds good
Shall we bring her too?
No problem
I thought I will treat you a meal
I like these springs
It's a car that only the president class can drive
It's a great privilege for a salesman to be able to drive a car like this
Here is good.
Here's in the middle of a rice field
I feel like I'm back in the country
She wants to learn dressmaking
Is it right?
Sorry for keeing you wait
It's good to learn dressmaking
When you leave school in Tokyo, you can get a job in the country
She'll work and go to school, but I wonder
if she has a job anywhere
I have no idea
It's hard to work and go to school at the same time
Can we let her live in my house?
Sure
You should ask him too
Please
It's nice to have someone to talk to, too
Mmmmm...
I thought you got married
Do not call me old woman.
I'm still 25 years old
I'm so tired.
I ate a lot of eel
So you are mistress
We will get married later
Our family thinks you get married
Because you ordered a copy of the family register
Don't just stand there, make some tea
You said you will get married
so you will kick Asai's wife out?
Rural areas and Tokyo are different environments
You don't understand what I think of
Hey you, why you plan to go to dressmaking school?
I thought you will get married
I'm not at ease, so I left the home
In your btother's letter
The house of the other person, Mr. Muro
They run a large orchard
Where is the tea?
You can look for them there
You will work with us from now
Why you don't marry him?
I don't like the life in country side
And he's the president of the youth association,
even though he's young, and he's very serious
He is good man. It is hard to find serious man
I'm not into serious man
I want to fall in love and get married
Someone come
Oh
Is Masuko in?
I'm here
Hey Yuki
I though I visited wrong house.
Who is she?
She is a daugher of my brother, Eiko
She didn't want to get married, so she left her home
She wants to learn dressmaking
Asai-san is coming here tonight?
I don't know
What's wrong?
Actually, Aoyagi is going to work
So I want you to let me stay here
I see. What kind of work he will do?
He will cheat a woman
While he was selling fake paintings.
He'd met the daughter of a rich politician
I see
So he will take money from her
Kind of
He's terrible
Finally we will be worst
What are you doing there, Eiko?
You should go to bed
It's ok if you stay here tonight
It's hard to live alone, isn't it?
It's ok if I get used to it
My wide die 5 years ago
Since then, I'm having single life
Don't you get married again?
I enjoy my single life
My father got married 4 times
Current wife is still 23 years old
She is just like my older sister
It's good that your father is being young
My father may be filthy, but I also have a lot of sympathy for him
A man is lonely when he's alone
Me too
I feel lonely
Do I make you feel less lonely?
I didn't mean that
It's ok if I kiss you
Kiss me
You are good at kissing
You can't do more
Why?
Because I won't be able to marry into a good place
A woman still has to get married
I will keep my virgin then
What's wrong with you?
Are you upset?
Can you kiss me again?
Can you?
I am a friend of Asai
As a lawyer, I'm objective
If you want to avoid talking and file a lawsuit,
I'll do that job
I asked her brother to come to Tokyo
You both wanted a clean resolution
There is no clean solution
Close your mouth
There is no need to file a lawsuit
Asai-san has no motivation to live with her
There is divorce paperwork.
Let's talk it out
Yes,
It's just a matter of alimony
I want 10 million yen
Close your mouth
Then I made this kind of paper
Asai said he will pay 1500000yen
He'd like it to be in monthly installments for three years
I am not goods
We want 3 million yen at least
Asai said he can pay 1500000yen at most
I wonder what is the main reason for divorce
Because their personalities don't match
Ah....
Here is nice apartment
How much is for a month?
Ah..let's go outside
To where?
Let's go to Yoshiko's place
To that old man?
It's been a long time to see him,
so Let's go
I'm back
I will go out so Please look after home
If Asai call
tell him I went to Yoshiko's place in Akasaka
I saw a magazin
One couple divorces every seven minutes in Japan
I see...One couple divorces every seven minutes
We will be one of them soon
Now for the first installment of 50,000 yen
Please affix your seal to the receipt
You can put the seal on it
I'll give you all the stuff from my house. You can take it home
Ah.. here it is
Well..that's all for now
Then see you
Hey you
Thank you for taking care of me for a age
(crying)
Stop crying
As I get older, the only thing I enjoy is looking at beautiful women
That's more of a retreat than anything else
You've come to see me, and I'd like to invite you to dinner but
I'm out of money, and this house is my only asset
I have to be stingy now
If my money runs out, my wife runs away
Hahahahahahahaha
Hey Yoshiko
Yes
We have 50 year old wine
Can you serve it to them?
Yes
Hey Yoshiko
The way I'm dressed is disrespectful to my guests
Bring Kimono to me
Yes
Excuse me a minute?
She is a very beautiful woman
She's the most beautiful thing in the world
She is more beautiful than any
Hahahahahahaha
He is crazy for Yoshiko
You did a good job.
I ended up being the poor one
There is a call for you
Are you Masuko?
I've finished the work
I see
You had a hard time, hadn't you?
I didn't want to stay home, so I came outside
Then I will be waiting here
I heard her brother works for the prefectural government
He is very serious
He took me 2 million yen
2 million yen is cheap
She has been with you for 7 years
I have been patient for 7 years
Hey, What are you doing so late
I'm picking up Asai's stuff
Just leave it
Just pack it up and mail it to him
You can throw away what you don't need over there
I can't do that
I don't want to look at his stuff, even his socks
I'll leave them all , then I go home
You should get some rest
Asai is so stupid
He'd been duped by a water girl
Let's toast,Ms
Thank you for your work
Congratulations
But I'll make it clear
It's your turn next
What are you talking about?
Is that so?
Let's get married right away
I will move to your place from tonight
I guess your ex wife's got a grudge against me
I think so. She looked very scary
I feel very fresh now
I couldn't focus on my work
That taught me
Are you sure?
(Station Announcements)
Brother
Wait a minute
Hello?
Yes
This is Asai
Well..Can I talk to his wife?
Who is it?
She says nothing
Hello?
This is Asai
Nice to talk with you
I'm his ex-wife Yuko
Who is it?
I will go home from now
I don't begrudge anyone but
You're the only one I hate
Hey, stop it
From Yuko?
Hey Yuko!
Hey
She is so nasty
She's sarcastic until right before she leaves
I feel scary
Don't worry
Shall we go to hot spring for a change?
That's good idea
Let's get rid of the bad memories
Shall we bring her too?
She have to go to school
I dont have to go shool today,
Just as well, since tomorrow is Sunday
I want to go
What's wrong? You don't eat?
You are good dancer,Eiko
Anyone can do this
You're good for a country girl
How dare you！
What's wrong?
Give me a beer
Let's dance
Hey Let's dance
It's been a long time to dance with you
It's like a honeymoon
I'm glad We could come here
Good night
You should go to bed early
Tomorrow we'll go around Izu and return to Tokyo
Hmm...
Hmmm..
It's good to travel sometime
We can go for traverl sometime
Only us?
Hahahahaha
So we go to bed
Yes
It's warm tonight
Wait wait!
Why you turn off the light?
Because...I'm shy
Are you shy?
I don't think so
It's like we're on our honeymoon
Do you drink whisky?
It's daytime, but I think I'll have a little drink
This is foreign one
This is Britsh too
I see. It must be expensive
I will give you one, Take it home
It's too expensive and I can't taste it
Hahahahaha
Doesn't Eiko hate the man with a blind date?
I don't know why Eiko hate him
His family runs a large orchard
He has a reputation for being serious
I think Eiko hate too serious guy
People laugh at you in the country when you say that
It would be convenient for Eiko to marry into Muro's family
I've been thinking about planting pears in the thicket behind my house
You've been thinking about it
They said they will give us 500,000 yen for the deposit
So you're more dedicated than she is
That's good for her too
They've got 50, 60 million in assets
So you got married?
We've been planning to do that from the beginning,
we just extended it a bit
That's good for you anyway
I'd heard you lived in an apartment,
so I figured it was no big deal
But this place is gorgeous
The rent must be high
It costs 55000yen
What?
55000yen?
How much you spend money in a month?
I spend 100000yen for eating
We spend 15000yen for 7 people
That's a luxury
Rural Fukushima and Tokyo are different
Mr.Asai earn money a lot?
He is not only working as car sells man but also do stock exchange
So brother, when you return him money?
You are already $400,000 in debt.
If the orchard goes well, I'll pay him back
Can I borrow another 100000yen ?
You're brazen
How can you ask for a loan without giving it back?
When Eiko will return from school?
Hey brother
Oh Eiko
What's wrong? Your father is here to pick you up
I don't feel like going home
But your father has come to bring you back
Hello?
Sis...
From your wife
Hello?
Yes she just came here
Um
I will tell her but..
Ok I get it
He will go home by train in the late evening
He said you have to go back right away
I don't like it
You don't go home easily so
Your father might think we're holding you back
I will be back in Tokyo if I return to home
I hear Mr. Muro is a good man
You'd better marry him
You're not responsible for me
I didn't mean that
I'm a distraction
Don't be so backward
Never mind.
I will go home
What the hell is wrong with your life?
Living in a $55,000 apartment is too extravagant
Why don't you move into a 15,000yen room and save up 40,000yen
I don't know how people can live like this
That's normal human life
I don't understand people who save all the time and live in poverty
It's living like that that makes you a bad woman
Hey Dad,You're always borrowing money from him,
and you can't talk shit like that?
I'll be doing a sales play with Mr. Aoyagi
We are not only go around Kyushu
I heard we'll be going as far as southern Kyushu
Go on like it's your honeymoon
So When you depart?
It's tomorrow
So I have a favor of you
20000yen is enough?
I'm sorry I always borrow money from you
Never mind
Here it is
Being woman is boring
Women can be happy or unhappy depending on the man
You are so lucky
You have much luck with men
Hello?
From Kasaoka
Kasaoka?
Asai's ex
Hello? Asai is out now
Hun
Oh right
OK OK I will tell him
What?
Kasaoka?
I send her money every month
I heard your ex wife is kind of dangerous. Why don't you go and help her?
She says so, but she's going to use me
Anyway, I'm out of her life
She might think I don't let you go
So Please go
Why I have to go to help her for you?
That's easy for you to say
Put yourself in my shoes
In her last letter,It says she were so mad
They're putting her in the attic
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
About your ex wife?
She is about to die
She said she wants to see me
I don't know why she is over me
I've talked to the Shokuta company
Oh good
At times like this, business is going the other way
Hum
Men are heartless
There is no choice
A relationship between a man and a woman begins with likes and dislikes
Once you hate him, you can't love him again
That's about it?
Is Asai coming?
Asai...
What did he say?
Mom...
You made a call for me
To Tokyo
Is Asai coming?
Yuko
Did you call him?
I want to meet Asai
Yuko
I believe Asai will come
Please take a rest
That woman...
That woman don't let him come here
Grrrrrr...
Yuko
What are you doing?
Asai..
What happend about Asai?
Let go
Yuko
Asai..
Asai..!!
She is like mad
Yuko
Are you OK, Yuko?
Asai..
Yuko!
Shall we send incense after all?
We should send
They contacted us by telegram
I have no idea.
It's up to you
We'll be able to settle this
We can send 10000yen
You are idiot.
Who can send 10000yen as a incense?
2000yen is enough.
They laugh at us
Who laugh at us.
I think they glad to recieve it
Your ex wife is dead. We have to do that much
Why you are on their side?
I feel bad somehow
You're not as small-minded as you think
Oh, what happend?
I'm back
Anyway come in
What happend?
I have escaped from them
I had a blind date for no choice
My father was wearing a kimono and was very excited
I thought about running away on the way
You're a difficult person
I told him from the start I didn't want to
But...
If you're going to marry, you'd better be serious
I don't want to farm in the country for the rest of my life
Life in the city is hard enough
It looks good, but...
You're living happily ever after
Not as good as you think
So Please let me stay here again
But your brother may angry
Where is grandfater?
He went to Meiji Shrine
I knew Singapore would win
He's at the Meiji Shrine right now
Yes
God's Will
What?
having a baby
Who?
Me
Oh..
What do you mean by Oh
It's 3 month
Grandpa is 64, right?
His ability is 55,6
Are you sure it's Grandpa's?
You are excuse
It's really his baby
I can only date one of him
I can't cheat him
You did it good
If anything should happen to Grandpa...
Of course people are going to kick me out
I was so serious
I can have a baby and live there
So I did my best
I wonder if I make a baby
Good
The only way to make a living here is to have baby
This is the best way
But you're no longer able to bear children
Yes true
I don't know if I can do that once
I will talk about it to my doctor
You might be able to manage
Leave it to you
Serve me a beer
Sure
Good taste
Wanna have a drink?
I can't drink
Are you drinking?
Yes, You want to drink?
I want
I think I'm thinking of having a baby
It's good right?
It's ok but can you?
I talked with Yoshiko
I went there because there's a good doctor
Oh right
I've heard that once you can't have a baby, it's impossible
According to the doctor
She said if I stay in the hospital for half a month, I'll be able to give birth
So I begged her
It works well?
You can use bath, Eiko
Sorry to bother you so late at night
Is this Asai's residence?
Yes we are
I'm Muro from Fukushima
Sorry for the sudden visit
Is Eiko Yoshioka here?
Who was it?
Eiko's marriage partner
Why he visited us so late at night
He came directly from Fukushima.
He wanted to see Eiko
Tell him she is not here
I can't do that
He talked my brother then came here
There is no choice.
It's not my business
I'm in trouble too
You can refuse politely
Eiko also does not like him
Mr Muro visit us
Tell him I'm not here
He knows that's a lie
I don't care if it's a lie
I don't want to see him
It's rude to visit a place like this
Sorry to bother you so late at night
I'm planning on taking the last train home tonight
I know it's rude of me, but I had to visit
Is Eiko here?
I'm sorry but
She is absent now
She said she stays at classmate's home tonight
I see
She is not here
I'm sorry that I couldn't help you, even though you took the time to come
Then
I'm sorry to have to say this
I"m thinking of getting married with her
Your father gave me permission to do so
Do you know about that?
Yes I have heard about that
When she came home
We had a blind date
She came here before I heard back from her
I can't give up
so I have come here
When she back home tomorrow, I will tell her about that
Please go home tonight
Yes
I will tell her to write a letter for you
Well...not a letter but I want to see her in real
Please come back another day
Well...Would you ask her about our mariage?
It depends on how she feels
Yes..
atchoo!
Who is it?
I got you some sherbet
Every day I do this, I feel like a sick person
Ah...
Melon too
When I visited Asai's shop just before
He was just in Kanda
He bought this at Sudacho
Mmmmm...
He goes home every night?
Yes he leaves home in the early morning
Umm...I feel very pain
I don't want to see the doctor every day
They're going to make it possible for you to have a baby,
so you have to be patient
Yes that's right but...
Mr.Muro has asked you again?
I got a letter from him
I feel very weird
It was like a love letter
He is really loving you
People like that will take care of you very well
I don't like
Shall I cut the melon?
I'll have it later so don't worry
OK
Then I'll make it cool
I hate the sound of this crow
Hey you, how long will it take for?
I guess 4 or 5 days more
I miss home day by day
I put the curtains in the wash
I'll clean up your room until you get back
Eiko
What?
You're all tense. What's wrong?
You think so?
Asai always carries a dirty handkerchief in his pocket
You need to take care of it
Ok I will
Thank you
I will see you again
I'm home
Welcome back
I had a dinner already
Would you like coffee or tea?
I'll have a beer after shower
Was Masuko ok?
She said she returns in 4 or 5 days
Come here with me
Hey, come on
Stop it
Never mind
You said you'd only do it once
It's same once or twice
You are very cute
I feel bad for my sister
This is bad
You're a thief
How can you do this
What do you mean by that?
I'll kill you
Stop it! You are crazy
You made me crazy
You're a thief cat
Hey you
What do you want from me?
I don't know what I can..
Not a particularly close relationship
If you want to just play
find another girl
It's bad you slept with Eiko
I'm sorry
I apologize for that
I didn't think you were
When she came to the hospital,
she was acting strange
When I returned home, then..
Hey
What you willo do?
By the looks of it, she's not going anywhere
I was very sorry, Sis
Sorry doesn't cut it
Because Asai-san forced me
You were into that
If you really don't like it, bite your tongue off and die
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
Leave our home tomorrow
Find a boarding house nearby
Move there
I didn't think she'd do something like that
I can't trust anyone now
She is cute girl so
A man like Asai tend to like her
I had bad luck
I took him from ex wife, now other girl took him
Hey, that man called Muro
The Youth Chairman who love Eiko
You shoud match make them
But Eiko hate him
You should manage it
If you blackmail her into marrying him
If you don't, she'll take Asai-san
You think so?
Pull yourself together
Between a man and a woman,
the one who is vague loses
Be positive for everything
I dont feel like doing it
How is your health now?
Can you have baby now?
The doctor says I'm ok
Look, I am like this now
Sometime he moves
This is good
Eiko does not like you so much
How can I say...I remeber that
She's been afraid of marriage since she was a child
But she can feel calm and rediscover herself now
I think she is ready for marrige now
Thank you for everything
Please talk with her about something
Yes, I get it
Oh my god
She saw us doing flirting
Hahahaha but
Having sex with your wife's niece is indiscreet
You are right but
She teased me when we were at home
Hey, she has come
Can you serve me a juice?
How's the boarding house?
Mr. Muro came to see me today
Your wife invited him
I see. He came
I'm sure you know that
You talked with her then invited him
Masuko really wanted to invite him
I'm already a distraction
I didn't mean that,Eiko
Why you don't see me at boarding house?
I will be in big trouble if she knows
She put me out of her way
From now
Your wife and Mr.Muro and I are supposed to meet at Ginza
I see
Then I will take you there
Don't worry, I will catch a cab
By cab?
We are over...
Bill please
Recently, rural areas have been modernized
We are willing to adopt new methods
Especially orchard management
requires scientific cultivation methods
Our young farmers form study group
I see. You have a hard time
I'm thinking of going to California next year for a field trip
He is good man,Eiko
You can go with him
Shall we go together?
I here it is dry weather there
Yes,It's a good climate for growing oranges
It's very humid here, so cultivation requires a lot of skill
Anyway please drink
Thank you
What you will do?
You should reply him
I still don't like
I don't want to marry with him
He is very good and serious man
It's not every day you meet someone that nice
I decide my life on my own
I'm telling you straight, just for your benefit
just for your benefit
Because I'm in the way, right?
You plan to take Asai from me
No!
True!
You want to rob Asai from me
You too
You robbed Asai from ex his wife
I didn't rob!
He came to love me
Me too
What the hell!
Sis...
I...
I'm not like a doll
I won't obey you
I'll do whatever I want
Are you going to be my love rival?
Yes I will
Let go
I'm gonna strangle you
I can't breath!
Let go!
Kill you!
Remember what I say, Eiko
If you took Asai from me
I will kill you
You marry him!
You understand?
If you do not follow me
Don’t you dare!
You understand?
You get it?
I was finally relieved
I felt a weight lifted off my shoulders
I was relieved to save face
How about holding their wedding in Tokyo?
That's good.
Let's do it in a fancy place like the Imperial Hotel
That's a good idea!
I'm sure she will be glad
It's more presentable and easier to manage
Leaving from Tokyo Station on their honeymoon is also a good way to make theirself presentable to people in the countryside
Try to find a good wedding venue
Yes I will do it right away
The earlier the better?
Yes Let's get this done while she's still in the mood
Mr. Muro is easily available
It's all thanks to you
Local sales is tough
I once slept in a farmer's shack
But you earned it, right?
We only made enough money to buy a ticket from Kagoshima to Tokyo
That's the way it is
How is Aoyagi doing?
He said we go to sell in Hokkaido
There's no point in struggling to stay in business
if you can't make money
You should separate from him
I've thought about leaving him many times before
But I couldn't
I like to be with such a man
Woman can't live alone
You think so?
You should keep Asai-san firmly
It's hard to keep man more than I thought
He has no relationship with Eiko?
I have no idea
Five more days to clean up.
I don't care if a few things go wrong
Hello? It's Eiko speaking
I want to see you for a short time
I'm in Shibuya now
Can you come to see me?
Just a little bit is enough
Hey, can you take me to somewhere for saying goodbye?
I'm on work, I can't travel far
I will get married soon
I want to say good bye to you
I will follow as everyone say
So can you do that?
You are bad girl
You seduced me
Follow me
Look.She's a great bride
You can't do that in a country beauty parlor
It's so wonderful
You are amazing.
You're magnificent
So Shall we go?
Are you going to go straight to the venue?
I don't want to keep them waiting. Let's get a move on
(The special express train for Nagoya will be departing from platform 15 shortly)
(Please stay back outside the white line)
Yes
Then see you
You want to eat something?
I don't want
I'm so tired
Shall I prepare a bath?
Don't worry
Shall will go to bed?
I will make a cup of hot tea for you
Hi,Your tea is ready
We've had our problems,
but she's going to be a good wife
It might be so
It's good to hold wedding
Shall we hold a wedding too?
That's sound good
It might be a good idea for us to prepare each other
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Yes
Finish