Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Teppo inu / Gun Dog (1965)
(Inu/Dog Series #5)
Decide which one you will go with.
Hey come on!
I lost all my money. I can't go back to Osaka.
Are you also from Osaka?
What's wrong?
I miss them.
Take this.
I don't borrow money at gambling places.
Kodama bro
The president is calling you
Thank you for your work.
Take this.
Leave me alone.
I'll do something about it
But I have no money...
Wait!
Dude!
Get it together!
You're the man I was talking to earlier.
Your arms are slipping
and your legs are getting scratched,
If I hadn't come, you wouldn't have moved.
I'm sorry
If I had just held a pistol, I wouldn't have lost to them
Why were they targeting you?
Please don't ask, okay?
Bro
Could you deliver this to Osaka for me?
300,000yen with the airplane...
I don't want to be the one carrying the money
Don't get me wrong.
My mother is sick and I want to send this to her.
It's better for you to show your filial piety yourself.
It can't be helped.
Ok, I'll take it
It's all right
Good evening
Are you really going back tomorrow?
Yes,I'll miss you.
I feel lonely without you, brother
Hey come on.
Listen
I'm finally taking you to Osaka
Really?
I'm really happy
If only you could enter here
Hey
It's a pistol!
Don’t do that.
Finally, I am in Osaka,
Welcome.
Hey old man, come here for a second
Are you going to order something?
Old man,there was something like this
in the pork soup.
This is Petrao's pork
You hit the jackpot!
Isn't this a red dog?
Just kidding, right?
That's not a dog
That's a cat, a cat.
Cat?
Do you think You can drink without money?
This person has really messed up!
If you're human,
then this guy is also human, not a monkey
You shouldn't be bossy
Are you a police?
Is that bad?
Kamoi, did you forget that I have eyes on my back?
It's been a while since you returned from Kyushu
Well, just a moment ago.
How did you know?
What did you come back here to do?
It's none of your business.
If you don't say that, you're homeless and we will protect you.
You're annyoing.
You're like a tax collector.
You should stop gambling.
If I don't do this, I can't eat.
If there is evidence,we can be arrested for gambling even if you are not caught in the act.
You understand, right?
There are many such people
You shouldn't be bossy.
It's like those who buy betting
tickets for horse racing or bicycle racing
Everyone here is a culprit in this, right?
Moreover, It's run by the government
Don't get in the way of my work.
Please crack down on them first
I'm just a small part of the prize money here
What do you think?
See you later.
Oh where is it?
Where's my river's Boston bag?
Don't you know?
I left my bag here
A bag? I don't know about any bag
You blackmail me?
you know anything?
No.
What are you doing?
Oh my god.
I'm here.
What are you going to do with me?
Oh it's a pistol
I'll take it
You are stupid.
Please pay me the fee.
I don't want to do that for free
Are you really thinking of going against our gang?
Bro
brother! Wait for me!
Give it back.
You're so annoying!
Oh you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's none of your business.
See you later.
Hey, wait a minute
What?
I guess I'll have to get your body check
Ok come on
If anything comes out, I'll treat you to a meal.
See, that's not it
You're really something, aren't you?
Well...
Here?
Oh here.
I'm glad I left this alone
Is this the Kodama family's house, right?
Yes
Are you his sister?
I'm glad to hear that
I brought this from your brother in Kyushu
Really?
Yes.
Who?
He's my brother's friend
I am Kamoi,
Nice to meet you
Well, please come in
Is he fine?
He's fine in Kyushu
Oh, is that so?
Is Kazuo in Kishu?
Not Kishu
Um, 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,
Kyushu
He's in Kyukanbetsu?
You don't understand....
I heard that my brother is in Kyushu
Oh, what is he doing there?
He's a site supervisor
Like this
Oh, is that so?
Are you his subordinate?
Yeah,I'm in his care.
Well, I should leave...
Um, I'm looking for something.
Excuse me.
You
What did you do?
Take a look at your feet
I have received money from him
Money
Money?
Did he give money with you?
Yeah
I see
He knows I have nerve pain that limits my mobility.
Make a tea for him.
please, don't mind me,
that's quite alright
Ok I get it
You can hear well now
Excuse me.
Wait.
I still haven't heard Kazuo's story,
Have a seat
I'm off
It's noisy if I'm late
Be careful going
So, where do you work?
She works at a car dealership
She is on the night shift today.
I get it.
Take care.
Wait.
I still haven't heard Kazuo's story,
Hey!
He ran away
Thank you for waiting for me
I wonder if my brother is doing well
Ah, he's doing well
You should have gone earlier, you know
Go.
Why did you want to meet
Kodama's sister?
Didn't you get in touch?
Don't you know 16 group?
16 group?
That's a name like a pawn shop
If you didn't know that, are you going to take a fine or hit me?
You talk too much, you brat
Why did you go to Kodama's apartment?
I just went to see his mother's illness
That's a lie
If you know it's a lie, don't ask
What did you say?
You're just messing around
This kid!
Remember and notice!
You're in the way!
Is boss here?
What's wrong?
A stranger is messing around
What's his name?
I don't know
I think he was asked by Kodama.
Take your eyes off that guy,
you might just become the target
Make sure to watch closely. if you don't, you won't do anything at all
Hey brother, are you
looking for something
Yes
That must be a pistol.
Don’t shout so loud,
Do you understand?
Yes
That's good.
Hey brother,
don't bet another 100 yen
I have no choice but to pay it.
Where is it?
it's to the east
East? It's over there
Where around there?
Well, if it's close, from Janjan Yokocho in Shinsekai
Nagoya, Tokyo, Hawaii, America,
Hey come on
Is that the pistol?
It might actually hit something
I can't tell anyone,
what should we do?
I have to make that
where's the guy with the pistol?
Oh police!
I am not.
I'm looking for that pistol
What the hell, are you
buying the pistol I made?
Are you stupid?
How can I pay for a water gun
with a sword?
What I'm looking for is, if I may
say, an important cultural asset!
It's on a different level!
Ugh, it stinks, but I wonder
what that guy is doing right now...
Come on
Shot! Three! Five!
It's so noisy
I'm not dealing with this here,
what are you talking about?
Come on,
Which one?
I'll bid this
6 and 7
Damn it.
Which one?
Hey, guy
No matter how small it is,
I won't forgive a fraud!
What you're doing is...
It's an old trick from long ago!
You're the one who's going to pull this scam!
I am in the 16 group!
Don't you forget it!
Just stop it, just stop it!
You all are also to blame for this painful situation
What do you mean by that?
We talked about it with a 10-yen coin
Now, try using a 100-yen coin
It's a one-way ticket
to the heaven
Let's do something more
there's no way I'm doing that again
What is this big brother doing?
Are you reedy?
What are you doing?
Shut up!
He's controlling it!
I just flicked the light switch a bit, hmm,
Welcome.
Oh you are working here
What kind of relationship does your brother and the 16th group?
My brother has nothing to do with that
Wait a minute
Why do you run away when you hear about the 16th group?
It has nothing to do with you
You're the guy from the 16th group last night?
You have a private car
Isn't it amazing how the money from day labor turns into a car
What?
What do you think?
How about making it bigger by playing Clasico?
What?
Wait
Here's not good to do that.
Get out from here
It's a magnificent new car, a new car!
Oh Tei-chan
Oh you
when did you come out?
I arrived last night
Did you arrive alone last night?
No.
I was with the man you treated.
His name is Kodama
My brother
Come here for a second
Don't shout too loud!
This person is Kodama's younger sister
She's a beautiful woman
So, what about my brother?
At Hiroshima station, you know
He got me a oyster lunch box.
It was even more delicious than I expected
I didn't hear anything like that
Hey, where was he going?
Kodama is either in Tokyo or Nagoya,
so don't interrupt the conversation! Just focus on your own thoughts
I wanna hit you.
How did  brother get hurt?
it's not serious, so don't worry about it
Well, where did that guy disappear to?
Hey, what are you doing standing there,
Big brother!
What's up?
Kodama is saying he's going home
What?
A woman who came from Hakata said she was with Kodama
Who is Kodama?
What is that outfit?
I was racing
You are stupid.
Kodama was originally an accomplice in
the bicycle racing operations of this group
He might mess up a little
We sent him to the Kyushu group, but he blackmailed 300,000 yen from the president
I'll make up for it
I handed him over with the promise that he wouldn't return from Kyushu
We tried to clean up after that, but he escapes and will start moving behind us
If cheating in Keirin is exposed, it will be a problem for us.
The police must be investigating us.
He's good at shooting
Isn't he aiming for the president?
I know that
By the way A guy who is a friend of Kodama
We have to use Kamoi Daisuke, a free shooter
Free?
He crashed Shishido, Daiko, Gamou
He's skillful
Which one we need to kill?
Blackmail Kamoi first
and ask where Kodama is
Brother, are you really coming over?
I can come over, but what are you doing?
That Tsukamoto Shoko's BG
It's turned out pretty good, hasn't it?
You know Tsukamoto Shoko?
Yeah, that neighborhood
OK I'm coming over.
Come on over now
I can't go right now because
I'm looking for something
For what?
Hey, that Boston bag was missing
Well then, The pistol is in the bag?
You should hurry up and get to work
Are you coming over?
Yes
Promise me
See you
Don't you have eyes in front?
I was sleeping and walk
Don't wake me up
You're still as stubborn as ever
There's something on your back
Is that a noodle?
You always eat udon, don't you?
Udon is the easiest to digest for me.
16 group?
How do you know that?
Well...
16 group is
They manage cabaret, Turkish baths, and other tourism businesses under the name of Tsukamoto trading company
The reality is that it is the center of an organization involved in, violence, bribery, horse racing fraud, and bicycle racing  fraud
They have a lot of power throughout the Kansai region
He is the one among the many victim
I know that Alcoholics
He's Hayakawa
He is a former racer
He had no money so he cooperated with 16 groups.
Won't you arrest the mastermind?
They are clever at doing evil things.
Just eating udon all the time won't let you escape easily
They keep their fraud a secret from the government.
They show the racers a fake list.
The racers feel comfortable cooperating with them.
But this is the trap
when th incident was exposed
The racers has disappeared from that area
This is how it works
There are also rumors that a guy used by them was sent to places like Kyushu
I guess that kind of sound will eventually be silenced
An accident of unknown cause
Moreover, it seems that there are two
or three cases of unexplained incidents
What are you going to do about that?
Oh it is your job.
Well, you should raise your salary, you know
Ah, that was delicious. By the way,
Wait
I won't treat you
Just pay your share, or you'll get arrested
You are still as exaggerated
as ever
It can't be helped.
Take care of this
Goodbye
Don't be ridiculous
You're going to make the store lose money,
You really are
an overly inquisitive person
What are you planning to do after drinking the customer's leftover sake? If you want it, just say you want it
Say it if you want it;
I want
this is not okay
This is mine.
If you want it,
you should pay taxes on it
This is not acceptable. Why would you do something so dirty?
You know, everyone pays taxes like I do, right?
Don't say things like that,
You're so annoying
Get him out
Forgive him
Oh you, I'm sorry
Thanks
You shouldn't act like a homeless person.
You were good bike racer
I can't forget that man's face
Police are investigating bicycle racing fraud
We've got a lead and we'll find it ourselves.
I'll find him and catch him myself.
I'm worried about your body, Hayakawa
Thanks.
You won't be able to find him in that condition.
Sorry.
Brother, visit me
Can I see your fortune?
should I let you see the person being questioned?
Please, please,
Have you been dumped by a woman?
I'm looking for a man.
This is quite funny
Are you going to come with us or Do you want to have surgery on your stomach?
My appendix is ​​more inside
Hey.
I should have my pistol
What are you going to do with us?
I would forget it! I’ll leave it to the doctor
I'll pay it later.
If you tell someone about this, starting tomorrow, you won't do this business.
You are really tough.
What do you think? A guy with guts
He has guts
He won't give up
You can't take it anymore
That's because it's a living body, isn't it?
Just one word
Tell us where you gonna meet with Kodama in Osaka
We'll release you
I'm looking for something
If I find that, I will came to see you.
A woman?
You are stupid.
That's a pistol I made.
The feel of it is great
Someone took it in Osaka
Bro
What?
It's true that he says.
Kuroko takes that,
You have it?
I am hiding it
in the roof of my apartment
You are stupid.
Why aren't you delivering it to boss?
Sorry.
I'm going to see our boss
Watch on him.
Damn it.
Oh shit.
Take 2 or 3
If the monk comes, what will happen?
The monk is here
You're so noisy, you pig! Huh?
You lose it
Try it again
Hey
Leave it to me.
What?
Open your mouth.
It hurts me.
You're stupid brad
From now on, You scream and I'll cut you
What's the hell?
So this is what Kamoi has?
huh? you got something good
Mitsuko, let him drink.
Will you work?
First, kill Hayakawa who was racer
He knows the fraud we do
That's all?
Of course, You have to kill Kodama too
By Kamoi's pistol
Kamoi becomes the culprit
that's how it is
Release Kamoi
Make him free
It's obvious that he'll get in touch with Kodama somewhere
Damn it.
Ok I won
Next
Once more.
I want my money back
The world of competition is tough, so come on,
Damn it.
Once more.
It can't be helped.
It's a shirt, a shirt
here we go!
This is your last chance, you know
I get it
Hurry up
So which one should I choose?
Is it this one?
You're staying calm
Are you drinking this?
It's a drink for woman
what?
It's for kids, isn't it?
Why not do it straight?
Alright!
I'm going to shove this one down your throat!
You bastard!
It hurts me.
Don't move!
Your eyes get better?
What?
Hold on.
I'm glad it saved us time
Kamoi
Sorry to misunderstand you
Forget it
I'm keeping your stolen pistol. Sorry
Don't say sorry
You did something nice.
Let me try it
He can't do anything with it
Let me try it.
Give it to him
What?
It's bad
It's okay.
Are you sure?
Leave it to me
It can't be helped.
Thank you very much.
It was just practice
Look at this.
Take it.
Once more
Open and fire.
Open!
Fire.
I want to challenge you with my pistol
Hey, sorry to intrude...
but, Tsuru-chan,
Cherry
So, Cherry-han?
I thought you were a Tsukamoto training company employee.
You're working at sex industry
Don't fool me.
I shouldn't be joking about anything
This place is run by Tsukamoto Training Company.
I work here so I'm a bath girl.
You hit me.
You were very hurt
Don't worry.
Who attacked you?
At the Columbia university of America
I've never heard of it
I'm starting to say it too,
but this is how it is, hey
You have a nice figure.
My hips and bust are internationally top-notch
Your height is pure Japanese style
but I've got a good balance going on
Yeah, you've got a solid balance horizontally
and that mole on your butt
This is fake.
Brother, please remove my mole
I really want to help you, but I' can't move.
You have no choice but to take it yourself
How?
I want you to rub it with the clay feet on that sheet
Hey, if you say something cool,
I'm feeling hot.
Turn it off.
Oh no. I took it out.
What now! Huh? What should I do
It's hot.
It's hot!
Can't you do something about this?
Take it out
Hurry up
and take it off!
Oh no. I took it out again.
I don't know what to do
It's hot!
Get it together!
Teruko, phone call.
This is Teruko on the phone
Bro.
where are you right now?
Don't get close to the apartment, okay?
I thought it was a call from your brother, wasn't it?
No, it was not
Then who was it from?
Oh,was it from Daisuke Kamoi?
You should be careful, that guy might end up being a problem later
He'll hand your brother over to the police.
He?
Yeah.
Ready?
Do you want your shoes polished?
Left.
That's enough.
You
Wait.
Wait!
It's dangerous for a woman to walk alone around here, you know?
Come on,
you should go home,I can't work
My boss gets mad at me
What's the hell?
I can't stay here any longer.
Leave from here.
What's wrong? Hey, what's going on? What's wrong?
Get it together.
Are you alright?
What's wrong?
I've seen you somewhere.
You're the alcoholic man.
I saw
I found it
What did you see?
Mikitai....
You don't have to talk much
Bring him out
I'm just a witness, don't keep me waiting
How's him?
A pistol bullet hit him in the heart.
This medallion ended up in his pocket, so he was saved.
This is a very good pistol.
Without this he would have died
Kamoi
Have you seen this?
I have no idea.
but I can smell of you
I can smell alcohol,
I think you have a stuffy nose.
What happened to that handmade pistol?
I threw it away a long time ago
I think I'll need to give you a little physical examination
That's not good
Won't you arrest me?
Chief?
The surgery went well
So, what about the witness statement?
I'll take care of it.
Hayakawa found the man who lured him into a scam.
He was shot with a pistol while trying to capture him.
So, this is a strategy of a certain organization.
A certain organization?
Yeah
This is the quickest way to find out where this pistol came from.
You know, should I also cooperate with the investigation?
This is quite a different attitude from during the day
What made you change?
Kamoi
Well then, I'll try to cooperate with you
I think you feel very encouraged
There is no need to cooperate
This physical evidence is enough
An unexpected person may be the culprit
That's part of the fun part of police work.
That is my pistol
A certain organization?
He gave me a hint
Kazuo hasn't called me about anything.
What happened to him?
He called my working place.
Really?
Where is he now?
He works on construction in Takayama.
He seems to be very busy.
I see.
Why didn't you tell me about it sooner?
I need Sake
You should drink beer.
I am a customer
You shouldn't come to a place like this
I'll be back soon.
Wait.
Why did you come to Osaka?
I'll kill Tsukamoto
I will compete with him
Will he accept the challenge?
If not, I will expose the cheating in Keirin.
I want to eliminate that group.
You'd better fight with him.
You will be killed by them.
You will also be arrested
I hear you have ties to the police.
Are you going to hand me over to the police?
Am I ? Don't call me an idiot,
Don't do unnecessarily
I'll make sure to kill Tsukamoto
You are stupid.
You are very selfish.
What about your mother and sister?
You shouldn't worry your parents.
So, you think about that question and left it to me
so just leave me alone
Kodama
Well, unfortunately, the
president is currently on a trip
I am Komae, the secretary section chief,
I see you are the secretary section chief
Let's put the past aside for now
16 Group has just been reborn
as Tsukamoto Commerce
and is running a completely honest business,
as you can see with our Turkish bath tourism project
By the way, where is the president traveling to?
It's the usual place, of course
It's sudden, but I always get in touch from the destination
I haven't received a call from him yet.
If you still have any doubts at this point,
please feel free to bring the Search warrant
or whatever you need to do
I mean, you don't even think about a handgun, do you?
please contact the police station
once the president returns
I apologize for the intrusion
This is the result of you messing up with Hayakawa
Take Kodama out in one shot
For Kamoi, let it flow for now.
Oh,16 group.
If the air is bad, the food tastes bad.
Get out
Where's Kodama?
What are you talking about?
We have the evidence.
If it's pepper, I have it
You bastard!
Hold on.
You sometimes keep in touch with Kodama's sister.
Kodama's younger sister?
She's saying so.
What is she saying? You let me walk free
You were waiting for me to contact Kodama.
This is our territory
Hey Kamoi.
you'll owe me a favor? Alright,
I don't really like selling favors, though
But if it's about buying, I like that
Don't you forget it!
I tried going there once
What about the inn, brother?
Mom? She's definitely not in good condition.
What? You have something to give me?
Memo?
He has come again
Were you on the phone with your brother?
From where?
No.
Your brother trusted me and brought me the money.
I made it.
He trusted me.
Please tell me where he is.
I can let your mother meet your brother.
I understand why your brother was expelled from Osaka.
If he continues like this he will become a big problem
This is for him
You are also a member of Group 16
What the heck is that?
Am I saying a lie?
That's a misunderstanding,
It's a misunderstanding
This is the second floor, isn't it?
I'm not saying like that
She's misunderstanding
who is she?
It doesn't matter who
It's frustrating, isn't it?
Cut it out
If I do that, my back hurts a lot.
Hey bro.
Can you hear my heartbeat?
Yeah, I can hear it, it’s normal
How does it feel?
Please say a kind word to me
it feels like being crushed under a dump truck,
I hate it, I hate it
Don't say something so off-base
Alright, alright, I got it then
Shall I say something dramatic?
I'm happy
Sorry
I'll have bad dream tonight.
Who?
Are you Kazuo Kodama?
I came here at 16 group’s request.
but I won't take even your life
Don't worry.
An-san
Wow, You're doing me a service too
Until you come to love me
How?
Don't mess with me!
Wow, Mama,
wow, you're so beautiful!
I'd like to get another massage
Come on.
There was a call for Kamoi-san
Huh? From whom?
The person said "Kodama" who was waiting at the apartment
Woman?
No, it was a man.
Let me get out.
Hurry up.
Brother!
Please don't tell mother
Hey.
You're here.
Hey, it's Kodama?
How about my mom?
Don't worry, I haven't told your mother anything
If we find out about the defect in the surveillance device, will you come to the station?
I have various things I want to ask you
He came all the way here
because my brother wanted to see our mother
Kamoi! You come too
Don't act like you're superior even though your salary is low
My brother moved to Kyushu without permission
She must be an acquaintance of the 16 group.
So?
My mother didn't notice,
but I was aware
I also noticed that he was associating with delinquent friends after leaving his job
But even in such times, my brother was thoughtful of our mother,
buying various things with part of his salary and bringing them home to send to her
So you are worried about your brother's behavior
You've moved to the current apartment with our mother
He should have turned himself in.
Isn't it pointless to say things that can't be helped by the police?
Kamoi.
That was fired from your pistol in the past
it's nostalgic
but no,
that's not it either.
This was the bullet that killed Kazuo Kodama
Wow, that was a perfect match!
Kamoi.
It look nice!
It's yours.
You shot my brother....
Please wait
I didn't.
Trust me.
I understand
You were keeping an eye on my brother
You didn't want to let me meet my brother
Please wait
What are you talking about? Do you think I would do something like that?
I was thinking of introducing you to your brother,
but that's a lie
It's a lie
It's a misunderstanding, and I don't know about that;
I have no idea
Here's the evidence
Well, listen up
I returned to Osaka and delivered the 300,000 yen
I received from Kodama to you all
No, no, before that at Daiyasuya, I met you
My Boston bag containing a pistol was stolen at that store.
Moreover I helped him in Hakata.
I gave him a lot of advice.
It's so strange if I killed him.
So why did you rush to the scene of Kodama's murder?
Well, that's strange, isn't it?
I see, this was launched to set a trap, huh?
I feel sorry for you, though
I have an alibi, you know?
It's an alibi that's almost too good
Back then, I was in a Turkish bath, right?
I was stuck in the box, and I couldn't move my hands or feet,
but I managed to get my head out. Should I go?
and then the next one is 4, right?
Oh this is strange.
but I wonder if the cherry has turned into a monkey.
That's strange
There were four middle numbers here,
Madam.
It's lucky to me
Do you know Room 4, Madam?
We don't create rooms based on the numbers
4 and 9
What?
You received a call from Kodama.
It must be a mistake, right?
hey, there was a Cherry, right? Hey, sis,
there was that Cherry, right?
There is no such person here
What a stupid.
Tsuruchan, Tsuruchan, Tsuruchan
Huh? There was someone
named Tsuruko, right?
I don't know,
but there was, right?
I don't know
The name of the shop, Cherry
She's a cute woman with big breasts and a big butt. You know, don't you?
I don't know
You know, don't you?
Kamoi, your alibi has collapsed, huh?
That's true, She was really here
You get it now?
I see
What are you going to do with me?
Hold on.
Are you alright?
Did it happen again?
An-san
Oh, it's you
Thank you for all your help back then
I was looking for you
I wanted to express my gratitude
That's fine, but how's your body?
I managed to sneak out of the hospital
You need to sleep, right?
I can't just lie down
I need to find that guy.
Is that man Kazuo Kodama, the man who lured you into cheating at bicycle racing?
Do you know him?
Where is he?
I don't know that guy's name,
but I remember his face
I caught him the other day and he got away.
He died.
He was killed.
This guy, this guy, this guy
Who killed him?
It's the same guy who shot you.
There was a bad person behind Kodama
They were always keeping an eye on you and Kodama's actions.
I'm so hungry
Just leave it to me
Welcome.
He'll have Sake
just give me some oden
I don't need Sake.
Why?
I promised Kimura detective that I would quit drinking.
Will that police officer come here?
Oh, I see,
you're not drinking?
No
That's too bad,
What on earth did you come here for, anyway?
That police officers are very noisy.
but that person is a good person, right?
Whether he's a good person or a bad person,
he'll put handcuffs on me
Why?
It's a long story if I start talking about it.
The pistol that shot you and Kodama was the same.
That pistol is mine
Hey, An-san, did you sell me and Kodama out?
Look, there are things you can say and things you can't
The bag containing it was stolen
Where?
At the Daiyasuya in Shinsekai
You were about to take a 100 yen
That was when you yelled at Kimura
I saw it
why didn't you say anything then?
I was daydreaming.
What an idiot, who was that?
He's a professional pickpocket.
Who?
What are you going to do with me?
Give me the pistol you stole.
I have no idea.
I saw it
Where is it?
Matsudo from Group 16 took it.
Matsudo?
You don't need to lie to me
Trust me
I know him.
Leave it to me.
I found out where he was.
Let's go
Alright.
This way
Kamoi
Give me back my pistol
I have no idea.
If you don't know that either, that's fine.
It seems the hot water is a bit lukewarm
Yeah
I will increase the temperature of the water
Don't do anything reckless
It's too hot!
Forgive me....
If you say that, I forgive you.
I gave it to my chairman
Where?
This is the chairman's house
I want to ask you one more thing.
Where is Cherry, who used to work here?
She's in a drying facility.
Watch on him
Oh This pistol is very cool.
Leave it ti me.
Hey, Cherry!
Are you there?
Help me out.
I'm coming now! Just wait a bit!
You're so heavy!
Who's the hell you are?
this guy came to help me!
Eat your meal at my house
You’re not even losing your weight!
If you don't hurry up to get out ,you'll run into something scary! Look,
That's what I say
Matsudo told me everything
Please take care of her.
See you later.
Where did Teruko go?
She just left a moment ago
Where to?
I don't know because she
left without saying anything
Can you tell her?
I understand who killed your brother
So please
Is here Kodama Teruko residence?
She's out now
Can you hand this over her?
(From Kazuo Kodama)
I feel sorry about your brother
It was that guy named
Kamoi who did it, right?
Well, it's only a matter of
time before he gets arrested
By the way, you were present at the moment of my brother's death, weren't you?
At that time, did you receive anything from your brother?
No.
Be honest.
Well, your brother is dead,
so there's no need for you
This is something a bit important for me
What are you talking about?
I don't understand at all
Your brother must have the item he intended to trade with me
Haven't you received it?
Do you have it?
No.
I see.
Phone call from Sister
Don't let police know.I'll take care of Kamoi.
Take that girl to my place
Where are we going?
He's not here.
Hold on.
He's gone...
Hey you! Raise your hands!
This is your pistol.
Next up after Kodama
is you, Kamoi
It's nice to die from your pistol
What's wrong?
Kamoi
Thanks.
This is working fine.
You damaged my gun
Where's Tsukamoto?
I've never played to kill anyone,
but when it comes to you, it's different
Where's Tsukamoto?
Suma's villa
Suma's villa?
Those guys are at Suma
Shall we go?
I need to let Detective Kimura know about the crime!
No we don't need to do it.
He's useless.
I can do it by myself.
Bro.
Give me what your brother gave you
I really don't know
I see, until you can tell me the truth
You're going to stay here for a while,
Boss!
Kamoi is here.
1 guy on right side.
2 guys on left side
Where did Okamoto go?
To the Wharf.
Help me!
Teruko!
Let me go! Let me go! No!
Help me out!
I'll shoot you.
Watch out!
Kamoi-san!
Let me go!
An-san!
That detective is here.
I called him
Hey, don't be an idiot,
Tsukamoto is there.
Don't get closer.
I'll kill her.
Help me out!
Get your hands off of me!
Tsukamoto, let her go!
Don't get closer.
I'll kill her.
Get your hands off of me!
What is he going to do?
Help me out!
Kamoi!
Give to to me
What happened if I missed to shoot?
Did you shoot?
Yes
You?
That Tsukamoto
He fell alone, no?
Give me the pistol.
I just threw away into the sea earlier,
Really?
It's wasteful
We arrested all of them.
Good job!
They only have scratches
No one has deep wounds
I want to see you face off against 007
What, you don't know?
007 is one of my brother.
Mother.
Kazuo was a really man.
Look, he was doing such dangerous work, and he was dead in the line of duty, right?
That's right
He become like this
Stay strong.
If you cry, Brother Kazuo will cry too
So from now on,
I'm going to do this for Brother Kazuo
Instead, I'll take care of you.
We have to work hard
Shall we head over there?
Let's go, let's go,
Kamoi-san
Ah, I get it.
What are you doing, idiot?
OK OK.
I just came to prove it
Do you know why your brother did that job?
If you are the sister of a criminal with a criminal record
Your future life and marriage will be over
He thought like that.
That's right, Detective Kimura also thanks to your brother's notes
Then be happy.
See you again.
Let's go.
Kamoi
He's such a good person.
He doesn't want us to be sad.
He dressed like that
He pretend not to know
Teruko
Your brother was died
Mom.
Congratulations.
Shall I polish your shoes?
This is my first job this year
Hey old man
Please give it back to me
Hey,call me brother
Thanks.
Come on, let's play a little
Sorry, but
I prefer more mature women.
You're pervert.
This year is the year of the horse
I make a wish.
Let's have a good year again this year,
This year is going to be fruitful, thank you
But the most celebratory thing is me
THE END