Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Teuchi (1963)
On 10/10 of the 2nd year of Meireki (1656)
A performance was held at Ohama Palace
Shindo
What can I do for you?
Goroju is visiting you
Please get back
Goroju is visiting me?
Please
OK
I'm here
What can I do for you?
Joi
You didn't know where you were and did something very rude today.
so you have to commit seppuku
seppuku?
I'll take it gratefully.
Do you have to commit seppuku because you yawned?
I yawned because I was bored
I may have yawned too
It's bad for them to give a boring performance
Shindo..you shouldn't do seppuku
Yeah, We'll help you
Yeah
Shindo..you shouldn't do seppuku
I replied, so I will commit seppuku
What? stop it
I've deiced my mind
Hey , listen
SHINDO's seppuku was ordered by Maeda.
What? Maeda
this is his plan
SHINDO's yawning is an insult to Maeda
I said that if we can't get rid of him, we'll send an army there.
They said like that?
The executives are going to hold Shindo accountable to calm the commotion.
We can't accept
let's go talk to them
Let's go
Hold on
Gorotai
it's not good to hit them
leave the matter to me
will you represent us?
Today's executives look like children to me
I'll go and beat them
we should leave it to him
Please help us
do you go alone?
Well
can someone go with me?
I'll go with you
Can you come with me?
Yes
genjiro..you shouldn't do seppuku
I will wait if you go to discuss
you are loyal,wait for us
Shall we go?
genjiro..,wait for us
Who do you think you owe your greatness to?
Because the bannermen are working hard.
It's never thanks to the feudal lords
Maeda was originally an enemy of the Tokugawa family.
I've heard their side of the story and made sense.
But why are you guys forcing Mr. Shindo to commit seppuku?
I know how you feel
But all the feudal lords in Japan are watching closely to see what will happen.
If the Shogunate rejects Maeda's offer in defense of SHINDO
What would the foreign feudal lords think?
The feudal lords from outside the shogunate are probably determined to distrust the Shogunate.
So what?
We don't have to worry about that
The Shogunate today owes its existence to the bannermen
We do not worship the lords of the outside world with all our hearts.
We must win the hearts of the lords.
Goroju
I understand what you say
but as your request
I think it's strange for Shindo to commit seppuku just because he yawned.
The feudal lords are fine, but they cannot suppress the discontent of the bannermen.
What do you think about this?
Bannermen are my people.
My people are patient.
They must put up with it
Can Shindo-san become a victim of you guys?
It can't be helped
Aoyama
To save the big bug, Tokugawa, you have to kill the little bug.
SHindo is little bug?
Yes
For the stability of the Tokugawa family
They are back!
Genjiro
You don't have to say it.
Forgive me
I am no longer an important person
my time is over
Forgive me
Ok,I'll do
Ok,I'll definitely do
but not easy to die
what are you going to do?
i want to decide the place
Where?
At Maeda place
I cut myself in front of his house
Watch me carefully
I will teach you how to cut the belly
Maeda, take a good look at me
you don't perform badly again
I will teach for the Maeda family.
Make it your family motto.
He was a good guy.
I never meant for any of this to happen.
He was my best friend.
He was going to die a spectacular death.
He was  fool.
he was a man who has put his life on the line for
the war is unlikely to end
After all, we may be Samurai, but we have no use in this world after all.
RIPS
I'm leaving
Kiku
You got wet?
Don't worry about me
wipe with this
Tono
Welcome
i want to dry her clothes
We'll take a rest here
I'll call workers
Drink and wait
Please come in
You look good.
take a good rest today
Can I take a good rest today?
Are you glad?
I'm glad with you
In the mansion, you have to be careful about the eyes of the situation
Never mind.
Women are a jealous lot.
You love me.
Don't be afraid of anyone.
It's a waste if I'm the only one who's happy
I'm afraid of my future
Kiku
Welcome back
Guest?
KONDO and others are waiting for you!
You back
we were waiting for you
What's the matter with you?
Look this
What do you mean?
We can't take any more of these cowardly executives.
If they look down on us, we have plans too
we form a group to defeat them
We fight with the feudal lords to protect our pride
We would like to invite you to Hiratsuka group
That's a little rough, don't you think?
Why you say so?
Aren't you offended by the shogunate's way of doing things?
Are you going to waste Shindo's death?
He was my best friend
I'm so frustrated
So you should
Listen
We Hatamoto are the SS of the Tokugawa family.
What will happen to the Tokugawa family if we collapse?
We may destroy the history of the Tokugawa family
I don't care
The executives don't recognize us.
If they won't allow it, we will force it.
will you join us?
Tell me
We're friend,right?
Aoyama
Welcome
I was surprised.
Kiku is here
have you been away for a while?
you should marry a man sooner
What are you saying about?
Welcome her
you became more beautiful
What are you saying about?
She's my sister
What?
Are you kiku?
you are my sister so beautiful
What's the hell?
This is a gift from Tono
Thank you very much
And I'm not just saying that because I got you this.
You should work hard.
She was so beautiful that I think you should marry her soon.
I think it's time for her to get married.
That's right
We don't have time
do you have a spouse?
No way. I don't have
You should quit working at the mansion and get married soon.
Bros
I'm not getting married.
Why you say so?
I want to work in the current mansion forever
What's the hell?
you must not be selfish
women have an expiration date
It's better to get married when you're young
Look her
What's the hell?
TONO will not be your husband
What are you talking about?
She and he have different identities
you should have a commoner and a normal family
I'm back
who is the visitor?
From Koishikawa
he is a very difficult visitor
why did he come here?
It's the usual business
he seems to have become an affair
So I thought he came very often these days.
With whom?
I don't know
Please take care of this
she changed her complexion
Oh..Kiku
you are beautiful as always
you have a lot of trouble every day
please have a little more patience
I'll call you when I need.
Get back
Let's hear your reply.
harima?
I decline
I'm not ready to take a wife yet
What do you think of the current times
The Toyotomi family has fallen.
No longer do samurai take credit on the battlefield and rise to power There is no such thing as an uprising
You must hold on to the vine of prosperity, thinking of the future through marriage
It is for the good of the house
I understand that much
You don't understand.
GENJIRO SHINDO is the good example
SHINDO?
He only understood what he was doing, and so he did a rash thing like standing up to the feudal lords.
He has destroyed yourself and your ancestral home.
Shindo has his own way of life
That's what's wrong with him
They've been cracking down even harder on the Hatamoto since that incident.
If you think your house is important...
You must be very careful.
So
You need a marriage that is good for my family and good for you.
Fighting!
Fighting between Hiratsuka and Machiya
Hey guys!
How are you feeling?
I have a short lifespan, so I hope I die soon.
Gorotai
don't care.
Old people like me are not important, but young people are.
I asked you to follow the problem with the Hiratsuka group.
Yes, I'm here for that matter too
Oh you knew
we are thinking the same
someone has to be very strict
They will surely dig their own graves.
but i can't control them anymore
you are the only one who can control them
Please take care of them for me
I'm thinking the same
I will join the Hiratsuka group
I am one with them.
I understand how they feel
I know I know
To be a member of the Hiratsuka group I want to share their joys and sorrows
I don't know how much I can do
Please, please
There is no one to protect them now
You're the only one who can.
Please... please...
Aoyama has joined us
Let's have a welcome party for him today
bring a lot of alcohol
Watch out! Okiku
What's this?
Are you ok?
This is a gift dish that Ieyasu gave us.
This is a family heirloom that should never be destroyed.
Is it such an important dish?
oh good
Oh, thank God.
You saved your life.
Oh dear
Please clean up quickly.
The person next door wants to talk to you
The person next door?
It seems that she suddenly took a vacation
did you take a vacation?
Thank you for your help until now. I will return to my hometown from today.
Oh I see
I'm here to greet you
Take care
how did she suddenly quit her job?
I heard that she has a good relationship with the lord.
He found new one
with the lord?
Yes, so she was fired
I feel sorry for her.
It's not good to have a romantic relationship with him
If a retainer falls in love with his master
then it doesn't matter if he is abandoned or killed.
Yeah, let's get back to work
I'm glad
My thoughts have come true.
What do you mean?
My first experience I always wanted to be with you
I forgot my inro in the parlor.
Please bring it
I get it.
I forgot my inro in the parlor
What's wrong?
Welcome back
Are you crying?
did you quarrel with someone?
I'm not crying
I need to see your face
You can't?
Tell me
you should be honest
Kiku
Sorry.
I was kidding
What's wrong?
Can a wimp be a bannerman's wife ?
Can I be a bannerman's wife?
No wonder
samurai don't lie
But my next door...
Oh you know
That's a very unavoidable circumstance.
So You were crying?
You're stupid
So you mean...
No matter how many women there are in this world. You are the only woman I love
Lord
no matter what i won't let you go
Even if I lose my job, I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
I'm really glad
Trust me
I'm back
Welcome back
Did you see Kiku today?
i haven't seen her since that time
i heard a rumor
About Kiku?
Not but Hiratsuka
What's wrong?
They are so ferocious that they even challenge officials.
now they are under control but
But it is expected that in the future they will be punished.
How about Aoyama lord?
He's good man
because he is a very nice person,The young hatamotos are trying to take advantage of him.
That's bad.
Okiku should leave from the house
Yes, true.
He's good man
But he has a samurai spirit
you go house and see how it goes
I can't.
i don't like them
Oh yeah,you go house and see how it goes
Me?
you are good at talking
And it's better if a woman goes
When a woman goes, the place softens.
I'm counting on you
did you have anything to do with lord
I had a sudden feeling the other day, but I didn't say anything because I was in front of my brother.
Oh you are...
That's what I thought
But that's not right.
Think about it.
You and him have different identities
He told me he didn't care
It could be but don't trust his words
what would you do if you got dumped like his ex lover?
My brother was worried about you too
I'm going to stay by him for the rest of my life.
are you going to marry him?
looks like he committed suicide with geisha?
he committed suicide with geisha?
Don't look
Go home
Don't look, I'll kill you
Is he mori?
The woman is Tamagiku?
I met her that night.
I feel sorry
He was serious man, but he seemed agitated.
he tried to get her out of her current job
I feel sorry about him
He lover her so much
He's kind
He seems to have committed suicide after being accused by officials.
I feel sorry about him
But i think she was happy
You think so,Kiku?
I think it's a woman's long-cherished desire to die being loved.
Kiku
Aoyama
Aoyama. Gorotai old man is in danger
You guys are here
Rakutaro
I'm your father
Ill go to heaven
I have been protecting Ieyasu Tokugawa since I was 96 years old.
Losing to Imagawa
I fought Takeda
I have endured hardships and hardships in accordance with the outline, wishing for the Tokugawa world.
and we took over the world
But when Tokugawa thought he had taken over the world,
I've become someone they don't need
So be careful
If the Tokugawa shogunate went out of control
You can't handle them
If someone who interferes with them appears
they kill them mercilessly
So put it up
put it up
this is the only way you can live
You get it?
this is my will
Gorotai...
Maeda!
They are coming
The bad guys who made Shindo HARAKIRI
Beat them
Wait
Did you forget about Gorotai's will?
I'll beat them first
Follow him
Wait!Wait!Wait!
Catch them
Come on
On behalf of all the 300 lords and princes of Japan, I hereby submit a request for an order to the Shogunate
They are confusing the MAEDA team
I want you to dispose of Hiratsuka immediately.
If not, we ask that you hand them over to us.
if you can't do it we will beat them
let us think about that for a moment
We have already committed seppuku against SHIBNDO Genjiro.
If we punish the entire HIRATSUKA clan again now.
The other Hatamoto will not remain silent.
If they rebel as a group, it will be a big deal in the world.
But we cannot hold back the bannermen any longer
Then how can we save the face of the Daimyo?
In ten years, maybe five,
things will be different.
But for now, as of today,
the Shogunate must only go along with what the lords say.
So about Hiratsuka's...
But if we don't want to kill them, we have no choice but to make peace with the lords.
make peace?
Yeah
make peace
I'm here
Welcome
Thank you.
I have something to tell you
Come closer
A princess named Akihime is related to Mr. Maeda.
I think it's possible to connect her with Hiratsuka-gumi
Triggered reconciliation between daimyo and hatamoto
I think this is a very positive aspect, but he is very stubborn.
He has had so many blind dates.
We have to carry on this
For our world
we expect that
Everyone is very troubled about Maeda's problem.
The General also very much wants them to get married.
I really understand what they say
I was so surprised when I heard.
You'll be Aoyama's wife
I thought I was dreaming
Anyway you're Aoyama's wife
it's very congratulations
Don't act like that
I'm so horned
he cries with joy
I will become the brother-in-law of the lord
I am honored
it's very congratulations
Yeah, it was really nice. I'm really happy that you became the wife of the Tono.
That's because you're a good girl, Okiku. You're a good girl.
Thanks
Please take good care of him
Are you sure that Aoyama will come?
He'll be sure to come
Did you tell him about Hiratsuka's disposition?
I bet he knew
I'm going to see the cherry blossoms today, so how about this kimono?
Shall I prepare another kimono?
That is ok
Aunt Koishikawa is coming today, so that's fine.
Oh she's coming
What's wrong?
she comes here for today's problem
you shouldn't think weird
She's princess
Thank you for coming
He is my nephew Haruma Aoyama
please start the ritual
She's the princess... so graceful...
and so beautiful.
Someone's here to see me?
Auntie is here to introduce a woman
a woman?
how old is she?
19years old
19years old?
She's one year younger than Okiku.
How does she look?
I hear she's the most beautiful of the brothers.
Who’s the hell is she?
she is the matchmaker of the lord
She's Daimyo"s daughter
Okiku, take out that plate
that plate?
An important customer is coming
The shop is very important, so please take it carefully.
he's going to have a date
A princess
I really worry....
But...
Harima! You are rude!
i can't take it anymore sorry
you must apologize to her
Harima
Aoyama
hold on, Harima Aoyama
Roju
We can no longer reconcile with the daimyo
The Hiratsuka group says they will attack Aoyama's house.
I know
What? You know?
Sorry
did you break that plate?
I think the lord will be very angry if he comes back.
you will be severely punished
Okiku broke that plate?
That Korai plate?
Oh my god , the lord will come back soon
the lord will come back soon?
Lord!
What's wrong?
big problem happened
Look at this
who broke the precious plate?
Who?
I broke it
Did you break it?
Yes I did
You
Are you sure?
i will take any punishment
I think it can't be helped if I accidentally break it
Will you forgive us?
Be sure to reflect on this.
Yes
We saved our life
Okiku was forgiven
I think to him
He said that if she accidentally broke a plate, she would not be punished.
She said she broke accidentally?
What are you talking about?
She broke it on purpose
What?
Forget about the plate
Give me the coat
why are you crying?
I'm so happy
Are you happy so much?
I am the happiest person in Japan
I'm not trying to kill you just by breaking a plate
please forgive me
What do you mean?
For what?
I did....I did...
What's wrong?
Actually
Lord
What's wrong?
Kiku broke the place on purpose
She broke it herself?
there are eyewitnesses
You said you accidentally broke the plate
Not accidentally
Shut up
you accidentally broke the plate,right?
He is saying true
You broke it yourself?
Yes
You broke it
You guys go back
We are just two here
Lord
Tell me
Why did you break that plate knowing that you would be killed?
Kiku
I didn't know today's cherry-blossom viewing party was your matchmaking party.
I lost track of what you were thinking when I heard that
i want to know your true feelings
You got off that plate to know my true feelings
You tried to make sure I cared about you or about that plate.
Yes
Are you sure?
Kiku
did you forget i said i will always be with you
Did you forget that I can only love you?
why didn't you trust me?
Forgive me.
Do women get jealous easily
I feel bad for being suspected
As you thought, I had an arranged date today.
If I accept it, my house and the Hiratsuka group will be safe.
But I was confuses
But I would like to give up my position and live with you.
Put out this plate
Yes
You get it?
I do not forgive you for sparing the plate.
Lord
please defeat me
I doubt your pure heart.
Kiku
When I knows a man's pure heart
I'm willing to die as punishment
I don't mind dying for that love
treasure shattered
my love is gone
Lord
tell her brother
What the hell
You guys wait here
He acts first
he seems to have made up his mind
He's strong
He's a great samurai, but do we have to get rid of him?
It can't helped
why were you punished?
why?
You were so happy to be the lord's wife.
And now you look like this.
Lord
What's wrong about my sis?
why do you wear that dress?
She and I vowed our future together, so I will die with her.
Lord
Forgive me,i understand your sorrow
she was unlucky to fall in love with me
you'll die with her....
i apologize to her in heaven
Take it for me
this is a wedding dress
put it on her
Kiku
you could marry him
Stay with him forever
really you are happy
You have formed a faction with the Hiratsuka clan and have often been lawless, and for this reason I have asked you to commit seppuku.
I'll take it
GOROJU mentioned
Nothing has changed for the Hiratsuka group
Thank you very much
Kiku,wait for me
Let's go to the heaven together
THE END