Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
You've been living in Asahikawa for three months now.
Ichiro,You like your new school?
I like it
No wonder.
HOKUEI. The junior high school is a prestigious private school with good facilities.
And our father is on the board of trustees with the largest endowment.
I'm sure you are in a good mood.
But Dad, why do we have to move all the time?
Sapporo to Hakodate
Hakodate to Muroran
Muroran to Otaru Otaru to Asahikawa
He never stays in the same place for more than three years.
You're like a gypsy.
Your father runs a lot of businesses in Hokkaido.
He lives in the town most convenient for his work at the time.
Parents are fine, but the kids are the worst off.
We're always moving from one school to another.
We're always in the middle of things with our boyfriends, and then we say goodbye.
You don't like too, right?
I don't care
You are carefree twenty-eight year old.
You envy me?
Sasabayashi here
Hold on
Yuri kishima calls you
She has a beautiful voice,your girlfriend?
No, we're just classmates.
It's me
in the park in front of my house?
Okay, I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
Actually, I'm quitting school at the end of this semester.
Why?
My father's a plasterer.
He doesn't have any work during the winter, so he's always taking bets.
He lost his gambling money this winter. To pay off his debt, he used all the money from his job.
Millions of yen of Sasabayashi Kanko's money.
My father's company?
If your father stares at him, he can't work in Asahikawa anymore.
That's why we are leaving town.
I'll ask my father to do something about it.
Wait,
Don't get me wrong
I just wanted to talk to you,
Don't worry, my dad knows what he's talking about.
Besides, it's Sunday. he is home.
Go home and wait for me and I'll call you later.
Sasabayashi
Dad
Dad, you there?
namie sis
Tsumiki no Hako / The House of Wooden Blocks (1968)
Ichiro's not eating breakfast these days.
What's wrong with him?
It's not just breakfast, he doesn't even show up for dinner.
I wonder what's going on with that girlfriend Shimayuri.
Namie,Chiro is not that stupid.
He's my child.
It's not like my son to fret over a girl.
I'm carrying on your chutzpah.
But that's okay.
He's finally getting frustrated with his environment.
That's progress, and something to be proud of.
Here you are, back of the Hokuei School.
Hello.
You're always early.
Bread and milk
Which bread will you have this morning?
Anything.
Cream bread is tasty
Don't say that
I'll get a Cream bread
Thank you
My change.
But I heard you don't like bread.
If you want, I can make you onigiri next time.
No thanks.
Good morning.
Give me 3 Onigiri
Three is too many every day.
I want 3
Oh Sasabayashi
What's going on? so early, Sasabayashi?
Sasabayashi
He's strange
Sasabayashi?
He's the son of Sasabayashi Goichi, who's the president of a number of Hokkaido tourist agencies, hotels, buses and countless other companies.
He moved into my class this April from Otaru
He's got good grades for the son of a rich man.
What was he doing here?
Hisayo
He just bought milk and bread.
Who are you?
Get out
I'm in trouble!
What?
I'll always be here to catch the loach.
Get lost!
What happened?
He drowned in the river.
I pulled him out and drained him.
are you okay?
I'm fine
Thank you so much.
I want to thank you
It's my fault.
I told him got out
See you
You've been turning your head away and not talking to me at all lately
My dad said He couldn’t about your dad.
No worry.
When I told my mother about it, she scolded me.
She said it's none of my business.
It's strange.My body is such an adult and she said I am still child.
You look so naughty
Sasabayashi
You were shy about paying for it.
I used to want to read it when I was at school.
It's normal to have an interest in it.
Good thing it was me who found it.
I'll take it back to the bookshop.
Let's have a cup of tea around here.
Sorry about the sermon.
Ouch
It's rare that you're in my house...
Don't go into people's rooms.
You've been acting so weird lately.
Why aren't you eating?
I can't eat here. The food is terrible.
I've had better ramen outside or oyakodon.
You don't look well and you've lost weight.
You're going to die soon.
I don't care if I die.
It's better than this house.
What are you talking about? It's a perfect, luxurious house.
You'll be damned if you complain.
Shut up!
Get out!
I can't.
We are brother
Be honest. Something's wrong.
Ichiro
I tell you.
What's wrong about Namie ?
She's our sister
She's not my sister, and if she was, she wouldn't be cuddling with my dad like a married couple.
That's not what parents do with their kids.
It could be incest.
I'm serious
What's wrong about Namie ?
I have no idea
She’s his mistress
Don't you think so?
That's a very good deduction.
My father's a terrible man.
This is a beast's house.
Even our mother lies a lot.
She's his mistress.
Our mother lies us
So what?
You know and you don't say a word.
Yeah
You don't care?
I care
Tell me what you think?
Adults are adults and children are children.
I make up my own world, and I keep it to myself.
I have to protect myself from dirty adults.
We can't live here
Don't play games with me, sister, they know what they're doing.
If you're really mad at them, why don't you get that bitch out of here and clean house?
You think he'll listen to you?
They'll just laugh at you
Ichiro,don't care about adults
You're an idiot for ruining your own life just because your parents are bad.
You are their side
I hate you
You're the one who's so twisted and filthy.
Oh, I'm filthy. That's because I'm my father's son.
You're blaming your parents for your filthiness.
If you're going to be filthy, why not be even filthier than your parents?
Okay, it's getting worse and worse
I'll take Namie off our dad's hands.
Don’t do that
You can't
He's a beast cloth woman.
I'm the son of a beast.　We're just as good as each other.
Who?
What were you doing?
We were talking about this house
How's my grade?
80 points
Thanks
How's my grade?
100 points.
You're great
Thanks
I wish I'd gotten a hundred, even if it was a lie.
I haven't gotten a hundred since I was a kid.
Where are you going?
Studying.
I'm still a senior in high school.
Next year I'm going to college.
Don't make me laugh.
You play the guitar all the time.
Your teacher... she specializes in math.
Maybe I'll get you a tutor.
You're wasting my time.
Women are stupid.
You despise women?
Your future wife is a woman.
I hate women.
Except for you
You really like me?
That's nice of you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Hi
Welcome
How's he?
He's in bed with a fever, but he's fine.
I wanna see you
Go ahead,he will be glad
I'm sorry, I got angry with you
If you'd like, you can stay for dinner.
I'll cook you a nice dinner.
I don’t care about my house
What do you like?
Anything.
leave it to me, then.
What should I cook
Only you and the little boy live here?
Yeah
I want a father
You shouldn't have that.
It's enough for Mom.
He's a very lonely boy.
I'm sure he'd love to see you sometimes.
I'll come, but I enjoy it here more than at home.
Why is that?
Why? You have a fine house, don't you?
It looks fine on the outside, but it's not so nice on the inside.
They're all beasts of prey. It's like hell.
It's like hell in there, whereas here it's heaven.
You are sweet, your son is cute
Hi
It's Sugiura
I'll be with you in a moment.
He's a frequent visitor, isn't he?
He always stops by on his way to and from school.
For what?
He loves my son
you haven't eaten dinner yet?
Please eat here
I'd appreciate it.
But you are single mother. I worry about people's eye
Not tonight.
We have other guests.
Who?
Sasabayashi from your class.
Where is he?
He was out the back.
He was out the back?
I don't know what's wrong.
It's because I'm here.
He's probably embarrassed.
Anyway, I'll prepare your dinner.
Good morning
What's wrong?
In your locker
Panties,bra,slip.
These are so gorgeous
That's probably the wrong locker for a female teacher.
I'll hang it in the staff room.
Sasabayashi,Middle school is when you want to get into mischief.
Last year, I lost a lot of money when they delivered ten portions of sushi I didn't order.
Compared to that, this is still OK.
No, don't throw stones.
I won't care!
Ichiro, it's a lie that you like me.
You don't really like me.
I do.
You used to hug me, bathe with me, spoil me.
Now you just stare at me with scary eyes.
I feel lonely
it's jealousy
That's why I'm going to marry
To where?
Taiwan.
I heard that Taiwanese are very warm-hearted and respectful of the Japanese.
It's far
It's a four-hour flight from Haneda.
If i don't think it's close, I won't go.
You don't really want to go.
But I have to
Don't go to Taiwan as a bride, stay at home
Then we'll be friends like old times?
Yeah
Really?
Sasabayashi
It's Sunday and I've come for a home visit.
There's no one at home.
He's in trouble.
Who are you?
I'm Ichiro's sister, Namie.
Please, come home. My mother will be with you.
Leave your seat.
I've got an important meeting with him
Please drink A cold beer
No, thank you.
Shall I get you a whiskey, then?
Or would you prefer a brandy?
Actually, Ichiro, his grades, which have been good ever since he transferred, have suddenly gone downhill.
His attitude is strange, and he doesn't eat at home.
Is there a reason?
There's no reason.
I think at that age they call it rebellion.
He's very difficult and doesn't talk to his parents.
But it's like measles, he'll get over it eventually, so it's best to leave him alone.
Teacher,
I'm Ichiro's sister, Midori
Nice to meet you
I'm Sugiura
You can't ask my Mom anything.
She's too busy buying tea ceremony rings and kimonos.
She doesn't think about the kids at all.
Young girls these days are a real pain in the ass.
She enjoys teasing their mothers.
Mum, she can put up with anything as long as she has money.
She thinks that if she keeps her kids in the lap of luxury, they won't complain.
It's funny because she's giving a talk on home education at the women's club.
Besides, my mum's a very vain woman, and she'd never let our flaws out of the house.
But I'm the complete opposite, I'm a bit of an exhibitionist.
Cut it out
I like you so much.
Will you teach me maths?
No, you won't.
He's too busy. He doesn't have time.
He's a good student, smart and charming enough.
I don't tutor pretty girls.
you are a coward
Mum, what's he doing here?
Why did you say that to the teacher?
What did you tell him?
I heard you'd bought bread and milk and finished breakfast.
Don't be such a wretched wretch!
Oh you talked about that
You'll definitely eat at home from now on.
All right...
NAMIE's going to Taiwan as a bride?
That's bullshit.
Who'd take her?
Why, she's beautiful and kind.
She's not kind.
She has a completely different personality than she looks
She's kinder than Mom.
I'm sorry.
I had a miscarriage.
We've already had two
Don't apologise to me.kids.
Your body is more important.
You'll stay here for the time being.
This girl, I think it's her, used to work in a bar in Noboribetsu, but she's only 15.
It's against the law, so I scolded owner and took her in.
Why don't you let her help you with the housework?
That's fine
What kind of parents would let their little girl work like this?
Sounds like an orphan.
Her uncle sold her off.
I feel sorry
You slept with our housemade
I'm going home country
I thought you were the only one who understood what I was talking about, so you're a normal woman after all.
It's ok if we divorce
I'll take my kids.
I won't leave them in the hands of a father who looks like an animal.
Yes I am an animal
animals kill for their children
I'll take my kids.
I'll kill you
Toki,You are a proud woman.
You want to be the laughing stock of the world when your master is taken by the HOUSEMAIDE?
You should be respected as my wife.
Namie will be our child.
Other two kids are still small
I can't trick them
In exchange, I'll give you the luxury of buying all the jewellery stores and kimonos you like.
Good evening
Oh you
I asked at the lodge, but they said you'd be on duty tonight.
So I rushed over immediately.
What do you want?
I have something important to discuss with you.
What's about?
What if... my dad has a mistress and they live in the same house?
Either I'll snub the bitch out, or I'll run away from home myself.
Or I'll leave him to make an example of his stupid father, and I'll become a MISTRESS too.
Or I'll kill myself.
is that the important thing you're talking about?
You're so insensitive... didn't you see my sister?
She's Father's Mistress
I mean, my family lives with the MISTRESS.
I see
So that's why Ichiro is in trouble
I found out when I was in primary school.
He's so easygoing.
He's just now realising and floundering.
He's at a bad age to find out.
But it's a secret.
I extort tens of thousands of dollars a month in hush money from my mum.
It's okay. I'm tight-lipped.
I've got a bastard of a father to thank for that.
I've learned the ins and outs of the male animal.
Secondary school teachers are the worst of the worst.
They're quick to touch a female student's bottom or breasts, but you're the exception.
A beautiful girl like me could seduce you and you wouldn't even hold my hand.
I like you even more now.
Sasabayashi It's almost summer holiday.
Not for me.
There's a camp from Lake Akan to Lake Kussharo during the summer holidays.
Three days, two nights.
I'm not interested in that.
But I'd really like you to go.
Why?
My mother said it's my last camp in junior high and I should attend.
After that, we are leaving Asahikawa.
That's why I want you to go with me.
I don't want to.
About Summer Camp Exposure ,Have you made up your mind?
I'm sure the food will be delicious and Our students will be delighted to have you overseeing the cooking.
Can I bring Kazuo?
Sure
Usually it's the teacher's family, but I'm single, and a friend I was counting on is ill.
I'll go.
he'll be so happy.
We haven't been away in years.
Well, thank goodness, 'cause this is gonna be a fun camping trip.
You like him?
I like most people.
Are you getting married?
No way, I have Kazuo
Don't get along with him.
I hate him
But he's your customer, he buys cigarettes from you every day.
I have to be friendly.
I'm a customer, too,
But not you.
You've saved Kazuo's life.
I like you
What did you tell him about?
We're going to the summer camp too.
We'd love it if you'd play with Kazuo while we're away.
Will you come?
Yes
Don't you sing?
Actually, I've been wanting to ask you for a while.
when did KAZUO father die?
Five years ago, when he was born,
You chose him.
He must have been a fine man.
You didn't remarry because you couldn't forget your late husband.
Quite the opposite.
It was too hard for me. I'll never marry again.
If that were true, I'd want to marry you
I'm a 30-year-old bachelor, generally decent.
I'm confident I could make you happy.
I'm confident I can make you happy and be a good father to Kazuo.
Will you marry me?
I'm not the kind of woman who can be your wife.
I'd like to know why.
I'm sure we'll have a chance to talk about it one day.
I feel good.
Why don't you lie down?
Like this?
Meditate with me.
Why are you doing this?
Come on.
We'll never see each other again.
So?
I have to admit, I really love you
Kiss me
I'll never see you again in the ninth grade.
I want to make happy memories.
No, I can't.
Unload my stuff.
Damn it
Sasabayashi
Hello, teacher
I took of your photo
Oh Midori, she is Ichiro's sister
Ichiro's sister?
Who's the pretty woman?
The wife of the milkman in front of the school.
That's where Ichiro gets his bread.
I bet you're in love with her.
there is a lot of age difference
There's no age between a man and a woman.
You like her too, don't you?
But I don't like her. She's my rival.
Why did you come here?
I came here with my dad to visit him in labour.
His Mistress is here too
He's a terrible father, isn't he?
That's a nice car.
Hi,I'm Sasabayashi
I know it's embarrassing, but please give it to your students.
Chocolate, gum and juice.
Thanks
You're a smart kid, aren't you?
How old are you?
5 years old
You're heavy
Dad, I've never seen you hold a child before in my life.
Give me a break
Now, excuse me.
I'm on my way to work.
I'm leaving Sapporo tomorrow for Tokyo, Osaka and possibly Kyushu.Bye.
You went all the way from Tokyo to Kyushu and these are your travel photos?
They're all of men's faces.
I'm more interested in men than scenery.
I've taken every face I've liked.
I'm disgusted with you
Why?
I'm seriously thinking about marriage.
I don't want to be single forever like Namie.
I'll have a family by the time I'm twenty-three.
I envy you.
A woman's happiness depends on the kind of person she lives with
No matter how much money and power you have, if he's a weirdo, you're screwed for life.
That's why I look at all kinds of men, to keep my eyes open.
But then, they're all boring men, aren't they?
They're all so bossy, even though they're on a low salary.
What's with the picture?
Oh, You forgot?, it's Ichiro's teacher.
No, I mean this woman
This is Ichiro's favourite milkman's wife.
She's one of the few beauties around here.
Oh I see
She's beautiful
Don't act weird, OK?
She's the mom who you slept with
Dad, what are you looking at?
That woman from the milkman's shop.
I think she's the one who used to be my secretary in Otaru.
Oh she is
I’m sure she is
You're right, she looks just like her.
Then maybe the kid's mine.
Have you slept with her?
Just once
Then I left
I can't believe it.
she had a baby.
I can't believe but this is true
You still love her
I like
More than I?
I've kept you for 13 years.
There's no comparison.
Tomorrow I'm going to Tokyo for a week, and tonight I'm going to treat you well.
Sex in a room next to my wife, makes me exciting
Welcome
Any chocolate is fine
Give me 2 dozen.
Thank you very much.
You run the shop all by yourself?
Does your husband work somewhere?
schoolteacher?
I don't have a husband.
No husband,but you have a kid?
He passed  away
A boy called Ichiro Sasabayashi comes here often?
Yes
For what?
He loves my kid
Kazuo will be very happy.
You’re lying.
You're the one who's happy.
Your kid is Sasabayashi Goichi's , isn't he?
No
Be honest
Excuse me, but what exactly is your relationship to Sasabayashi?
I'll tell you if you want to know.
I'm his mistress
I know what's on your mind
You want to get money from him for the child.
You've got it all wrong.
I don't want money
What the hell?
I am your customer
I know what's on your mind
You want to control Ichiro and get back together with him again.
I know you do.
I can't talk to you.
Please go home
You can't fake it.
Remember...
As long as I'm here, you'll never get your way.
I caught 5 loaches
Good for you.
Hello, Ichiro.
This is no place for you.
Go home
Get out
What are you doing here?
You pushed me away today?
You know, because you are dad's mistress
Oh you knew
Of course I do, don't make fun of me.
You hate me?
I can't even look at it.
You're lying.
You really like me, don't you?
Get out or I'll push you away again.
If you want me to leave, fine.
I haven't had a home here since I was born.
I don't know anything about that,
I'm a headword.
I grew up being sold from bar to bar.
I was always beaten up and yelled at for breaking a double plate.
They always told me to get out
So what?
He's the only one who's ever stood up for me.
I came to this house thinking I'd be a good maid, and I was so happy
But he suddenly attacked me
I don't want to hear about it.
Ichiro, a child without parents... Any kind of human affection makes us happy.
I loved your father.
Is that bad for me?
Of course you are
But I wasn't a bad girl from the start.
I've been a bad girl for a long time.
I was comfortable.
I've been in this house too long...
But I have to leave
People are suffering because of me.
I'm scared of the outside world.
I'll be bullied and beaten up again, and I'll have a bad time, of course I will.
But it's my destiny
Right?
I like you.
Kiss me goodbye.
You don't like neither?
You hate me so much?
See you
Stay here
It's my dad who's the bad
But I can't hate him.
He saved my life.
You're an idiot, you know that?
I don't care if you killed him.
It's just that he messed up your life
If you hadn't picked me up, I'd be a plaything for a lot of guys right now.
I don't think so
You are wrong
I'm right
Smells good.
Smells like Milk
you are a lily flower
What do you think of this dress?
It looks good on you.
I'm so happy.
You are bad
Why?
You slept me and my dad
You're idiot.
I only like Ichiro.
we cuddled every night for a week until morning.
But when he comes home tonight..
What's wrong ?
You're idiot.
If you're so suspicious, keep an eye on me all night.
Of course you are going.
I'm not going there.
I swear to you.
If you betray me, I don't know what I'll do.
All right.
You're the one who's suspicious.
What?
The milkman's wife, Hisayo... you like her, don't you?
Have you ever been held like this?
No way
Which one do you like more?
You're both beautiful.
She's kind
me?
I'm scared.
Don't go out with her.
Why?
You'll regret it one day.
Give me this knife.
It's rare to see Ichiro at home, what's going on?
He's finally grown up after his rebellion.
The only thing that's grown up is his body.
He looked at the girls funny,
and even got cheeky with his moustache.
Shut up
Namie, are you there?
Where'd she go?
Namie
Oh, my God, you're here.
Oh, shit.
I didn't know you had this trick up your sleeve.
About this?
Your mum had them made.
It's a publicity stunt.
My Mom?
He moves all the time for the sake of publicity.
He moves to another city as soon as he thinks my cover is blown.
It's all your mother's idea.
I don't care about any of that, sister.
You cheated on me and slept with Daddy, you liar.
I don't have a choice.
I don't want to do what you want me to do, either.
If I refuse, he'll kill you.
Don't make a lie
He's scary
You can't just run away from this house.
He'll find you. Hell kill you half to death.
Don't make a lie.
You wanna stay with him,right?
Why?
why do I want this life?
I'm never married, never free to play with my boyfriend.
I'm always cooped up in the house. It's like prison.
Shut up.
You kill me?
Ok, kill me
If it makes you feel better.
Someday somebody's going to kill me anyway.
kill me
What's the matter with you?
You can't kill me?
If you don't do something, just get out.
Damn it
What are you doing?
This is my dad's mistress room.
Get out
Stop trying to seduce Ichiro
seduce ?
You're overreacting, I'm just taking a little something from HISAYO.
He's a 15 year old kid.
Don't play with him.
I turned him into a full-fledged adult.
You should be thanking me.
Shame on you.
If you ever lay a hand on him again, I'll never forgive you.
You've got to be kidding me.
He interested in me
If I'd come out of daddy's room...
He would have killed me.
He would have killed you, but you got what you deserved.
You messed this house up.
Sorry... it's not my fault.
Blame on your dad
He's just an animal
But he's an animal who plays with animals.
So Ichiro is also an animal.
He slept with me
He's my daddy's boy.
You too ,Midori
Why?
You chase men's asses all year round.
How do you know what you're doing?
I'm not like you
Your idea is too old
These days, there are plenty of young ladies who fall in love with married men and destroy their families.
What are you talking about?
You like money.
You can't stop living in the lap of luxury.
You don't know what's going to happen to you either.
You might be 4th mistress
Don't worry.
I'm not like you
But what if they forcefully manhandle you like they did me?
I'd die.
Your idea is too old
If I were you, I'd let Dad be Dad and Ichiro be Ichiro.
I'd get along with both of them.
That's not funny.
Ichiro, I can't believe you'd let a woman like this go to you.You are still baby
I'm not
You are.
Mind and body are disconnected.
Your heart loves Hisayo, but Your  body loves this woman.
A real grown-up loves a woman with both body and soul.
Daddy's girl is disgusting.
She's like rotten tomatoes.
I tell you but I'm not his only woman
There's another woman.
Who?
Hisayo.
Ichiro's favorite woman
What?
That little boy you're loving so much. Your beloved Kazuo... that's father's son.
Congratulations.
You've got your brother
That's bullshit.
You can't beat me up all you want.
Facts are facts.
If you doubt me so much, ask Hisako.
Shut up
Thank you for your kindness.
You are welcome
I'm sure I'll be able to repay you.
I'll be waiting.
Sir, I'm sorry to bother you on duty, but can Kazuo stay at school tonight?
No problem.
Why?
Summer vacation will be over soon, a
I'm going to a wholesale store in Sapporo to stock up!
You are busy
Hisayo
What's going on with you?
Kazuo is my father's son?
No
I knew it.
I thought you were the only one I trusted.
All women are bullshit.
I'm not bullshit.
Whose child is that?
My own child.
How can a woman have a child on her own?
I bet you smiled when you saw me playing with him
I'll tell you the truth.
Please listen to me
I'm going to tell you the truth about my past for the first time.
You're all lying.
Shut up.Sasabayashi
Five years ago.
I was living in Otaru and working as Sasabayashi's secretary.
My father was an accountant for a company
One of his subordinates misappropriated 700,000 yen.
To fill the hole, my father became neurotic.
And my mother became seriously ill.
Then I told Sasabayashi everything
He told me He gave cheque so come to restraint
I was raped
And the check went to waste.
Dad
Why did you die?
When I got home, I found my father had committed suicide.
My mother died three days later from the shock.
So that one night, one time, that's all it took to give birth to KAZUO?
I didn't want to give birth, but the child is innocent.
I couldn't kill him.
I gave birth while working as a maid at an inn in Obihiro.
Hisayo, you're too serious like your father.
My own children are adorable and I can't let them go.
I borrowed money from the innkeeper to raise him and start this restaurant.
So he's my brother after all.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to cheat you.
Poor Kazuo, he has no father.
I thought at least his real brother would take care of him.
Auntie, I'm not coming here anymore.
I hate my father's women.
No
Hisayo is not his woman.
If she's his woman, she'd have made him recognize the kids and gotten all the child support and property he's got.
It's same
Hisayo lived with Kazuo all by herself.
You can understand the pain and suffering?
I don't know what it's like.
You're an animal either
She was happy to be in my father's arms.
She would have laughed
Sasabayashi
What's the matter with you?
Why don't you shut up?
Stupid!
Don't be so naive.
Just because your father's a jerk doesn't mean you're a jerk.
When you're angry, you should study harder.
You're gonna be a great person.
He's gonna apologize to you
Shut up!
What the hell?
You' re evil.
Not only Namie, but also HISAYO, you are an asshole!
Ichiro, you're an adult now and you should know about it
All Women are a toy.
People who fall in love with them are fools. Remember it
You are still an animal.
I'm gonna kill you.
Can you kill me?
It's just a girl thing.
I knew it
In exchange, I'll do something worse.
I'll do something so bad, it'll be in the papers, and I'll humiliate you.
He's got such a pretty face, it's hard to believe he's that guy's kid.
Who's there?
Kazuo!
Sugiura, the teacher, is an idiot.
I can't believe he left the stove on and went outside.
I'd advise against it.
I donate a lot of money to a school that was burned down.
I can't believe he let a kid stay at the duty station.
I think He is dating with Hisayo.
Teachers these days do shady things behind the scenes.
Dad,
You don't recognize a child named KAZUO,OK?
Of course not.
I don't want to be blamed for the property or the child support.
First of all, I never know what she might have done after that.It might not even be my kid.
You sure?
Don't worry about it.
It's my policy to have women and not have children.
That's why you won't let me have one either.
Except you.
You'll lose your sex appeal and your taste buds if you have kids.
I won't leave you no matter what kind of grandmother I become, okay?
Okay, okay.
Ichiro
What?
Arson is a serious crime, punishable by death.
That fire at the school last night... was that your doing?
Not me
Okay, then.
So even if... you did it, don't say a word.
We don't have a shred of evidence.
If this goes to court, we won't lose.
I'll spend every dime and lawyer I have to get you acquitted.
Not me
I've been caught in the net of the law many times. But I never confessed.
That's why I'm now a proud owner of Hokkaido's tourism business.
You're my son.
Don't make a mistake that will get you caught by the police.
If you become an ex-convict. Your life is over.
All right
And NAMIE is a valued customer of mine.
If you try anything funny, I won't let you get away with it.
Dad, Look at me
Something's changed, hasn't it?
What?
I might have a baby
You sure?
I showed it to the doctor and he said I'm seven months pregnant.
Who's guy?
I don't know
I met this guy when I went skiing this winter.
He came into my room at night, out of the blue, and he forced his way into my panties.
I get it.
Get an abortion.
No
You're stupid.
You have not got married yet
How about Hisayo?
She had her daddy's baby before she got married.
I'm gonna do the same thing.
That's different case
So you don't care what happens to other people, but you do care about your own daughter?
Don't say bullshit.
See a doctor with your mom
No.
It's too late
She's twitching in my belly!
She's so cute!
You idiot!
Two months and seven months are the same. We can have a C-section.
Seven months is a full human being.
What kind of parent tells someone to kill them?
No wonder your kids are so stupid.
Seriously you can't raise a child.
You're stupid.
Get an abortion.
I heard you outside the door.
You're the one who set Mr. Sugiura's shift on fire?
To frame him?
No
He's resigning to answer for your crimes.
It's not fair of you to stand there and watch.
You were going to destroy our father's face in the first place.
Why don't you go to the police and come clean?
He'll get upset, and he'll straighten up a little.
Leave me alone
I'm leaving this house.
I'm not going back while NAMIE's here.
Of course I lied about being pregnant.
I was just trying to scare my father.
Follow me and be brave
Your enemy is your father.
You'll be a big boy when you beat him.
Don't let him beat you.
See you
Ms. Ishihara.
I am so sorry.
I burned Kazuo because of my carelessness.
I can't believe you started that fire.
I'm sure you're protecting someone.
I'm careless sometime
I forgot to turn off the stove.
You really want to quit, don't you?
I've already submitted my resignation.
Actually, I lost my confident
I've supported ICHIRO up until now, like beating him up, but to no effect
I'm not a good teacher.
I'm going to Tokyo for a while to think about it.
If I regain my confidence, I'll teach again.
I'll ask you to marry me again.
I like you even more now that you've told me about your past, a
I'll be waiting for you.
I never married until now... because I was afraid of men.
I thought they'd all be like Sasabayashi Goichi.
That's terrible.
Men come in all shapes and sizes.
There are men like you.
I've only recently come to realize that.
I want to quit this impossible life of being a woman alone.
It causes a lot of trouble for those around me.
Sasabayashi
Do you want something to say?
No
I want
I think this hat belongs to you.
I picked it up near the inn room at the fire.
Take it.
It's not mine.
I'll give it back anyway.
Take it back.
You think I started the fire, don't you?
So why don't you just say so?
You can talk to the police.
If you're mad at me for getting fired, hit me.
I don't want to.
You're not a kid. You're a grown man.
You can take care of yourself.
You're so good at covering for other people's sins.
You've come all this way.
Go see Kazuo
He's waiting for you... make him happy.
Come on, boy.
He's here
Hi
Don't worry.
Fortunately, KAZUO's burns are minor.
After the treatment, it will be completely healed.
Well, I'll be on my way.
I have a train to catch.
I'll take you to the front.
Ichiro, will you stay by Kazuo's side during this time?
Yeah
Thanks
My fingers got stuck together from the burns.
That's weird.
why didn't you see it?
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
I'm your real brother but...
I'm sorry
I can't believe Midori ran away from home.
What a bunch of pathetic children.
I can't believe you're home-schooling these pathetic kids.
All you do is play.
Have you ever taken them seriously?
Can they live in a house like this all the time?
I've done my best, in my own painful way.
A mother who can't even bring up her own children is a failure.
You're disgusting.
Hello? Is this the police?
I set fire to Hokuei Junior High School.
His name is Ichiro Sasabayashi
Yes, I'm the son of GOICHI
Arrest me immediately!
Ichiro
You
I'll tell them why you set the fire.
I'll tell them everything that happened in this house.
You're stupid
I knew it was my fault.
I should have left from you
This house is already falling apart.
It's falling apart like a house of blocks.
What have I been doing?
You're stupid!
Stop complaining.
Goodbye.
THE END