Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Waga Shogai no Hagayakeru Hi (1948)
The Brightest Day of My Life (1948)
In 1945
August 14
The eve of defeat in the war
Mr.Uda Mishima, here?
Uda? It is me.
Do you need something?
I'm here to get your life.
My life?
What are you going to do
with my life?
You are a political criminal.
Shut up.
Calm down.
The acceptance of the Ousdam Declaration
is the only way to save Japan
You're wrong. Keeping war until the end is what will save Japan
You will soon understand the true.
This is when we will understand who led Japan into the tragedy of war
Foolish.
Come on.
Stay away.
Father!
Stay strong.
Are you alright?
Takako.
It's time for Japan to be reborn.
For that, sacrifices are necessary
Don't be sad,
Father! Father!
Father!
Yusuke
Ueno
Yay, I wonder what's going on?
Just leave him alone.
He's an addict.
Hey,Shut up.
What's wrong, senpai?
Are you okay?
What's going on!
Jiro
The medicine is no longer effective
Where's Dad?
Is it the teacher?
He's on the second floor
The second floor, huh?
Yeah, that's fine.
what's that money about?
As promised, we'll break up
from today we're strangers
No, no, no, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Do you want more medicine?
I have a call from Sakai-san of Showa Industries.
Sakai-san?
He will come over to the office
Oh really?
What about Kei-chan?
It's none of your business., so go down
Don't play here.
Hello?
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Thank you for coming.
The newspapers have also produced good articles.
Thanks to you
Please come in.
It's just a mere million yen, after all
When I'm thanked, I actually feel embarrassed
it's more like we are managing with your money
He is my right arm
He's Colonel Moriyama, the chief public relations officer of the former Burma Dispatch 21st Army
This is Mr. Sakai from Showa Sangyo
I am Moriyama
I'm Sakai.
The reason our newspaper is managing to get by is entirely thanks to him
Thank you very much in advance
Same here.
Moriyama.
Call Numazaki.
Mr.Sakai
We appreciate your financial support.
and I hope to repay you someday
Please let me know
whenever you want
Actually, I came to ask you about that today
Could you please give me something from your pocket for my sake?
Is this it?
There are some supplies in my factory.
I see.
The committee heard the rumor.
They'll uncover them tomorrow.
Apparently someone tipped him off
So?
with your power,
Somehow....
with the power of my mind?
Umazaki arrived
Excuse me.
I parted with Tomi.
Do you know about the black dress she wore to the hall since Friday?
She's a substitute for Tomi, so please talk to her, okay?
Leave Midori-chan alone
She's so cheeky,
it's fine, isn't it?
Hey, if you're a newcomer, I want you to at least greet us like a newcomer should
I'm called Midori
Hmph, what are you talking about?
I don't want to say hello
If you don't know my name, just look at my name tag
You can read, right?
You said something I’ve heard before
Try saying that again, will you?
I’ll say it as many times as it takes
I'm different for those women who can't work unless they greet you
Don't mess with me
Don’t do that.
Just let it be, let it be
You raised your hand, didn't you?
Hey.
Damn it
Stop it.
Damn it, remember this next time
what?
Don't make such a racket,
hey, thank you
Could you go out for me?
What?
Just come, it doesn't matter what
Damn it.
A highball, please
You're so great.
What do you want?
Master wants to take care of you.
What do you think?
So you're saying you're the customer-pulling, huh?
Well, that's true.
What happens if I say I don't want to?
It's not a big deal,
I just want you to quit here
I don't think you would say no.
Well then, shall I give it a try?
Hey, let's skip the small talk
I hate wasting time
You just need to make up your mind
You sound just like a robot, insulting people without a care
That's right, I'm not human
Now, let's go to the master's room
It's on the second floor up those stairs
Like that?
She's quite a nice woman, isn't she?
Hey Kei, I'm sorry about earlier
Could you dance with me?
Come on, Kei,
Kei.
can't I go back to how Sensei an I used to be?
Cheer up.
Even though he was so kind to me
Why did he suddenly become so cold?
I guess I'll just give up
But it was you who put your hands together.
I can't part.
Why don't you ask him.
No way, the reason is clear
He has another woman besides you
What's wrong?
You hate it?
I can do anything I set my mind to
That's the kind of man he is
I have a condition
Tell me.
I want to ask the president of the patriotic newspaper,
not the master of the cabaret.
so let me hear it
because I like your shitty situation
I want you to use one person
It's piece of cake.
Somewhere that doesn't attract too much attention
It's someone with a complicated situation
That's right
Alright, the deal is done
Hi.
I'm Sagawa.
I am Hirabayashi
Thank you very much this time.
Please.
I understand you were a prosecutor during the war.
The times have changed so much that it has become difficult to live from our jobs
But please rest assured
I will take on your heartfelt wishes
The accounting department would be good
No one will notice, and by the way,
Moriyama-san
This is Hirabayashi-san
Please introduce them to the accounting department
Please come.
Well then, thank you for your help
She's miss.
Please take a break from the transaction
That's true, but it's still not complete, is it?
I need to see how I will be able to work
I'll be right back
Oh, please do
Wait a moment,
big sister
What's wrong?
Make sure to treat those guys by 10 o'clock
Wait a minute, let's go have lunch together
He just went now
There's no doubt we can carry it out?
Don't worry,he can
Trust us.
Natsu, your turn.
Excuse me, where is Numazaki?
Big brother is over there
What's wrong?
Thank you for your hard work today.
it's a showdown!
It's a showdown
Hey, Dad
Please give me some alcohol
Do you want a jin?
What's the hell?
Mr. Masasakai is waiting on the second floor,
Huh? What is that, such a dirty man
Is he planning to dance on three legs?
It seems the police have come.
Hey Jiro, come down
Um, are you with the police?
No,I'm just observing
Oh, it was just an observation
Just observing, huh?
Jiro.
Is that you, umazaki?
Who is it?
It's me, Takakura
Mr. Takakura? Aren't you alone?
Hey, don't act like an idiot
doing something like that
Let's go over there
Please, go ahead
Please.
It's Numazaki, long time
Takakura-kun, I'm Numazaki.
I knew it, you were alive after all
I am dressed like that.
What are you doing here?
If you look at this, you'll understand
When I saw you last time,
you had confident eyes,
but did you come all this way just to say that?
No, it was a coincidence that I met you
I came to look for the gang that obstructed the investigation of the shadowy goods,
and you are what?
I am a reporter for the Democratic News.
Is that gang in this cabaret?
Well, they probably are
You should be careful.
You should be careful,saying something trivial could cost you your life
Leave those matters to the police
There are men even the police can't handle
He obstructed the crackdown
It's not just a joke; you must know that man well
Surely, he's inside this building
millions of Japanese people have died for war.
My brother died.
and some of my friends also died.
I thought it would be okay to die too, wishing to live forever in death
But what does that matter? It was a hollow illusion
The war was not fought by the Japanese
It's a war of aggression carried out by military factions as part of the military business
What a scene it is for those who have thrown away their lives
Isn't it pitiful?
It's millions of war dead, tens of millions of war victims
it's a dream.
It's a nightmare
it's no joke—if it's a dream, I'll wake up
Our lives burned away and were lost
Spinning like a pawn with all our strength
Let's spin that common one more time
A new Japan is beginning, moving, and advancing; you will understand its form now
You will also come to understand your own form accurately
The world is moving now
You are happy.
You live boldly
With such courage.
human history has been depicted in the midst of a raging tide,
and everyone has lived through it
I'm no good; I've withdrawn from life
I can't go back to being human
Please come this way
if it's dancer's room,
you just need to walk up these stairs
Could you please call her here?
Is it okay if we just meet for a bit?
Please go ahead.
what's wrong?
Takao
Shizuko is saying she wants you to come
She says let's have a meal together to celebrate my job offer
I don't wanna go.
come on
Shizuko is really wanting to see you
Both my older sister and brother
must be looking down on me in their hearts
It's not true.
Hey.
Is he Mr. Sagawa from the Aikoku newspaper, right?
And the master here
He is your boss, huh?
Well, that's about it
Anyway, come visit once
What?
I'll come again
Next time I show up here,
your boss is in trouble
Be careful until then.
What's wrong?
It's none of your business.
Your good person is waiting
You don't really belong in this apartment
How about a house with a white bathroom and a soft bed?
That sounds nice,
let's do it later
you're being noisy
Since it's a body that was sold anyway
I won't run away anymore
So okay.
But tonight is no good
No? Why not?
I can't.
Didn't you understand?
Wait for 2 more days,
2 days?
Then it will be the day after tomorrow
Let's go to Kamakura
This is the new house I bought
It's okay if I owe you.
Really? Thank you.
Then I'm off.
Numazaki will take care of you
Numazaki?
What job does he do?
Is he unemployed?
It could be.
Well,
Lady,please come this way.
Don't worry.
Well then, excuse me
Hold on.
Are you leaving?
Your lover will be coming soon
I'm just in the way
You're just a tout
At least have some tea
Don't worry.
Thank you for your work.
What kind of man is Sagawa?
He's a great man.
A great man?
Goodbye
Hold on.
The entrance is over there
You're a smart person.
You already know the layout of this house
If it's about this house, I know even where the trash can is
This is my old friend's house.
Shall I play you about something?
Believe it or not, I used to
be called a lady back in the day.
There are many such women after the war.
Go home
I can stay for just 5 more minutes
I'll also talk about Sagawa for your reference
So what happens next?
You're quite curious
I'm interested in your story
I put myself through shame to make a living.
I had to provide for my siblings.
About Kenji?
And I wanted revenge
Did you make it?
And don't make fun of me.
I'm looking for the man who assassinated my father.
he shone like a light in the darkness
That child had the eyes of a soldier
On August 14th
He killed my dad.
That house burned down, my father died,
and though it's not your line,
there are many hardships
I have lived only with the weapon of the woman's body
So splendidly like this
My brother Hirabayashi is a man known as the demon prosecutor
He put all freedom lovers in prison during the war.
He's a terrible man
, and now he's trembling in fear of revenge
What's wrong? Huh?
I've run out of my medication.
I don't know if he's a demon prosecutor or what, but
There's no need to be that scared
That's a very pathetic phobia.
Yet, they look down on me
I'm here right now
I was assassinated for those people
Where is your father, who was assassinated?
He's in here.
Mistumasa Toda.
My father.
I knew it.
Killing such an important person is completely wrong
Do you remember the officer's face at that time?
I can't understand; it was pitch dark,
but his eyes were shining
How about it? Should we go home from here?
Go home?
Just for this moment,I am a human being
Even a worthless person can, in a moment, possess the soul of a good person
Now, let's go
You are one of Sagawa's underlings, right?
That's right, I'm the man who sold my body
and gave my soul to Sagawa
And now, I'm telling you to get away from Sagawa
That guy is someone who will suck the bones dry
Originally, he was a gambler who mixed with the criminals
During the war, he colluded with the military,
roaming the occupied territories and doing
everything he could as a brothel manager
After the defeat, he hides behind the mask of democracy
He has a wife,
children, and a tall mansion
He even own a villa like this
He is a detestable person who only uses the facade of a calm life for himself
Once I shake his hand, it's over
This sample is me
I've become such a yakuza-like man
Huh? Isn't that you, senpai?
With a woman.
Huh? What's going on here?
This is getting complicated, isn't it?
Kei.
I wonder if everything will be okay
For what?
Is Sagawa coming back soon?
Don't worry about it.
your body is fine?
I'll be okay
He's here.
Jiro.
Can't you here me?
My apologies.
Ask Numazaki to come my room.
Do you need something?
Have a seat.
Say something.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
Oh, is it about today?
Actually, I have a small request regarding that
Could you send that woman for me?
You are quite funny
Huh? I've fallen in love with a woman for the first time
Please give it to me
Why don't you go to a cup shop and cool your head?
Then let's talk again
I see, let's cool it down.
Damn it.
Umazaki is no longer usable
It seems better for you not to be here, so hurry home
I'll send you off
I'll be waiting at the bridge, so get ready, okay?
Hey Aki-chan
hey Aki-chan, are you really going to kill him?
Because it's an order, right?
But you, big brother....
He has been acting like a fool lately.
Hey Aki-chan
Did it hurt?
Cheer up
Thank you.
But you're really good at this
I was sent as a temporary nurse during the war since middle school
Hmm, there are things I learned in the war that can be useful
Oh, how did you get this wound?
It's nothing, just a battle scar
Did you get hit by a bullet?
A cut? Huh?
Did something happen?
Huh? I'm going home,
you can't just stay like that,
you need to wear right?
It's dangerous, so please stay here.
It's fine if you stay here
But I'm going home.
Stay here for a while.
I don't wanna be alone now
Well, I'm glad the wounds are not serious.
Sorry for causing you trouble
It's nice to be doing this, isn't it?
Yeah, it's nice
I feel a bit hazy
You know, I'm just remembering something right now
Back when I was a child
There was a time when I fell asleep while playing hide and seek
Why were you so kind to me?
It seems that love can inspire courage in people
Me?
Yeah, you're a good person
Yeah, I'm just a worthless yakuza
Humans are not perfect
Your words are healthy and positive
You should get out of this society quickly, huh?
If you help me to do that,
You are stupid.
Was that you who shoot me behind?
No.
Aki.
What?
Aki?
I was just told by the boss to keep watch
Go home and say him bullshit.
I'm going to greet him.
so I'm just here to cool my head and say hello, okay?
Doesn't it hurt, Kei-chan?
I'm not particularly concerned
Then what is this?
This hole is nothing
Don't mess with me!
You bastard! Ugh!
new democratic media
leave from here
They seem to have realized something
Just give him money
How much?
5,000 yen
I'm Sagawa
I am Takakura
Thank you for meeting me despite your busy schedule.
Have a seat.
It seems like you're having some trouble
It's just that I can't dance
Well, let me put it simply
Are you not involved in the Showa Sangyo's confiscation of materials incident?
Huh? I don't really understand the meaning anymore
As you can see, I'm a newspaper person on the first floor, and that newspaper has a neutral nature
It's interesting how you expose things recklessly like that
I also take pictures of newspapers
Our newspaper is on the side of the people
We won't use gangs to interfere with investigations
This is something you shouldn't hear
It seems that I have some connection to the Showa Sangyo incident
Mr. Sagawa, I have quite a
bit of confidence in saying this.
I don't know what kind of confidence you have, though
If I have any doubts, the police should come;
Police will tie me up, right?
You can't be tied up by the police
The only thing that can tie you up is the opportunity presented by society, like a newspaper
You'll regret this soon enough
That's not how you should speak
You should say that only after you have clear evidence
I have about 80% of that evidence in my hands
I tracked down the truck that was carrying the gang, and there should be one of my classmates among them
Who are you talking about?
Who?
I got taken for a ride at the pachinko last night
From behind, you know
So what about that?
I feel like I have to thank you,
so I'm currently looking for the person who made this happen
Oh, it's you, Umazaki
You're here.
Oh, is this your classmate?
If you need something from me, come later.
Is this alright, President?
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey, Takakura,
what's going on?
Look at this leg.
It's this leg
Ah, how many people have been deprived of peace
and freedom and died miserably for his sake?
In the cruel empire of death, forced to create a rhythm in a dark trial,
everything that loves guns has been thrown into prison for him
Even the old demon Kenji, who was once wise, must be living a life now afraid of modern sounds, right?
It's okay to be afraid
It's okay to suffer
While I was locked up there,
my wife died
She had a pitiful death
Thinking about that,
I hate him
That Hirabayashi
He might come here
Takako
What should I do?
You shouldn't have to suffer so much
You shouldn't have done such terrible things
It's a military faction, it's a political party
If you have such a noble excuse,
then there's no need to be so anxious, right?
Takako, please be bullied that much
I don't mind suffering
it's sad because she's my wife and family
Can't you ask Mr. Sagawa for help?
Yes, please.
I think I'm going to stop dating Mr. Sagawa
Huh, why?
Welcome!
Oh, it was Mr. Sagawa
I thought it was someone else,
and I wanted to talk to you
What do you need from me?
Hirabayashi-san,
Takakura-kun has challenged you to a duel! Huh?
A duel?
What will you do?
Will you accept it?
Absolutely not!
I can't.
Do it.
I'm right here with you
I'm a man too
Once I take you into my custody,
I will finally be able to support you
It's just fortunate that he made the request
This is self-defense on our part
This will stabilize your life
You won't have to live in fear,
although Numazaki is there on the other side.
Numazaki?
That's not true.
you just don't know
Takakura and Numazaki are friends from school days
I heard Numazaki brought Takakura to the newspaper company
I can't believe it
Well, that's up to you, I suppose
However, if you find out that he is the murderer, your perception of him might change somewhat
After all, it's probably a crime you had him commit
On the night of August 14, just before the defeat, he assassinated one of the key figures
What's wrong with wound?
He doesn't seem to care at all about killing someone
He will even sabotage his own side
for the sake of money
That guy is terrible.
Takakura is trying to expose the
our actions in the newspaper,
He is provoking a duel.
He made the request
Feel free to take on the challenge with confidence
Yes.
Takako
What should I do then?
Mr.Hirabayashi.
Is it okay to come to Shohei Bridge at 10 o'clock?
Ah, but
well, don't worry
I'm right here with you
What should I do, Takako?
Takako.
You know, he wants to duel with you
he used a reverse grip
It's ridiculous that someone like me would be challenged to a duel, isn't it?
He's the man they call the demon prosecutor
If it comes down to it,
he will reveal his true identity from back in the day
This is a means to defeat you in self-defense
I don't want to misunderstand such foolishness as lineage in this day and age
I will justly judge in the name of society and bring a harsh lawsuit
I completely agree with
that, however...
He is currently filling in the land at 10 PM tonight
I should be waiting for you under the Kobiyashi Bridge at Sanjukenbori
Anyway, did you say it?
Huh?
You should clearly say that you
will file a complaint from your own mouth,
but there is something more important than that
I need to settle the conversation with Sagawa.
Mr. Takakura, our president, won't run away
On the contrary, he wants to have a discussion with you
First, take care of what has come your way before that
It's almost 10 o'clock
What's wrong Numazaki ?
Moriyama, medicine?
Medicine?
I don't have anything like that
Just ask that person for it
What?
He needs something.
Huh?
What did you come here for?
I need the medicine again.
You are a selfish man
I don't know
Go home
the medicine is here?
Open it! Let it out!
Let it out!
Stop it.
Don’t mess with me.
For you,
How much have I spent until today?
The medicine for you costs 1,500 yen a day.
You were the first to make me drink it.
I'm sorry about that. Well then, I'll stop it right now.
Please, just one more time
If I weren't here, you wouldn't be able
to get your hands on the Medicine.
Please.
So, are you going to listen to what I say?
Sure.
Are you sure?
Can you kill your friend, the reporter?
Let that Hirabayashi-san have a duel.
You don't even have to wave your hand directly
I hope they both fall at the same time
I can't do something like that.
The key to the medicine is here
What do you think?
The medicine is here
What will you do?
Please give me my medicine quickly
Don't you want to feel better?
Your head will dry up soon, and your blood will freeze
So, what do you think? Are you going to do it?
I'll do anything.
What?
Oh you.
Sagawa
Just leave
Open up!Sagawa
Sagawa
You are so persistent
Why did you come?
I came because I have a favor to ask
Please
Get out.
I'm just a loser
Let me go.
You and I don't care anymore
Get out.
Just wait a minute!
Open up!Sagawa
Damn it.
Hirabayashi has just arrived.
Mr. Hirabayashi
You remember my face, don't you?
I'm Takakura, the one was taken over by you
I won't duel.
I will judge you in the name of the law.
I will definitely make you atone for your sins.
Hirabayashi-san
Sagawa-san!
Sagawa-san!! Please come!
Taka-chan, Takako-san.
What's wrong?
Numazaki, stop it!
I'm not going to duel anyone
I told you it's just a meeting
but you came.
No way.
Damn it, stop! Did you bring me here to make me duel?
Don't say such foolish things.
Can you support me?
You're man.
You must settle your own past
I made a promise with you!
Good luck,Numazaki.
Sagawa-san! Sagawa-san!
if we attract attention, It will be troublesome
Let's go home
You better keep your eyes on here.
Umazaki!
I understand what you guys are trying to do!
What the hell are you? Are you even human?
Do you know what you're trying to do right now?
Everything is going as Sagawa planned.
even Kei-chan might get caught up in it
That's the kind of guy he is
Sagawa has been using Kei-chan with drugs all this time
I see.
I didn't know that.
Takako
Takakura was a good person
I won't run or hide anymore.
if there's someone to judge me, let them judge
Even if it's just one day,
I want to live a human life where I can laugh.
Brother!
Now, if you want to defeat me, go ahead and try
Even if I collapse here
and now, there are countless eyes of the people behind me
You can't deceive those eyes.
You and I are no longer friends;
I'm leaving now,
Tomorrow's newspaper will have an article about obstruction of justice
Numazaki is late, isn't he?
I also kill him tonight.
I hope he did well.
Moriyama.
Can you take a look?
Let's go take a look
The rain has probably stopped.
Numazaki
How about having a drink?
It went well?
Thank you for your hard work
I will return the cup
I have been in your care for a long time,
but I must now cut ties
I see, that's good to hear
You're going to give me medicine again, aren't you?
My body will no longer need that, I suppose
What does that mean?
I plan to go from here to the one place that can fix the support
I'm going to the Metropolitan Police Department.
I will be in a jail.
In a jail?
That way, I will be able to crush the gang surrounding you, the society, the nest of corruption that has poisoned everything
That is the least I can do to atone for my sins
That's quite an outrageous claim you have there
Wait!
Can't you breath?
Get your hands off of me!
You should suffer more.
You have committed a crime that has defiled society.
Help me.
Suffer more, suffer more, it's good to suffer
He's dead...
I killed him...
I killed someone again
Takako.
It was also me who killed your father
I did it.
I knew it.
You knew it?
Turn yourself in and get out
And with your new beginning
You killed my father.
That sin is redeemed by your current feelings.
It will be compensated.
I can forgive you too
so let's go.
Someone is coming, huh?
Hey.
You should turn yourself in after assessing the situation.
Well...
Would you like to stop by my room?
Which one you want?
Hmm? right one is Sagawa's right?
Oh yeah.
but it was a short relationship, wasn't it?
Short yet infinitely long
Dawn is approaching.
This is the sake we love for our wedding, isn't it?
Today is truly the shining day of my life.
Kei.
I'm glad you are alive.
I'm so glad I got to meet you.
Same here.
THE END