Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
BURY ME DEEP
Hello?
What?
Where are you coming from?
I come from Tokyo
You sound like a country person.
I was in Kyushu on vacation
After all, Tokyo people are no good in the countryside.
I was supposed to be on vacation for half a month, but I cut it short after a week and came back.
I see
I want to take a hot spring in Kyushu as long as I have money
People in Tokyo miss the lights and noise of this city
Have you changed in Tokyo?
Stocks crashed
There were many suicides
That's a life
Life is more fun with such events!
Who are you?
Hey
Why you are here?
Oh
Welcome back home
You back home late
No, I back home early
So tell me who you are
Don't pretend you don't know
Do you want to drink?
Unfortunately I hate brandy
I only drink scotch
I have no idea
I think something is wrong
You are Nakabe,aren't you?
Yes I am
So I'm right
I don't know what you are doing
I am a lawyer
That's scary job
You have a plan for what you're going to do.
Let's be with me tonight
I have no idea
You know what
You smell good
What kind of perfume do you use?
It ’s a Parisian perfume called Disaster
It ’s a disaster in Japanese.
That's a disaster for which I am grateful.
I'm worried about what will happen after this
He's coming
We can show off him
Excuse me but I came to collect rent
I'm sorry to bother you
I'll come tomorrow
He was the superintendent.
Let's start
For what?
Good things
Oh!
Are you OK?
Take me
I want you to go home now
Put on your cloth
Hey!
You can't sleep here
Give me some water
Water?
Here is your water
Don't sleep
Wake up!
Oh my god
Tell me where do you live?
Tokyo apartment room 7
This is where I am now
She's up to some mischief.
Hello?
I'm Nakabe in Tokyo apartment
Can you send me a cab?
How long does it take?
3 mins, I see, thanks
Put on cloth
We are here as promised to take pictures of your love scenes.
What?
Who did this mischief?
We detectives do not leak personal information
There is a beautiful woman here and we will take her picture
No one here. go home!
Don't make fun of me
I'm here for work
No one here. go home!
Damn it, they come here to take a photo. that's bullshit
I’m sorry to have kept you waiting
What's wrong?
She's drunker
Those customers are unwelcome
If she doesn't wake up, take her to the police
This is the money
Leave it to you
Oh my god
Where is Michi
I sent her by cab
Don't tell a lie.
She is hiding somewhere
Who are you by the way?
Hey, I'm a lawyer
I will sue you for illegal invasion
It smells of her perfume.
Where is her?
She's my girl.
Don't play with her anymore!
Who is he?
Today is a very strange night
This is what Tokyo is
Tokyo is too exciting
I wonder I can go to sleep
It was a disaster
Is it English or French?
Hey, wake up!
Who are you guys?
I'm Inspector Takeda of the Metropolitan Police Department
Police?
Did something happen?
Look, Is the man?
Yes he is
What's wrong?
Oh you are the...
I took sleeping pills.
Did you get up?
No...
She's still sleeping
It means you died in the car
Eh?
What did you make her drink?
I didn't.
She was drunk
What?
That
This alcohol
She was drinking this
Is this yours?
She brought this in
Please come to the police station anyway
I don't understand what you say.
She was drinking alone in the apartment
She obviously came to your room
It is incongruous that you do not know it.
I still have a headache because of sleeping pills
Yes that's right.
That's incongruous
I have no idea
Why she came in your room?
I'm sure Mr. Akutagawa forgot to lock it.
Mr. Akutagawa?
He has been a friend of mine since childhood
He is a sergeant in a trading company called Akutagawa Bussan.
I lent him the key and rented the room
For love affair?
He was discussing divorce with his wife
He stayed at a friend's house or hotel instead of going home
So She was his lover?
I think so
As a result of the inspection, this was included in that brandy
There was a chloran
This is a medicine that makes you sleepy and faint
Are you sure that Brandy is not yours?
I am not a brandy drinker. I have never bought one.
Why was it in your room?
You make me say the same thing over and over again
She brought it in or something
It's your job to find out
Detective man and cameraman Then a strange man came in
Do you remember them?
Yes I do
If they really came here to take pictures, there must be a reason.
We should investigate Akutagawa first
Will you help us?
Please come in
Welcome Nakabe-san
You come earlier
I came back to Tokyo last night
He is Inspector Takeda of the Metropolitan Police Department
Nice to meet you
Please have a seat
Is something happened?
A woman died in my apartment last night
Oh
I don't know her at all
Why she was his room?
We don't know well.
I thought she was a friend of your husband
He used my room while I was away
That is what I came to ask you about.
Where is your husband?
He's been away for a while
Why?
That's a very rude question
It's Ok.
We were talking about divorce
What is the cause of your divorce?
He has mistress?
Stop saying it
Do you know a woman called Michi
I don't know her.
He's lonely and like women, but he doesn't have a mistress
Do you know where he is now?
I have no idea
I'm sorry to hear that it's very rude.
We are leaving now
Are you leaving now?
We'll see you soon
I didn't sleep last night
You can't sleep today
There are many newspaper reporters in front of your apartment
There are many newspaper reporters
So you can stay here
I have a lot to discuss with him.
Thank you
Can I stay here?
Yes
But Please help me find Mr. Akutagawa
OK
Sorry to disturb you
Take care
See you
Why does he play with women when he has such a beautiful wife?
Marital relationships are difficult
So don't you get married
I just don't have a marriage partner
I will pick you up at 5 o'clock
I've been waiting for you
I heard that the distribution of property is over
I received this house and shares totaling 20 million yen.
He is thinking of me and blames himself for the divorce.
He is a very honest and weak man
You are too strong compared to him
That's probably the cause of your divorce
I think of myself as a weak woman
I can't live without someone's support
You are very nicely raised
You are very educated
You acted fine to make him stronger
You were perfect wife
He was weak husband
In the result
You just made his inferiority complex harder.
Why didn't you consult with us?
If you talked to us, we wouldn't have to divorce.
Chizu-san
I would gladly consult if you really loved him
I didn't love him from the beginning
I just wanted his money
I was able to be with him
You are strong
On the contrary he loved you.
So he couldn't live with you
You can live with him together even if you don't love him
He loves you so he divorces
You and he have completely different personalities
I don't want to be the one to arbitrate between you guys.
Are your lawyers doing it right?
Yes. He's doing well
What are you going to do after divorcing?
I haven't decided yet
I'm living alone now
I need someone who support me
Wife, your meal is ready
I see.
Please come
This is Akutagawa's
Thank you
We will prepare your bath, so please come in when you are ready.
Please make yourself at home
Oh, you are awake
I couldn't sleep
Why?
I was thinking of you and Akutagawa
Nakabe-san
Am I bad woman?
Why?
I'm scared of myself
Please help me,Nakabe-san
Chizu-san
Time will heal your hearts and minds.
You need to wait
There are times in life when you have to be patient.
May I help you?
Mr.Takeda is waiting for Nakabe-san
I'll be there soon
Welcome
Where is Akutagawa?
He's in back
It's good timing,Nakabe-san
We're in trouble
Welcome
Akutagawa
Hey, Akutagawa!
He was terribly drunk from last night.
He fell asleep here.
We're in trouble
Can you take him out?
Madam, come here
I'm leave it to you
Hey, Akutagawa!
Who're you?
Oh Nakabe
I thought you were in Kyushu
I was bored so I've come back earlier
I understand you've been
drinking since last night.
No way, I've just started to drink
Give me brandy!
Oh, I have an appointment.
What time is it now?
I have an appointment with nice woman
At your room
Can you stay at hotel for me?
Wait. What her name?
I have no idea.
I won't know until I see her.
You are so drunk that you have gotten the days wrong by a day.
Don't say bullshit.
I've made an appointment on 31st May
But Today is 1st of June
She was died
Eh?
She was poisoned.
She was died as soon as She left my room.
So I was suspected by police
Please explain to me why you have appointment with the woman
He is Takeda police
I have no idea.
Ask Tamai lawyer
What's wrong with Tamai lawyer?
In short,We ended up divorcing, but relatives blamed
Chizu.
They say all is her fault
So I made a plan
I cheat systematically.
I get my picture taken.
I am photographed by a weekly magazine having sex with a woman
So they stop blaming her.
Chizu is also hurtled
It means, I am so bad man, Chizu is nice wife.
So we can divorce easily
Do you think this is good idea?
Did you ask the plan to Tamai lawyer?
That's right. I asked him to send a woman who can play with me
Then camera man comes
The door was open.
Did you unlock on purpose?
Yes I intended
Did you know there was poison in the brandy?
I have no idea at all
Please trust me
The key is Tamai lawyer
I want you to see her dead body
Do you know her?
We don't know her identity yet
I have no idea
Manager.
He's Tamai lawyer
I'm Takeda
That's a problem
I was surprised to read the news
Is she the woman whom you sent Nakabe's room?
Yes She is
She's called Michi Oka strip dancer
What do you have something to do with her?
She was a key witness in a case I was working on.
Did you ask the witness in another case
to be the woman in Mr. Akutagawa's play?
Yes, She took this work for 100000yen
So I wrote an address memo and give it to her
Tokyo apartment 2F room 7.
That's my room
I got suspected because of you
You are Nakabe,right?
I've heard about you from Chizu
Did you know there was poison in the brandy?
I have no idea
What is your other case?
This is the issue of Mr. Tokumaru's estate's auto accident.
Please explain to us in detail
It was 15th Nov, half year ago
54 years Old Tokumaru returned with a woman
called Keiko matsumoto who is 25 years old bar hostess
Let's go
Please go together
Thanks
Then, half an hour later, a terrible accident
happened.
He may have fallen asleep at the wheel.
Michi oka found the car.
She was the first witness
Both the driver and Tokumaru died instantly.
Only his wife Keiko was alive at the moment
Michi asked a nearby person to call the police
Keiko died when the ambulance came
Michi OKa is the only witness who can prove that Tokumaru-san died before Keiko-san.
That's right
Mr. Tokumaru had a formal will
If Tokumaru dies first, 80% of his property will belong to his wife.
The remaining 20% will belong to his niece, Megumi Tokumaru.
If Keiko dies first, 80% of heritage will belong to Megumi Tokumaru.
The remaining 20% will be donated to social work
How much is his legacy?
It's about 200 million yen
It's about 200 million yen?
That's a lot of money.
Enough amount to motivate a crime
For now, Tokumaru died first, so the property belongs to Keiko.
However, Keiko also died, so his property belongs to her close relatives.
Who is the her close relatives?
Keiko's older brother Hideo Matsumoto.
Who asked for this case?
From the Matsuoto
I see
You proceeded to negotiate with Mr. Mitchie to make his testimony legally valid.
That's right
The other passenger who got in the car with them also died?
He is missing now
He is missing now?
According to Michi, he was thrown out of the car when the accident happened.
He wasn't there when she called and came back to the scene
That's strange
You lost one of your important witnesses in this case, right?
That's right
If this case is related to an inheritance
Megumi Tokumaru has a motive to kill Michi
A man named Hideo Matsumoto is also related to inheritance.
And you are related too,Tamai
Why do you think so?
You've already collected the testimony you need, right?
If you had decided to give some rebate to MICHI
It ’s better to kill her
You!
Don't say bullshit
Please stop selfish reasoning
So you are saying I am innocent.
maybe
Thanks
This is a disaster
disaster?
It is called disaster in English
Hello? I'm Nakabe
Who are you?
Mind your own business.
You talked about Michi?
Yes I did
Listen.
You should be careful
If you talk about strange things, you will be killed.
Unfortunately I am lawyer.
I'm used to being threatened.
You should be careful
Be careful before it's too late
Wait!
Who was he?
Tokumaru side?
Or Matsumoto?
Hello? I'm Nakabe
Oh chizu
I was innocent I'm sorry to worry
That's good to hear
I was very worried about you
Have you found the culprit yet?
Eh? Akutagawa and Tamai?
Oh no...
They are so stupid
But The killer may have used the madness to confuse the case.
That's scary
I am also responsible
I'm scared and painful every day
I can't stand anymore
Chizu-san
Please rest without thinking tonight
Time will heal you
See you
Good night
There was poison in this brandy
Manager
Thanks for your work
He was there when I went near the Michi's apartment
He looks just like the guy who went to your apartment
You killed her!
Sit down
I'm sure he is
I see
Is he michi's man?
He was her gigolo
He tried to get some money from her handbag while she was taking a bath and found a piece of paper with your address on it.
Oh that memo
He misunderstood and went to your house
He may have been jealous and poisoned Brandy
I don't know!
I loved her
It's impossible I killed her
How did you get that diamond ring?
She gave it to me
Don't tell a lie!
You stole it!
Let him rest a little.
It ’s better not to talk too much in front of a lawyer.
Was there anything in her room?
500,000 yen was deposited in her bankbook last November 20th
November 20th?
She started working at a nightclub called Manhattan from that day
It's a lot of money for a contract
Manager
I found it
Good
This ring is said to have been sent to his wife by Mr. Tokumaru, who died in a car accident.
Oh this is Tokumaru's
Yoshikawa has this
It ’s a 3 carat diamond.
Why did Michi have this?
This is Keiko's belongings, so it belongs to her brother, Hideo Matsumoto.
Michi had deal something?
She might have wanted the ring instead of giving a favorable testimony
Or she may have stolen this ring at the scene of the accident
In any case,Michi has something to do with the issue of inheritance of Tokumaru's heritage.
You are in danger if you are involved in this case
I had a threatening phone call last night
He thought michi said something to me
I would like to see the face of the person I made the threatening call to.
Excuse me
I'm sorry to interrupt you but is there Megumi Tokumaru?
It's me
I quickly realized that you were Michi's lawyer
I saw it in the newspaper
I see
So You knew her
Yes I met her for the first time on the morning of the day she died
Where?
At my apartment
I asked her to visit me.
She said my uncle died first but wanted to ask if it was true
What she said?
She said she would be willing to change her testimony if I gave her half of my inheritance.
Who do you talk to about this issue?
My uncle has died.
I have no relatives
How about Hideo Matsumoto?
I only met him a couple of times.
I hate him
Can you introduce me to a good lawyer?
I need a good, inexpensive, honest and kind lawyer
There is no such lawyer
Lawyers are all realistic
We want a high paid job
Finally I want to ask you another one
Did you give her any presents?
For example, a ring or brandy
Is it a poisoned Brandy?
You think I killed her?
Because she is the only witness against you.
There was enough ...
motive for the murder?
It's true that I don't hesitate to kill people for money
Because my uncle is gone and no one is supporting me.
I understand.
Thank you
If you need the lawyer I'll introduce you
Hello?
Who?
What?
I am a person from insurance company
insurance company?
Ikebo!
An insurance company person is here.
It seems that Grandpa Kumai had life insurance.
If all goes well, money will come in again.
Which company?
I'm from Showa insurance company
How much is life insurance?
5 million
Are you police,right?
I won't be fooled.
I contacted various insurance companies
The old man didn't have any insurance with any insurance company.
Don't pretend to be the police
So let me ask you plainly.
Why did you give Michi a diamond ring?
I have been asked by police about it many times
I need to ask you again
How much did Michi ask you for a rebate?
A lawyer said 20%
In addition, I was asked for a diamond ring that my sister was wearing at the time of the accident.
So did he write the conditions?
But when that document is ready, Mr. Michie is in the way.
You have a motive for murder
No way.
I don't do that
I won't do anything dangerous like murdering
Michi was talking to Tokumaru's niece
So This would make anyone want to kill her.
Really?
She talks to Tokumaru's niece?
I'll hit her if she's alive
OK that's enough
Unfortunately I'm not police
I'm a lawyer named Nakabe
See you
Who's he?
Welcome back.
I told the superintendent of the apartment building that I am your sister and he unlocked the door.
This is for you
The newspaper said you like whiskey
You look different
It doesn't contain poison, right?
Because I am very careful about unauthorized entry of women.
Don't worry
I'm here to ask you something
Will you be my lawyer?
I'm not the romantic lawyer you want
It's ok
I will give you the money I was going to give to Michi-san.
In short,Is it 50% of the heritage you receive?
And if that wasn't enough, I can give you all of it.
What do you mean?
I want to marry you
Because I am alone
I need someone who support me
I was crashed on you when I met you first time
Look
Do you think I am cute?
I would be more beautiful if I spent more money.
The more money a woman spends, the more beautiful she becomes
I think it's good but I need to think about it
I will wait until you feel like it
But you can be my lawyer, right?
Ok I will
I'm glad
This is my address
Thanks
You know what
I have another request for you
What?
Will you kiss me one time?
As a sign of the contract
I don't feel safe.
Eh?
So please
Ready?
Love is wonderful
So please
Don't move
Hold up!
Who are you?
It's me
Do you remember my face?
Sakae's Matsukichi?
That's right
You took a fraud case 3 years ago and collected bullshit
testimony.
I was in jail.
Who asked you this?
No one asked me
I'm just here to get back at you.
Don't tell a lie!
I'm sure someone asked you.
He gave you the pistol and drugs
What?
I can see it in your eyes and your wrists.
You have the wrong person to hold a grudge
against.
You got out of jail, but who gave you the drugs?
Shut up!
It's not your business
Say it!
Who asked you?
You will go back to jail for illegal possession of firearms and breaking and entering, if you don't tell me.
Forgive me.
I'll say it
I was asked by Goda.
The boss of Goda company
Goda company?
Why he targets me?
I have no idea.
Please forgive me
Don't tell him otherwise I'll be killed
Damn it
Drugs are no longer effective.
I need to take a drug!
Hello?
Oh Chizu-san
I have not found out it yet
The issue of Mr. Tokumaru's legacy certainly has something to do with
it.
I met with both sides of the inheritance rights holders
today.
Don't involved in that so much
Someone might try to kill you
Eh? Someone just tried to attack you by pistol?
Are you safe now?
That's scary
Please Nakabe-san
Stay out of this case.
Because I'm anxious every day and it's hard for
me.
I'll be mad
So Let's have dinner tomorrow
Listen to music and relax!
Don't worry about me
Good night
The boss of Goda company
Goda?
Did you find out?
It's easy for me
What kind of guy is he?
He's modern gang
He was arrested for extortion several years ago.
He was sentenced to 10 years in prison.
He got sick in prison and was paroled on the grounds of illness.
He owns Mitchi's strip bar, but I don't think he had anything to do with the case.
Or you got any news?
Don't think too much.
Thank you!
I got good information
He owns Mitchi's strip bar
The Goda sent Sakai to kill me
There's something
Welcome back
I went there
How was it?
I checked passenger manifests at the airline.
There are only 10 passengers
Exclude Tokumaru and Keiko, there were 8 passengers
They are couple
They are Parent and child
Other 4 passengers, he and he are Catholic
priests
Catholic nun
Ichiro Sanada
The person is left
I could find out his address
Fake name?
Maybe
I see
OK, I'll go to Manhatten bar tonight
Are you Ok to go there alone?
We can go together
No way, I have a date with a woman
I have a date with a woman
Cheers
For what?
For your happiness
Do I have happiness?
People all think so
Either people in a hurry every day and people unhappy, or people have a dream and people happy.
I am the latter.
Will you dance with me?
I'm waiting for you
Whiskey
Excuse me because my friend came
Thanks for last night
Where can I meet with Goda?
I don't know
If you lie, you'll be in jail again
Tell me
Do you want to see him so much?
I'll ask him.
Wait here
Who's the guy?
He's Goda's subordinate
Welcome
Oh long time no see
I asked her out
I thought she should relieve stress
That's kind of you
Let's drink together
Bring brandy
She is the best celebrity in Japan
Clam down
You look good couple
The upcoming incident has convinced all my relatives to divorce.
You are free to have a date
But Please be careful about beautiful women
I should have been more careful
I am the loser of life
Let's dance with someone
I'll dance
Let's dance
Chizu-san
I'll go home
Our boss is waiting for you
Can you call me later?
Where's he?
I suggest you back off this case.
You wrote this?
No
I've brought him
Come in
First of all, I'm sick
The country worried me and gave me home care
I see.
Here's your house?
Yes I'm living here
This room is registered properly
So What can I do for you?
Your voice looks exactly like the threatening phone I received earlier
I have no idea
So what’s this?
You drugged Mr. Sakai and tried to kill me.
And you wrote this
I have no idea
It's bad for your health if you make a loud voice
When did Mitchi-san start dancing at that bar?
You are not the police, so why should I talk to you?
I don't force to answer
I know the date, 20th Nov
Was she your lover?
No way,
She just wanted my money
You didn't kill her, right?
Of course
Why do you get involved in this case?
This case involves a heritage issue.
Mr. Tokumaru's daughter has asked me to represent her.
Listen, I'm sure you have something to do with this case
Your subordinate met Hideo Matsumoto yesterday
What?
If he wants to get his commission, he has to get a little more than his daughter's share.
It was necessary to overturn her testimony
Shut up!
I'm sick so leave me alone
How much you need to get back this issue?
If you try to kill me I will tell the police about this pistol
Take care of your health
Damn it
That dude
Need cab?
I don't need
Welcome
Wait!
Are you OK?
Stop
My room is there
Oh Nakabe-san
There is big problem again
Again?
Around here?
It's a close distance
Can I get fingerprints?
I can't find it
Oh Nakabe
What's wrong?
Akutagawa!
I thought you were killed
Look
The criminal was looking at his shadow
He tried to kill me?
maybe.
2 shots in close distance
It seems that he wrapped the pistol in a blanket and shot it
The sound of the shower was so noisy that the neighbor didn't understand it.
Damn it. who killed him
Do you have an alibi?
Eh?
You are also one of the suspects
I hear you are dating with the wife
No way
Why should I kill my best friend since I was a kid
The police will prove my alibi
I was at the police station last night after being attacked by a pistol in the town
Oh, who tried to kill you?
I'm sorry
As you know
He died on my behalf
Don't say that
He seemed dead before he died
I made him do that
I'd rather be responsible for it.
I was purposely running away from your problems.
I'm thinking of going on a trip for a while
I'm thinking of going to a quiet place
That's good for you
Enjoy yourself
Will you go with me?
I'd love to have you.
Oh you are here
It's been a disaster.
But your divorce problem has been resolved naturally.
You are mean
Watch your mouth.
Sorry
By the way
I understand that you have retained Tokumaru Megumi at all. to represent you in an estate matter.
Yes that's true
I see
Wife
It is better to solve these problems so each other democratically!
A lawyer is a collaborator.
Why was my collaborator attacked so many times?
What does this have to do with me?
At least you and your client are suspicious
I'll sue you if you're rude
Stop it
I'm leaving now
Let's talk about your family register problem later
I was sorry to bother you
See you
Promise me what I said
Yes, if I'm free
Good morning
We have a visitor.
Who?
He doesn't say his name
Oh
Isn't it supposed that you can't go out except at the hospital at home?
I sneaked out
You have something wrong
Actually I was caught in a trap
Will you be my attorney?
What is your mansion's requirement?
I want no part of this issue.
I have enough money
What makes you so afraid?
I can't say
I can overcome this crisis if you ignore the disadvantages to me
I reject
I'm not such a lawyer
What?
Please get out
You are so nasty
What happened to the bandage?
I just got a little injured.
Don't crush my face
Don't tell anyone I visited you
I know
You're on parole, so it's a problem.
Damn it
Oh Goda?
We'll find out now
Goda got injured on his wrist
I don't know where Sakai is
Yoshikawa lives in Michi's apartment
Gouda's subordinates Kochi is missing
He had a great fight with Goda.
What is the cause?
Find out the cause of his injury anyway.
He may have been injured with a pistol
Kochi had a great fight with Goda.
Money or woman
Where are you going to?
I'll see Yoshikawa at Michi's apartment
Here it is
Thanks
Don't move
No worry
He's just knocked out from the beating I gave
him.
Why you've come here?
That's good you are here.
I'm here to ask about you to Yoshikawa
Sit down
What do you want to know about me?
About Michi
I recently had a fight with him.
He was just her jigoro
Michi is mine so her property is mine
But All her things were sold.
Are you looking for her diamond ring?
So you are here to get it from Yoshikawa,right?
That's right.
But he said police took the ring
Damn it
Did you fight with Goda?
About Matsumoto's share of property or Micchi?
Goda neither want money nor her body
He was treated by her
Why?
I can't say.
I need to go
Listen,
Don't tell anyone that I came here
It is easy to kill you
Are you left handed?
This pistol is the only legacy my parents left
me.
Get him some water.
He'll be awake
Get well
Welcome back
Oh you
The superintendent thinks I am totally your
sister.
You had a hard time
Two people were killed in this room. Aren't you
afraid?
I don't care.
I'll take care of you
What's this?
Shinjuku messenger deliverer it
I'm heading to Hakone
I'll stay at Tonosawa inn
I'll be waiting for you
Can I guess?
From a wife?
No
Your face is telling it
I'm good at reading people's minds.
Are you going?
I won't go
I'm good cooking,ain't  I?
It's better to not to go
Excuse me
We have your visitor
Come in
Thanks for coming
Yes
I'm glad
I've been waiting for this
Chizu-san
It's the first time I see your happy face
Really
I need to take care of Akutagawa's property after
I back  to Tokyo
Will you work on our problem?
It's too troublesome
The tax office is nagging me and my relatives are
complaining.
I don't want to ask to Tamai, so Please
Can you stay one more night?
I need to take care of the case
We'll come back when the case is solved.
I thought you accepted my request to stay out of that case.
I'm trying to work my way to the end.
I can't forgive a person who killed Akutagawa
Really
I will avenge him.
You are really strong
I feel very scary
That's so me
I'll catch 5 pm's train
You really go back?
Yes
Hi
Hey!
You are still alive
Hi
Everyone worry you were missing
I just got some rest
By the way,Have you found the cause of GODA's hand injury?
I checked and it was just a bruise.
Doctors say he has a bad heart.
Doctors say the next time he goes back to prison, he won't make it out
alive.
By the way, The Kochi is left handed?
I have no idea.
Why?
He was at Michi's apartment when I visited there
He used his left hand
He's right handed
He used to be a boxer.
His right strait punch was popular
Something is strange
He got his right hand injured so he used his
left hand
I got it!
Hello
Matsumoto-san
Hideo!
Oh you
If they find out you and I know each other, we're in big trouble.
I didn't want to come here
Kochi is trying to betray me
We don't need the girl
Go upstairs
Have a drink
I can't drink
Kochi is threatening you, right?
He said he would announce your relationship with his dead sister
He is mother fucker
Don't tell anyone about Keiko and me
I know
Tell me your condition if you want to share the legacy
Shut up!
I don't want Tokumaru's property
Do you know where is Kochi?
No
Tell him I give him money but Get off this case.
OK?
Is he the former husband of Keiko?
Yes, he was rich boss before
Why he does not want money?
I have no idea.
He used to be very money hungry.
I found out where Sakai is
Really?
He's in Kiba
Hi I'm Takeda
Are you Takeda?
I'm Nakabe
Goda visited Matsumoto's shop
He was the lover of Tokumaru who died.
Kochi seems to have threatened Matsumoto for that.
But Goda said he doesn't want money
He is a blackmail professional.
But Why?
He hates being involved in the case
I doubt it
I found out that  Sakai is in kiba
I'll go there.
Where are you?
Ok let's meet there
That room
The contractor of the room seems to be a drug patient
He's Matsukichi for sure
help me
Wait
Shit!
Matsukichi!
Who attacked you?
Kochi
He shot you
Matsukichi!
He’s dead
He was beaten and hit his head
Kochi did it
He run away
The criminal is Kochi.
Catch him
Welcome back.
We have a visitor for you
Hi
Welcome back.
I just came back
You should have stayed more
I missed you
How did the case go?
Another murder has just happened
Matsuyoshi Sakai was killed
We know the culprit
That's scary
I think he will be arrested soon and the case will be resolved
I have a weird phone call for you.
From Kochi
Kochi.
connect me
Hi, I'm Nakabe
You can't get away with it, so turn yourself in.
Wait
I didn't mean to kill him
I only hit him once
I have a criminal record, so it's a bit of a problem if it's a murder
If you admit that was a coincidence, I will turn myself in.
Why you attacked him?
He saw me tending to an injury to my right hand the night I shot you.
He threatened me because he wanted drug money
That's why I got so mad.
Why you shot me?
Actually, I have a weak spot in Matsumoto about GODA.
That's a big deal, so I threatened Matsumoto.
He took me up on my offer.
But you are a lawyer who denies Matsumoto's story
So I threatened you
I get it
If you kill Michi and Akutagawa, you are definitely the death penalty.
I definitely didn't kill them
Trust me
I didn't mean to kill Sakai
Where are you now?
What?
I'll go with you. so wait there
Matsuki's murderer turns himself in.
I'll go there
He killed Akutagawa too?
He said he didn't but The case will be resolved soon
Ouch!
This is a wound shot with a pistol
It hurts
What is Goda's secret?
He is the former husband of KEIKO, who is related to Tokumaru
Did they formally get married?
Yes. they were registered
In short,Keiko broke up with Goda and got married
Did they formally file a marriage registration?
They submitted the document
But It was fake document
What? Fake?
Why?
Goda was in a jail for long time
Keiko was with Tokumaru while Goda was in a jail
Goda refused divorce
so Keiko asked Matsumoto
He did something
Keiko entered into marriage with Tokumaru-san before divorcing Tokumaru
This is a duplicate marriage.
No.
Marriage between Tokumaru and Keiko is invalid
In short
Matsumoto does not have the right to inherit heritage
That's why you threatened Matsumoto.
Yes
Why did Goda get so angry to know that
Because you were stealing the share?
He's so angry for another reason
Do you have any idea?
He wasn't in the club for a few days after the car accident
I think he went to Kansai in search of Keiko
He was on parole
He makes a fool of the police
Why did he take the risk and go to Kansai?
There must be some reason
Let's check Goda
The case will be resolved soon
What?
Police is here
Police?
What's wrong?
I'm Higuchi
I'm sick.
Can you come tomorrow?
We are here for urgent business
You have a marital relationship with Keiko Matsumoto in the family register.
So what?
I have nothing to do with the case
Why did you pay Michi 500,000 yen?
For a contract
It was too much for contract
You went to Kansai in search of Keiko Matsumoto.
Don't say bullshit.
I'm sick
We looked up a hotel in Kansai
You went to stop their marriage.
Why do you think so?
I finally get it
You can't leave the hospital or home on your own
You boarded the plane under the alias Ichiro Sanada.
The airplane stewardess is the witness
There were only ten passengers, and the girls said they could easily recognize him by his face.
I loved Keiko
I know I can't leave here without permission
And I'm sick
But I had to go
Did you meet her?
Yes
She told me to wait for a while because she will take as much money as possible from Mr. Tokumaru.
She introduced Tokumaru that I was her uncle
So you came back with the three of you
Yes. I'm so sick
Next time I go to jail, I'll be dead
I wanted to spend the last part of my life in this club I built
I desperately escaped from the scene of the traffic accident
Your right hand was injured at the time of the car accident
Yes
After that Michi came to my club for an interview
She remembered my face
She threatened me and demanded an exorbitant contract fee.
That's all
Why did you threaten me on the phone?
Because I thought MICHI told you that I went to Kansai
That's all
I did not threaten you with me during this time.
Now we have a pretty good idea of what the whole case is about.
If you keep Keiko's duplicate marriage a secret, Hideo Matsumoto will inherit the property.
You worked for him
MICHI now knows about it and threatened you about their duplicate marriage.
You gave Michi a poisoned brandy
I didn't do that
Megumi Tokumaru asked Nakabe Lawyer for the case.
You accidentally shot and killed Mr. Akutagawa
I don't know Akutagawa
Don't say bullshit
You guys are bullying me
I don't know at all
I don't want to go to jail
You are not working on Ms. Matsumoto's estate issue knowing about Keiko's duplicate marriage?
No way.
I didn't know
If you did, you would have to go to jail too
Here are two copies of the family register for Keiko
Marriage between Tokumaru and Keiko Matsumoto is invalid
You acknowledge that Megumi Tokumaru will be an inheritance of heritage?
Yes you are right
I had a terrible time.
Hello
Oh
Let's have a drink together
She's Megumi Tokumaru
Tamai worked for nothing so He laments.
That's too bad.
I can pay him
That's kind to him
So Please toast for me
This is Johnnie walker
I brought this from the apartment
I see
Are there cups?
Please
Did GODA confess to the crime?
He has been denying
Stewardess admits he is with Tokumaru
There's one more thing I don't agree with you
on.
The police will have everything sorted out
I should have never put on the act like your wife told me
to.
I feel responsible.
put on the act? about Michi?
Akutagawa got drunk and told his wife
His wife tried to stop me
But Akutagawa really wanted me to act
Here it is
Cheers for you
I'll answer
Hello? Nakabe?
He's here
From a woman
Hello
Chizu-san
I just saw a newspaper
You've solved the case, congratulations.
I'm glad
I still have my doubts.
I think Goda tell everything later
I want to see you
Come to my apartment
OK then I will visit you
Hello?
What's wrong?
There was a poison in this whiskey
Hello?
Tamai-san
Tamai was killed.
I'll get back to you
Tamai-san
Here is West Ginza building.
Please come right now
He's died
OK
What happened?
Suddenly in agony he collapsed.
Who called police?
When did you bring the whiskey to Nakabe's room?
3,4days ago
Where did you buy it?
At Sanyo department
You've brought it this morning
Yes, I thought we'll have a drink together
Was the whiskey cork open?
The amount of whiskey was the same, but the whiskey cork was
open.
Someone put poison in it at his apartment
If you didn't
Do you suspect me?
You pretend to be his sister, and go to his room
often
No one can go to his room besides you
There is
Who?
The person who give the key to Akutagawa
Takeda-san
We have paid too much attention to the Tokumaru couple's inheritance problems.
The two incidents were related by coincidence.
The killer used the other case to hide his own case
Goda didn't kill Michi and Akutagawa?
This is so scary
I can't believe this
I never thought about that
Where are you going?
Please leave me alone...
Nakabe has come
Welcome
What happened to Tamai-san
He was dead soon
Someone put poison in the whiskey at my room
Someone tried to kill me
Oh
I'm glad you are safe
It was close
I was died if you didn't call me
That's scary
You saved my life.
Chizu-san
Be honest
Eh?
For what?
Be honest
I have no idea
What are you talking about?
Can you return the key?
The key that Akutagawa had
You used the key and entered my room to put
poison in the whiskey
I didn't
I take care of the key but I didn't do it
Michi was killed by poison
Akutagawa was killed by mistaking
We had this idea
By the way, Tamai told me before he died that you knew that Michi went to my apartment for the act
I thought those two murders were opposite.
In short,Michi was killed by mistaking
Akutagawa was killed on purpose
Tamai was killed and I tried to find out how the poison comes
I'm starting to think this reasoning of mine is correct.
I was so scared that my legs trembled for the first time in my life
That's interesting
What does this have to do with me?
It wasn't the brandy she brought
You poisoned his favorite brandy to kill Akutagawa
You put it in my room in advance
You thought he would drink the brandy whenever he came to the room
The key to my room remained open from the morning
Do you think I did it?
Yes
Why I have to kiss him?
He admitted the divorce and gave me some money
You really didn't want to divorce
The stock certificates you received have lost half their value in the recent crash.
You plotted to get all of his property.
In short. If you kill him before you divorce
Stop it!
Don't say that
You have done this horrible thing
You pretended to aim at me and shot Akutagawa through the door.
You pretended that you accidentally shot Akutagawa with a pistol
I didn't do it for money
But
You were clever
You know that Mitchi will be an important reference for the Tokumaru case
I tried to divert their attention there
You wrote a threatening note at a nightclub
And finally
You were so afraid of me that you poisoned the whiskey.
You know everything
But there are some differences
It ’s a woman ’s feeling.
Will you listen to ?
Sure
You think of me as a strong woman
I'm really a weak woman
I was raised by the power of money
I can't live without money
The stock market crashed and I was very inconsolable.
I wanted more money
But Michi was dead
I regret
Indeed, I used the inheritance issue to try to somehow fool them.
But I went home after being bullied by Akutagawa at the club
I thought I was very pathetic
So I wanted to hear your voice
But I heard Akutagawa's voice and heard something terrible again
I thought I could get money with you if I killed Akutagawa
I'm really bad woman
I killed him
I suddenly felt scared
I'm scared of you
I thought so when I heard from you in Hakone
I went back to Tokyo and poisoned whiskey in your office
Then I was very upset
I just called because I didn't want you to drink the whiskey
Can you understand my feelings?
Are you going to call the police on me?
Tell me
I thought this would happen someday
I also have a pill
Wish I could have spent even one pleasant day with you.
Please
Please sleep with me
This is the last request
Can't you because I'm a bad girl?
Nakabe-san
This is the last farewell.
Hug me
I need to say good bye
Please
You are a strong person
good bye
Be happy
Chizu-san
Nakabe-san
I am
Bad woman
Bury bad women like me deep in the earth.
People's blame and your hatred too
Bury them in the ground, too.
Bury them
Chizu-san
You were weak woman
THE END