Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Tamako
Let's play together
We brought fireworks
What happened?
Are you embarrassed?
You look young
How old are you?
Do you want to know?
I'm 15
Like A Barbarian
Here we go
When I see fireworks, I remember a saying: "Vie fireworks"
Vie fireworks?
Does that mean Beautiful?
It is not. Vie is french
Vie? Like c'est la vie (this is life)?
It means life
You have a good pronunciation
I studied
Fireworks like life
What a painful saying
What a great writer you are!
It was written in a high school textbook
It was a short story by Ryunosuke Akutagawa
A French officer came for technical guidance in the Meiji era
He saw the fireworks one day and said
Fireworks like life
I was impressed with it
French is very romantic
If I say it's very unpleasant
France fits the scene very well
Ei-Chan
Eiji
Hello?
Is that Eiji?
No one with you,right?
Listen carefully
Our boss was killed
Anyway, Come here alone.
Why?
I'll explain to you later
My first novel, which I wrote when I was 15, received recognition
They said I was a girl genius.
I was impressed with you.
Thank you very much
I felt like I had it all figured out back then.
But As I got older, I understood the parts I didn't understand before.
I was very happy when I realized that.
I know how you feel
I still don't understand any of it.
But lately
I think I knew what I was getting at when I was 15, 16, 17.
I feel I knew
Tamako
Yeah
You need to stop being so negative.
Um
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting
Big brother?
Takeguchi-san
Oh Eiji
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Our boss was killed
Who did it?
I have no idea.
It was quick
There was a deal tonight.
Our boss was going to meet his girl on the way back home
I was waiting for him outside
So I got injured
By the way
I need to ask you for a favor
Look at the bag there
Did you find it?
This?
Yeah
What's inside?
Guns.
What are we doing with these them?
Better not caught up a gang warfare.
Don't freak out
Take it easy.
Do what you always do.
That's it
It would be a waste if the police confiscated it.
This is a business, business you know?
I'll call you later.
Go.
30min...no.. Call police 15min later
30min or 1 hour
I'll let the time pass me by
Are you OK?
You are drunker
I'm ok.
I'm not drunk
By the way, your birthday is coming soon
Not yet
Your birthday is end of August
Really?
Enjoy yourself
We know it's a little early, but let's celebrate your birthday.
Eiji
Hi
Are you working from now on?
I've finished it
The guest was gang
ganster (yakuza)
You should be careful
See you
What the hell?
This is really bullshit
Hello?
How are you?
I'm Hirosawa.
Please wait a min
From head office
Hello?
I'm Ichido
Sorry not yet
We will take care of this
OK?
Call Yoshimoto
I've managed it.
Can you bring us Takeguchi?
I know.
I don't get involved in fighting
But A member of my crew was killed.
I am a President of Yakuza group
I'm trying to get closure.
I'm counting on you
What would you like to drink?
I want a beer
Tamako
What happened today?
I have a night adventure
I also want to have a night adventure
How are you?
- You look fine, I have a gift for you
- What is it?
I used them for today's shoot
To Eiji Nakai
How are you,Eiji
I'm very fine
I am thinking about either you or Ichijo
I'm talking about the next boss
So tell me
About the woman
Only that woman knows that Amenishi (the killed boss) was there
So tell me about the woman
Please tell me the age and fashion/outfits of this woman he was meeting
Tell me now
She is about 20 years old
She wore white clothes
She wore polka dot clothes
She wore white trousers
She wore a hat
She wore a hat?
Yes
Ouch
Wait!
Please Wait!
It's rude not to apologize for pushing me away.
What the hell are you doing?
What do you mean?
Just take it
Say sorry
Who the hell are you?
You pretend you are great.
Who the hell are you then?
Are you drunk?
Hey
Who the hell you think you are.
Why are you touching me.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takeshi
She's cute
She's cute but strong
A strong woman is nice
Watch out for him
He is such a nasty man
That's business
What kind of work do you do?
I am in the service business of foreign transactions
You're doing a serious job, right?
I thought you were a yakuza
Why do you laugh?
Welcome
Parent company members are here.
What kind of work do you do?
You can guess
Well.. you're not student
Don't leave
Hi
Is she your girl?
Kind of
Something is strange
Can you go out?
I'm sorry
Do what I say
Go to bathroom
Why?
Hurry up
Wait
Don't move
Please make a line
Get away!
You are violent and nice
Open!
I will charge you for the repair of the door.
You knocked on the door very strongly
I'm leaving!
I will charge you for the repair of the door.
What the hell is this?
I have no idea
Anyway
Let's go
Get your hand off me!
That is easier to run
Are you good at running?
I was a track and field athlete
That's good
It's been a long time since I run
Do you feel good?
It's good
You look painful
It's hard
Because you are not exercising
I might be
Shit
They seem to be jogging every morning
They are a new type of yakuza
They are so serious
Why do I have to run away with you?
I have no idea
It seems they want to catch you
Why?
Let's meet later at the bar "Presso"
Let's break up into two
You go first
Go!
Fireworks like life
I get it.
Thank you for your hard work
please
I'll be here for a while
Ok finished.
Sorry for the inconvenience
Not at all
I'm leaving
The woman seems to have been found
The woman you were talking about
I see
She was with a man named Eiji
But she turned down
Eiji?
That bodyguard man
Let us find them
Bring him without killing him
Hey,let's go
Don't worry.
Take a rest
He's stupid, but why?
Did it happen at 11 o'clock?
It happened for an hour and a half from 11:00
I do not understand English
Excuse me
Please have a seat there
Please tell us your name and profession
We cannot make a record without that information
Let's will meet up at the bar "Presso"
Who would go there!
I seem to be involved in some crime
I know
Sorry to have kept you waiting
Sorry
You smell good
You slapped me twice a day
I will return this to you
Why did they chase us?
It's better not to know
I'll send you home
I had fun
Don't pretend
Yeah
See you
Shit!
You baster!
What did you do to our boss!
You idiot!
Get in the car
Are you OK?
I can take you a hospital
Don't do that
Why?
Don't take me to the hospital
OK
Please give me a cigarette
Why are you laughing?
We are still together
Yeah
I had a feeling like this
I wish you had told me what would happen in advance
Do you hurt your wounds?
Look ahead!
Please give me another cigarette
Smoking is not good for injury
I'm practicing smoking from a wound
Cut it out!
I'm sorry
Don't be embarrased
I want to go to the bathroom and vomit
I did my best
You should take some rest
Good morning
Is it Tuesday today?
Yeah.
How is your job?
Not so bad
I will cook something for you
I don't need it today
Why?
I'm going to cook myself
I see.
I want to clean the room
I don't need it
Why?
I see
I don't want to disturb you
I get it, I get it
I will come again next week
Sorry
That's good for you
Eat properly
This year's firework display was boring
You can play the rest of fireworks
Cheer up.
There is no perfect human
Everyone goes their own way.
Akiko
I want some water
Did you awake?
Yeah
Wait
Here it is
benzalkonium chloride
prolam emicol
I will make Shonan a better place to live......
I'm full
Yakuza Boss shot to death
Did you get up?
What did you read?
Nothing
You look young
Stupid
You have a good guess
This is just deduction method
used by the detectives
Something strange?
No, I'm just impressed
What are you going to do from now on?
I'll think about it
You are strange girl.
You don't seem scared
I am scared!
- Really?
- Yes!
Are you OK?
I had dreams
I could hear the sound of wave
What dream you have?
I forgot
I want to smoke
You shouldn't smoke
Shall we drink?
We can't
Whois it? Eiji?
I had bad dream
Chicken BBQ will be our breakfast
You're nasty!
I want to ask you for a favor
Yeah, I sent the key in the letter
Yeah, thanks
I won't go but a jeep will pick you up
Yeah, I didn't mean that
Bye
I want to ask you for a favor
I get it
Let's change the local town with youngerster power
Don't you remember?
You were in a nightclub about a week ago
Yeah
I was there too.
I was watching you
I was watching because I thought there was a pretty woman
Thank you
You are Geek
I forgot to tell something to Eiji on the phone earlier.
I am the woman of the murdered yakuza boss.
You?
Yeah, that's incident
Never tell anyone else.
Did you sleep with him?
It's a business
It was a lot of fun today
I'm very tired
They are too noisy
How old are you?
Do you want to know?
Yes
I'm 15
If each pistol costs 500,000 yen, the total is 6,000,000 yen.
It's big money
It's a small amount of money for the yakuza today.
You know a lot
You are also familiar with difficult characters, aren't you?
Don't say that
I'm leaving tomorrow
How can I call you?
I'm new to being with a novelist
How can I say
Tomorrow?
Yeah
I see
How can I call you?
"You" is ok
Are you really good cook?
I'm not a professional cook but I can cook
Your injury got better
How do you know that?
Because you talk so much
Don't be stupid
Hello?
Yamaguchi company
Eiji?
Where are you now?
You have to tell me something
You send guys to attack me for some mistake?
I trusted you
I have come to hate the yakuza world.
I get a pistol instead of a treatment table.
Listen,Eiji
Wait there before big problems occur
I will do my best for Shonan......
I've made up my mind
I see
I feel really sorry
What the hell is he thinking?
I'll eat a lot
Come on
Ta da
It's like a different world here
I never thought this would happen
Wait here
Today, I read your novel while I was waiting
I had never read a book that long in my life.
How was it?
How can I say
It was good
There were a lot of unreadable characters
I'm a little tired
Did you sleep?
What?
Can you open?
I don't know you very well
What?
I have something I want to show you
It's a gun with drugs in it.
If it's a transaction, it's two birds with one stone.
So there was no pistol bullet
Look, this
He killed his boss and pistol whipped himself to make it look like a Yakuza war.
He put the pistol in that bag
Well, he thought it through.
You are noisy and premature.
You are just misunderstanding
Eiji
Takiguchi-san?
Is that Takiguchi-san?
Takiguchi!
Come on!
Stop it
I can't see anything
Is there anything that can make noises?
Only some fireworks
Wait
Open the window
Why?
Stay away
Today is my birthday
What?
I hated birthdays since I was a kid
My birthday is August 31st
It's the last day of summer vacation
So no one comes to my birthday party
I don't know......
What?
I don't know my birthday
But women often ask me about my birthday.
I always give them a fake birthday.
I find it very unpleasant to say that
I didn't make it
Why don't they attack us?
Daybreak
They are waiting for the daylight
We can't do anything
Help me
Little more
Happy birthday
I'll join your birthday party
31st August will be my birthday from now on
Happy birthday