Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
I used to get into fights when I was a kid.
I didn't like to fight, but I used to get into fights.
Bullshit
I have been popular with women since I was a kid
Really
Girls helped my home work
Here it is
So My grade was bad
Sometimes I have a fight for some reason
Hey, go home!
There was my mother's grave here three years ago
The grave was destroyed
So I got angry
A homeless dog
I like that kind of woman
I don't have a house so I think it's better to be on the side of my favorite girl
Do you get it?
Both me and you are the flowers of the Tone River
I'll iron your pants
So give me
Wait, does it cost a lot?
It's free of charge
Free? then thank you
We do not charge anything other than room rates
I see
So this is free too?
I'm kidding
Please polish my shoes, prepare a toothbrush, and wash my clothes.
Did your clothes tear?
When I fell, my clothes broke a little
Don't look my cock
Don't be upset
Your angry face is cute
You look just like my dead sister
Did your sister die?
I was kidding, I have no sister
Towel and soap will be in the bathroom
Thanks
Damn it
Who broke my mother's grave and built a ranch
Stop it
They fight, don't they?
What's wrong?
Wait wait wait!
Wait, not here
What the hell?
What's wrong?
Wait
What the hell?
We've been together so long.
I can't do that
Wait!
Don't get involved with them
Stop it please
Stop it
It's not fair to attack one woman with a bunch of men.
What the hell?
Run away
Don't touch her
I'm not taking to you
I protect her
It's none of your business
Can you kill me with this?
It's dangerous to have this
Hey, bring him
Run away
Stay down
Don't let you guys pass here
Hey he has escaped
Follow him
That woman is in the house
The group you just saw are from the Daiko team
Kobe's?
They are growing in power
They got into a fight with the locals last year when they smashed up a tomb and built a golf course.
They did it?
Ok, I get angry
Wait, they are dangerous
Oh fire
fire
I don't care
Wait
Let me go
Wait!
Where is the fire going?
cabaret Takamatsu is burning
Oh I see
Beware of fire
He is the manager of yesterday's fire cabaret Takamatsu
He feels responsible and wanted to commit suicide
Thanks for last night
You've got the wrong guy.
Our president is very pleased
Your president?
I have nothing to do with him
Please go downstairs
He wants to thank you
He misunderstands something
I'm handsome, so I know he won't make a mistake.
You have a nice car
He's the president?
Yes
You want to thank me
For last night
For last night?
I got into a fight last night, but I didn't see you guys.
Are you executives of Daiko team?
Oh I get it
They are our enemies
What the hell?
I'll give you cigarette money
I'll give you
What's this
For your tobacco money
I can buy a lot of cigarettes with this money
Why do you know my name?
I have many fake names
I don't usually use my real name
You checked the lodging note
That's right
You also stayed there
Yes
You misunderstood something and got into a fight with the Daiko team
Don't say bullshit
I just wanted to protect that woman
Later I heard they broke the grave
That woman was Daiko team's spy
What?
They aimed us
That woman was looking for out room
At first I thought you were their companion
Then we checked the lodging note
I see
What's your name?
Goro Numano of Numano Tourism Co., Ltd.
This business card costs 5 yen per sheet.
I return this
You don't receive his busyness card?
It's a waste because it costs 5 yen per sheet.
I hate business cards
You are a wealthy man, right?
I already remember your information
Kita in Osaka City is Yaku Toko Building Room 305
Phone numbers are 341-2852
I have a high memory
I still have my other skills.
This money is enough for one cigarette
I'll give you another cigaret
Keep the money
You guys are better than me
But I'm sure I'm more handsome than you guys
This is not a taxi
He is the vice president of our company
He is the vice president of your company?
Oh Kobe,
get me off here
This is the fee
Let me go
They broke my mother's grave and built a golf course.
I'm going to complain to them
You can't go in there alone.
I think I can
I have lived on my own
You killed one of them
He dead?
You should wait in Osaka until everything settles down
I return this
Where are we going?
Nothing special
We are just walking around?
I'm introducing you to everyone.
What?
I'm not Geisha girl
Shall we go back to company?
Everyone is there
What's wrong?
You are the man in Kyoto
You are the man in Minami
Do you know them
I got to know him a month ago through a friend's introduction
He went away a month ago with a big mouth.
He is a rumored man who killed a person
I'm not
Have a seat
Thanks
I'll sit here
Let me bid
You're betting a lot of money.
Take a bid
I lost
Work hard from tomorrow
I know.
I have to work because I don't have money
See you
Use this
Thanks
Oh it's hot!
This is hot water, so it's hot
Did you boil?
Hot water is boiling all day in here
Because it is the latest technology now
I see
That's fine
Have you never stayed at this hotel?
I have only stayed at a first-class hotel
The hotel here is a cheap hotel
You are good at kidding
This is an old hotel
It seems that it will take 5 years to recover this construction cost
The building looks cheap and the service is simple.
It seems that those sweets are purchased cheaply
Our salary is also cheap
You had better not work here
I'm thinking of quitting this job but
You are here now, so I'm thinking of working here little more
You like me?
You are cute
You look like my dead lover
Did your lover die?
She held my hand and died on a snowy night
Does she look like me?
Your eyes look exactly like
Love me as a substitute for that dead lover
I'm a homeless dog so I don't know when I will disappear
I don't care
Passion is something that burns temporarily
Quickly?
Let me think for a moment
Passion is something that burns temporarily
OK I get it
I will definitely go the way I have decided
Are you virgin?
I'm going to be hated later.
I'm a virgin but don't look down
It hurts
What?
Nothing
You know what
Hello? yes, the bath has been fixed
Yes
What's wrong?
From our guest
I see
It can't be helped
Welcome
Please collect money through the back door.
We'll have visitors here.
Gas prices here are cheap.
The bath is heated by oil.
Thanks
Did you get the full amount of insurance money?
Who are you?
I'm your body guard
So the boss hired you to make sure I didn't run off with the
money.
The boss didn't hire me.
I'm doing this on my own
You stupid.
I don't need any guards
Hi!
Hi, wait
Hey
What?
Don't follow her
It's none of your business
Don't chase me
Hi, don't run away
What's wrong?
I'm sorry about the other night.
Talk to me something
You are boring,
Say something
What's your name?
I'm Daisuke Kamoi
hat's your name?
Karasawa
Asako
Asako?
You have a good name.
Your name means morning?
I hear you have something to do with Daiko team
Is that right?
I have nothing to do with them
Why you were in Shikoku?
Where do you live?
I can guess you live around here
Right?
It seems you are on the way of going home
Do you work at Bar or cabaret?
Or club?
No, let me go
What do you do for living?
I believe you have something to do with Daiko
team
They control you?
I will support you if so
That's what I thought
And
Wait!
You've drop something
Get out of my way
I believe you have something to do with Daiko
team
We can talk about Daiko
Shut up,
I don't want to talk with you
I think I'm more handsome than you
You are boring
Wait
What the hell?
Just do your job.
And keep your eyes on the insurance money
Don't chase her.
Otherwise you will go to death
I don't care about my life
Your life is worthless.
What the hell?
You don't have to give the money to Daiko
In any case, they take the money
I will visit you later for fire
For fire?
He's so nasty
Bar No.8
Did you get the insurance money?
Yes let's share.
100 for Oba team, 150 for Shindaku
50 for Numahachi
150 for Tomita
450 in total
You get it?
Hello? Shindaku?
I'm Numano
Is your boss there?
I've asked our subordinate to bring there the 150
You can pay me back later with interest.
Yes 30%
What? 20%, No way
Don't make fun of me
I worked hard for the money
30% interest, 3 months for the limit
Yes 3 months
You guys can make a profit of 3 million yen a month with that money.
Anyway
Money is needed to crush the Daiko group golf course
We need government support
To get a loan from the government, We have to make an effort.
I'm counting on you.
30% interest, 3 months for the limit
This person is really serious
He works hard
He works hard wherever he goes
I want to sign a contract with Suzuki Tourism Office on the 3rd floor of the North Building
Boss
I gave the money to Oba and Shinraku
Give me the receipt
You need 24 prefabricated beds
24 sets of tables and chairs
When can you deliver?
About 1 week
5 days OK?
5 days?
We also want a lighting fixture and a luxurious stand
This is also 24 sets
Okay, We'll get it right away
In 5 days please
We are in hurry
We will prepare them within 5 days
Thanks
Thank you for your order
See you
Say hi to your boss
5 days
We will cancel the Atsugi Building on the north side on the 6th day.
OK?
Today is the 12th, so it will be canceled on the 18th.
I don't know what kind of work the company here does
You run love hotel
You guys also do loan sharks
You also broker furniture.
It ’s the same mysterious as you.
What? I gave you the receipt
I'm not talking about the recipe
You dropped something before
It's none of your business
Show me
Oh
You made this?
Yes I made it
I like this too
The performance is twice that of a normal pistol.
This is my most prized possession.
What do you think?
This is so cool
This is real
This is automatic pistol
Do you want to shoot?
Shoot someone?
No way
You can use this in the town
I'll bring you somewhere
I'm excited
My pee leaked
You look so excited
Which do you like most girl and pistol?
girl and pistol?
I like both
Kamoi
I hate this pistol
Your name sounds like a bird. That's why it's not good.
It's none of my business
My name has been this way for generations.
I was getting better
At first he was good, but at the end I was better
I refreshed my feeling
You played a good match with him, isn't it?
Aoi
What can I do for you?
You didn't work properly
Don't get in the way of my work
I just want you to keep our promise
I gave the money
This is not enough
Don't give me shit
Hey guys, go back work
kamisawa,
Have you seen a new store?
I am going to see from now on
You go now
Take this
Hey Aoi,
We have to pretend that you and I are not on good terms
They find that we are working together
Yes,that's right
If they find out, we're in trouble.
We will set fire tonight
Tonight?
It's too early
I don't think so
Fire!
Really?
Run away!
My stuff is here
Where should I run away?
Run away!
My hand bag is there
Forget it
Let's go
What can we do?
It's burning well
I forgot to take my watch
My neck less is there
You are Manager!
You take responsibility
You were dead if we didn't guide you
Hey
Look this
I told you to visit
You are a marauder
Get out
It's messed up by fire extinguishing work
Are the guests okay?
Don't ask me
Our president took care of them
I didn't expect him to set fire
What the guest left behind was a handbag for the wristwatch spare.
Then it's nonflammable
This canned food is okay
All the things left behind by the guests are okay
Who are you?
Police?
The firepower was strong, but the building's walls are very thin.
It was quick to extinguish the fire
I'm asking Who are you?
I told you I'm your guard
Why you know my name?
You checked my identify?
Are you from Shikoku?
Shikoku?
Why you ask me?
It's none of your business
What?
What is the cause of this fire?
It was a misfire
Police and fire department announced so
The Insurance money was paid
I don't know
Even if the insurance pays out, the president will just shake his profits and I won't get any money.
I see,
It was a misfire
There's been a recent dispute between the police and the fire department.
That's good for you
Who is he?
He's so nasty
I'm sorry, president
When I went to the North Building, Mr. Suzuki wasn't there.
Please pay 1.6 million yen
Please
It's none of my business
He spoofed my name
I know nothing
Please complain to Mr. Aoi Kiroku
Don't say that
I'm counting on you
Shut up!
It's none of my business
You should talk with Aoi.
Don't come here anymore
Hey
I see.
Aoi set the fire
Yes,
He ran away with 42 million insurance money
Set fire
I see.
So the fire spread quickly
You should find him
I can't chase him because I don't know where he is
Where is he?
He is in Daiko group in Kobe
Daiko?
He's in Daiko?
He was in contact with the Daiko group
I finally found out that he had a lot to do with the group
I hear you do a good job
That's why I hid the fact that you had a history of murder.
So I'm counting on you
No way
I don't want to obey your orders
I can quit this job
What? you don't?
No
I have already given you money
Money?
It looks like I got married to this company
Do you think you got the money for free?
Don't talk about money
That money was taken by fraudulent means, right?
What did you say?
You hit me
Hit me more
You hit me for 50,000 yen at a time
You hit me for 300,000 yen at 6 time
That will be fair
Hit me
You hit me for 50,000 yen at a time
You don't want to pay
You are stingy
50,000
100,000
150,000
200,000
250,000
300,000
Good, I'll return some
50,000
100,000
150,000
200,000
250,000
Damn it
Fuck you
I'll stop.
It's waste money
My debt is 250,000
I have nothing to do with you anymore
OK?
Where are you going?
It's none of your business
I'll go wherever I want
The woman had this lighter
This lighter was given to a customer to commemorate the opening of the store last year.
Who in the Daiko Group did you give this ?
I think this indirectly passed to the Daiko group
I get it
Wait
You can stay upstairs
You like caring
I will come again when I feel like it
Mr. Numano is smart but sometimes makes mistakes
He believed in you
I was also worried
I thought he found me
Because he is the chairman of the Osaka group
So what will we do?
Do we wait here until we settle down and then go to Okayama?
Or Kyushu?
We'll be safe if we stay with the captain.
I'm running away with 4 million yen.
Numano must chase me
So in the end
We'll kill Numano?
Aoi?
It's better not to kill Numano now
If we kill him now, we'll be in trouble.
So
I'll kill time here
Don't worry about women and alcohol
There is a guy who do a good job with my subordinates
What?
What's wrong?
Kamoi in the Numano group has been missing
Kamoi?
I see
Numano asked him to find me
Let's play
Sure
Red
I lost
You are so lucky
Take off your underwear
You take his underwear too
Can I give you the elastic band of my underwear?
Are you crazy?
I don't need your dirty underwear.
I'll return you all
Are you sure?
I'm just killing time here
Don't catch a cold
Hey
Do you know any good business?
I have 200,000
200,000?
It's a lot
How about smuggling Western liquor?
smuggling Western liquor?
I hate being ordered by someone
No one order you
You enter a foreign ship in the port, negotiate and buy with it
That's interesting
Do I use any special boat?
You don't have to use that
If you do that, the police will find you
You go there by swimming
by swimming?
Yes by swimming
You can't swim?
I can swim, but
I can't make this wet
You have a  pistol
I cherish this
Are you good at shooting?
I'm expert
You should go to the Olympics
go to the Olympics?
I have no fixed address, so I can't
I see
Don't tell anyone I have a pistol
I know
You
I'm arresting you for illegal gun possession.
You are police!
Don't move!
Freeze!
Ouch!
Help me
Thanks, bill is there
Thank you
Where did you hide the gun?
Pistol?
I don't know what are you talking about
What is that?
I saw it
I see
Are you really police?
Why you don't bring me to police station?
You are not, right?
What are you doing?
I'm hungry
I won't treat this meal.
I know you have no money
If you don't pay me, I'll bring you in for eating and drinking without
paying.
What the hell!
You've brought me here.
You should treat me to this noddle
It's not free!
You are good at joking
Do you want to live with me?
I can't live with a police
And I like this homeless life
Why you are in Kobe?
Take a guess.
Because of that woman and Daiko group who broke your mother's grave
Why you know that?
I've looked up everything
Shall I tell you where that woman is?
Tell me
Can I ask you something if I tell it?
What's that?
Sure if I could help it
What the hell?
Watch on Numano and Aoi
Aoi has taken Numano's insurance money and run away
That's what I thought
You are here because Numano ask you to find Aoi
No way
I'm not looking for Aoi
You should find him
No way
I have a grudge against the DAIKO group, but not against Aoi.
I see
You won't find him
So I won't tell where that woman is
I'll find her by myself
You can't find her
Why are you looking for Aoi and Numano?
Numano's set fire 5 cases in this 5 years
This is clearly an insurance fraud.
But there is no evidence
I need the evidence
You should ask police
But there is no evidence
So you should give up
I won't give up
My colleague was killed by Aoi during an internal
investigation.
So please
Find him
Will you get paid more per month if the case is
solved?
Little
That's ridiculous that your salary will be raise and I will be arrested
I'm just asking you if you could bring Aoi
Then I can arrest him for some reason
Then you will investigate
Yes
You'll arrest me too
I need you to testify to the facts in court.
No way
Hey, pay your bill
I won't treat you
You are persistent
I'll arrest you
You are bullshit
Bye
Hey
So Please
If you do, I will tell you where that woman works
She is so beautiful
Ok.  I will do what you want
Is Fukunishi here?
Midoris-san, please go to No.5 table
I finally found you
I could hear your voice
Are you free tonight?
Who are you?
He is the man who caused the murder in Shikoku
Oh you are alive
What's wrong?
It's none of your business
I just want to talk with her
Don't touch her
Wait
What's the hell are you doing?
I will never let go of the woman I once liked
I will chase her
Don't say bullshit
You are mother fucker
Hey
What the hell
You are bullshit
I pretend to sleep in order to get in here
Don't say bullshit
What do you want?
Can I see that girl?
How much you pay?
I have no money
You guys broke my mother's grave, right?
What the hell are you talking?
What?
You won't give me that girl?
Don't get angry
We can't give the Asako to you in the end
Our client wants her
Is that right?
She is his girl now
We give the Asako to our client
Boss
What?
I want to tell you something
Please don't give my lover to the customer
Listen
When did you become great?
Please boss
Please don't give my lover to the customer
Hey
Stop splitting up the group.
It's none of your business
I like to stop the fighting
Can you give me the girl if you don't want to give her to the customer
No way
But bear in mind
It's better if you give me the girl
It's a shame to play women in the same group
Leave it to me.
You can give up your mind and she'd be happy
Shut up
I'm waiting for your reply
I can't forgive you guys
You guys broke my mother's grave
I will fight back with you guys
Please the girl in 10 days if you don't want
Please me 42 million if you can't that
42 million?
The insurance money
What do you think?
Don't say bullshit
Aoi doesn't do it
I'm not talking about Aoi
See you
She's nice
Hey, you didn't pay
Eh?
Pay the money
What I have to pay?
Don't pretend you don't know
Pay the money
Oh clean my cloth
You are insist.
If I tell the police you will be arrested
I don't worry about that
Then I will go to the police alone
You bite me
You look like a rabies
Pay the money
What's wrong?
Oh ryoko
Oh, Manege
What are you doing here?
He played for free last night.
Pay the money
You become a Whore?
Yes, Because I just need my body
Don't push yourself too hard
Pay the money
Hey you,
I have no money
What?
It hurts
Stop it
Look at me
I found 200 yen
This is not enough
I have no money
I have no money anymore
It's no use looking for it anymore
What can we do?
It seems he has no money
You are the lover of this woman?
Don't say bullshit
I'm just friend
I see
Get out of here
Forgive him
Ok I get it
Get out of here
Ok, sorry to make you trouble
You are nasty woman
What?
I didn't do anything
Why do you laugh?
200 yen is ok,
I didn't lose myself
Thank you
I work there, 2F.
Do you want to come to play?
I don't feel like playing
You don't like me?
No no, I don't feel well.
My stomach is bad
So I don't work today
I will see you when I get better
I won't work with you
Did you find the girl?
Yes the girl was there but It was difficult to take out.
and Aoi was not there
I won't work with you
Hey, you promised
But you didn't tell me where she lives
What did you say
Stop it
I'm familiar with here
Ok I will find him
Don't make a lie
You know?
Anyway come with me
Fuck you
Don't resent me
He will go home
Thank you
Oh Mama!
I'll come back tomorrow
Thank you
See you tomorrow
Thank you, go home now
See you
I'm tired
I'm going out
Where are you going?
I'm going to go get some air.
Do you have an affair?
You will take care of me for a month so I can't betray you.
Can I believe?
Trust me
OK OK
What? She quit job?
tell me where she has gone?
I don't know
You don't know?
Oh you are here
Sorry for the last time.
I didn't mean that
You were so mean
Don't get upset
Where is the girl?
I know but I can't tell
Because you broke our promise
I see
She's gone too far.
Did she die?
Are you stupid?
She's alive
If she's alive, I'll find her alone.
You've given up fighting with Aoi?
Aoi is in Daiko.
You are the only who can fight with him
I don't care about him.
I just need her
Daiko hide her
You like her so much?
I like what I like, and I don't like what I don't like.
I'll do whatever I want
See you
As long as she is here, he can't leave from Kobe
Don't come closer
Kill her when you come
Oh you are here
Don't come closer
Let's talk
Wait!
Kou-Chan
You can't see your boss either way
What is a fatal injury
This
Isn't he drowning?
He drinks a lot of water but is not drowning
Can you announce that he's dead in water?
Why?
I don't want to be known to Daiko
Please write the facts on the documents and announce to the media that you are dead.
I think this case is deep
So please
What did you do?
There is a police outside
Why the police know our plan?
Calm down
I don't think Numano get arrested now
It seems Koichi has been dead
He seems to have died in water
He seems to have died in water?
If he died on the job, his buddies will bring the incense.
We can have a good funeral for him
But it would be embarrassing if he died after drinking water
Ask police to take care of him
Bring his bones later
Koichi's girlfriend seems to have gone somewhere with that man.
But he's easy to find.
We've already set up a lookout.
Don't worry,Aoi
If you want to be killed by your lover
Use this
I killed your lover
so use this
You told me you'd rather be killed by that lover.
I also want to be killed by a woman I like
Kill me
There's nothing in my head that makes me sound
light.
It's more stable if you hold it with both hands.
Shoot me
Why you don't shoot me?
Well..I have no money
I'll be homeless after I pay the hotel fee
You'll be fine if you kill me
I have money
I got rid of my household goods when I ran away.
I don't need this money
I should leave?
No?
Why?
You hate me,right?
I'm not comfortable to be here
I'm leaving.
You should use that money, and leave here
Be careful of Daiko group
We should leave here
Then I'm going
Wait
What's wrong?
Can you book a ticket for Tokyo with this money?
Are you going to Tokyo?
Yes, I have friends there
Ok I will go to book
Wait for me
Where have you been?
I'm originally homeless
I'm originally homeless, so what?
You can come back to me whenever you want
The new bartender is too young.
I'm living with a woman I like.
Do you seduce me?
I get it, I won't treat this
You are so mean
I want to drink
Do you have money?
I have no money
How much?
you only have 5000 yen?
You drunk more than 10000yen
What?
Ken
This man eats and drinks without paying.
I want to drink
Fuck you
You made me angry
The ticket for Tokyo were sold out
You are lying
You think so?
Yes
This is the first lie I've ever told in my life.
Why?
Don't ask me why!
Why do you like those gangsters?
Shit!
They are all rubbish
You are rubbish too
Yes I am
The yakuza are nothing but scum.
They are no use
I'm sorry for that
You're going to live in denial about who you
are.
You think you're boring.
I don't think so
There are good yakuza and there are bad yakuza.
I'm good yakuza
I'm a cool gangster living on my own.
Your last lover was a pathetic man.
You were killed if I was not there at that time
Anyone who thinks it's a good idea to be killed by yakuza is an idiot.
He protected me so
How much you loved him?
It's not uncommon for a gangster's woman to be taken by a client.
He was not Yakuza
He was not?
Don't say bullshit.
He was really Yakuza
He has a pistol
Needless to say
Ok, You loved him so much,
I have no choice to leave here
I don't want to hear about your ex lover
They broke my mother's grave. I just hate them.
That's it
Wait, I hate them too
I was not his girlfriend
What do you mean?
What are you saying about it?
Say you loved him!
He's my younger brother
What?
Your younger brother?
You're not making any sense.
Don't try to rely on me.
It's true
We both lived in my hometown.
We didn't have any relatives.
It was the land I came back to after the war.
You came back to after the war.
He had worked in Kobe after graduating from junior high school. He wrote to me every month.
But He stopped writing to me. He couldn't escape from Daiko when I visited to Kobe
I didn't know she was your younger brother
He told me we should pretend to lover. Otherwise Daiko attack me
This is what he loves me
He introduced me a quiet bar for working
We were waiting for a chance to escape, but we couldn't.
He planed to kill me and kill himself
He protected me.
That's what he loves me
I should have told me at bar
I couldn't tell you. I was worried The Guy who is Wakamatsu took me
I was idiot
Please hit me
Never mind
I'll protect you
You might annoy
But I'll protect you
I'll protect you
Have a seat
I'll treat you a meal today
Please ask the police to hand over the remains of Koichi Karasawa to me.
She can't go out for some reason
Daiko came to pick up the remains of Koichi
Karasawa
Really?
They'll use the remains to collect incense.
Tell them why, and they'll give you the money.
OK
Are you going to get it?
I will get it
Don't do that
It's none of your business
Where did you hide her?
You'll be in trouble
I don't care about it
You are in Daiko now. and found Aoi
You don't want to fight with Aoi anymore
I really don't want to fight with Aoi
Why I can't get his bone?
Because It's ours
Humanity is important in this world.
We are not in normal world
Listen, We'll give you his bone if you accept our
deal
Deal?
I know you hided his girl anywhere
We want her
We'll give you his borne in return
You idiot
What?
I'll give you her in return
So We can't give you
What are you going to do with her?
Do you guys give her to a guest named Akamatsu?
That's right
He requested the woman
He requested? He's not king
I can't give you
If you don't give it, let's play one-on-one
Ok, that's interesting
Ok you fight with Akamatsu
Tell me
Sure  I can
Shooting?
When?
Where?
You can decide it
Boss, Kamoi knows everything, so he acted like that
I think so
He is not so clever
Anyway He knows Aoi is here
Boss,Before it's too late, Let's contact Numano from our end.
I won't run away
I won't run away.
I was just shopping around
Damn it
Wanna fight?
Fuck you
Watch out
You are an employee of a furniture store, right?
You were in Numano office.
I was deceived
He's in Daiko now
He crushed my company
It's none of my business
Please call him
Akamatsu is Aoi
Akamatsu is Aoi?
I'll see Numano again.
Hey
Aoi kill him
Aoi
Why you are here?
I'll leave
Who killed Koichi?
I have no idea
Do you know this?
What's this?
Don't pretend you don't know
This is that weapon
Eh?
He was killed by this
I see
Daiko found where you live
Anyone come?
Who?
Daiko
Only this cat came
What are you doing?
I didn't kill Koichi
He was killed by a knife
You are mine.
I’m never gonna let you go
It's true.
There are witnesses in the police
I have never loved women
I don't know what I want to do in these situations.
Tell me what should I do in this situation?
You hate me?
No?
Run away
I can't.
You need his bone,right?
Don't worry
I don't think so
They broke my mother's grave
We should get the bone
I'm a real Yakuza
I value humanity.
I have never escaped
Ok I get it
You make me gamble
Daiko gets me if you lose
That's what you think
No way
I'll win
I think Koichi would be happy if we lived a life of poverty and happiness here.
We can start new life from here,Kobe
Daybreak soon
We can start new life
Yes,that's right
Don't you think so?
Good morning
Akamatsu says
He's Aoi
You've known?
The promised day is tomorrow, right?
It seems that he's not feeling well tomorrow
I'm ready anytime
I'll take a walk
Don't go
You can go to Tokyo or wherever you want to go
I will find you later
Don't go
It's none of your business
Let's go
We go together
I'll take care of her
What?
She's Aoi's girl
She's mine
Can you go with me?
Get out
Fuck you
Damn it
Kamoi, this is the Yakuza
They are coming
Run away
No
Let's raise his monthly salary
Will you provide accommodation for a homeless?
Yes
Please take care of her food and where she lives.
I will testify in court instead
I wish I could go to jail with her
Your salary is too low to take care of her
Please take care of the formalities so that I can take her to jail, to her prison.
Don't go
THE END