Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Dear voters
Please vote for Ochiai MASAHIDE in the upcoming mayoral election!
He is a new politician who will solve political problems at the root and build a healthy society.
Please vote for Ochiai MASAHIDE
He's the new politician.
Hey, let's take turns
We are tried to work on this
Five times a minute, three hundred times an hour. From six in the morning until, let's see, nine at night.
4500 times
It's ridiculous.
It's not ridiculous.
Why?
If Mr. Ochiai is elected, this town will be a better place to live, and our gas and electricity bills will be lower.
You like him?
He's a professor, an M.D., austere, deluxe suit.
I love him.
That's why I don't want women to vote.
Japanese politics is not much different when it comes to innovative parties.
In fact, the gas and electricity bills would be higher with an innovative party.
Reforms and progress are not done in this country. They don't do reform or progress in this country, do they?
It's because of men like you, who are just as bad as you are.
Hey, let's take turns
Let's free this town from dirty politics!
Please vote for Ochiai MASAHIDE
It's so hot, I don't know why the heating in the lodge is so strong.
I can't wait to hear what you have to say about it.
I will
But it's very scary.
I'm sober... and I need to get drunk.
Well, you'll have to drink more to keep me company.
Let's drink together
Hey, is anyone home?
Welcome.
It's bad nobody here
I'm sorry.
I was bored
How many guests do you have?
That's only two couples.
What's going on?
Eloping.
There's a fear of suicide.
A company president of about 40 and a female office worker of about 20.
Well...
We have those guests?
Both couples are young.
What a nuisance.
It's our shift time.
I'm sure you'd like to go home and have a drink.
I'm getting a lump in my throat.
One such guest, not staying overnight but on a break
They are upstairs in room 12.
I'd like to meet with them just in case
By the way, How about the election?
I don't care one way or the other.
When the new mayor takes over, this hotel will be shut down.
This town has been under the Conservative Party's thumb for the last ten years.
I'm tired of it.
We have to change
Do you want me to bring a beer for you?
No way
She has not come yet
Can I have a light?
Thanks
They are dead
What?
No matter how many times I knocked, there was no answer. I thought it was weird, so I opened the door.
He chocked her
She's stripper Akiko
I've seen this guy before.
It's OCHIAI.
OCHIAI, candidate for mayor.
A murder has been reported at the Washington Hotel.
A murder?
Yami o Yokogire / Across Darkness (1959)
There's been a murder.
22:55 at the Washington Hotel.
Victim was strangled to death.
Suspect is Ochiai MASAHIDE
22:55 at the Washington Hotel.
There's been a murder.
Victim was strangled to death.
Suspect is Ochiai MASAHIDE
The investigation headquarters is at the marginal police station.
I have no idea
We were during sex
Again
There's been a murder.
22:55 at the Washington Hotel.
Victim was strangled to death.
Suspect is Ochiai MASAHIDE
You are just playboy
You are bad!
You killed Akiko
You killed my wife
What the hell?
I won't forgive you
You played my wife
Damn it
Oh Ishizuka?
Thanks
I heard you found the crime scene.
Yeah
Who's suspect?
I don't want to live long.
A mayoral candidate committed murder.
The victim is Akiko, a popular stripper
It's a nasty world we live in.
I can't even think about it.
But the room was locked from the inside.
There are plenty of duplicate keys in that little hotel.
I'll leave those difficult cases to the brass at the precinct.
Did the hotel guests check it out?
There were two other couples there.
They're all having a good time, a
There are no weird hotel servants.
No
I'm too busy to write the report
My hands are shaking. I can't write very well.
You drink too much.
I don't have anything else to do.
You've been an officer for 30 years. You'll know how I feel.
Give me a light, please.
Light?
There's one
What's wrong?
I'm sure there was one
Who?
One of the weirdos asked me to light his cigarette.
I don't want to get old. It's easy to forget
Can I talk to Ikuta chief?
I will get bonus soon
I'm in a daze.
I doubt you'll make it till then.
I'm ok. because Ikuta is with me
What's the first thing I'm going to buy when I get my bonus?
A fishing rod?
A TV.
My wife's probably sick in bed.
Ikuta chief?
I'm Katayama.
I forgot to mention something important.
What? The guy with the scars on his face?
Brown Jacket?
Why you didn't tell me earlier?
Were you being drunker?
OK I get it
Why did you meet Akiko?
Because she was going to provide me with information that would benefit the election.
information that would benefit the election?
Why did you go the hotel?
She said it would be less conspicuous.
She says she'll be killed if she's found.
I see.
Did you get that information?
Before I could ask her, someone hit me out of the blue and I passed out.
someone?
Maybe you got drunk and fell and hit your head somewhere.
Give me a break
So you don't remember strangling her?
No
What about this face and hand worm reveal?
We found a piece of your skin under her fingernail.
By the way, you have a tendency to drink heavily.
I have a tendency to drink heavily?
When you were a student and then an assistant professor, you got into a drunken brawl.
That was a long time ago.
When you sobered up, you told the officer you didn't remember anything.
Yes
so same again?
I just had two whiskeys.
You had a lot of alcohol in your blood.
It's a trap to get me voted out of office, too.
I don't know if you can understand that.
Don't get excited.
You're going to cool off in jail.
I'm innocent.
One more week and it's time to vote.
Until then, I will plead my innocence to the people of this town.
Don't do that
This is a fishing town, and it's always been known for its rowdiness.
You'll be safer here.
You're working with the mayor now, aren't you?
Help me
get hands off of me
Like this election is over.
He's a fool.
I can't believe he'd put his hands on a woman.
I wanna seduce you
I'm honored.
Wanna play with me?
Really?
I don't know if he was born in this town, but I hate the idea of him coming out of Tokyo to be mayor.
We, the Conservative Party, are the ones who rebuilt this town from the war to what it is today.
We can't let a socialist like Ochiai take over this town of righteousness and humanity.
Well, take your time.
I have to go for greeting
I'm disappointed with him
He's a long shot, but he'll get what he wants.
He's got the support of Mr. Hirose, who says he can't sleep with his feet on the street.
Sorry I didn't notice you
He and Mr. Okada, Bureau Chief of Toa Japan, are a rare combination.
What are you talking about?
Mr. Mayor, I'd like you to hear this.
Actually, between you and me.
My headquarters is planning a major expansion into this region.
So We need Mr.Hirose's support
Only people who have always liked him and his fights and expositions more are here.
and women
And they've been called component newspapers for a long time, but they're newspapers with a firm foothold in the market.
There's no room for your newspaper.
Good evening.
What's going on news paper?
I got it
Is this the creation of Mr. Hirose, the Toto Nippo and
Mr. Hirose, the Toto Nippo and Mr. Hirose are teaming up to crush the Seibu Shimbun?
That's a good idea
Without that kind of excitement, there's no point in making a newspaper.
Can't you ever go back?
Is it really appropriate for the editor-in-chief to be wandering around here now?
I'm here to hear your opinion.
You can't stop laughing, can you?
Mr. Ochiai candidate just fell off his horse.
No way
Your face is telling so
Right,Hirose?
It could be
It's a bad taste in the mouth to have my henchmen bad-mouthing you.
Excuse me
At best, you can come up with a shocking tactic.
He's a nasty man
But he's a great guy.
He was bought from Tokyo by the editor-in-chief of the Seibu Shimbun, and in three years, he turned the Seibu into a top newspaper in western Japan.
He's too good for the SEIBU
It could be
How's your baby?
He's 1 month 3 days
Do you have the site schematics ready?
Soon
What are the police saying?
Common crime of passion, lover's quarrel.
Did you check out Akiko's background?
She was born a poor fisherman's daughter, a juvenile delinquent, then a jazz singer, and finally a stripper.
A woman's life?
We've got some great photos, Mr. Director.
You have one hour left until the deadline, so hang in there.
And don't write anything that's a bluff or a lie.
I know, I know.
I know, I know. Ishizuka's got some interesting stuff.
Tell me
The stripper case... that could be reversed.
What?
Officer Katayama saw a strange man just before he found the case.
A man with scars.
If he's the culprit...
I think it's a trap to crush Ochiai.
A trap... I see...
I think you're doing a little too well.
I'm confident.
You sure?
I've been chasing that scarred guy
I can't stop you
Yeah
Okay, go ahead.
But be careful. If there's a politician involved, it's too noisy.
I'm fine.
Wait
You should be tidy up
But you remind me of my younger self.
When it comes to news, I change the color of my eyes and run like a hound
You're my goal
You are bit of a prick
but it's true.
I've been trying to emulate you ever since I joined the company
Can you?
Yes
You sure?
You'll see.
I'll become your second generation.
But don't be a drunk like me.
Other companies are saying dumb things.
Stop there
Chief
The man Katayama-san saw.
Did you find out his identity?
What's that?
The man with the scars.
I don't know.
I was there when Katayama-san called you last night.
That call?
Tell me
Katayama called again, apologizing that he'd misjudged
he'd misjudged?
I got angry with him
He's an alcoholic, a nice guy, his only problem is his drinking.
But
I'm a busy man.
I've had five car accidents since this morning, and I haven't had time for a cup of tea.
The road is too narrow
You can't drive
The car is bad
You should complain to the mayor.
He's always appealing to the mayor to expand the city's roads.
But as soon as he's elected, there's no budget, so the project's canceled.
What's wrong?
Katayama officer is in?
He's on holiday
He's on holiday?
Why do you think my body aches when I get old?
Because you push yourself too hard when you were young.
You eat poorly and work too hard.
When a Japanese woman turns fifty.
80% of them suffer from neuralgia.
I'm a reporter for the Seibu newspaper.
Where is your husband...?
He's on holiday
He's on holiday? Where?
I can't believe he's just going to wander around wherever he likes. He left Early this morning.
Shouldn't he tell you
no
I've been working on a new project.
We've started to feature people who work for the city in a quiet and inconspicuous way.
Katayama-san was chosen to be the first one.
I came to you for photos and materials.
I'll make it.
I keep everything that belongs to my husband.
I'm sorry.
Newspaper clippings, employee pensions, life insurance,
Being a cop is not for the faint of heart, like my husband.
Still, in another three months, he'll get his pension.
Then he said he'd quit right away and take a job as a bank guard.
Hello?
This is. It's a hobby of mine.
You already have all kinds of people coming to the spa, don't you?
Newlyweds, corporate groups, dubious business associates...
I take a photo of them
There's something good
One of these days I'm going to publish it in a photo magazine.
What can I do for you?
I'm looking for Nishiya inn
Nishiya inn?
They are over the bridge
Katayama
Oh you.
How about a drink?
Why did you retract your testimony?
We don't need to talk about that.
Let's drink
You can't get drunk on this.
Why did you retract your testimony?
One innocent person thrown in the dark because of you.
Just because of you, one innocent man is thrown in a dark place.
Who's the one who shut your mouth?
You've screwed up a lot of jobs because of your drinking.
And the IKUTA chief is the one who covered for you.
You have to listen to him,right?
It was IKUTA who put you on leave, wasn't it?
If you get fired now, you won't get your pension.
Katayama-san, if you don't say anything, you're affirming what I said.
Please don't pick on me, too.
I'm asking you for a favor
You're going to get a commendation for protecting a murderer?
The man with the scars... what if you catch him?
I don't know anybody with scars.
You tell me you saw him. You tell us you saw him, and we'll give you something from our company in lieu of the bounty.
I'll talk to the director.
lair
No, it's true... our director takes drastic measures when he has to.
Shut up
If you keep quiet...
This town won't get any better if you keep quiet.
Tell me the truth.
You saw him?
I don't know
What are you so scared of?
I'm not scared.
What's this?
How many cops would bring something like this?
I'm scared.
Scared of who?
A killer
A killer?
That's the guy with the scars.
He knows you're here?
No
Wait here, and don't go anywhere.
I'll pick you up tonight at 8:00 and take you someplace safe.
A hotly contested game for the championship is well into the second half.
I miss rugby, this and that, but I used to be a college halfback.
Finally, the Toto Nippo has started a fancy sales pitch
They're going to bring professional baseball and sumo to our town.
Scared ?
They have a lot of money
TOTO's capital is 700 million, ours is 720,000, roughly a hundred times more.
Newspapers don't do business with entertainment, we do business with articles
Do you have a confident?
I've never lost a game in my life.
I definitely win
Toto will be in the red, and they'll pull out of Tokyo.
Director
You got news,right?
8pm
It's time to work
This Katayama guy is a bit of a time bomb.
Once he explodes, it's not just the police, it'll blow up this town.
You can't risk it alone.
Take a couple of guys and take him to our inn.
And while you're at it, check around for strippers.
That killer must be hanging around them
I'm from the SEIBU newspaper.
How many times have you been here?
That's enough!
It's my first time.
You guys are like a gang of fools.
You go from door to door, taking pictures of people's houses.
You don't care about people's feelings.
I'm not
How could I know?
You know about Akiko?
go to the police and ask them.
I told them last night.
I want to hear it from you.
I'll call the police.
It'll be more trouble than it's worth.
It's easier to talk.
We've been friends since we were girls' school in Shikoku.
Why did you live here together?
We danced in the same theater.
You must be popular.
You have a nice figure.
What do you want to talk?
How did the Akiko look like when she left?
She didn't want to.
He dragged her out.
He dragged her out?
Who?
I don't know
What did he look like?
What if he's the one who killed her?
Maybe it was the guy with the scars?
I don't know
I know you'd love to get your hands on that story and make a few extra bucks, but...
But that has nothing to do with me.
I'm not going to put my life on the line for you.
put your life on the line?
You sound like someone's scared of you.
You're persistent.
I don't know. Go home
Hi, I'm Tokuhi
No... I know
I get it
Who?
A friend
Very scary friend.
It's none of your business
I'll tell you what, I'm a wimp anyway.
It could be
I'm a dancer. just dancing is fine
Yeah, you're right. We're all so cute.
Call me if you changed your mind.
See you tomorrow.
My daughter is going to Europe next time.
Your daughter who went to music school?
She's going to France to study music.
That's nice
And before she leaves Japan, she wants to give a farewell concert in her hometown.
Can you support her?
Let me think.
I was surprised
There are a lot of gentlemen from this town here.
In the old days, they were all yakuza or fishermen's bosses.
I never thought music would come to this town.
The world has changed.
Director
Excuse me
You've got a lot of face.
What's wrong?
The hit man took out AKIKO.
A girl named Motomi lives with him. She won't give us his description.
I see, so?
So I'll go one more time tomorrow and stick with it.
Don't push it.
She's quite pretty.
I'll go get Katayama-san.
Drink before you go
Give him sake
What do you want?
High ball
Another wine
You'll lose your stomach after the next surgery.
Since when are you my wife?
Since three years ago.
Bon appétit!
You even drink like me.
Work hard
Thank you for the drink.
He's a pretty boy
Yes
What are you doing here?
I came to see Katayama-san.
Katayama's dead.
Who killed him?
He killed himself.
What?
He shot himself in the temple with his own gun.
The shot was not heard over the noise from the pachinko parlor in front.
The maid found him at 7:30.
I can't believe it
There's no question about it.
That's what the lab said.
No
What?
no, he was murdered.
They're terrible people.
Hey, Seibu Shimbun, don't make up some crazy story!
I see
Mr. Director, please let me write
I want to take Katayama's place.
What do you think?
Leave it to him
How about you,Desk?
I'm for it
Ok. We'll leave it to you
But don't assume Katayama was murdered.
There's no clear evidence.
It's a questionable suicide.
Yeah
What's wrong?
The boss wants to see you.
Boss?
Why?
I don't know.
Come to the office at 10:00.
Get in the car,Ishizuka
How's your business?
It's not good
Oh yes, please come to my house tonight for Yuki's birthday!
He became fat.
He eats a lot
If Mr. Ishizuka hadn't been there, we'd be celebrating the first anniversary of his death.
It's amazing what the newspapers can do.
You flew in the plane and delivered the medicine.
What's wrong?
Nothing
You're kind of weird, aren't you?
Oh, yeah, you said you were going to HIROSE.
I got a call.
You shouldn't go.
I wonder if you've seen a gangster with a scar on his chin.
I saw him in the paper this morning... the hit man.
Why don't you check with your buddies?
But be careful about Hirose
Shall I wait for you?
No thanks
How about golf?
I'll enjoy golf when I'm a minister.
I see.
Please take this
I'll take this
But that doesn't mean we should make it sound like the bill will pass the Diet anytime soon.
SEIBU's Ishizuka is here
Have a seat.I read the morning paper.
It's good.
But there's a lot of bullshit in there.
But you've got guts.
What can I do for you?
I'm bringing the Aoki Circus to town.
You know it?
The best circus in the Orient, they say.
I'd like to invite the children of unemployed coal miners for free on the first day.
With lunch and snacks.
At the end of the day, they take a picture.
You're supposed to sit in the middle of them and smile.
We have two weeks before the first day.
I want you to write an article about the circus.
Put in a picture or a cartoon.
Here's one.
write something funny for the kids.
Before the election, you're supposed to be a good?
You should listen to him
Be polite
is that all?
Don't let your brush tip slide too far when you're young.
Well, I just thought I'd give you a heads-up.
Once I start running, I can't stop.
Torii went to the hospital this morning to pick up Akiko's body.
I hope Professa and that German bastard go to their deaths soon!
Really
What are you doing here?
I thought it was about time you had a conscience.
I don't know anything about that.
You don't hate the man who killed Akiko?
She's your friend.
Stop it
I won't stop until you open your mouth.
Get hands off of me
What are you doing with her?
We were both remembering Akiko.
Shut up
You mess with this woman, you're gonna get yourself in trouble.
be careful with that.
I'll see you again.
Poor girl. Killing such a beautiful young woman.
She was even having a baby.
baby?
When they brought her here, they shed their kimonos, and I recognized it at a glance.I'm a woman.
From 3 pm
Dr.Inakami
Oh you
Are you at work?
I'm working part-time on a manuscript for some extra cash.
you can get cancer in your 20s
Yeah,Be careful.
You performed an autopsy on Akiko's body.
Yeah
Are the results as published in the newspaper?
Is there anything suspicious?
You withheld something, didn't you?
No
Akiko is pregnant, isn't she?
What the hell?
How many months was she?
What are you talking about?
Show me the original autopsy report.
I can't
Then the court will hear your case.
Bye
Wait
I tell you
How many months was she?
She was five months pregnant.
The fetus was stunted, so it wasn't obvious.
Why didn't you publish it?
Ikuta told me
Ikuta?
He says it's because he's only trying to defame her, not because he's involved in a crime.
Why is that irrelevant?
The police say Ochiai strangled AKIKO out of romantic entanglement.
If she was five months pregnant, AKIKO was going to have a baby.
How she could fall in love with Ochiai?
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't mention it.
It would jeopardize my position.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
This region has always been a Conservative area.
How we've worked so hard to build a groundswell of innovation.
And now it's all gone to shit.
I'm sorry to hear that.
There are only two days left to vote.
If we don't, we'll lose the election.
The revolutionary party has no choice but to back down.
You guys came in here on your own and started this election.
We can't be responsible for it.
Secretary General.
Who are you?
I'm a reporter for the SEIBU newspaper.
I have no use for you.
Have you come to pick up another bad news story?
I'm here to help you.
I'm busy.
Do you want to send Mr. Ochiai to jail?
What?
Believe in the power of newspapers.
Modern newspapers have more power than the police.
What the hell was that information AKIKO brought to you in the first place?
Toto Newspaper is now buying up newsstands and shutting down our newspaper. They want to shut down our newspapers.
They have money because they raised newspaper prices.
I heard they loaded up Hirose, the distributor's boss, with a lot of cash.
We should be careful of him
How long have you been a reporter?
Hirose may be a prick, but he's not that stupid.
I'd know that if he made an enemy of me.
but...
If you're struggling, you're gonna get thin-headed.
I tracked down the hit man and found out some good news.
Ochiai's campaign office found out.
What?
Remember the U.S. Army campground in the center of the city?
It was crawling with women of the night.
The city forced the original owner to buy it from the city for a low price to expand a planned urban road.
Yeah last year
But the city suddenly canceled the project.
It happens every time.
They're going to sell it to the private sector again.
So, what's the bottom line?
At that time, the mayor, the former alderman, and the main alderman... They gave it to Hirose for nothing.
Hirose is now planning to make a fortune by building a movie theater and a Turkish bath there.
You have proof?
AKIKO was supposed to sell that information to Ochiai.
AKIKO?
AKIKO happened to be invited to the entertainment and witnessed the scene of the alderman's bribe.
I see
Why don't we do everything we can to expose this corruption?
Let's put Hirose in jail.
It's time for the old man to pay his dues.
Let's get it on
How about you?
I'm willing to do
Hey, Ishizuka.
You're getting a little sharp around here.
Not so much.
You're just starting out.
Tidy up
Work hard
A man named Mr. Yamano is here
Yamano?
Yamano
I know who has the scars.
One of our guys picked him up from the station about five days ago.
Where'd he go?
At HIROSE's house.
Don't tell anyone.
Life is precious.
I'm a gangster and I play the trumpet.
She's the only one I took seriously.
And she took me seriously.
I'm glad
She was nice to me, too.
She was nice to everyone
She was so nice
Ochiai killed her
Why you are here?
You've come to interrupt?
I'm here to give her flower
you don't know how Akiko felt.
Why don't you care who killed Akiko?
He'll be executed or
I'll kill him.
Ochiai didn't kill her but the one with the scars.
Don't say bullshit
If you think I'm lying, ask Motomi.
You're ridiculous.
Why are you following me around?
It's fate, I guess.
You like her?
yeah I like her
Don't touch her
Who asked me to do this?
Your boss, Hirose.
What?
Call me if you change your mind, right?
You're insist
I'll beat you
Good night
He's bullshit
I hear you're quite pleased with what you're saying.
The police are incompetent.
You're very quick on the uptake, aren't you?
That's not your wisdom.
Who asked you?
Did Ochiai and the rest of the revolutionary party find you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Who asked you to look into me?
I asked
I see
What's the hell who you are
You people think that the revolutionary party is progressive as long as it attacks the Conservative Party.
I've been mayor for ten years and the city is thriving.
I'm not doing a stingy job.
Who made the money?
Newspapers are violent.
They write lies about what is and isn't true.
It may be free speech, but I won't allow it.
I can't forgive them
What are you going to do?
Kill him like Officer Katayama? Use a hit man?
Or pay me off to keep my mouth shut like he did with IKUTA?
What the hell?
you're reading a lousy report and doing a blinkered version
You don't know anything.
Ikuta is being paid off?
not only him but also Aldermen and maybe even the mayor.
SEIBU
Pls Shut up.
Shut up?
Come with me
I'm the one who made you the director of this place.
I spoke to the police department and they selected you, a countryman.
If you wanted to wear this shiny uniform forever...
Get rid of him.
You talked about it and decided to hook me up with a misdemeanor?
Don't be stupid.
Is it true about Ikuta?
Ikuta ignored the report that he saw the hit man.
He didn't disclose the fact that Akiko Strip was five months pregnant.
Secrets come with the territory.
I can't disclose every single one.
I understand you're protective of your men.But one day you'll be strangled.
I want an answer by the end of the day tomorrow.
The director wants to see you.
I'm sure he'll give you a letter of commendation.
For your excellent work on the case.
The director wants to see you.
What did you tell the director?
He'll tell you.
Your tie's crooked.
Wife
I feel so bad
What did they talk about?
About his pension
They won't give you?
They'll let you out, but on one condition.
What's the condition?
They want me to prove that my husband was crazy when he took his leave.
Then they said they would pay me a special severance package, even though He would be three months short.
They told me I would have trouble making ends meet from now on.
They are a jerk.
But I don't want to.
I don't want to say that my husband was crazy. I feel sorry for that man who died.
I'm sorry, but I don't need my severance pay anymore.
If I work, I can make it.
I'm still 52
You're right.
This project...
we've got some interesting stuff here.
A collection of human faces.
Humans have strange faces.
Like a pig, not a pig. Like a raccoon, not a raccoon.
Humans are monsters, aren't we?
Why don't we take a break and look at these pictures?
The Human Zoo
I'm gonna vote for this guy.
That's one hell of a scar you got there.
He's like wolf
Hello, is this Ishida Photo Agency?
Yes
Yes, sir.
I shot it two days ago and sent it to you right away.
No actor in the movies has a face like that.
Where did you see him?
I took this telephoto shot of him wandering around the bridge.
Of course, the inn is in the background.
I cropped it down to just his face.
I have the negative of the photo.
I'll get it later
Vote? maybe
He's a killer.
How do you know?
The day before yesterday, Officer Katayama died.
He walked through the same hot spring resort that day.
That's not much to go on.
It's just a hunch.
I'm sure it's him.
Yeah, good hunch.
It's about to get interesting.
Show this picture to AKIKO's friends.
If she looks any different, go to the police right away. Find out his criminal record.
The police can't leave him alone if they have this much evidence.
Welcome
You call me a lot
I wanted to see you.
What you wanna drink?
I don't wanna drink anything
No matter how many time we meet,
It is pointless
Continuity is the key to love.
Depends on who you're talking to.
You're not going to change your mind?
No
Then why did you come out here?
I came to tell you that it's not safe for you to hang around me any longer.
This guy might kill me?
You may recognize him... the man who took Akiko out.
I don't know him.
Well, that's all right.
Call me if you remember.
Hold on.
What?
You really need to stay away from me.
I don't want to.
I can't back out of a girl I like.
I was sent out here today to check on you.
I know that.
You're idiot
I know that too
But I was born that way.
There's no point in me hating my parents.
You don't either?
I have no parents
You're gonna miss them?
I'll be fine.
I have had a lot of boyfriends
If I make you my wife, my father and mother will be happy.
They'll celebrate with rice cakes.
Our rice cakes are just as good as yours.
Don't be silly.
This guy is a great criminal.
Five counts of murder, five counts of assault, Jiro Mori.
He's not famous around here.
But in Kanto, he's a notorious killer the police have to keep an eye on. In the Kanto region, the police are keeping a close eye on him.
Call Nakayama officer
Ishizuka
What?
I tell you
Ochiai is the victim.He's the one who did it.
I'll make sure we catch him. He's not the only one.
We'll also look into the people behind him.
Even Alderman or mayor
What did Mr. Ikuta say?
He was placed on administrative leave.
Who gave him money?
HE didn't say.
He's idiot
But it's not Ikuta who's to blame.
It's the people who paid him off.
Cops are paid a drop in the bucket.
Cops can't help it if they're a little tempted by money.
Me either
It took me a long time to get where I am.
I don't want to leave it.
But I'm still a cop.
I'm a cop to the bone.
I'm not gonna let a crime go unpunished.
Nakayama officer is not here
no?
He went to the Otani hot springs where the body was found dead a few hours ago.
Otani Hot Springs.
Who died?
The photographer at the entrance.
The photographer
Seibu Shimbun.
There is no negative
Try to find somehow
This is not clear
Please
Welcome
Good evening.
It's finally the Kyushu series between Japan and Seibu Newspaper.
We don't stand a chance.
You're on home turf.You've got ACE, don't you?
Even if we trade Hirose for a home run hitter...
The trade price is too high.
I've always wondered why you don't get a wife.
I mean, you're a good-looking guy, so I'm sure there's no shortage of women.
I have no one to be my wife.
You're lair.
You like to work so much?
I have no choice but to work
Here comes the cute little guy.
What's the matter? You don't look well.
Don't get upset just because the photographer was killed.
It's as if we've discovered who the enemy really is.
That's what I'm wondering, how did they know about the photographers?
Did you tell anyone about the photograph?
No one.
I just showed it to Motomi.
We must have a spy in there somewhere.
Cheer up
In my experience. In times like this, I don't think about it. I just get drunk and I go to bed.
You wake up in the morning and you have a good idea.
Cheer up
What do you wanna drink?
High ball
High ball for him.
I'll have one as usual
But one after another, important witnesses are being erased.
I don't know what to do.
You said you were going to copy me.
Have you forgotten?
I haven't forgotten.
Then drink, drink, and sleep tonight... like a baby.
Damn it!
Where the hell is SPY?
Are you alright?
It's just this much booze.
I was frustrated.
I get it. I get it.
I'm sorry.
Good night.
Damn it!
Where the hell is SPY?
To Kagetsu
He's been waiting for you
He's here
Sorry I'm late
That's enough
What drink?
Give me English whiskey
The Whiskey you got from Governor?
Yeah
What's wrong?
I'm talking about the TOTO Daily News.
Mr. Hirose, are you trying to give them a boost?
You're an idiot.
There's always been a SEIBU newspaper in this area.
I'm the one who brought you here from Tokyo in the first place.
I helped you make it into a prestigious newspaper.
In return, I helped you a lot.
I did most of the work that made you a household name.
I never wrote a single bad thing about you.
But I've promoted the good ones with a tail.
I'd appreciate it
But it's up to you.
You mean?
How are you handling this case?
You let ishujuka say whatever he wants.
In return, I do SPY.
Don't publish anything Ishizuka writes.
OK
But there are two conditions.
What is it?
To stop TOTO Nippo from moving in.
and?
Do not touch the Ishizuka
Is that it?
Yeah
Dunlop balls are the only way to go.
Even I can get up to 95.
No, it's your skill, Mr. Mayor.
Nice pad
I got slimmer since I play golf
I'm ten years younger.
So your bed life too?
Can you introduce me some young girls?
Well, I guess I'll be making my campaign speech.
I'm going to make one last push.
I just heard something.
I heard the police started an investigation into the camp's down payment.
That man
Call Mr. Hirose.
I hope we are okay.
The police are on the warpath these days.
Don't worry.
In a democracy, the police are the politicians' watchdogs.
Bite the thief, but wag their tail to their master.
All cops, leave your caps on and meet me at the editor's office.
You got it.
Hey Bombshell.
What's going on?
I'm trying to figure out how Hirose GROUP does it.
Every business in this region is related to Hirose.
Almost all Hirose's siblings, subsidiaries, and major shareholders.
Representatives, prefectural assemblymen, city councilmen.
They all have Hirose strings attached.
The gang has 1,000 members.
They always come at the sound of Hirose's voice.
What's the matter?
You seem awfully serious.
I knew it.
What?
There's no Hirose spy here
Mr. Ishizuka, you haven't woken up from your hangover!
What do you mean about spy?
You smell like garlic.
I like dumpling
What do you mean about spy?
I'm sorry, that's a little boring.
Why don't you go lie down in the infirmary for an hour or so?
Our new nurse is so sexy
Are you guys doing ok?
It's always good to see you in high gear.
Hirose is very suspicious
But he shows no evidence.
Does he have any proof?
Without it, all our investigations will be speculation.
We can't write an article if it's speculation.
I hear you've been subpoenaing aldermen one by one since this morning.
Do we have a warrant for the D.A.?
I'm just asking as a witness.
How much of his corruption is based on this?
I've been doing a little canvassing.
It's thoughtless of you to ask a city councilman to come in here like that.
What do you want?
The police are there to keep the peace.
What you're doing is the opposite.
You're disrupting the calm of society, unsettling people's minds.
You sound like a Communist.
I will not allow you to do that.
On behalf of the entire bar association, I'm saying this.
That's all I'm saying.
Who?
He's a lawyer for HIROSE.
He's harassing you
I'm fine.
I'm ready.
Has the corruption investigation opened up any room for maneuvering?
It's hard to find evidence.
I can give you a name or two.
And that's it.
Their mouths are tied with gold.
They don't say
HIROSE is holding a woman and look how we do
What about the hit man?
I can't track him again.
After all, this is the home of the Yakuza.
Once he's in, it's hard to get out.
It's hard to find him
What?
Ishizuka?
There's no such a police
Hello, this is Ishizuka.
It's me
You
I miss you.
I've been having second thoughts.
Tonight at 10:00, I want you to meet me at the backstage door.
I'm looking around
Thanks for coming
I'm glad you reconsidered.
You beat me to it.
I saw you dance.
How was it?
You're not a good dancer, but you have a good body.
You make me want to marry you.
You're an idiot.
You'd make a great wife.
That's ridiculous
What can I do for you?
How much will you give me if I talk?
Deal?
That's right.
I have to get out of town.
And the best way to do that is with money.
It's okay, my company is big and the economy is booming.
Are you OK?
What's wrong?
Get out from here!
I told you to stay away from this woman.
I forgot.
I'll make sure you don't.
Look at how he get punished
It's better than your dancing
First, I'll do a spell.
We'll fool the police.
Don't waste your beer
You don't even make enough money.
You've got panache.
Try it again
Serves you right.
Your jacket got dirty
What do you think?
That's funny.
Beat him. someone might come
Take care of her
We don't want any mess around here, do we?
Who?
It's me,Motomi
What do you want?
I want to apologize.
You don't need
It's ok
Open the door
Are you alone?
Yes
Really?
Open the door
What do you want?
Are you ok?
I was tricked
Kakegawa threatened me.
My bad
It can't be helped..
Lie down.
Shall I lay out a futon for you? No, I'll patch you up.
You don't need
Let me help you.
I used to be a nurse.
How did you end up as a stripper?
The doctors tricked me. They threw me away.
It's like something out of a novel.
Yeah
Take off your jacket
I'm not so badly hurt, am I?
Next time Kakegawa comes around, you'll get your ass handed to you.
I see
I'm sure Kakegawa will take you out again.
I'm going home.
I hope you're feeling better soon.
You too.
I should stay here?
Up to you
I wanna be here
You miss having a man around at night?
I'm going home.
Up to you
I'll tell you everything and
I know, money right?
No.
Let me stay here
Why?
I don't know what's going to happen tomorrow if I talk to you.
That's why I'd like to spend just tonight by your side.
I'm having so much fun being around you.
I've never had a good time with you before.
And I don't think I ever will.
So just tonight.
You can stay as long as you want.
Really?
I want you to stay, too.
You were right, it was that hit man with the scars who took out Akiko.
That's what I thought
That's not all.
The night before that, Hirose came to see her
Hirose?
That's right.
Yes, he wanted to give Akiko a job.
job?
Bring Mr. Ochiai to the hotel.
You're a good girl after all.
There's more.
Akiko left her notebook.
If she die, she wants me to report it to the police.
But I was too scared to go.
Looks like it has a congressman's name on it.
This is awesome.
It's got everyone involved with the U.S. military camp payments.
I could die in here.
With your testimony and this notebook, we can take down HIROSE.
Mr. Takazawa must be pleased.
I'll wait here alone?
I'll be right back.
Don't leave the room.
That's a great of a thing to do.
We'll definitely win.
Let's write an article on all of them.
Let's destroy HIROSE.
We have evidence, we have witnesses, and now it's not just speculation.
Let's go to our office
Ishizuka found all the evidence.
What are you going to do,Hirose?
Where is Ishizuka?
I don't know.
You promised not to touch Ishizuka.
You don't tell me what to do.All you have to do is let me know.
Just like you did at the photo studio.
where he is?
I don't know
Ok, so I'll leave it to you
Director
What?
You are the spy?
Oh, yeah.
You were working for a murderer.
Hirose did it
It's the same thing.
I wanted to help you.
You told me about the hit man when Officer Katayama told me.
Hirose had you in his sights from that moment on.
You killed two innocent people to save me?
Don't be exciting
I was an idiot.
You believed in me.
You taught me how to do my job.
and I tried my best to emulate you.
You tricked me
You knew everything.
If you'd wanted to, you could've crushed Hirose.
Why didn't you?
For some reasons.
You didn't want to die.
I've been working hard
So you wanted money?
Money for drinks at the bar.
I can't drink much with half a stomach.
Calm down.
No way.
I'm so upset
Director's a spy.
That's funny
I'm quitting the company.
I don't want to work for you anymore.
Where's motomi?
You want to kill MOTOMI too?
No, I don't know. I never know.
You just have to trust me on this.
Don't hang up, Ishizuka
Come out!
I know
What's the hell?
Where's Kakegawa?
Say
You
You're getting yourself half killed again?
I want to talk to you alone.
What?
You're scared of me?
I'm scared of you?
That's funny
What's the hell?
What do you want to talk about?
Akiko was pregnant.
What?
Five months pregnant.
Your baby.
Don't say Bullshit.
That's why Akiko didn't want to see Ochiai.
Guess who forced her to see him?
Your boss,Hirose
Don't say Bullshit.
Who took her to the hotel by force? The hit man.
You’re lair
Ask Motomi.
She knows everything
How's her?
I made her sleep
I'm about to give her some pills.
If I put this much in her, she'll be dead in a heartbeat.
Boss's order?
Of course not.
If we sell this off, we're looking at 300,000 in cash.
Stay strong
Do you understand me?
Akiko was pregnant?
She didn't say anything to me.
You said, "I don't want a baby, put it down.
But Akiko wanted to see your baby.
Damn it
She'd also been saving up for a baby and she'd need the money.
I don't know what will happen to you
Shut up
Where are you going?
To visit my wife's grave.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I told you I don't care when I die.
I don't want to die.
The only thing I have to look forward to anymore is living with you.
How's your newspaper?
I hate the newspaper
Let's go somewhere far away.
The president wants to see you.
The president?Ishizuka has not come yet
I haven't heard from him since this morning.
I see
Takasawa,something goes wrong
What's wrong?
Half the newspaper dealers in the city have refused to carry our paper from next month.
Hirose was finally seduced by TOTO.
Hirose ?
Hirose took a lot of money from them
That's not all.
Hirose isn't happy with the way you're handling the post
He makes it clear that he doesn't like the way you're letting young reporters run wild.
I trust you.
I'm trusting you because I trust you.
But you know what?
We must sell newspaper
It's a shame that TOTO is taking advantage of us.
Can't you do something about the article?
I wanna swim
It's too cold
I'm fine.
When I was a kid, about this time, I used to go in the ocean to pick up shells.
You look sad
Must be the sunset.
I knew you'd think about newspaper
Don't talk to me about newspapers.
I don't care what happens to a newspaper that's sold its soul to the bad guys.
I say the same thing over and over again.
I wonder if there is any way to come up with an idea that will bring about a comeback
With TOTO and HIROSE as enemies
This is like going to war with the US and the Soviet Union.
There's nothing we can do.
Let's get it on.
Mr. President, don't worry.
I've never lost a game.
Beer
You can drink
It was hard work.
But a woman's happiness is so simple.
Marry the man you love.
Live in the same house, have children.
But I can't seem to find him.
Well, here he is.
Every guys said so
You think I'm lying?
I don't care if it's a lie.
I'm dirty anyway.
Don't worry.
We're all dirty.
I'm getting sleepy.
Bill please
370yen
I knew you liked newspapers.
No, I don't.
I'd like to beat the director to a pulp.
Thanks
Is everyone here?
Where's Ishizuka?
We're looking for him
There's still time for the morning paper.
Listen
I don't have much time, so I'll make it simple.
I'm here to keep this paper afloat.
I've been holding hands with the BOSS.
And that BOSS is Hirose.
Hirose?
When I came from Tokyo to be the editor-in-chief of this newspaper.
This was still a third-rate newspaper.
My job was to turn this place into the premier local newspaper.
I needed money
But banks were not yet willing to lend money.
So the first thing I did was to train the best people and pull them out.
You also pulled them out from other newspapers with a 30% monthly salary increase.
Expand the sales network.
No matter how much money we had, it was never enough.
That's when I hooked up with HIROSE.
I used his money
And through his dealers, I made inroads into the rest of the world.
Seibu Shinbun is now a first-rate local newspaper that can even compete with Chuo Shinbun.
I hooked up with the bad guys for the paper.
I don't have a choice.
Director
I didn't have a choice.
In a country like this, you have to live first, even if you have to push people away
Justice and morality don't mean a thing.
We should stay strong
Fortunately or unfortunately...
When the election started, the stripper case against Ochiai came up.
HIROSE is behind it.
So you're telling us not to write?
Wait
Don't be fooled!
I've been waiting for you
He's Hirose's spy.
He's the one who broke every lead I had.
And a few people died because of it.
Katayama, the cop.
The photographer from the hot spring resort.
You're the one who nailed us for writing a speculative story, and you're the one who fudged the truth.
Really?
That's true
Ishizuka's right
I've been waiting for you
I want you to write me a full report on every case you look into right now.
You guys split up the details of the post
You write the main story, and you write it thick and fast.
If I write it, I'll beat you to death, too.
You can write "murderer," "spy," whatever you want.
You still look like you don't believe me.
Call HiRose.
Now's the time I'll clearly cut him off in front of everyone.
Hirose Transport?
Mr. President, please.
Mr. President?
Our Director wanna talk to you
Good evening. How are you?
Did you hear from the President?
Look in tomorrow morning's paper.
Your picture will be in the papers, loud and clear.
Are you trying to fuck with me?
Stripper killings, corruption in U.S. military camps.
It says everything about you.
Everyone can even see the number of blacks on your back.
What are you doing?
Don't get upset
I like newspapers after all.
You're in the way.
Anyway, I'm thinking of letting him walk around on her own tomorrow.
We'll beat you for starters.
We gonna take out the biggest boss in this area.
Our news value is full marks!
I'm sure sales will go up a lot tomorrow.
Is that all you have to say?
Tomorrow, this town will be reborn.
Ochiai will be released.
No wonder he's getting all the sympathy he deserves.
Our newspaper will finally grow together with this revolutionary politician.
At the very least, you should give TOTO some love.
You think you can get away with that?
You and I are going to have to get along.
How was it?
Let's get it on
Two hours to go before the morning paper's deadline.
Show Hirose and TOTO News the power of the SEIBU newspaper.
I'm counting on you
Let's do it!
Ok.Let's go, guys!
This is a memo I've been working on for years.
It's got every bad thing Hirose did.
Use this one, too, and write as much as you can.
Ishizuka, you're finally the second generation.
Definitely my second generation.
That's great!
But don't become a gangster like me.
Don't be a philistine.Don't get dirty.
Be more outraged at the injustice in the world
Director
Don't say a word.
Come on, we're running out of time.
Start writing.
Director
You
Can I get a light?
Hey
five more minutes, whether you're crying or laughing.
It's time for the birthday of the regular morning paper.
Hello, this is Seibu newspaper
Eh?
What's wrong?
Our director was killed by a hit man
Wait
Newspapers have to meet deadlines.
They don't wait for us on deadline.
We can offer incense anytime we want.
Let's do it!