A CO-PRODUCTION BETWEEN TOEI INC.
AND NIPPON TELEVISION NETWORK
A TOEI PRESENTATION
- 1, 2, 3...
Stop it!
Cut it out!
You'll get in trouble again.
Are you still mad?
Come on, Kaori-chan.
Here.
Try it.
Ow!
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Leon, Leon, paw!
Darn!
Takarazuka.
Last stop, Takarazuka.
The train that just arrived is the Express
Train heading to Osaka Umeda.
It will make local stops
until Ishibashi.
TO TRAP A KIDNAPPER
In Osaka, winter has arrived and the
chill has suddenly taken over.
At such a time, the news of
a dear friends passing...
Even my heart feels the chill.
That person is a hostess at a bar
I frequented called Sonesagi.
Oh my, Oh-san!
You came all the way from Kobe!
It's been 30 years since I went to the bar.
Just when I was starting out as a journalist.
When I made a mistake she comforted
me, and when I reported a scoop,
she rejoiced as if it happened to her.
With her support,
I was able to become a
decent journalist.
That's right. She was the perfect mother figure
for a journalist who was just starting out.
She found out about her
cancer last December.
She was born in Uwajima,
Ehime Prefecture.
When she was young, she was
adopted by her relatives.
She got married in the country,
but then got quickly divorced.
To Kyushu, and then to Osaka.
A life she finally established
with much struggle.
I'm certain it was
disheartening for her.
We never even held hands,
but to think that someone so
good and honest is gone...
I am overcome with sadness
and anger.
Why are you crying!
She was a lucky woman.
This is the famous Yomiuri Newspaper!
And to have such a beautiful article
written by the chief of the Social
Department is extremely rare.
That's right.
She hated crybabies.
Chief, come on, please.
Her favorite song,
"Dancing All Night."
- Please sing it for us.
- All right!
Hiromi-chan, cheer up.
You too, Naoko-chan.
Everyone, please drink, be happy and
have as much fun as you possibly can!
Sweet moments make the
heart skip a beat
Moved by the beauty of the night
Hey, stop crying and dance.
In the reflection of a candle
in your eyes
I'll happily dance...
Thirty years...
I've devoted to being a journalist.
This bar knows everything about
my young adult life.
So young.
Dancing all night
Close your eyes
Cheer up, come on.
Yes, hello?
What? Yes, he's here.
What?
Spend the last night
at this place
Yes, it's me.
What's the matter?
What? When?
Yes, understood.
All right.
Yes, I got it.
Captain, the Hogyo Police Department
informed us of a kidnapping incident.
- Where?
- In Takarazuka.
It's within the jurisdiction of the Hanshin Branch.
Oh, that's you.
I'm heading to Takarazuka Station
right away. Let's go.
- Yes.
The Hyogo HQ should be making
an announcement soon.
I'm going to excuse
myself now too.
Oh!
Thank you.
Yomiuri Newspaper
Chief!
Get plenty of reporters on the case!
We're going full force.
- Yes, yes, Kobe Branch.
- It's me.
Oh, Branch Manager, we were just
informed by the Hyogo HQ.
There's going to be an
announcement at 8:15.
I'm still in Osaka. The express train
just left. I won't make it in time.
I'll do my best to get
back right away.
Get everyone on it.
I'm counting on you!
- Yocchan, hang in there.
- Yoshio.
- Please take care of him.
Please take care of him.
Shin Kobe, Shin Kobe.
Thank you for riding with us.
Oh, Koutaro-san!
Oh, Tomo-chan!
Hi! I'm sorry!
I was surprised because
you came suddenly.
I got a room at the
Takarazuka hotel,
so I thought we'd enjoy a drive
through Rokkogoe.
- Were you able to take days off?
- Yes.
I made a fuss and got tomorrow
as a paid vacation.
Koutaro-san, my parents are trying to
have me in an arranged marriage.
My mother says she isn't comfortable
with me marrying you.
You're too busy,
Koutaro-san.
Because ever since you started working for a
newspaper company, you're always too busy.
That's why I wanted to have a serious
discussion with you today.
- I'm sorry I'm late.
- Hey, Koutaro.
Hyogo Police HQ, an announcement
at 8:15, got it?
Hey!
The Captain is already on his way!
Run!
- Oh no...
- What happened?
- My contact lens.
- Contacts?
How are you so clumsy?
Um...
I found it, I found it!
- See, here it is.
- Thank you.
Gimme a break.
- Shape up.
- I'm still missing the other one.
Hurry up, then.
I found it!
I found it.
- Idiot, hurry up! Hurry, go!
- Yes!
Ow!
Superman!
- Good job.
- They're here.
Um, I have a report.
There was a kidnapping incident
this afternoon in Hyogo.
The victim's Noboru Mitamura, 33, a pediatrician
residing within the Takarazuka precinct.
After graduating from
medical school in Tokyo,
he opened a clinic in
Nishonomiya two years ago.
He has one son and his
name is Hideyuki.
A private school in
Toyonaka City...
He's 7 years old and attends Toyonaka
Wakaba Gakuen, a private school.
As usual, around 3:30 pm,
as he was heading home from school,
someone was waiting for him,
and kidnapped him
near his home.
Have there been any
ransom demands?
Um, at a little after 5 pm., there was a phone
call from a young man to the victim's house.
Mitamura-san's wife, Hisako-san,
27, answered the phone
and was told to prepare
30,000,000 yen.
He threatened that if she contacted the
police, he'd relent on the money,
but she'd have to relent on
seeing her child again, too.
That's why we would like
your cooperation,
so refrain from gathering information
and covering the incident for a while.
We very much require
your cooperation.
You mentioned "for a while,"
but when do you expect for us
to be released from this
agreement?
In that regard, either when
the victim is found,
or when the kidnapper is arrested and we've
determined the victim's safety.
Or when the need to keep it
a secret ceases to exist,
and when those facts are confirmed
by the detective sergeant.
We'll no longer require your aid when such
reports are made at a press conference.
- Well, that sounds like news censorship.
- A child's life is at stake.
So, you've confirmed that
the child is still alive?
Unfortunately, not yet.
- So it's possible that he could already be dead.
- All we can do is...
...do what we can and believe that the victim
is still alive until we have confirmed his death.
But Captain, the confirmation...
I believe that's all the questions.
We request that you report to your
superiors and consider our proposal,
and officially come to terms with the cooperative
agreement as soon as possible.
- We are counting on you.
- We will distribute the agreement,
and a picture of the victim.
Tsushima-sama, there's a
phone call for you.
Hello?
I'll put her on now.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Tomo-chan, it looks like it
will take a little longer.
I promise to be there
as soon as I'm done.
Please start without me.
That took some time.
- Good work.
- Yeah.
- This is the Cooperative Agreement.
- What? Huh? Let me see.
- I've contacted everyone.
- I see.
- Everyone should be here.
Wow, he's a cute kid.
The Hyogo Police HQ is rushing us for
an answer. How should we reply?
If a child's life is on the line,
we can't really refuse, can we?
We'll collect information within
the acceptable parameters.
It will be heavily restricted
in his hometown.
Hey, why don't you go to Tokyo?
Tokyo.
Ah, thank you for coming.
We will have Detective Sergeant
Narusawa in charge of this case.
The investigation HQ will be at the Hyogo
Police HQ and all the developments related to
the investigation will be reported
from here. Thank you.
Will you send instructions for
the investigation from here too?
No, we've set up a command
center at the Takarazuka Branch.
Investigative Chief Kenmochi
is heading there now.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's going on?
If we knew this would happen,
we would have taken the train.
It'll be tomorrow morning by the
time we get to Takarazuka.
What?
- It's a police car.
- Okay, got it.
Follow it.
- Wouldn't we get in trouble?
- It's all right, just do it.
- Hurry!
- Okay!
- I'm counting on you.
- Yes!
Captain, excuse me.
Captain.
I am not going to permit news coverage
here. Have them go home.
Yes, sir.
- I need to go to the restroom.
- I need to use the restroom.
Has there been any contact
from the kidnapper?
N-no, not yet.
Victim's home - Mitamura
Hello?
Is this Mitamura-san?
The is Ueda from the PTA.
I'm sorry to call so late at night.
Actually, I heard that Takuue-sensei
is leaving the school.
She's getting married.
- Hey!
- I've talked to Nishina-san's wife too.
And we were wondering if we need
to get her a wedding gift.
So how about tomorrow?
- Can we stop by?
- I understand.
Um, tomorrow is...
...no good.
I'll leave the gift up to you
and everyone else.
If tomorrow doesn't work
for you...
Thank you.
Yes?
- You're the wife, yes?
- Huh?!
Yes, um...
How is my son?
My son...
- Calm down.
- Yes.
You know, Takarazuka
Shinohhashi, right?
Yes, Takarazuka Shinohhashi.
Get a cab and cross that
bridge on your own.
Yes.
When you cross the bridge,
there's a construction site.
Get rid of the cab there.
You'll see a power shovel.
How is my son doing?!
Um, he has a cold right
now. So...
If you come to the power shovel,
you'll find out.
Is he well!?
Hello? Hello?
Hello...?
- How is it?
- No, we couldn't get it.
This is the Victim Countermeasure Team.
We just had a call from the kidnapper.
Takarazuka Shinohhashi.
A construction site up ahead.
Power shovel is the target.
This is Ariga from the Pursuit Team.
We'll be at the destination
in 5 minutes.
No! No! No!
Hide-kun? Hide-kun?
Hide-kun?
Do you understand what happens when
you inform the cops?
Next time, you'll end up
seeing your dead kid.
No good!
What are all these articles?
"Great Work by Police,
Kidnapper Captured."
"Hideyuki-chan Safe, Parents Cry for Joy."
They're all happy endings.
Make sure you have one
ready where the kid dies.
- I can't!
- What?
We don't know if he'll
be killed yet.
- Of course.
- Maybe he's alive.
Can we just kill him and
write about it?
Think about the parents' feelings.
- It's too cruel.
- Are you stupid?!
If it's true, you write about
it, no matter how cruel.
That's what a journalist does!
If you think it's cruel, then
blame the kidnapper!
Understood?!
Make sure it's ready by tomorrow morning!
Yes, hello?
- Why don't you take it?!
- What? Oh.
- Hey, Koutaro.
- Yes.
This. Take it.
- Hello?
- Koutaro-san, will you really come?
You'll come, won't you?
I see, it's really late already.
I understand.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
In most instances, the victims get killed
right after they're kidnapped.
That's usually the case.
Hello, it's me.
Looks like I need to stay
for a few days.
Yes.
Is the fever down?
Oh, I see.
Take care.
Okay.
- Is your wife sick?
- Huh? Oh, no.
Our son got an eye surgery.
It's not a big deal.
But he's the same age as the
boy that was kidnapped.
So, I just wanted to check in.
All right, I'm going to
get some shut eye.
- Make sure you eat.
- Yes.
Despite Hideyuki-chan's parents'
desperate wish, he was mercilessly killed...
Captain, I don't think there'll be
any progress tonight.
There will be tomorrow,
so please get some rest.
Captain.
Do you understand what will happen
if you inform the police?
Next time, you'll end up seeing
your dead kid.
The kidnapper is hiding it well,
but he definitely has
a Kansai accent.
And there is a possibility that
he's using a car,
but he does need to collect
the ransom,
so we can assume that he is
situated
somewhere within a 30 to 40 km
radius of Takarazuka.
Make sure to tell the patrolling officers
to tighten vehicle inspections.
Oh, and make sure to check
the trunk of the cars.
The kid could be hidden there.
Yes!
Hello?
- The money.
- Money?
I'll make sure we get the money.
- So please...
- Today is Saturday.
Make sure to get 30,000,000 yen ready
before noon, while the bank is open.
Yes, um...
My son.
Please let me hear his voice. He...
Better to see his face than
to hear his voice, no?
Just a little bit if it's all right.
My son...
My son's voice.
Hello? Hello...
An announcement.
An urgent announcement!
Today at 5:28 pm. there was a
fourth call from the kidnapper.
We signed the agreement, so we
have to refrain from reporting it.
But that doesn't mean
that it's okay
for us to just do as the police say,
do nothing, and take a nap.
We must have everything
prepared,
so that we'll be ready when we're
released from the agreement.
But a child's life is at stake.
I hate to repeat myself, but don't get
within close proximity of the police.
Absolutely no direct interviews,
including phone interviews.
Just be extremely cautious.
- Social Section Chief.
- Yes.
I'm sure you're already aware, but
I'm going to remind you just in case.
All right?
In regards to interview preparations,
the HQ's Social Departments, the Hanshin
Branch and the Kobe Branch,
these three will work as a team
and work out of Takarazuka.
They should all be there already.
Wow, the big honcho is
here in person?
- It must be some story.
- It's a secret.
- I know, I know.
- Hello, it's been a while.
Good to see you too.
Hey, please, come on.
What?
You've grown so much!
Hurry up.
Eat and take a bath.
Isn't there another kid?
Where's the outlet?
- It's under there.
- Oh, I see.
Yes, please.
100,000 yen or 200,000 yen.
More would be extremely helpful.
I'll give it back no matter what.
Please.
I need it before noon today.
The reason is...
...a life.
My son's life is on the line.
Yes, yes.
150,0000 yen? In cash?
Thank you!
Thank you.
I can't thank you enough.
Thank you. Thank you.
Come on, let's eat.
If you don't eat, you won't have
energy when you need it.
Yes.
Kaori.
- Okay.
- See you later!
- Watch out for cars.
- Okay!
- Good morning.
- Ah, good morning.
Kazuo!
It's you, Kazuo!
Hey, it's me!
It's Kubo-da.
Did you forget?
We were together in high school,
Shinko-da Kubo.
Huh? Long time no see.
Did you come back because
your mother isn't feeling well?
In that case, can you give me a ride?
Okay, please?
This is great. Thanks.
All right.
The sound of the loom brings
back memories, doesn't it?
Yeah.
I'm a salaryman.
I work for a fisherman's co-op,
so the pay isn't great, but
the fishermen say if they didn't catch
fish we wouldn't earn a penny.
Well, at least it's a stable lifestyle.
Your brother also gave up
being a fisherman,
and went to work at a factory for
a luggage company in Toyooka.
Oh, over there!
Please stop there.
Hey. Hey.
You don't know that Nobuyo Shoji
is back, do you?
She left home and switched
men a lot,
but one day she came back on her own,
and now she works for a credit co-op.
Can you believe that Nobuyo
is at a credit co-op?
Makes me laugh.
I'm sure she'll hook up with another
man and run away with his money.
Well, thanks a lot!
Mom.
Thank you. Thank you.
You haven't eaten yet,
have you?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
My husband hasn't been back
the last couple of days.
What is it about?
A promissory note from your husband to a man
named Moriyasu ended up with me, so...
Really?
It's only 2,000,000 yen, but the
deadline is approaching,
so I want him to call me as
soon as he returns.
Please, have him call me.
Excuse me, have you
seen my husband?
I haven't seen him in a while.
- Has anyone seen Kazuyan recently?
- Nope.
Hello, this is Furuya.
Is my husband there?
He hasn't come recently.
Hello, mother?
It's Yoshie.
Have you heard from
Kazuo lately?
Hello?
It's me.
You...
If you were going back home, why
didn't you say something?
I wasn't planning on it.
Did you want something?
I won't know if you don't tell me.
You...
You borrowed money without
telling me, didn't you?
I don't owe any money.
But a man was here earlier...
He had a promissory note that you wrote
to someone named Moriyasu.
That must be some kind
of mistake.
But he said to call as soon as you got
home and gave his business card.
I said that's some kind
of mistake.
Moriyasu must have used my
name without permission,
and did some things
behind my back.
Just ignore it.
Are you sure you don't
owe any money?
Of course not.
Stop worrying about it.
Sweetheart...
Dear Grandma,
This is a holiday photo of Kaori
Who were you talking to?
To Yoshie.
How is everyone?
They're all well.
Kaori-chan must be tall.
Yeah.
I hear she goes to a
good school.
Can you cut it?
You used to, like this.
Here you go.
Um, I would like to take
the day off...
Sure, that's fine.
- It must be hard for you too.
- Yes.
Do you want more?
Are you done?
- I'm done.
- All right.
Can I have two boxes
of cigarettes?
And can you break 10 yen?
Here.
Thank you.
The money?
Is the 30,000,000 yen ready?
Yes, it's ready.
How is my son?
- He's fine. Stop worrying.
- But I want to hear...
Place the money in a bag and
be ready to go out at any time.
Hello?!
Kazuo!
The other one hardly ever comes home.
Why don't you stay here for a night?
There's been an emergency.
I need to get going.
That's too bad.
- All right then.
- Wait.
Wait a minute.
It was sudden,
so I have no gifts.
Please give this to Kaori-chan.
Tell her it's from Grandma.
- You don't have to.
- It's okay.
Okay, go.
Thank you.
- See you.
- Be careful!
Okay.
What is it?
Yes.
Is Moriyasu-san here?
Sir, you have a guest.
My goodness, what a surprise.
Please come this way.
Please, come on in.
- One hot.
- Yes.
Here.
It's all right.
You don't need to be so uptight.
It used to be your
husband's place.
A debt collector came to
visit my husband today.
A debt collector?
I haven't got a clue.
Stop playing dumb!
That's harsh.
Just sit.
He said my husband is responsible.
He had a promissory note
of 2,000,000 yen.
There's no way you don't
know about it.
Sure, I received the promissory note
from your husband.
But where that note ends up is out of
my control once it's out of my hands.
It can be passed around,
and it's none of my concern who
comes to collect at your door.
That's common knowledge.
So he did do it,
after all...
What, you're his wife
and you didn't know?
Why 2,000,000 yen?
To put an end to that loan,
of course.
You tricked my husband
with the promissory note,
then you took this place from him and
now a debt? It's too much.
Stop treating me like a criminal.
How about it?
Instead of being with that loser husband
of yours, why not be my woman?
You won't have to worry about any debt
and I'll take real good care of you!
Stop... Stop...
I heard from Nobu-chan.
It's been some time.
Kazuo!
Kazuo?
Kazuo! Kazuo!
Where did he go?
Kazuo!
What are you doing
with a child?!
Are you just going to abandon me?!
Bastard!
Kazuo!
I need to pee.
Pee.
I need to pee!
Pee!
Come on, hurry up.
- Fill it up.
- Okay.
- Wait a minute!
- Huh?
- Just 20 liters.
- Okay, 20 liters.
Here.
I like bread with cream.
But I like ones with jam better.
Six o'clock.
"Amigo."
Place the money in
a paper bag.
- That's strange.
- Something happened.
This is Tashiro.
7 disguised patrol cars left quietly.
Were there any announcements
at the Police HQ?
Nothing.
That's strange.
Can you please call Kobe?
All right.
Yes, Kobe.
Is this Aka-chan?
What? The police?
There are no announcements.
Ask the two undercover.
How about you, U-yan?
No matter what we ask, we get told
to get out, so we have no clue.
You're supposed to be the snapper
turtle. Stop being pathetic.
You bite again and again
and again!
Go ask again!
Contact Nabe in the box and have him check
out what's going on at the Hyogo Police HQ.
All right, I'll contact him
right away.
Hello? Assistant chief, Nabe.
Urgent announcement.
Sixth call from the kidnapper.
"6 pm., Kiyoshikoujin 1 chome
in Takarazuka, Amigo.
Bring the money to Amigo."
Kiyoshikoujin...
Oh, this is it.
1 chome.
Here it is.
Right here.
- Where?
- It's a café.
This is it.
Team 2.
We're in place, as planned.
Team 3, in place.
All right.
Pay attention to all cars passing by.
Command Center, this is Inugai.
Everyone is in place.
This is Kitagawa, Chief Patrol
Officer of the Pursuit Team.
No contact from the
kidnapper yet.
A white car has cruised down
the main street three times.
Inukai Detective to Kuwahara
Patrol Chief Officer.
A suspicious person found.
Confirm the number and report.
Number confirmed.
Kobe 58 sa 4561.
Yoshie!
Yoshie.
I'm home.
Daddy's home!
Welcome home.
While you were gone,
I was walking Leon.
Is that so?
I'm proud of you.
- Kaori, bath.
- I'll take it after I eat.
Go now.
- Kaori.
- I'll take a bath with daddy.
- Kaori!
- All right! Let's take a bath together!
Okay!
Why did you have to lie to me?
I've finally come to terms
with our new life.
We got rid of the bigger
car and dog.
Why try so hard to put Kaori
in a private school?
But you're still chasing the dream you
had when you owned your café.
Even if it's not such a flashy job, if you decided
to work hard, I figured we could work it out.
That's how I've managed
until now.
But if you owe 2,000,000 yen
to a loan shark,
it won't do any good no matter
how hard you work.
It's useless!
Hey, have mommy wipe you.
If you could have just told me
from the beginning...
I just didn't want to worry you.
And we don't have to talk about
this in front of Kaori, do we?
- We can talk about it at length later.
- Stop changing the subject.
- Why do I have to change the subject?
- Aren't you?
You're always lying!
Go upstairs and get ready
for school tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Sunday.
- Just hurry up.
- Is dinner ready? I'm hungry.
I'll be quick.
Here.
Towel.
I don't understand you
anymore.
Are you really thinking
about Kaori and me?
I really thought about taking Kaori
and leaving today,
but unlike you, I don't have a home
or family to depend on.
I want Kaori to grow up
with a father...
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to
worry about.
I wasn't sure, so...
I couldn't tell you until now,
but I'll have the money soon.
I'll have over 10,000,000 yen.
I'll buy back the café too.
Kaori wouldn't have to
change schools either.
There was a guy I took
care of in the past.
He built supermarkets
everywhere,
and he's going to lend me money
with almost no interest.
I'm supposed to meet him
at a café at 8 pm.
It's 7:30 pm. now.
I'm going to see him now.
I'll bring home good news.
Oh, no.
I left my wallet somewhere.
Can you lend me
10,000 yen?
- You've got to be kidding me!
- Yoshie.
Stop talking nonsense.
It's 30,000,000 yen!
How does a man talking about 3,0000,000
yen not have 10,000 yen?!
I told you already!
- I left my wallet somewhere!
- All right!
I understand, so stop talking!
Yoshie!
Take everything!
Everything in the house!
Everything here is yours!
- Take everything!
- Yoshie, calm down.
I'm telling you to take it!
This is the remainder of what
I made from my part-time job.
We haven't even paid Kaori's tuition.
This is all of it!
- You haven't...
- I'm sorry.
- You haven't had any income...
This is everything!
All of it!
Yoshie!
Be good to mom!
What's this?
Hide-chan gave it to me.
- Hide-chan?
- He's a good friend.
He wasn't at school today,
so I couldn't play with him.
Can I borrow 10,000 yen?
Your wife came this afternoon.
She's a feisty one.
I said 10,000 yen.
Sir, here's your change.
Welcome.
What's going on?
So many couples I haven't seen before.
- I'll leave it here.
- Thank you.
Hello. Amigo.
Is there a Mitamura-san there?
- Hello?
- Hello.
I've been waiting here since
6 pm., as promised.
What are you talking about?!
You broke your promise,
and told the cops, so I can't
make it there! Damn it!
I haven't told them...
Stop lying!
There's tons of cops there!
Hello?
We haven't told the police anything.
Hello?!
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Please! Please trust us and give
us one more chance!
All right.
The airport lobby.
The airport?
The lobby at Itami Airport?
If you go by car it's quick.
Wait there.
Y-yes...
If I find the police next time, you might
as well give up on the kid.
Hello? Hello?
Hello?!
Contact the backup team!
He may be planning an escape.
- Captain!
- It's a bluff!
There's no way he's aware
of our presence.
Itami Airport Lobby.
Why didn't the kidnapper
appear at Amigo?
- He probably knew that there were cops there.
- No calls from the kidnapper?
The investigation is at a critical juncture
so please don't inquire any more.
But we suspect nothing else
will happen tonight.
Don't treat us like fools.
We're not that stupid.
We've honored the agreement and
haven't interviewed anyone at all.
In return, the police have an obligation
to inform us on a regular basis.
That's right.
You're useless.
- Get us the Detective Chief.
- This won't do.
It's an urgent message from the
Takarazuka Command Center.
"A suspicious car spotted
in front of Amigo.
From the license plate,
we've confirmed that it belongs to someone
who works for a newspaper company."
You talk about the agreement,
but you're the ones breaking it!
Huh?
The police are saying that
nothing will happen tonight.
Hello, this is the Takarazuka
Delivery Office.
Koutarou-san?
I'm at Itami Airport.
Why?
I'm going back to Tokyo
on the last flight.
I thought I'd let you know.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to
apologize anymore.
You will never quit being
a journalist.
I can't deal with someone whose job keeps
them from seeing their partner.
It won't work out between us.
- Tomo-chan, wait.
- Goodbye.
Tomo-chan!
You're on, Shiho-chan.
Mari-chan, too.
Go and talk to her.
What are you doing?
I wet my pants.
Forget it. Forget it.
You're not going to get mad?
- Are you warm enough?
- Yes.
- You must be hungry.
- If it's bread, I like...
- You like bread with jam, right?
I'll go and get some now.
I'll let you go home in
a little bit, all right?
Mister.
Can you take off the blindfold?
Wow, stars!
Excuse me, excuse me!
Here's bread with jam.
Hey, I got you bread
with jam.
Bread with jam.
Hey.
A kid won't last in this
cold temperature.
It may take a bit longer
than expected.
Well, why don't we get some
shut eye while we can.
That's true.
Then let's get some sleep.
Oh, sorry.
Thank you.
I would love to show
my wife that style.
Oh, that's right.
Sorry.
Yes, Takarazuka.
It's me. I got information from Kakinuma,
who I sent to Tokyo.
According to a branch of the police department,
something's happening tonight.
The location of the exchange changed.
It's at Itami Airport.
- At the ticket lobby.
- Damn it!
Tomo-chan, you waited for me.
Yes.
- You have to leave now.
- Why?
Come.
We have a message for
the following guest.
Mitamura-sama, Mitamura-sama.
Please pick up the phone at the information
desk on the first floor lobby.
The police are here!
That's impossible!
Who are those couples
walking around?
They were at Amigo earlier.
Those are cops!
Don't kill my son, please!
Please, save my son!
I'll do anything!
Please save my son!
Please!
Hello? Hello?
I'm cold. Mommy.
I'm cold.
Cold.
You'll catch a cold
sleeping out here.
Mom, Mom!
Dad came home.
He left with my water bottle.
He just left.
Honey!
Honey! Honey!
Honey... Honey...
Die! Die!
Hello?! Hello?!
I killed the kid.
It's your fault for notifying
the police!
What?
I've had enough of the kid.
I don't know what to
do with him.
Hideyuki!
He's alive?
Hideyuki's alive?
Is he safe?
He's safe?
Look, this is really the
very last time!
Your last chance!
Do you understand?!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Can we please listen
to his voice?
That way we can calm down.
Is he eating something?
He isn't crying?
Is he well rested?
10 yen.
I don't have 10 yen!
I don't have time!
This is your last chance.
You better not do
anything to ruin it.
Yes, we promise not to let
the police come near.
The money! There's no deal unless we
exchange the child for the money!
Yes, so where should we bring it,
and what time?
What time?
I don't have a watch.
My watch!
Not even 10 yen.
- The place, the place.
- Are you ready?
In front of the car shop.
Car shop!
In front of the car shop!
- Please don't come anymore.
- No, we can't do that.
Worst case scenario, you'll lose
both the money and your son.
We don't care about the money.
If my son comes back
frozen and dead,
but we hadn't given
up the money,
what would I tell my child...?
I won't be able to live
with myself...
I just want to give the
kidnapper this money.
Detective.
Do you have a child
of your own?
If you have your own child,
you must understand.
Don't come with us.
Promise not to follow us.
Promise.
Chief, is it really all right to let
them go by themselves?
It's fine.
Don't interfere.
What? They left?
I approved.
I'm making a formal
request myself.
Don't interfere with them.
Idiots!
The police have only one responsibility!
To capture the criminal
that broke the law!
But as a parent...
Myself, as a parent...
Don't let your emotions get in the way.
Tell me where they're going.
If we don't go, we lose the chance
to arrest the kidnapper.
Tell me! It's an order.
It's almost 4 o'clock.
- What's going on?
- You were still here?
- Get rid of them.
- Say something!
How annoying!
I'm not backing down at this
point no matter what!
- Hey, a patrol car.
- All right.
Ow.
There's someone
here already.
Why did you come?
Bastards!
Why did you come?!
Hey, your driver's license.
Show me your driver's license.
Didn't you hear me?
Hey.
Hey!
I'm going to check
your trunk.
There's a child!
Is he dead?
Hey, kid, hey!
Kid, hey, kid!
Kid!
Thank you, thank you!
Then, we'll be going now.
All right!
Thank goodness.
- He's been arrested!
- What?
- Emergency arrest.
- What, an emergency arrest?
The kidnapper was arrested?
How about the child? Is he safe?
If he's safe, then we start interviewing!
Hello, report!
The child is safe!
Good! A special report!
Sequel tomorrow,
and then more on Monday.
We'll use the entire front page!
So, we aren't bound by the
agreement anymore?
- I'm checking now.
- Okay.
You're being called.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Hey, who's covering the crime scene?
- Yes?
- All right, you go.
- Yes!
- Okay, I'll drive.
- Hurry up!
Thank you.
At 8:30, they've decided to release
us from the agreement.
What are you talking about?
We're already on the move.
What? Darn!
What do you expect? If we waited
for you, nothing would get done.
Yes, but still...
The "News Coverage Agreement"
isn't "News Coverage Restriction!"
- You're sure about the place?
- I think so.
Can we really trust you?
Yomiuri 94, 94.
This is Osaka Yomiuri 3.
We're driving down below.
Please guide us.
Understood. The crime scene is on
the right bank of the Takeko River.
Right by the mouth of the
river is a silver car.
The trunk's opened and there
are police surrounding it.
Got it.
Any sign of the child?
- No.
- The kidnapper?
No.
A police car just came up the
river bank on the right.
Maybe they're in it.
Understood.
Oh, that's it!
Kou-chan! You can take a picture
when we drive past by, right?
- What are you doing?
- I have to...
That guy in the middle
is the kidnapper.
Oh, what the hell?
Stop the car! What the hell?
Hey!
What kind of driving is that?
- I'm sorry, my hand slipped.
- What are you doing?!
- Hurry, get that car out of the way!
- Raise your head!
It's the middle of the program,
but we have news.
The son of a pediatrician in
Takarazuka was kidnapped,
and the kidnapper who demanded
ransom was arrested.
The kidnapper's name is Kazuo Furuya, 29,
residing in Toyonaka-shi,
and currently out of work.
It's believed that he resorted to kidnapping
after failing to manage his café business.
The shocking revelation is that
the kidnapper is actually a parent
of a classmate attending the same
school as Hideyuki Mitamura,
the boy who was kidnapped.
Furuya has confessed to
learning that the boy's father
was a doctor via the
school register,
and he believed that with enough threats,
the boy's father would pay the ransom
without contacting the police.
At Toyonaka Wakaba Gakuen,
everyone is celebrating
"Hideyuki-chan's Rescue to Safety, "
however, the shocking news that the kidnapper
was the father of a classmate
is creating a somewhat
gloomy atmosphere.
Now, we will report from the hospital
where Hideyuki is being nursed.
The press conference being held
there will be reported live.
Mitamura-san, your current
feeling in one word.
I'm thankful to everyone,
and I'm very happy.
It was my fault.
All my fault.
I kept on bothering him about money.
I did it...
You must hate the kidnapper.
How do you feel about him?
Please be honest.
I hate him.
Hideyuki-kun, how was it?
Was the kidnapper scary?
Smile. Hide-kun, we're glad
you're safe now.
Come on, smile.
Smile.
Hide-kun, over here.
Kaori! Kaori!
Hurry! Hurry!
Nakamura-san, you know where
the wife is, right?
Please tell us.
You're hiding, right?
We know you're hiding.
- That ruckus outside has nothing to do with us.
- Isn't it your fault?!
Really. It's got nothing
to do with us.
Tell us the truth!
It's just that... Daddy needs to
go work in a faraway place.
He won't be able to come
back anytime soon.
We'll miss him, but you'll
be okay, right?
Kaori...
Kaori is smart.
So smart, so smart!
Tell us the truth!
If you feel bad, why don't you
apologize to the victims?!
Kaori.
Kaori, get up.
Kaori, we're going to go to
Grandma's place in Tango.
You'll go to a new school there.
And wait for daddy to
come back.
Here.
I love my dad!
The wind is breathing
It's breathing
It caresses the soft hair
Creates waves in the lake
The wind is breathing
- Good job!
- You did well, huh?
- Let's drink, let's drink.
- How was it?
- I struck out.
They must have gone
to hide with a relative.
Hey.
But it tastes darn good.
- Really good!
- I look forward to the morning paper.
You did well.
- Good job.
I guess we should head
on home.
- Good night.
Yes! Oh, Kama-chan.
It's me. Yes.
What?
I see.
Our company was taken off
the police's reporter club.
Why?
- For breaking the agreement.
- That can't be.
They say that 20 minutes before they
released us from the agreement at 8:30,
one of our helicopters
was in flight.
Here's the proof.
Ironically, it's the picture in our
special edition. Look at this!
"Photographed from company
helicopter at 8:10."
So how about that white car?
- Branch manager.
- Yes?
- It's from the chief.
- The chief?
- Yes.
- You heard about us being taken off the list.
But we didn't do anything against the
principle behind the agreement.
We took action after we confirmed
Hideyuki's safety.
The agreement was for the sake
of the child, so it's all right.
Great job.
It's quite a special edition.
It's the culmination of everyone's efforts,
despite the agreement's limitations.
Great job. Really.
Yes!
The wind is breathing
It's breathing
It caresses the soft hair
Creates waves in the lake
The wind is breathing
The stars are breathing
They're breathing
As they swirl endlessly
Without a sound
The stars are breathing
The life of all living things
As they fight, as they long
for each other
The life of all living things
The people are breathing
They're breathing
They breathe out their suffering
They breathe in their sorrow
The people are breathing
Directed by:
Shunya Ito
THE END