Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Snow in Shinano.
Just like the name,
She looks like she was beautifully born out of the snow.
Yuki Fujin Ezu / Portrait of Madame Yuki / A Picture of Madame Yuki
(Produced in 1968 / Released in 1975)
Madam Yuki was born in this village.
That was last year,
Yuki's father,Elders of the House of Lords
and he was our village boss long ago
It was on the day that Shakushi Shinano Chozaemon passed away
Hamako is living in a villa by the lake
Thanks to my help, on the day of the funeral,
I went to help out at Gohontei at Shinanoike.
This was the first of Hamako's apprenticeship.
Excuse me.
it's Hama.
Oh you.
Thank you in advance.
Where should I put those flowers?
Just leave them there.
I get it.
How's okin?
She told me to say hello to you.
The lake is still frozen?
But the mountains are pure white
mountains?
I heard you didn't have your mom.
She died last year.
She was good friends with Okin
My father died in the Philippines because of war.
so I'm glad I had a good person come here.
Sorry, I can't do anything.
Excuse me.
I'm Tsuya.
Please come in.
Ohin.
She was so nice person.
It's dark.
She was looking so healthy when I met her the other day
What are you doing? Get out.
Yes.
I’m sorry.
How lonely you are.
Thanks.
Gotoshi has not arrived yet?
I telegramed.
I know it's far Kyoto from Tokyo.
But, it was three days ago.
Who is going to take care of the funeral
I just met Osumi there
Is Yuki here?
She's here.
The wake guests are here.
I see.
By the way, about funeral
I'm sure you must be tired.
If Yuki's mother were alive,
She was nice person
I wanted to take orders from her.
But she passed away 20 years ago.
From the age of 16, I have been taking care of you
I have mentioned them in order of age
Time is not an issue.
Just by being by your side, you can't do your job as a woman
You are just a maid.
What's the hell?
I’m sorry.
Who on earth is the person who did something strange with other guys?
Did I do that?
Don't pretend you don't know.
I know everything
What?
Please excuse me for playing quietly
I’m sorry.
Let's go over there.
It's fine
I'd be humiliated in front of the Buddha.
I can't keep quiet.
We all have the same idea.
The dead lord left a difficult problem.
The daimyo's blood is tainted
It was like a zoo.
Thank you for taking care of us.
Not at all
I'm sorry for him.
I'm Yamazaki from antique store.
Please give me Okra's treasure
I'll give you all the high-end stuff.
Yogoretachi...
Chudanna is leaving.
Chichiya!
Welcome back
You...
everyone is here.
Who are you?
I'm Yamazaki from antique store.
You're Matsutomo.
I'm sorry for him.
I'll give you old antique.
Please make a big sale.
Thank you.
Welcome back.
Who's her?
She the new maid from Shinshu.
my name is Hana.
How old was your father?
He was 73.
He lived long.
Did you know that Osumi was dating  with Tsuchiya?
No.
You're ignorance
Beside this house,
mansion in Yokohama
And Some in Asakusa.
All was taken by Tsuchiya.
After I got the telegram, I started researching banking.
Property taxes and other things left us penniless
This mansion has also been seized, so nothing of the Shinano family's assets will be left
Our father is also a bit absent-minded, +he's an old-fashioned lord
He was like a bucket of water.
Don't talk badly about him.
Tonight is the wake.
You think it's really my fault
So I'm a paper with a dowry
Hey.
I am not taken care of.
What's the hell?
No money is the same as no head
I'm not gonna do anything. I'm gonna die
The person named Kikunaka is here.
The cheap writer?
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Shinano family is no good either.
What do you think?
Why don't you write a novel about us?
Excuse me.
They found our relationship.
It's all over for us, the Shinano family too.
It feels like a dream
Lords are victims of war, too.
You got fat?
MacArthur came.
We had no family or civilians
Christ's Fall and the Fall of the World
Excuse me
I received the news.
Thanks.
Not at all.
Apparently the lord has passed away
Who will clean up Mr. Goto's mess from now on?
He said making a lotion or building tourist hotel.
And then he falls for some worthless woman again
These days, he's been spending a lot of time with that
girl in Kyoto and he hardly ever come back to Tokyo
Well, shall I worship?
I'm so tired
Look, that novelist teacher is a pretty good guy
It seems that Mrs. Yuki is also interested in him.
But he has a wife and kid.
It's time to go.
Yes, I forgot to bring the paper.
I'll go now
, Hama-chan
He's little strange, so be careful.
At times like that, at times like that,
you put force into your abdomen under your navel.
you say it so well.
Excuse me.
I've brought some water.
Please come in.
I'll leave it here
Bring it here.
Hey.
Hey, Take care of her clothes.
Fold them.
Yes.
Mrs. Yuki...
35000!
36000!
38000! anyone wanna bid?
ok 38000yen.
Next is the 86th Makie Children's Dance
50000!50000!50000!
60000! 70000!
75000!
75000! anyone wanna bid?
He turned the Shinano family's villa into an inn business.
We find that hard to believe.
Hotel Shinano...
Hello?
This is Hotel Shinano.
Oh master..This is Kin.
Will you arrive tonight?
Ok I get it.
Any guest has come?
Master will arrive.
He was calling from Kashiwara station.
He'll come here by car.
We are not busy.
Not many guest comes.
Get ready for bath.
Kikunaga sensei want meal at 6 o'clock.
Where's wife?
She's with sensei.
Again?
Her husband will come.
Really?
Please tell that to her.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
What?
I wondered your wife was here.
She went down stairs.
I was evicted from my Tokyo home and  moved to Shinanojiri Village
Mrs. Yuki has already written about this Shinano tree
Mrs.Yuki.
Your husband is going to be here soon.
I see.
Yes, it's a great winter scenery.
Is your husband coming from Kyoto?
Yes.
It could be.
there's only here and Kyoto.
Here is where you can only live.
Hotel Shinano is the last castle for you.
Do you remember?
Autumn Foliage in Takao.
Yuki-chan's white face was covered in maple leaves
It was not only that.
Looking back...
What is love...
Underneath it all is something to be feared.
Wife.
Has he arrived?
Yes.
He is with Kyoto person.
Here is pretty good.
You guys remodel well.
We're lucky.
What happened to Yuki?
Please wait in the room over there.
Where?
Monkey room.
Do you think I am like monkey?
I want to run this hotel too.
Hold on.
What happened to Yuki?
she is coming.
Let's call her soon
I see.
You can drink too, right?
Drink it.
Come here.
You're cute.
Remember, the Gion?
on the way back from Gion
It was fun with Kikunaka.
Yes he was with us.
We went to see the autumn leaves.
He looked happy.
Serve her.
You serve her.
Let's have fun tonight.
Drink it.
What's this?
This is Shinshu's iced tofu.
This is good for your beauty.
This room is old.
It's old-fashioned.
Yuki likes this kind of stuff.
Are you making money?
We are in the red
I'm managing the money exchange.
Yuki, that's a bad hobby
that's a bad hobby
Let's have fun more.
Let me manage here.
You're greedy woman
You told me you wanted to be singer so I made music band for you.
You said you wants to be an actress, so next I introduced you a film company.
Let me manage here.
I don't feel well.
I'll see you soon.
See you later.
Hama
Yes.
please come to my room tonight.
Please rest together
It hurts.
I can't see the wife
She must be her husband's room.
Really?
She forgot to lock the door so she went upstairs
Then she entered his room.
I can't believe it.
She was crying.
That's true.
Naoyuki-san likes you.
In the end, you are brought back to here.
You know about that.
Deep down, you seem to hate Naoyuki
You think so?
You just don't notice it.
You like me.
However,you feel guilty about your husband.
she was able to get rid of the feelings of infidelity
That's a ridiculous.
but that's not a virtue or anything
There is an old sermon called "Karukaya"
I still perform it in plays around the countryside
The samurai who had lived with her wife and mistress together.
He loved the two of them for a while
One day
The women play together at the Sugoroku table
The man was surprised to see the shadow reflected in the shoji screen from outside
They were turned into snakes and they started biting each other
The husband was so terrified by the woman's obsession that he spent a year traveling to Mount Koya
There's no need to worry about Naoyuki shaving his head though
Your marriage is a kind of planned marriage.
You were indifferent to your marriage,
so now you're not emotionally attached to your husband
This old thing doesn't apply to the modern day
In other words, it's material for a play
What should I do?
Break up with him.
He won't
It's up to you.
So you were here.
Where's Aya?
She's taking a bath.
She's a woman who likes baths.
By the way, I didn't know you were staying there for a while
I like you.
No one say anything.
I love you
thank you for staying at Hotel Shinano
it's quiet here.
It's a really good place to write
It's too quiet for me
Yuki, come here.
Yuki-san and I
Christmas in the mountains Merry Christmas
Let's do something nice
I won in Kyoto.
Let's bid.
What?
your most important thing.
What's that?
There is.
Tell me.
It's Mrs.Yuki.
Right?
No way.
I'll take her.
OK.
Are you sure?
It's your turn.
Good.
Let's see then
I won
I see
Where have you been? Merry Christmas
Your bath is long. I don't know where you're washing
What you will give me?
Again.
What a nice ring
This is a memento of my mother's.
Buy it for me.
I will.
Let's dance.
I got you from Naoyuki
You can see the crystal.
Look, what a wonderful gift.
This is what god made.
No, it's a human too.
Human is made by God.
Men and women.
Yuki.
Wife.
Wife got problem.
wife.
Yuki.
She didn't wake up so I came to see her.
Then...
Does she have a pulse?
Doctor will come right away?
What happened to Naoyuki?
He went to Akakura with her girl.
For fun?
Yes.
he is a troubled man
Hey.
What happened to Yuki? Is she okay?
She was at home.
What?
Welcome back.
What happened to Yuki?
Yuki is quietly taking a break now
You bastard!
She doesn't want to meet you.
What?
Remember the old day in Ueno.
I picked you up because you were a clever kid
You are an orphan of war.
Yuki is in another house?
She must be with Kikunaka.
If she hadn't been any danger to her life, I wouldn't have come back
Bring me Brandy.
Stay here.
You look upset.
Don't bully your wife.
I don't.
Do you have someone named Ayako who your loves?
Yuki is in love with me
Yuki, as its name suggests, melts quickly if you just warm it up a little
There's a monster living inside Yuki's body
Monster?
The monster is a fiery snake
Why did you do that?
Why medicine?
Naoyuki want to leave the management of this house to Ayako-san.
I tried my best.
but you can't.
I was in half way.
For everything.
You're suffering in the storm.
But no matter how hard you work..
I'll try.
Excuse me.
Kikunaga sensei is here?
Oh kin.
This is a telegram from Tokyo
What's about?
My wife is in critical condition.
She's been bedridden for five years now.
She's either malnourished or has a chest condition.
We were living in extreme poverty
Let's go home by trian.
You.
You can't leave Naoyuki.
You were just disappointed that you lost to someone from Kyoto. You were just frustrated.
Hold on.
I'll have Hama-san take you to the station on your way home.
in place of me.
She's a beautiful woman.
The truth is that it cannot be dismissed as old,
But...
it is deep and full of secrets and mysteries.
Is that so?
I'll carry it.
Yuki is strong against me,but she's weak against that man
Look, the snow has already melted
She is like a distant snow scape to me
How are you feeling?
I heard Kikunaka's gone home.
Why are you turning red?
I'll let Ayako take charge of here from tomorrow.
You can stay here,
Only Ohin is no use.
If things continue like this, even if I borrow money, the interest will be volcanic
Actually, I couldn't go back to Kyoto because I was so debt-ridden
I'm leaving this. I don't want anymore.
I'm really leaving
Just for 3 months...
Mrs Yuki too..
13220 yen payment on delivery
If she is not educated maid, it's ok.
but she has bachelor's degree
Oshidori room's guest is leaving.
Three bottles of beer
Towel, toothbrush,some cigarettes,
Please add these amounts as well
I'm off to the station.
Buy medicine for cold.
Hey,Come here.
Hey, hey Kikunaga-san will come.
You look so nice.
I'll come to the station to pick him up.
You spend money very lavishly.
You embezzle from the books.
I don't.
Check the book keep.
What are you going to do with her?
I'm off to the station.
Hey.
I'm make up for it.
Are you?
I'll sell my personal belonging.
We already sold that diamond.
I didn't know that.
You're lying.
Yuki is the legal wife and I am just mistress.
Marry me,  marry me
That's a good idea, let's do that
Kick that person out.
Leave her here.
You'll probably be able to be legal wife.
What are you talking about?
You have unfinished business with YUKI.
You have been taken care by him
You look down on me.
I took care of his parents and siblings, and finally it was all over
Who can live with legal wife and mistress together?
Hey,I feel like crying. .
What's wrong with this family?
The winds of life are blowing all over the world
I hope you die because you are causing trouble for other people
It would be better if you died.
I hope you die.
Stop it....
Darling...
Do you feel cold?
Where's Yuki?
Yuki-san has moved.
Eh?
To The back of the park.
I see.
The Kyoto woman caused trouble.
Yes.
I'll take some rest too.
please tell Yuki-san
I would be waiting her in the basement hall in two hours.
You get it?
Yes.
No one can die alone.
Now or tomorrow...
how can even our hearts not die?
When you die, life is like a shadow.
I thought you'd come.
It will be a while.
What is that?
It's the sound of ice
It's the sound of ice?
The ice on the lake is cracking.
They are screaming with excitement.
Did you know this poem?
I love these ice, I love these fleeting thoughts.
I love those bright, unscented flowers
I sympathize with what lies beneath the ice
I always encourage my life.
The moment when we groan in the fragrance of life
I love these ice.
I love these fleeting thoughts.
Let's put on fire.
I can't.
I didn't know how to put it on.
You are ohin after all.
Your hand is as cold as ice.
Where's your wife?
She's dead.
She passed away?
When I arrived in Tokyo
She had already taken his last breath.
I didn't know
I didn't tell everyone.
Yuki-san.
This is not good idea.
I'll marry to Hamako.
I love the pure heart of a virgin
But I will never forget that stern response, the cracking of the icy ice.
You live in a different world than me
It's because of snowing. It might be because of the snow
It's spring in Japan now, after a long war
The sound of the spring
You will disappears along with that sound.
That may be your destiny
The chilling sound of ice cracking
I love these fleeting thoughts
He loves you.
So by marrying me, he wants to forget about you.
I love you too, ma'am.
I hope you take care of yourself
Excuse me.
Hama-san.
Be happy
ma'am.
For me.
A dirty blood.
You.
You probably don't own a knife,right?
hysteria.
You can't live without me.
Who are you!
I kill you!
You dude!
What's wrong? I LOVEYOU.
What happened?
Wait a min.
You dude!
Master.
What happened?
He was trying to kill me.
It's attempted murder.
Say sorry to him.
Damn it.
He's idiot.
Where's master?
Yuki.
Did you know that?
Well, I had a vague feeling that.
It was okay.
Take a rest.
misfortunes never come singly
I was kicked out
This house has been taken.
They changed the registered name.
will you come with me?
Where are you going?
Kansai.
If you go there, there are a lot of people I've taken care of
Let's see, I'll ask Kyoka in Gion.
She is doing Geisha business.
She'd be happy.
How about my baby?
Get an abortion.
I don't want.
Listen,
It was because of you that I played around with women.
Same for Ayako, there's no such thing as a worthless woman
So you are my treasure
You can't leave me and neither can I
You know that, don't you?
We are well matched couple.
I beg you, go with me
I'm going to get the first train.
Hurry up.
Get ready soon.
Can you go with me? then I'll be waiting downstairs when it's ready
I beg you.
Damn it!
Don't look down on me.
I'll get you back.
Please
You are lonely woman.
I'm lonely too.
I am an orphan.
You are noble.
But we are lonely.
Madam, I will accompany you.
Where are we going?
across the sea.
across the sea?
There is a quiet place around Matsugasaki
There is a quiet place?
It's not good to have you as a geisha.
I don't like it
Wife, please come with me
I beg you.
Wife
Wife, please go together
Wife.
Let's go.
Isn't it beautiful, ma'am?
It feels like spring already.
You can see the Village there.
I'll look back..
Love is the shadow of a mask.
Underneath it all is a fearful shame.
Madam Yuki?
Were you born in such a remote mountain area?
What  a clear evening.
You can see the mountains
Myoko Kurohime Iizuma
hama-chan said
You are like a snow.
Here's your tea.
The ice melts, spring is near.
Seitaro.
Butterbur Blossom Blossoms by the Waterside.
Wife.
Would you like me to give you a shoulder massage?
No.
you can have an apple.
I'm fine with that. Will you get heat?
Lemon, look, I bought it here
These are too sour.
I don't understand.
Will you get heat?
Wife.
Is this your husband's baby?
Or Kikunaga's?
I know everything.
Mr. Kikunaga didn't get Hama-chan instead of you.
You are snow.
Hama-chan is just mud. Mud can't turn into snow
A maid is more convenient for taking care of one's personal needs.
I wonder my baby is being healthy...
you're a helpless person.
You can't do any of the housework or laundry that other people can do.
That's why you are beautiful.
I told you it's beautiful because of the snow.
Your husband is a jerk, but for some reason you like him.
I don't understand about you guys.
So I wanted to kill him
I want to kill Kikunaga too. He stole your heart.
And because you are too noble, he ran away.
I feel good.
You don't know about my feeling.
I don't know.
I don't know for me.
Let's go to Tokyo.
Come with me to Tokyo.
Yes, I'll work there.
I can do anything, even as a waiter or a bartender
Take good care of you and feed you at least one meal.
Your wife is too beautiful to live in this murky world
But please stay as snow fairy all the time.
Thank you Sentaro.
thank you.
Madam, would you like me to massage you?
You're really stiff
In truth, I would even give my life for you.
If you ask me for my life, I will die immediately without any hesitation
I would happily die
I won't let anyone to get you.
Wife!
Naokoyuki..I should go mad and die
Kikunaka....
bloodstained.
I have to die.
Mrs. Yuki!
THE END