Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Zoku Teppo Inu / Return of Gun Dog (1966)
(Inu/Dog Series #6)
Miyoshi!
Takara is also there.
They betrayed us.
Bring out the item
Hurry up
Get out!
What are you doing?
Hurry up to open the trunk
Carry it
Put it inside
Miyoshi,
Calm down
This is a threat
Damn it
Police,
Run away!
Hurry up! Miyoshi
Don't worry.
Hurry up!
Captain!
Are you alright?
Well, that's how it is if I happened to be there
The car can't get away.
You're making a story
What are you talking about?
This is true.
I went to visit that detective today and heard the story
That Kimura's face was filled with regret
So, I told that  I would take revenge, so they asked me to get a job with the police
The police said they couldn't afford to pay such a high reward because my gun skills are incredible.
That's just common sense
Has the getaway car been found?
They managed to escape and are now missing.
The police doesn’t work
I am thinking about it right now
I intend to run in the next election.
Don't be foolish
If I become a member of parliament, I can freely use a pistol.
Just stop already
You need to take this a bit more seriously, or I'm going to get really angry, you know?
You are wearing cute clothes
You think so?
It's good on you
This clothing comes in various colors.
You look so nice.
Really?
Welcome
Can I get  a brandy?
Could you turn this way a little?
You'll listen to my concerns, won't you?
Hurry to tell me
My mother is sick, right?
My younger brother graduated from university and got a job, didn't he?
And I guess I need to practice singing
It's been really tough lately
Yeah
I can't make ends meet on the income I earn working at a pachinko parlor.
I've been thinking about moving in Tokyo,
What do you think?
but if you want to go, you can just go and do it
I want to throw tape at you as you leave, but...
The Shrinkage doesn't let me open the windows, so I'll pass
Did you listen to me with your back turned?
Huh? my eyes really do want to see beautiful things.
I'm listening to the conversation properly, so that's fine, right?
Yeah, I see
I didn't know you were such a man
It hurts
You're very good
Are you going to have some too?
Well, if you ask nicely, I can make it for you
Shall we pay?
I can't just turn around when I'm being challenged by a woman
Let's play
Well then, I'll go first.
Wow, you are so great
I might be lose
Here it is
Thank you very much.
Here I go
The last one....
Wow!
I lost
Take it.
I can't take it
Why?
I can't take money from you for that game.
But...
Don't worry.
Hey, hey, hey, you won, right?
You get the money
That's right
Men doesn't care about such things.
What are you saying?
You don't have any money, so I always treat you.
Since you don't have any money, take that money.
I approached and said it, but I would like you to take it
Well, that's true
I can't
You're such a man as I thought
You change your mind when you meet a beautiful woman.
Tama?
What?
Samurai won't eat
Kamoi.
Then at least let me treat you to something and take you home
You wouldn't say no to that, would you?
Here?
The corner where the pawn shop is
I wonder if we can meet again?
I don't really know
I'm a wanderer.
Take care.
Hey"
Where were you without paying your lodging fees?
Wait and take it off!
I can't take my clothes off in a place like this
What are you talking about?
This will cover your lodging expenses.
hurry up and take it off!
I get it, I'm taking it off!
I'm taking it off!
Alright!
I'll give you this too!
I'll give you this too
that's how it is
If you were that rich girl,
you would have given some pocket money, right?
But I refused it.
Why?
Hey, a man who takes money
from a woman is a worthless man,
Kamoi?
Tama!
What are you wearing?
So it's finally over,
where are you going?
I'm going to Tokyo
To Tokyo?
Yeah, I've already decided
on a place to work
You finally make a debut?
Are you going to record something?
No, that's not it
Are you going to sing at night club ?
Well, it's not that, but it's an artistic job
That's pretty good, isn't it?
If it's an artistic job, that's something impressive,
but it's a bit lonely that I can't hear
Catamaran’s singing anymore, isn't it?
Don't say like that.
I got preparation money
And I'll give some to Kamoi
Oh I see
Well, it's not a man who receives money from a woman.
That's right, but even so, I don't need it
Don't say something so distant
Please accept my feelings, okay?
It's fine, just take it, just take it
After all, I'm not the kind of guy who can get money from women
You can't take it in front of everyone
Well then, I'll stop giving that to you
Tama-chan. You left some money.
That's not mine.
See you.
Tama-chan.
Picking up money is not a shame for a man.
I like that way she thinks
It went very well
I didn't receive this but I did pick this up, you know
So, with this, I need ti have my clothes back from that old lady
Take it
You're very calculating.
You are right over after smelling of money
Please go ahead and wear it
Oh no, you are so polite that it's creepy.
Take it
Don't worry.
Is that okay? Don't you need it?
I don't need it
I received the money from Ms.Saki
from Ms.Saki?
Check your pocket inside
Pocket?
Yes Sir
Hey come on
Help me
Pocket?
What was it?
There's a car key and even a car receipt and a map
Kitano-cho, Ikuta Ward, Kobe City
Akitsu Sensual
Mr.Koizumi,
This is my father.
No, please go ahead as you are.
I am Daisuke Kamoi
Well, thank you for her help this time
No, no, from now on,
it's me who will be in your care
Kyoko,right?
Actually, Kamoi-san
There will be an exhibition of my father's treasured Chinese antiques in Tokyo soon
We have to transport it to Tokyo
I really want Mr. Kamoi to take on that transportation role
Your driving skills are outstanding,
and you're good at shooting too, right?
How did you know that?
After that darts game the other day,
I've completely become your fan
Could you please carry it together with Kyoko?
what exactly is this Chinese minor art?
Shall I show you?
Have a drink.
Thank you very much.
This is it
Ah, please, this is a traditional Chinese marine soldier
During the era when military might was emphasized
and nations fought, each king issued their own currency
Now, It seems that there are very
few things that are this vivid without pain
Just this alone is worth millions
So, transporting this to Tokyo means it's worth several tens of millions, right?
Could you please help with that?
Well, that's a problem
I don't have a fixed address,
and I don't have a driver's license either
I was really nervous thinking I might get caught at the checkpoint just now
I'll do the driving
So, Mr. Kamoi, it would be great if you could accompany me as a security
Right?
That's right.
But...
Let's go
If you can deliver it safely, I will make sure to give you a generous reward
Please go ahead
Well, you can't refuse, can you?
Actually, just the other day,
something was targeted for transport to a museum in Nagoya
Well, I got the information
I managed to get through safely by using some junk
When is the departure?
It's from tomorrow morning
Well, it might be ok but
Okay, I'll do it
Thank you.
Please
Dad,I can relax tonight, right?
The one dancing slowly is Kamoi
Kyoto’s lover?
No, he's just her security
Akitsu is such an idiot
Just because she cut ties with me, she has to rely on that guy
Welcome.
Brandy
Shall we take care of him?
I'll do it on the road in 53
If that's the case, then both Item and Kyoko will be ours
I think it's better not to be too concern on Kyoko
What?
What if we focused solely on the item?
We killed a police officer the other day.
But we only got junk
It was not worth-able
Akitsu weighed me against Kyoko and chose Kyoko
This time, Kyoko and the goods will definitely not escape
I can't keep getting beaten up by that guy over and over
Thank you for waiting
This is Akitsu
Excuse me for intruding
Have a seat.
What can I do for you?
Well, I wanted to ask you something about your car
This is the number
You found it.
where was it located?
What do you mean?
Recently, The car was stolen
We are going smoothly
For what?
Your driving
What's that?
Don't talk to me
Wow, it's Mount Fuji!
We could notice the airflow
He's coming
Damn it.
What the hell happened?
We got a flat tire
Damn it, did I underestimate that Kamoi guy?
Mr.Akitsu
We just parted ways in Kobe this morning
Thank you, Kamoi-san, that really helped me out
I came first
I was waiting for you
I see.
Hey, they're important
Be careful while carrying them
I am really tired
She drove alone, you know
I haven't done it even once, I feel sorry for her
Don't worry.
Mr. Kamoi removed the obstacles along the way
By the way,
Who exactly are those guys?
We'll talk about that later, okay?
He just did one shot
I see.
No, I would like to see your skills
No, no, my pistol isn't for show
Well, don't say that
Even if it's launched from here,
We won't hear any sound
I'm sorry
Well, since Dad is here
too, I want to see it as well, okay?
Just one shot?
No way
I can't believe you would say that
He's lying
It can't be helped.
Mr. Kamoi, why you look so upset?
I want to dance with Kyoko
That old man won't let me dance with his daughter?
his daughter?
Isn't she his daughter?
I leave it to your guess
Kamoi, you're quite straightforward
If you see someone, think of them as a thief
I was fooled.
Hold on.
If that information were to come out, I would be fired.
Please, I beg you
So in the end, the one who's the most foolish is me, huh?
It's too late to strangle that old man
Kamoi
How about you go with a slightly more clueless expression?
You don't know anything about him
What's his job?
I don't even know
Well then, Mr.Kamoi,please keep going.
Come on
Kamoi, what's wrong?
That's not it
I heard that  Kamoi dislike this kind of atmosphere
That was careless of me
Well then, let's change the location
Yeah
I won't do anything bad
I also have a story that I really want you to hear
Well then, let's go.
Well..so
Akitsu Joji, which had been under the protection of the Takara group, suddenly turned against them and launched an attack to steal the assets
Right?
You don't like that approach,
I was asked to take down the leader of the Takara Group
Well, that's the kind of story it is?
That's right.
The reason for Takara's betrayal is Women and desire?
Well, that's common
They are very annoying for me to be around.
It's a distraction from work, you know
Is that all you have to say?
but in return, the rewards will be generous
TAKARA is targeting antique art?
Don't say bullshit.
You should say everything before your blood pressure goes up
I understand everything
If you're targeting the antiques,
you should ask the police to keep them safe or take them to a museum,
I know. I won't keep hiding it forever
Actually, what looks like antiques is actually contraband
We're transporting gold bars and diamonds
from Kobe to Tokyo by land, you know?
Oh my god.
What do you think about that, Dad?
Why don't you just tell everything?
My relationship with Dad,
I'm the owner of this shop, and Dad's mistress
Thank you very much.
Takara wants her, doesn't he?
That's right
I told you everything
Kamoi
I want that to be settled properly
Settle what needs to be settled
I can't do that
I have other business.
It's a foolish rivalry between the fox and the raccoon
Well, it's a good match
Have a drink
but I don't need
Don't say such things.
This is a relationship between two naked people, isn't it,
Isn't it unnatural for men to have a relationship while being naked?
I turn down
Didn't you once assistance with smuggling?
I thought it was an exhibit.
If you just do it,
I'll take care of you for life
I can take care of myself for life
The only issue is whether I kill Takara nor not
I won't
My pistol isn't that much of a killer, you know
But now that you’ve heard this
it's interesting
Are you trying to erase me?
I won't let that happen
With this, money will come in from over there as much as I want,
You have a nice little gun.
It's cold.
I'll give you a hot sake
Try to shoot me
A pistol filled with water can send the ball flying backwards.
It might be good to try it out
Kamoi
Shibaura Warehouse No. 3
Wait
You are persistent
hey Kamoi-san
You don't have any money,do you?
Then why don't you stay at a hotel?
I've already arranged it over here
I'll deliver the plane ticket tomorrow
I don't need it
I won't get me with that trick
I don't know when you'll kill me
Please don't say that;
it makes it hard for me to calm down
My feelings and body just can't settle down
Yukie-san
He's an important customer, so go with him,
Don't give him back.
I'm refusing that
What are you hesitating for?
Hurry up and go
Kamoi-san
I don't need
kamoi
Are you crying?
Let me check if those are real tears
Oh this is real
Please don't tease me.
Kamoi-san, please protect me and help me
What on earth is
the reason for helping you?
I have a weakness for women's tears
Especially the smell of a girl's tears is something else!
Where is the thing that came from Kansai today?
You have to say it or I'll kill you.
Where is it?
Just beat him
Boss!
I discovered here
You don't do any more
Boss
Will I be promoted?
Don't get carried away
Ok I get it
What's wrong?
kamoi did it
kamoi ?
Takara went to the warehouse in Shibaura and stole the goods.
Really?
He tricked me
Hold on.
The only people who know that item is in the warehouse in Shibaura are you, me, and Kamoi.
and one more person, right?
Is it Yukie?
No way
When Kamoi came back,Yukie was on the phone
She acted weird
If you don't believe it, that's fine,
but you'll regret it later
Where is Yukie?
She took Kamoi to the hotel
They entered the room together
That's right, I see
I got it, understood
I think I should properly lecture your boyfriend,
I'll tell him that being a Yakuza is boring.
Come here.
Let's not do that
I will incur the wrath of your lover
You've calmed down
So, can't we each go our separate ways?
Move
I'm going to borrow this for a bit.
Ah, I've had quite a bit to drink today
Good night
Am I hungover?
Is she taking a bath?
Excuse me
She's dead
She get killed
I have to run away
Oh my god.
If I run away, my fingerprints will remain and I will be identified as the culprit.
What to do with her and the body
I'll call the police
Wait
Before that, I'm cleaning up my dangerous stuff
What? Did I kill her?
Don't say bullshit.
You know, Why do I have to kill a beautiful woman?
Weren't you just drunk and didn't realize?
Think about it carefully
I was sleeping
That's all
What's the purpose of coming to Tokyo?
Well....
Can't you do that?
I can tell
I came looking for a woman
you know, Tamamura Tamako,
who's 19 and a bit chubby
Tamamura Tamako?
She shares the same name as a stripper who is under arrest on 175 charges.
I heard she said she came from Osaka
Yeah, is she really going to be a stripper?
You should tell the truth.
According to the testimony of the person in charge,
after guiding the two,she said you closed the door
That door, when closed from the inside,
doesn't open where a key can be used from the outside
Moreover, the victim was being strangulationd in the bath
That's why someone was in that room first
That person was hiding in the bath
Didn't you notice that until the woman was naked?
Someone may have strangled her and then stripped her naked.
Well, no matter how many times I say it, I know that I can undress a living woman, but I can't undress a dead woman either
Tama-chan
The police are with you.
It's been a long time since I last saw you.
You really look like a mess, don't you?
It's been a while since we last met, so let's go out for a drink
Let's go
You are stupid.
what are you guys doing? This isn't the place for that
You were only referred to the prosecutor's office.
You are a murder suspect
Wait, what do you mean by murder?
I don't know anything
When I woke up in the morning,
The woman I was sleeping with is killed naked
that's a perverse murder
What's wrong with you?
Me?
I was dancing in Asakusa, you know?
I exposed my private parts
I was arrested on suspicion of obscenity
I think the customers enjoy that?
Of course, they do
But the police brought me here.
Basically, I didn't know that the police tend to ignore people's happiness
It's true
Stop it
This proves the circumstances of Daisuke Kano and Tamako Tanakoko, you understand?
You get it?
So Let's go.
Hold on.
You can't go home.
Do you still not trust me?
Gakumaru?
What?
Yukie betrayed us
So we made the culprit kamoi
If there's no woman, it won't work
Anyway, tie that guy up first
We'll talk after that.
This is Akitsu's order
If you have a complaint, come see him directly
Where is the president?
He's in probably Iwahachi.
Hey, who Killed Yukie? I came to get revenge on her.
Tell me.
Well, don't panic.
Don't get us wrong.
A man named Kamoi has been reported to the police
He was the man who was at the hotel with Yukie at that time
Kamoi?
Daisuke Kamoi
I hear he's supposedly a bit more
handsome than you
If this is a lie, I'll let myself be shot anytime
Go cool your head
What a ridiculous guy has brought this in
Ota, Be careful.
I’m sorry.
Sakumaru-san
That was just a young guy who was dating with Yukie
Was it okay to return him quietly?
What evidence do I have?
Those who are killed will be killed
Shall I set you free?
Really?
That helps me out, I could even treat you 100 bowls of udon
However, there's a condition
What?
as I investigate the victim's sister,
I found out she was also the secretary of President Akitsu,
and I had met the victim at Akitsu's house before,
You must know where he is.
There's no way you can say you don't know.
If I say that, can I really be free?
If you know, tell me
Hey, what's up with Tama-chan?
I released her.
She's back at the slip theater again.
That's great!
I have one more thing to ask you
Do you know why I came to Tokyo?
I heard from Suriyasu
He also came to Tokyo
Oh Yasu's come to Tokyo too.
Hold on.
We should get along well
Hey! You can do anything you want,
Hey
Don't mess with the Kansai vibe
while you're in Tokyo!
We are the territory around here.
Just spit out what you get
This is all of it, this is all of it!
Forgive me....  Forgive me....
Hey, you are Yassan
Yassan
Tama
I met you in Tokyo.
I can't believe it.
Newcomer,
What did you do?
Shut up.
Let me get out!
I was betrayed.
Please include the person who betrayed me here.
Let me get out!
So, what are you doing?
Shut up.
What's wrong?
The promise with the boss was different!
He betrayed me
What promise?
It's about sharing the work.
What a stingy boss
It's unfortunate, so you should give up.
Aren't you still young?
You have parents, right?
There's mom...
Hey, I'm not saying anything bad,
Being a Yakuza is a boring job.
You were tricked into being put here by your boss
Quit your Yakuza job and become a normal person.
Who are you?
I don't need to say my name
Daisuke Kamoi,
Get out
He's the Kamoi..
Who is it?
Oh, it's been a while
I thought you had no use for me anymore,
I don't have any for you
but he has
Who is this person?
I'm a friend of Kamoi-kun
I would like to ask you a little about Akitsu
He is not here today
I think he went to Sakumaru's place.
What does that mean?
He is a manager of a cabaret in Daitokai
Hello
May I ask who you are?
I would like to meet Mr. Sakumaru
Ah, I apologize for making you wait for a while
By the way, I made the request under the current conditions
Come on, can't you do something about it?
Because the preparation aspect doesn't match
Please don't say such cold things
It's a tough job, so I asked for help
Who's them?
it's the manager of the band that comes and goes
It's troublesome to be in a relationship
I am Sakumaru.
I hear you have something prepared
Is Mr. Akitsu from Akitsu
Trading here?
No, he is not here.
Excuse me, but could you clarify your relationship with Mr. Akitsu?
Ah, I am hoping him to invest in this cabaret
He is the major shareholder here
Everyone, be careful of pickpockets. They're targeting you, yes, they're targeting you
Hey, keep your valuable items secure. That's good, yes, be careful of pickpockets
Ah, I can smell pickpockets around here.
Be careful, be careful.
Yassan
Oh Kamoi.
Ah,, it's been a while! How have you been?
You just missed Tama-chan's show.
You said it's not a song, it's an artistic endeavor
Strip....
My mother is sick in bed so I need money
I told my mother in letter I wanted to be a fashion model.
Yeah, fashion model
Fashion model?
Yeah, then mom...
She's going to Tokyo
Where is your hometown?
Shimane
Oh, um, yes, yes,
It's Yasuke song
why did you write something like that?
Well, I guess that's meant to be filial piety
I thought I'd make my mom happy,
but to make her too happy, she'll come to Tokyo
Well, that's a good thing
You have to cherish her,you should be filial to those who come to visit
Well, Tamachan, If she comes to Tokyo, please treat her to a meal.
Where will she stay if she comes to Tokyo?
Here's fine
Fashion models live in big apartments with rent of 100,000 yen.
You need money to be a good son to your parents
I don't know what to do
All I can do is pickpocket
If I did that, I'd be beaten up in Tokyo.
Leave it to me! I’m doing my best,
but Tama-chan, you mustn't betray your parents
In this world, those who disappoint their parents are the worst
I'm somehow managing,
Are you sure?
This?
Wouldn't it be better to kill someone like that?
Idiot!
I don't use my pistol for murderer... Oh... I slipped up there
I left my pistol
Can you lend me a hand?
Where?
It's the murder scene at that hotel, right?
No way
I hate a ghost
what an idiot you are
Do ghosts even appear these days?
If they did, it would be a beautiful naked ghost or a noodle ghost
Nude?
Well, that's a bit funny
but I guess I'll pass because
it's scary.
What are you talking about?
When she see your eyes like that...
She should be so surprised that she run away
Come on.
Hey, wait a minute
The problem is how to get the key to that hotel
If that's the case, why not leave it to me?
If that's the case, I'll leave it to you.
I'll call the hotel front desk once to check what's going on
before that
What are you going to do?
you'll understand if you just watch
Take it out?
Look at that
See?
You hid something!
That's a pistol bullet, isn't it?
Yeah
You hide them there
But
These shoes are a bit small
So when I grip the pistol
It's hard to put it in
It would be great if you made bigger shoes!
If I hide something like this, It will be found soon
Oh yeah
Are there any electrical tools in the Strip room?
If that's the case, something like a belt to wrap around the waist
That's perfect
Could you bring that one over here?
I'll go get it
Wait Tama
because I really want to buy a huge apartment for you
Is that true? I'm looking forward to it
Hey Kamoi
Will you marry me?
Just wait a moment, um,
Let's talk after your mother arrives.
and I think we need parental consent for the marriage, right?
So please talk to my mom about it
I will...
Come on.
Come in
The door is open
Oh my god.
To immediately rent out a room where a murder took place is even more money-crazed than Osaka.
Let's go.
Just wait a moment
I'm coming out soon
Is there a ghost or what?
Ghosts don't take baths
Hurry up
It's hard to find it
Hurry up, hurry up
Hurry up
Do it more efficiently
The opposite way, that's right
Yeah.
Hurry up and she'll get out of the bath!
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Oh? Dad! Dad!
What are you doing?
She's calling Dad!
Did she keep her father waiting?
You're such a fool
Who would wait for their real father
while taking a bath?
What do you mean?
That man gives her a lot of money.
I want money too.
I can't.
Damn it.
Alright, that's enough.
Where did you hide the Shibaura items?
I got it, it's at the Harumi warehouse
Who is going to guide you this time?
Is it someone from your group?
He's a punk named Sokichi
You haven't contacted him yet,right?
Now, throw these guys into a basement
Wait! Boss, Forgive me....
I really have to team up with you after all
Please let the past be the past, I beg you
Boss
It's because you say such weak things that people look down on you!
Keep quiet!
I beg you
I have no use for dogs that bite their owners
Now, throw these guys into a basement
I know you're angry.
Mr. Takara is truly regretting it from the bottom of his heart
Please forgive him
Do you really regret it?
It's an unconditional surrender
I'll do anything
In exchange
In exchange?
In exchange, can you give me Kyoko?
Kyoko?
Can't you give up?
Takara, He is very tolerant
If you love her that much,
He says he can give Kyoko to you
However, until now, the share of one job will be reduced to one minute
Don't be ridiculous,
Step back
and eliminate that punk named Sokichi
Let's use this as a souvenir, sounds good?
This man has a earthworms
Come on.
I understand that there are foxes and raccoons involved, but...
, having earthworms on him is still something else
Don't say anything silly
Wherever this man goes,
Grim Reapers follow him around
Be careful
Don't say anything silly
Am I the Grim Reaper?
Well, I trust that it's close
It'll be again!
If I weren't here,
this man would be saved
Anyway let's go
Stay down.
Get your hands off of me!
You are my enemy.
Your enemy?
What grudge do you have against me?
Did you forget what I said
in the jail?
You killed Yukie
What did you say? Yukie?
That's right!
Aktisu's secretary.
Don't play dumb!
Is that so?
Are you the her lovers?
You're a confusing guy! Listen well!
Before she was killed
She wanted me to lecture you on
Don't say bullshit.
Dead people can't talk
I won't die
I didn't kill her
Look, I'm being released like this, aren't I?
I can't trust the police.
I have a proper investigation going on!
Investigation?
Who said?
That is false information
The reason I'm still hanging around in this Tokyo
is to find a person who killed Yukie-san
What is your relationship with the Takara group?
You can't just settle things with fighting with the boss
It's none of your business, so just leave it alone
Would you like to join me in finding her killer?
Don't say bullshit.
Remember this!
I will definitely avenge my enemy
so wait a minute!
Get your hands off of me!
Hurry up to come
Kamoi, help me.
You have a nice voice
He forced me
He told me to become Takara's woman.
Akitsu told the little brat that I killed Yukie?
This guy killed Yukie
I see...he
Kamoi, please help me
I am going to be killed
Even if you are killed, You are a very good woman
Don't say like that.
Why are you going to be killed?
Akitsu and Takara held hands again
There was a cost to that
I don't want to do that anymore,
What are you going to do?
I want to escape from here
Where are you going?
I'll leave it to you,
Please
Don't be so unreasonable.
I'm busy making money right now
I really don't have that much free time, you know
You need money ?
I can't afford to rent a fancy apartment
Your place?
I really need money right now. Hey,
Kamoi-san, how about we help each other out?
You have the power I want,
and I have the money you want
How about we exchange?
That's a great idea, so let's do it.
Just wait a moment.
I need to call before that
Hello?
Could you get in touch with Detective Kimura?
He is a detective who loves udon
and has come from Osaka
Kamoi
Hey Yassan,did you stay here?
It's been a while since we've seen a Malaria
Is a Malaria showing up at this time? Come on up,
Tama-chan, are you off today?
I'm really hungry
I slipped out
Who is this person?
Ai? Oh! Is she the young lady you met at the bar in Osaka?
What young lady? She's Akitsu's woman
she was about to be killed, but I helped her out
Tama-chan, good news
She could pay for your apartment rent
You can rent it starting tomorrow
How much you have?
That's incredible!
If you love him, I'll turn down
Don't get me wrong.
I heard about your mother from Kamoi-san,
and I was touched by your sincerity
I'm serious, Tama-chan
Listen
Well, I guess if I did something like this, I wouldn't be able to do it either
You will be filial to your parents with this money.
Life doesn't go smoothly, does it?
Good-looking people aren't pure, and those who are pure, well...
Hey, what exactly are you trying to say?
What am I talking about?
I completely forgot
But you know, Tama-chan...
This is different from smuggled goods
I gave the contraband to the hit man.
The Yatate was arrested
and Kyoko was disappeared
It seems this is indeed the work of Kamoi
So, what about Soukichi?
I found him the other day in Shinjuku and cornered him
He managed to escape just before we could catch him, and now we're searching for him
Yatate won't say about him.
The problem is with Kyoko, Sokichi, and Kamoi
If those three get involved in police, it could be bad
Takara, We can't afford to hesitate
We have to eliminate Kyoko along with him
Let me take care of getting rid of Kamoi
Okay?
May I?
No
No?
How about this?
No
This is good on you.
Good?
It's fine
Fine feathers make fine birds.
but is there some mistake?
Why is that?
Please don't listen, okay?
Can you see I am a top-class fashion model?
Yeah, Yassan?
Yes Yes
She's a top-class, surpassing even the top-class
Wait a minute
That's more like the style of top-singer than a fashion model
Nama-chan? There was that song you practiced with an advance payment,right?
I want to hear that again after a long time
Same here.
Really? Will you actually listen my
rehearse for the recital?
Ready?
Are you alright?
Hurry up and stand, Your clothes get dirty
I'm standing
Like this?
Excuse me.
Don't get mad,
By the way When your mom will come?
Tomorrow at 10AM, from that Shimene to Osaka, right?
My brother is coming with her from Osaka on a jet
Airline
I am here.
So-chan
Mom
It's hard.
Four, five, six, seven
No matter what, there's always one left over, isn't there?
Yassan
You've been saying there's one left over since earlier
But you ate a lot
Someone has come
I have to go
Wait a minute!
Tell that I'm Tamura Tamako's manager,
a fashion model
Don't forget,
I'm here!
Welcome back!
Please, come in,
Sou-chan,Come in
Yes
Sou-chan,come in
I'll introduce you ahead, right?
This is my younger brother, Soukichi
He graduated from university this spring
He got a job in Osaka
This is..
I am her manager,Daisuke Kamoi
Nice to meet you.
Wow! You lined it up beautifully
Oh my, there's black cod roe on top of the mackerel
That's called caviar
It tastes delicious when you simmer this in soy sauce
Hey, So-chan, what's wrong with you?
Put down your bag and sit comfortably
You don't have to be so stiff too, right?
How about your mom?
Kamoi
My mother was still sick
She thought she would reassure me
I received a letter saying that she
definitely want to come to Tokyo
Well, but....
That must be quite difficult
Kamoi, say properly
Ah, I see
Well, as a mother, I hope your mom wrote that
to reassure her daughter
I'm really about to cry
Sou-chan, you're hungry, right?
Let's have lunch
You should sit down too
Hey, is everything ready,Yacchan?
It's all set
Yeah, it's soup
I can't eat too hot
so I'll have this later
Alright everyone, let's start
So-chan, eat a lot
We have no time. Hurry up
Let's go
I don't need the jacket.
No?
I need a hat
Give me white one
Don't be vague
Handbag!
White one.
Get ready properly
What about the car?
The car?
Yes, it's on its way
Car?
Yes
And please say it properly
I'm saying it properly
Is that alright?
Let's go
Manager, um, I'm going out for about three hours
Is that so? Have a good time
Come on
I'm alright.
I worried about you
but I was surprised that I didn't know you were her younger brother
By the way, how did you graduate from university?
That's a lie, is it?
It's to reassure the country's mother and sister
I was being chased by former members of the Takara group and Akitsu Shoji in Shinjuku and Shibuya
I thought this was bad, so I returned to the country...
and then my sister sent a airline ticket and some pocket money
I thought that might be the case
Did your mother tell you to go here?
I thought it might be my fate to be drawn to Tokyo, so I left my country
Well, Yukie and you were in
real romantic relationship?
While working with Akitsu
We are grooming session with Yukie, we ended up sympathizing with each other
Yeah, that's right
Yukie joined Akitsu Trading thinking it was a normal company.
She ended up experiencing Akitsu's violence
I'm so frustrated to hear that
Then?
So, that's why Yukie was waiting for a chance to take revenge on Akitsu
But She ended up to be killed.
but what about you? You voluntarily joined the Takara group
You are stupid.
You're totally idiot
However, when I came out to Osaka, all my belongings and money were taken from me
The Takara group members treated me to a meal.
At that time, I thought They were kind
I see, that's a bit of an exaggeration
Well, everyone has those moments when they inadvertently step into the world of the yakuza
I remember that
It was a lie that my sister was a fashion model?
Hey, whether you believe it or not is up to you
But believing means wishing for the other person's happiness
Whether it's better for you to believe that your sister will be happy
Think about it.
But Kamoi-san
I understand, it's sad for your sister
to be drunk on this lie she's built up
I won't help if I do other things
But I want to make her Mom feel at ease and make her happy, isn't that the sincere feeling of your sister?
No matter how old we get, a mother is always something nostalgic
Well, that nostalgic thing make your sister tell a lie
I hope you understand
Kamoi-san,What about your Mom?
She's already passed away,
leaving her worried all the time
I am helping your sister because...
I want to make up for that
I'm sorry, Kamoi-san
You're so kind
I'm sorry for what I said
Never mind.
I will help find the person who killed Yukie.
That's good to me.
Catch the Yatate who who work at Akitsu.
He must be the murder
There are more masterminds.
just wait, wait
You know, is it okay if you and your sister live in Tokyo someday? I hope it won't be a bad life
Akitsu, Takara, and Sakumaru team up ?
That's definitely true
I see.
Here you go
Look, you should take good care of your sister
Now, I am going out for a bit
Just to be clear,
Don't go wandering around that area alright?
OK?
Hey
Welcome.
Fetsune
I don't want a Ketsune
Give me fox udon
Oh? Even though there is fox udon in Osaka, there isn't any kitsune udon
The fox cries, but...
I wonder what Ketsune cry
Are you really going to eat or not
over something like that?
Which is it?
I'll eat Kitsune, but I
don't need Ketsune udon.
Come on, don't say that, the udon here is really good, you know
Oh you are here.
You really love udon
You are in Tokyo but eat Udon
This is the wisdom I gained.
What's wrong?
The line was cut at Yatate
, and behind the Mita Yukie killing, there is a much bigger mountain
That lead has been cut off
Is it really okay for you to ask me something like that?
Is it just me talking to myself
You mean, I'm free to listen it?
If I trace back the organization behind Yatate,
I can also understand the truth behind the murder case of Mochiuki
Yatate knows, but does not say anything
A confession alone is not evidence
We need to investigate his surroundings.
From the outside?
But if you eat udon, you'll probably end up at the wise
I'm in trouble because I can't do that
If that's the case, then you waste the Udon fee
Come on, do your best!
Hey!
Kamoi!
what are you planning to do from now on?
Please, just run away.
I don't care where,
just take me with you
You always have Akitsu and Takara's eyes
following you around
There is only one thing you can do right now.
What's that?
You should turn yourself in to the police
Tell everything what you did
That's the best
I can't do it,Kamoi.
You were really planning to die once
You wouldn't be able to do it, would you?
No, Kamoi, you held me in Osaka
I was...
It couldn't be helped.
Come on, I'll take you right in front of the police
You haven't been doing only bad things, have you?
Tama-chan has be saved by you
Well, if you turn yourself in,
This will serve as evidence of Yatate's murder.
It's sake for Yukie-san
I can't do that for my child.
Child?
Do you have a child?
Yes.
My mother is raising him in Aomori.
Isn't that a child of Akitsu?
No
I see.
It's painful to be seen as a woman like me
when the child grows up
I think the investigation will get underway at some point.
I want to say this until that happens
If by any chance.....
That's you being too selfish
Please don't say that so much
Something went wrong.
What?
Soukichi was found by the Takara group.
He's an idiot.
Takara contacted me about that matter just now.
He said if you come I will give him to you.
He'll contact you later.
I just warned him to walk carefully.
Does Tama know about that?
No she does not.
Kamoi
Why are you so flustered?
Sometimes there are days like this, right?
Just stay still for a moment and sit here, okay?
Why?
I have something to discuss
I really appreciate it from the bottom of my heart
My younger brother said he wants me to succeed as a fashion model and even wrote a letter to our mom about it
Well, that was good
There's one more thing I want to talk about
What?
My brother is going back  home, right? I want you to come to the country with me
Why?
I want you to talk about that
story with my mom about marriage
Well, that story....
Well, I suppose that's what it was about at that time
Well, that's true, but Soukichi is late
I think he's hanging out with his classmates for the first time in a while.
Is it Daisuke Kamoi?
Yes That's right.
This is Takara.
Did you hear the phone call earlier?
Yes,I certainly received it
Thank you very much for your kindness
Answer seriously
Um, could you please wait a moment?
Who?
Tama-chan,
Good news.
It's strange how the world works, isn't it?
I don't know who was watching or where
They want to use Tamachan for a fashion job
Wow, I'm so happy!
He is in a hurry.
Please go quickly
I wonder if they prepared some costumes
at the venue
They said they already had costumes prepared.
Hurry up, hurry up
I'm going now, okay, have a good day!
Where is the location?
I forgot to tell you that.
Tokyo Stadium,
I'll get a taxi to Tokyo Stadium
I'm off
Take care.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting due to family matters.
You give me back Soukichi, but do you want Kyoko?
You're smarter than I thought
I want to say that whether to hand over Kyoko or not
It is a matter of life and death
If that's the condition, then it's bad on our part
It's okay to kill Soukichi, right?
Don't be ridiculous,
I won't let you kill Soukichi,
and I won't hand over Kyoko either
I guess there's no helping it
if my kindness doesn't get through
Don't blame me.
Kamoi is the enemy.
When you go to heaven, kill Kamoi
Bros.
I'll save this guy's life as promised
But there's one more condition
Call Kamoi
Hello?
Kamoi-san
It's me, Kyoko
Hey, where are you?
What are you doing?
I really want to meet you
Tonight at 11 PM at Warehouse
What?
Hello?
Kamoi! If you value Kyoko's
life, drop the gun and come out with your hands behind your neck!
Kamoi! Hurry up!
Come on.
Why do you want to do this?
Lies...
What lies?
Child...
Child?
Hold me.
Stay strong.
You are stupid.
Turn around!
The gun is out of bullets
Just one shot is left
Hurry to kill him!
You'll be over soon.
Hold on.
You guys stay back
It's a one-on-one match with you
The moment our hand touches the gun is when the match begins!
Wait!
Kamoi!
Sou-chan
Please work hard
I do
I need a fire
Don't handcuff him in front of her.
What are you saying?
I have no idea.
Who are you?
What?
I'll talk to you after the train leaves.
Alright, I understand.
Kamoi.
Excuse me, do you know this person?
Well then, it's nice to meet him for the first time
Are you all going to Osaka together?
I'm the only one who came to see you off
Oh, is that so?
What do you do for a living?
I'm a fashion model.
Is he your younger brother?
I'm a first-year salaryman
By the way, what about you?
I'm a detective.
I'm a pickpocket.
and what about you?
I'm like a stray dog.
I see, speaking of which, you don't have a collar, do you?
No, I have neither a collar nor any family, money
All you have is guts and determination
Hurry up.
See you
Come
Well then, please go ahead,
I'm taking the Tohoku Main Line
Tohoku Main Line?
This is Kyoko.
Kyoko's hometown is Aomori Prefecture.
Kyoko.
I had more than just courage and guts.
Thanks to that, I can go to Aomori Prefecture for free.
Please be patient.
I'll be patient with you too.
THE END