Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
When Japan's defeat in the Pacific War was imminent, Kisaburo Omiya
and I were ordered by the Kwantung Army to be transferred to the South.
We tried to get out of the army.
This was the game of our lives.
Stay down!
Get out!
soldier gangster
What happened?
I thought everything was going to be okay.
Damn it.
We are unlucky
Did you awake?
Where is here?
This is the main army hospital.
Omiya
Ouch!
Don't move yet
You may have bruised your lower back and have back pain.
Omiya, You should give up to seduce girls
You should stop that.
Really?
I'm better than you.
I just hit my head and chest
Other is fine
You'll do an x-ray later.
Mr.
That nurse is nice
Her name is Kyoko Ogata
She is 22 years old
You know about her a lot
Would you rather be with your wife?
She is much nicer
But I still love my wife
Mr.
My cock is still active
I see
X-rays showed that Ms. Omiya's back pain was fine.
We got better soon
But later,What we feared has come to pass.
Omiya!
Arita,Omiya,
We're going to question you.
You were on that train that blew up.?
Yes
You were transferred from the 123rd, and you were on a different
train.
That's right
Why you guys were on that train?
He and I were on the train as guards.
Who cut off the train?
I don't know
Why you don't know?
I'm sure you know because you were on the train as
guards.
I was concentrating on the front
How about you?
Same with him
Did you never look back?
When I looked back, there was no problem
Right?
When did the train cut off
Stupid!
I'm asking you
In fact he hit his head and went crazy
Take a rest,Omiya
However, the train was separated, so the our team were saved.
I think that was fine
It's bad!
In any case, we don't know
This is a mysterious case
Did you tell anyone about this incident?
No
This case
It must be the work of the enemy to obstruct the movement of southern troops.
This is a military secret so make it absolutely secret
Don't talk to anyone.
You understand!
Yes
Ouch
Does it hurt?
It still hurts a little
It's strange. I think the bruise has already healed
I'll give you a massage later
Yes please
Omiya, good news.
We will return to the mainland
We can go back to the original squad
Omiya, you are not glad?
I want to be here
I and Omiya were told to get packed stuff this evening
We can go back to the original squad
We will return to the mainland
And we break up with this army
This is so good news to us
Salute!
Arita,Omiya
Give orders to you
Sure
Corporal Arita and Private First Class Omiya.
On April 15th
Order you to transfer to the 422 unit
It's different from what I heard
We were told we could return to the mainland.
Our convenience has changed
Other troops have moved south, leaving only you
You were supposed to go to mainland
But it's good to go to move south
We're leaving tonight
OK?
Salute!
Omiya
We have ties to the military.
Damn it!
Omiya-san
Thank you for all the help you have given me
You are likely to be assigned to the 422 unit
I'm not lucky
Why?
The numbers are bad(422)
Oh,The 422 unit also has my brother
Really?
My brother's name is Ogata Shiro.
He belongs to Takujima team
Tell him I'm fine if you met him
I will meet your brother and be sure to tell it
Thank you for your kindness
I thank you.
Don't be so humble.
It's not so you
I have a favor of you
What?
I have something I want to commemorate
Tell me
Your...
I want
I want your hair
Please
Oh my hair?
Not hair..another hair
Eh?
I may die
I may not be able to meet you anymore
So I want it
I am
I close my eye
Please
I want to make it my amulet
She won't
Please
The next day I and Mr. Omiya headed for a new mission
We are leaving the hospital
420 units are about 1 km west
It's in a small village
I tell you
We will be assigned to this unit on April 15th
We'll work hard
OK
You guys were in the Kwantung Army
Yes
The Kwantung Army is great, but you have no practical experience yet
We have a lot of practical experience
People who have no experience in combat are not real soldiers
Be well trained and do your best
Yes
Good.
Receive instructions from personnel
Yes
I'm Iwanami, a personnel manager
I'm oldest here
I've been working hard in the army
Both the captain and he are very intimidating
There are many veteran soldiers here
You all seem very high and mighty.
I'm back!
Say loud!
Hey, come here guys
Yes
What year are you?
I'm 3rd year
Are you active soldier?
I'm active
You lack training
Listen
You still lack experience
There are a lot of 5 and 6 year old soldiers here
Yes
What's wrong?
It's nothing
What?
What year are you?
First year
First year?
Don't speak cheeky
Don't laugh
I'll teach you
Open your legs
Omiya quickly became popular on this army.
Move forward
Oh shit
What's wrong?
I lost muzzle
You should give up
It's gone
Oh shit
I'll give you mine
If you do that you will be punished
I can't be bothered with you.
Never mind
Your sister took care of me
So I need to help you
This is something small
I see.
Then I'll take it
But yours..
Here it is
I'm tired
I'll have a bath
He's good singer
Excuse me
It is good weather
Yes true
Well
Do you guys have a lot of experience?
I'm from the Kwantung Army
Lately
from the Kwantung Army
Did you come from around the border?
Yes there
Oh I see
I'm Araki from the 3rd unit
I'm Uzaki from the 3rd unit
I see.
Are you a sergeant
Yes
I'll wash your back
Wait wait
You have a nice figure
I feel good
I want to ask you something
Is there a beautiful woman in this town?
Women?
Lately I had no sex life
There is a comfort station near here
There are many good women when you go to Japan town
Really?
Geisha girls are there
Geisha?
I definitely want to go there
I got out
Thank you
Salute!
He seems to like women
Yes true
He forgot this
I'll send him
Omiya 1st grade soldier
Still 1st grade soldier?
That kid!
Salute!
Stay
Omiya
reply
Yes
You've forgotten
Take it.
I found this
Why are you afraid?
You were very intimidating in the bathroom
This unit is very tough
You understand?
Clench your teeth and open your crotch
Chief
I sanction him
What?
I am his comrade
It's your fault that he's no good
Ok, you sanction him
Yes
What's wrong?
You hit him as a sanction
Hitting him only hurts my hand
Are you a man?
OK. I will show you
Ready?
Ouch!
That's what I told you
See you guys
Damn it
Do you know where is Omiya?
He's just gone out
with other party
Which party?
I don't know
I thought he was called by another unit
I thought yesterday's sergeants would get him back
Kitagawa is here
You were Sumo wrestler,right?
Yes I was
What class?
Juryo class
Juryo class?
What is your specialty?
Stakeout.
Knock him down with a stake.
Is it okay to stun him?
It's OK
Beat him
Yes sir
He has a hard face
Damn it
Beat him!
You've given up?
You are a weak guy
Stand up!
Beat you!
Fuck you!
You are here as I thought
Stop it!
Omiya!
Sanctions on him should have ended yesterday
And There is no reason to sanction him
What?
You guys misunderstood him as an instructor
It's not his fault.
Is it okay for newcomers to dominate in the bathroom?
Is it okay for newcomers to use the group leader?
He was born with a face like this.
It's not his fault.
So we are trying to change his face
Shall I change your face too?
You can treat this guy too
I get it
Stand up!
Fuck you!
Your turn!
Stop it!
help us!
Forgive me!
Stop it,Omiya!
After this incident, Omiya was spotted by the Unit.
I consulted with President Yagi, who is the most serious in the unit.
Please protect Omiya
I'm in trouble.
There is no problem if it is inland
We have live ammunition for the guns
It ’s a very dangerous place.
Can you treat him as a special soldier?
I have to manage him?
Then he doesn't have to work with them
But can he work properly?
It's okay until the current situation settles down
Please!
Since then, Mr. Omiya has been given a special job.
He is doing the woman's work.
He is cleaning, washing and cleaning the bath
He also prepares meals and buys meals
Who am I?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm the reincarnation of Mr. Omiya.
I'll try my best to explain him.
Excuse me
Come in
I brought you some watermelon.
Sit down
How's your work?
It's easy,right?
You can go out and see girls
You should thank to us
I asked our boss that you work as helper
I won
I lost again
I quit
Mr.Yagi has no luck
Can you play this?
I can't
Try it
I don't want to deal with him.
I have no money
I give you money
5 yen is enough
Thank you
I take it
Leader
What?
Let's keep our statuses equal when it comes to
gambling.
What do you mean?
Even if I won,I might be the case I got nothing
Don't worry.
Trust me
Then I will play
Please
How much it will be?
Up to you
start from 3 yen
Here
Please
It's coming now
You didn't get this?
It seems you are used to it
Kind of
My turn
Sorry
I take it
What?
I won
Sorry
You are used to this game
Well..I was just lucky
Don't say bullshit
Let's keep our statuses equal
I take this
I return the money you lend me
I won many times
I'm lucky
well..this is my first time I won that many times
I have to save my money
I can borrow you some money
I'm here to tell you something
How's going?
Yes I'm doing well
I thought you were doing well
I bought this on the way of shopping
This is sake, so rare
I went to the town
It must cost a lot
I got the money from the president so it's okay
I won a bet.
I have something I want you to write
Write what?
A letter
To Kyoko Ogata
Do you want me to write for you?
You can't write?
I can write little
You're big but you can't do anything
I am a carnivore
Stupid
I won't write for you
Please write by all means
You just have to write the lyrics
Please write
What should I write?
Write I love her
You mean it?
You have a pure heart.
For her
I've always loved different women but she's special
She's very nice
I should have made a confession
You have me Sake so it can't helped
Please give me some more sake.
I'll like more like sexy
Please write seriously
Ok
Omiya! come on
Yes
Thank you for your work
Come in
There is a soldier
Don't worry
Do you have a sake?
Yes
Is there a bath?
The bath is ready
I want to take a bath
Let's take a bath together
Where did Mr. Yagi go?
He is busy with war
How's your bath?
Just fine
Wash my back
Yes
Come in
May I?
Come in!
Yes
I'll come in
Wash her back
Yes
Excuse me
Thank you
Omiya
It's rare to see a woman naked
Wash carefully
Yes
Come here
He can hear
Never mind
President!
What?
I'll go for shopping
What you will buy?
It's a must-have item
Soldiers are not accepted at night
I'll give you some money, so thank you.
It is a rule not to work after dinner
I can't wait
She is free,isn't she?
If found, there will be penalties.
Take it!
Oh you
Thank you for your time the other day.
How are you?
What?
Oh you.. what are you doing here?
It's a rule violation
I know
I came here to give a message from the president
You are kidding
I'm not
Right?
Yes
Really
You bastard
Damn it
I didn't know you are helper now
let's go
Thank you
I like soldiers better
Are you first year soldier?
I like them most
Because it's cute
But you look like a very veteran face
I can hear
Look above
The ceiling is connected
Really
What's wrong?
Kimura hasn't come back yet
He's three hours late
Did you check
He is not here
I see
Find him!
Will you stay here tonight?
A young soldier named Kimura escaped
Kimura?
He escaped well
He'll be found soon
Really?
Of course
It's easy. Kenpei team will find him
But it can be difficult to catch him
Do you know Kenpei team ?
I had a little relationship before
I think it's easy to get away from the army
Don't be a prude.
Why you don't escape?
Because I have my reasons.
Good evening
Iwanami leader is not here tonight
I know that
Yagi leader is here?
He's here
May I see him?
I didn't know that
She is very feminine tonight
Women are mysterious creatures
If Mr. Iwanami finds out, it will be very serious.
I want to take you home with me when I'm discharged.
Really
I'm happy with your feelings
But I'm bad
I'm not good enough for you
I'm serious
I can't be discharged as long as the war lasts.
I may possibly go to the South.
But wherever I go, my feelings don't change
To south?
You're getting into a tougher situation
I'm sad if you are gone
We can't do anything
But I won't forget about you
Can I have some water?
Here it is
It tastes good
Don't tell Iwanami leader
I know
You have a hard time
Be patient
Omiya,I'm Iwanami
Yes
Omiya!
I'll open soon
Oh my god
Please hide
To where?
There is a closet
Open now!
I'll open soon
Your clothes
What were you doing?
I was sleeping
I thought you would stay
I was planed to stay over but we found the Kimura
There was such a contact
Oh I see
You should have stayed over
What did you say?
Thank you for your hard work
I feel cold
You are mean
Awwww
What?
Ah!
I feel cold
What are you doing?
I'm sorry
Did you bring her?
Yes
What?
Stop it!
I'm Geisha girl
I sleep anyone who pay me
Is that bad?
I don't care you sleep anyone
So why you are upset?
You had sex behind my back.
Stop it!
I called her
What?
Why you slept with Omiya?
You are lying
If you bring her, you should sleep with her, right?
Why you try to cheat me?
You could have just asked me for advice.
She is just whore
Don't insult her
What?
That's why you can't do your job at all.
You've been hit and run away when you were a newcomer
You are weak man
You are stupid
What?
I said you are stupid
It's my choice to like Mr. Yagi.
You like him?
Yes I love him
I won't sleep with you anymore
It's funny
You said you sleep with anyone for money
I won't sleep with you anymore
It ’s better to sleep with a bear than to sleep with you.
I'll make her to return home
My clothes
Never mind
I was fired a helper
We just got word that the enemy is here.
I went to battle
Go!
The enemy escaped after attacking the village
Only the old man and the daughter remained
Go!
Only two
There was no result
Do we report them as important people?
Yes
Have him shot.
Why don't you let a new solider kill him?
Yes let's do it
How about woman?
It's a waste to kill a woman
Confine her
Bring your guns!
Ready?
We've decided to put him to death.
You need to practice
Kill him and gain experience
Kill this old man and practice
Ready
Leader
Will you wait?
What?
This old man is obviously sick
Killing sick people, even in training, is not a good
idea.
What did you say?
Do you have any solid evidence that this old man is related to the
military?
I don't care about evidence.
Even enemies have a right to be treated fairly.
You
Do not disobey my orders!
I mean
If you kill this old man, you'll make enemies in return.
It will only provoke the enemy.
Shout up
You preach to me?
I'm a soldier, but I like to have an opinion.
You have a military mindset.
You guys follow me
Get Ready!
Wait!
Do not follow his orders.
Fuck you!
Get Ready!
Hey guys, stop it
Damn it
Stop it,Iwanami leader
What did you say?
Hey listen
Call off the execution.
Leader
Lock this man up somewhere.
You did good job
I've changed my mind about you.
But there may be a punishment.
What Can I do for you?
Do you feel like a hero?
Don't be proud too much
So what?
Come
Fuck you!
Dinner is not ready?
We'll get ready soon
Excuse me
Where is Arita?
Arita-san
I'm OK
It's a terrible injury.
That leaders hit you?
How many?
I'm going to get even.
Wait
I have no patience for this.
Omiya
I'm going to be a problem in military council.
I don't want to get you involved.
Never mind
I've always hated him.
Omiya!
Can you come with me,Kurozume leader?
What the hell?
I'm here to get even with you, Mr. Arai.
Omiya!
This is the military.
Don't get me wrong.
Don't look down us
Fuck you!
Damn it!
Wait, dude!
Ouch!
Fuck you!
Help me!
It was the captain's order to hit Arita.
What's wrong?Omiya
Where is leader
He's on patrol
The other captain gave the order and hit Arita-san.
So what?
Why you don't care?
Keep him safe.
Are you here to fight with me?
Yeah
Omiya
Your actions will only annoy Arita more and more.
Is that OK with you?
He was beaten, but it never came up in the meeting.
If you make things even bigger, we're in trouble.
If you're worried about him, be quiet.
Damn it
Why you don't understand
I understand
The captain was trying to get him to do something
rash.
There is no problem
We're going to interrogate a woman today, so bring her in at
10:00.
Yes
Listen, only woman
He is pervert
He wants to have sex with her
I'm going to sabotage it.
I'm sorry
Be quiet
Stay down
Go, Go!
Get out
Thank you
Oh you are here
How's your condition?
I'm fine
Your face looks funny
Never mind
It's so quiet
Nights like this make me sentimental.
Yes
You think so?
It reminds me of when I was a kid.
My father beat me and I spent all night staring at the stars.
Were you crying?
I was pretty when I was a kid.
But
Human destiny is a mystery.
If I hadn't joined the army, I never would have met you.
That's true
I didn't even see Nurse Ogata.
Being in the military is not a bad thing.
You are stupid.
You like being in the military ?
I don't mean that
We try to be free to do what you want in the
army.
Your way of life may be more decent than me
You're still very human.
You are a much more natural and free person than I am
The prisoners have escaped
This is the problem
They have run away completely
You did it?
I hate that leader so I did it
You really don't follow the discipline of the army
I'll go talk to them.
Wait
When they find out what you've done, you'll be shot.
You are a really serious person
Tomorrow is another day
Tomorrow will take care of itself
It's the enemy!
You guys,wait here
I was punished for seven days for insubordination to a Corporal.
Mr. Okada and Mr. Ishikawa were punished for 10 days because they escaped from prisoners of war.
I felt responsible
Your meal is here
Thanks
How's here?
You stupid.
Here is bad
Please smoke
You are kind
I stayed here before
How's army?
We're a little confused because of various incidents
I think there will be bigger problems later
Oh yeah
Tokyo has been wiped out in a massive air raid.
Really?
This is a problem
We can't live too long
President Yagi died in such a war
People in the upper echelons are eating a good meal without participating in the war.
That's not fair
I don't want to give up my precious life
Did you see Mr. Yagi's corpse?
No.
What's wrong?
He was shot in the heart from his back.
The enemy has not killed him
Someone on our side killed him
You said earlier that Mr. Iwanami and Mr. Yagi had a fight over a female issue
Besides the women, those two were always fighting.
Iwanami leader?
He may have killed Mr. Yagi
Shall I look for ammunition in his bones?
You can see who killed by looking at the ammunition
Can I get Mr. Iwanami's pistol?
Leave it to me
Omiya
After the cremation, I'll stay at Yagi's house tonight
You should come
Bring Sake Omiya
Let's have a drink together tonight to pray for Yagi's soul
It's a funeral
I'll go home
What's wrong?
I don't like dark moods.
You are merciless.
Yagi loved you
At least pray for him
Ridiculous
All my tears have died
Omiya
Drink more
Yagi-san
You stupid
Why are you dead?
Someko.
Forget about him
I've already forgotten about him
You are liar
Did you love him so much?
No way
I don't love anyone else
Ridiculous
I don't like military personnel
Shave your hair if you loved him
I'll cut your hair
What the hell
Stop it
Damn it
Let me go
OK
Do whatever you want
Work hard
Chief
I have a favor of you
What?
The car doesn't move so please lend me some people
This is an urgent business
I see
I'll get some people ready for you.
Hey,Omiya
Good luck because it's heavy
Let's move
What's wrong?
You can't move the truck?
I'll help them
Ogata-san
Oh Omiya-san
It's been a long time
You look good
Thank you
You know him?
I met him at the Army Hospital before
Thank you for taking care of me at that time
I still take good care of the amulet you gave me
Let's try again
Get out!
I'll do it alone.
Here we go
Thank you
You don't change at all
I was ordered to transfer to a field hospital the other day
Oh I see
I'm very busy after being transferred and I'm in charge of your group
How is my brother,Shiro?
Ah..he's fine but
What's wrong with my brother?
Well...
Please get in the car.
We're going
Yes
See you
Talk to you later
May I see my brother?
That's a little difficult.
His disposal has not been decided yet
He may be a problem at the meeting
He's at least seven years in prison if it matters at a military meeting
I don't mind any disposition .
I want to see him once
Actually, you can't, but I'll give you a special once-over.
Thank you
But here is not good
He'll meet you in secret at my place
Hey helper
Yes
Bring some beer
This is not military equipment.
Make yourself at home
Yes
Oh yeah,
You can stay over tonight
What?
Thanks for your work
It tastes good
Leader, Kyoko is here
I see.
So you are upset
But it's a little weird.
I asked army, and they said she's gone already
If she were to leave, she'd come to me to say hello.
Didn't she go home early because of you?
But it's a little weird.
It's strange to go home without saying anything
Right?
The leader took the girls home for lunch, so I got the day off.
Which woman?
She is a red cross nurse
A nurse?
Omiya!
No!
It's OK
If you want to help your brother, sleep with me
Stop it!
I see.
You really hate
So do whatever you want.
I don't care what will happen to your brother
Is that Ok with you?
This is the place of war.
We don't know what will happen tomorrow
You have sex with me and no one knows
No!
Stay down
What the hell!
I am your leader!
You are not my leader
What did you say?
I'll also revenge the other day
Fuck you
Stand up!
Omiya!
Stop it!
I don't care what happens to me.
Say sorry to her
Fuck you
Go to hell
I get it
Forgive me
You take her to see her brother?
I do
You sure?
Yes trust me
Hey
Thanks
The leader's orders are for her to visit her brother.
What?
This is our leader's order
Are you sure?
OK come in
Omiya
You're going to be punished.
Are you try to run away again?
How about you?
I can't let you escape alone
Shall we escape together?
I don't want to separate with you
Me too
They are coming to try to catch us
Leave it to me
Stat down!
We won't escape
We've brought them
Line up there
Omiya
You assaulted the leader.
I'll never forgive you for assaulting your own leader.
Arita
You didn't stop him, but you did allow him to illegally visit Ogata's sister.
You're just as guilty.
I'm court-martialing the two of you.
Never mind
Do whatever you want
What?
I'm charging you with murder.
Hey Iwanami
You killed Yagi leader
I'm court-martialing of you.
Shout up!
Why did I kill Yagi?
We have a evidence
What?
It's interesting.
Show me the evidence
OK. We tell you
Listen carefully, you guys
Look at this
The bullet from this pistol is the one that pierced Mr. Yagi's back through his heart.
These are bullets from your pistol.
Look carefully
These two bullets have the same traces.
In short
Meaning they were fired from the same handgun.
Don't say bullshit!
If you hand us over to the Kempeitai, this fact will come to light.
It means you'll be punished, too.
This is interesting
You can do whatever you want
They are lair.
They're just trying to intimidate me.
What did you say?
What the hell
You guys,Beat them!
This is my order
Damn it!
Fuck you
Stop it!
I'll beat him
I'm going to avenge Mr. Yagi.
How's it?
You're not worth killing.
Killing you is no fun.
I will have you tried by court-martial.
We are going back
Over there!
Omiya!
Stop it!
Don't run away!
Over there!
Damn it!
Shit!
Are you OK?
We are safe now
You people have gotten me into a lot of trouble
This is what we're meant to be.
Being in the military is the worst.
Take care of yourself
Yes
I'll write a letter to you later
Where are we going, Omiya?
Leave it to me
I'm sorry to accompany you.
You are really stupid
You're a helpless man.
The end