Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Zoku zoku Judai no Seiten / Judai no Seiten 3 (1953)
Oh, it's the same, this morning.
What?
Well, you see, Kakcchan is coming from over there. It's been about three days since then
That's when we pass each other
He definitely bad to stare at my face like that
He's bad student.
I'll glare at him.
Hey.
You've got rice stuck on your cheek, huh?
That was funny.
Good morning.
Asou and the others are late.
That's right, it's Tadokoro-san, isn't it?
No, that's not it.
Hey come on.
She's coming now.
Good morning.
Good morning!
He came right on time
Today we begin with Lesson 9, Chapter 3.
Otomo-kun
Please translate this into Japanese
He and she, or she and he, the elm tree....
he and he, good good....
He and She
With that attitude, you'll never be able to write a love letter, will you?
Ms.Tadokoro.
Please say it in Japanese?
When the two first met
Today he stands alone beneath that tree.
Whilst occasionally thinking of her
He was lonely there.
She whispered softly
Winds comes along
Very good
She was in mood
She's pretty good
She must be with someone who has loved or experienced heartbreak
So she was in the mood like that
But honestly, that's true
You know? You lived with your sister
She live her sister who is a dancer in that apartment, right?
So It can't be helped.
That's a hurtful way to say it to someone like that
Stop it
What's wrong?
I don't understand why he is like that
San-chan said something silly again.
I'm back!
Welcome home. It was hot, wasn't it?
I can't wait for summer vacation to start
That's right, it's the last summer vacation for you.
Hey, sister, living as a single woman...
Isn't it just inevitable to become a dancer?
It can't be that simple, right?
So, do you do it because you like it?
Even my studies fee...
We can get by with your father's inheritance, right?
That's right.
so does that mean you really do it because you like it?
Not really,
but I don't want you to work  for me like that.
it's just so frustrating to say
Don't be cheeky.
Rather, you clearly like doing it
It's really robust and healthy.
You know, what makes me happiest is that
Keiko-chan has no dark shadows and is so cheerful
I really dislike crying baby
Well then, I'm off
Welcome back home
Welcome back!
I'm home.
Welcome back,
Setsuko. Today is the day for practice, isn't it?
The teacher is waiting, so please hurry up
Yes.
Setsuko
What's wrong? Is something happening
during your practice?
You act so bad
It's true that we haven't talked to you about this yet,
and we are at fault too
Shingo is the heir of Arai, our business partner
you are no longer a child
and it's time to talk about your marriage
We also got enthusiastic about it
I was thinking that maybe you guys should start dating around this time
So, does that mean we're engaged?
Well, that might have been the case in the past
These days, you don't have to think so rigidly about it
Well, I feel the same way
You want to raise her to be a daughter who is as disciplined as possible
But when it comes to an old established shop
like ours, is that really all there is to it?
I won't let you date someone who I think
is not good from a parent's perspective
Shingo is a reliable young man, after all
Oh, by the way,
about the concert tickets,
you wouldn't want to go alone, right?
I got two of them.
You know? We meet him each other every morning
That was the guy called Kaku
Oh that guy
but suddenly and without permission....
I absolutely oppose it too
Please be on my side, Chieko-san.
Of course
For Young women
There's no more restraint than this
That's right,
what should we do about this?
Just break it!
That's right.
Well, what is that?
it's wonderful!
That's jazz from Sonan University
I want to go
How much?
I'll give it to you
Really? Yeah, thanks!
Can you give me one?
Thinking about it,
it's a great opportunity
And he might be nice.
I have observed something on your behalf
If she comes, make sure to introduce me too
But I wonder if jazz is really suitable for a first-time place
does that mean Kabukiza is better?
In a place like that,
you won't even get a half-hearted response,
and you can't hold her hands either.
In that regard, jazz is like a jolt that shakes your heart, right?
Whether you hold her hands or touch feet,
there's nothing to be embarrassed about
Well, modern Miya is limited to jazz concerts
Hmph, is there really such?
But you did a good job, didn't you?
If you stick like that
I don't know how many years ahead,
but it's certain that she is nice.
Young women these days
they don't take it seriously
But do we have a responsibility
too?
Hey
They are waiting! Hurry up, hurry up!
Oh see you.
I told you to calm down a bit
This is normal
When I get excited, it's something else, isn't it?
You're a troublesome person.
B-12
hey we can't wait
Isn't that seat incorrect? Yes,
there's no mistake about it
Kakcchan
Do you know him?
Introduce me.
Please
See you.
Please take care of her.
Your lover?
No.
Please.
Please
Arai
I know you were supposed to date with Setsuko.
Do you have enough money and time,right?
Yes.
Then we will go on behalf of her.
Let's go.
Welcome
Here it is
What hobbies do you have?
Hmm, I guess fishing
Have you had any friendships with women so far?
Not at all
I can trust those words, right?
Did you hear about the American data pose that came last time? Thank you
No.
Well, what about Quattro?
Oh no.
then you can't really talk,can you?
You're just a lazy person who doesn't even try
If you get dumped by a girl friend, that's one thing, but to get dumped before you even say a word to your fiancée is something else
I thought someone like you would be a friend, but that was quick
But you know, I actually like the fact that Setsuko doesn't pay any attention to me
That's quite silly.
At least look back at me a little
If I just blow a little, girls gather around like a swarm
I'm really struggling with how to handle it.
Don't get too carried away and forget that you're a student
Getting carried away with popularity can lead to a halt in the essentials
The exam is until tomorrow, you know
Yes
Please make sure to do your best.
Yeah, that's fine,
but about going camping
You forgot again,didn't you?
That's right
I'm definitely going to the bank today
You're a bit too carefree, you know
The total for the reporter's fee, food expenses, and other miscellaneous costs is 3,500 yen
I want a little more pocket money, though
I'll give it to you
Since we're all going to Kawamura tomorrow, so don't forget!
It's okay
Take care.
Women need someone they can rely on
It's tough to live alone, you know
You don't have to worry about living expenses
Cheers to Cherio
Soon it will be time for today's broadcast to end completely
Well then, everyone, good night and sweet dreams
Good morning, everyone in the countryside
It's an early bird
What's wrong?
Hey, this is the money for the camping trip
I don't want this money
This isn't bank money, is it?
Whose money is this?
What kind of money is this?
Keiko-chan, the truth is that the money
from the bank has long been gone
I'm sorry for keeping it quiet,
but I didn't want to worry you, Keiko-chan
Well then,my tuition too?
Sister.
I'm really sorry, I'm really sorry, I'm sorry, big sister
It's nothing like that
I will leave school and work.
How foolish
If you did that, then I'd be in trouble.
You understand, right, Keiko-chan?
How wonderful it would have been
if we were men brothers
No, I shouldn't think miserably just because we are women
You're right, Keiko-chan. From now on,
You're right.
I'll share everything and consult with you since you've grown up so much
I've been looking forward to this for a long time
Right now, I really feel like I'm all alone
So please go have a great time
camping with this money,
but this money...
Keiko-chan
This money was given to me by someone who might become Keiko-chan's older brother
Please don't ask me anything today
You have an exam coming up, right?
Get ready.
You seem really confident! That's amazing
You stayed up all night studying
Your eyes are swollen
Because I cried
Even Keiko-chan cries
You are definitely a girl after all
Keiko-chan
What are you going to do with this?
I was in the wrong
I'm asking why you wrote it
Please give me any punishment
Answer my question
Come in.
I asked him to tell me
That's not true.
I did it on my own
No, it was my fault
I understand, I understand. I'm not a judge
I clearly acknowledge the cheating mistake,
but at the same time, I also greatly recognize the friendship you all have in trying to cover for each other.
However,
Let me say this: from now on, Tadokoro-san, you should not be too grateful for Kajikawa-kun's actions
And Kajikawa-kun, you should not think of your actions as heroic and get carried away by that
To put it bluntly, you both understand this because you are male and female students in the same class
Alright? then go home.
If you go camping, the mood will be more in tune with the secret.
We are gathering and making plans
Hurry up and come
It's a 20-minute break,
but it's too early
Nanika-chan! It's dangerous! Hey!
Watch out.
Come on.
Damn it.
Oh shit.
hey
it's mealtime
That's right, if I told you to stop,
then stop it
There's no competition,
there's no competition,
Just stop it.
No competition!
it's mealtime
i am tired.
Come here
You guys go back by boat first.
I'll swim
That's not fair.
Let's go.
Tan-chan
Is there any problem with food?
Don't fail at cooking like yesterday
It should be okay today, right?
It's okay, I cooked well
Is that so?
It's over baked
Were you sleeping?
Ah, I'm hungry, ah, I'm tired, let's eat now
Look, we can't eat it
Oh my god.
He always burns the rice
You should stop cooking.
Thank you, I can play
Idiot!
You have to practice cooking meals.
It's not my fault,
the assistant escaped while I was sleeping
You idiot!
Isn't there a guy named Masae Nishiaki?
Ah?
Masae Nishiaki?
For the camp?
but it seems like she hadn't come
Really? That's strange
She should definitely be here, though.
Hi.
What's wrong?
Look, this was from the girl who came with you someday
she definitely wants me to come too
It seems like your girl too is joining us
What do you think?
Shall we go together?
It seems that there was a mistake with the venue for the jazz competition the other day
This time, we're going to switch things up and talk about the romantic side
Let's go.
Let's make sure to take this opportunity tomorrow
I don't know which room it is,
but leave it to me.
What are you going to do?
Leave it to me.
See?
Just as I aimed
I see
Oh, you're here! Yay,
I'm so happy!
You really came!
I was allowed to come early
I'm going to wake everyone up,
so how about a party?
We can have an overnight
around the camp room!
Right? Sounds great!
Everyone, wake up!
Wake up! It's still too early to sleep! Hurry up!
Can you hear that? Let's dance!
Let's make a fire! It's going to be romantic.
Okay!
You promised to teach me how to dance
You should watch the fire.
I'm counting on you not to put out the fire!
It's not funny
so please dance with me later.
Sure.
Do you know him?
Well, a little.
Who is Asao Setsuko?
Look,there's that person over there
Get it together, or I'm going to lose my mood
Ah, welcome,
Good evening.
You know a lot of people
Not really.
Good evening.
So everyone, are you guys going to hang out all night?
Let's take turns swapping partners and dance
Please woman choose.
I choose you,Sayama.
I mean, everyone has changed partners,
We have to change too
No way, other people don't share your interests at all
You must dance with me.
Keiko-chan looks like she's having a blast
I make a fire
I almost want to turn off the fire.
Doesn't Setsuko-san completely dislike me?
I don't think that's the case.
But you haven't really been dating at all, right?
Then why does she avoid me?
In other words,
for us, love is incredibly romantic and emotional
But when it comes to marriage,
it feels different...
and it's physiological, right?
Physiological?
That's right
So when you suddenly say you're engaged like that,
it totally ruins the romance,
you know?
This is the perfect opportunity!
Who?
It's me, Shingo
Setsuko, I have something I want to talk to you about
I can hear you from here, please don't come in
I want to date you again, not just as a fiancee or anything like that
Isn't it the same?
My first impression might have been bad,but I don't intend
to be the kind of man who you would dislike from the start
But it's impossible to suddenly say that I should just like you
Please leave.
But Keiko is already an adult;
she thinks she can understand everything about her older sister
I wonder what kind of person will become my older brother.
I wonder what kind of person will become
Keiko's older brother.
Arai.
Oh, it seems like things didn't go well with Setsuko-san?
It seems that every time I meet that person, I leave an increasingly bad impression
You think too much.
Wa!
You're not surprised at all, huh?
Of course, you're so childish.
You are calm
What do you want to talk about?
Speaking of which, I...
I thought the camp would be even more fun
Because isn't this the best we can do?
It's actually quite fun
We are not just childish.
We can't just be giggling from morning till night, can we?
It's not like that
Even if I stay quiet
There are fun things
I wonder what they could be
I'll be clear, but you're only talking to the university students who came later, aren't you?
I really dislike people who try to monopolize friendships like that
I am not monopolizing
I just think I have a special friendship with Keiko-chan
So that means you like me, right?
Yeah
I like you too
I might really like you
But only as friends
of course
But you know, when we reach our age,
there are times when we can't just limit ourselves to friendship issues anymore
So, is it about love?
No, it's something much bigger
Marriage? Yeah
Well, it's kind of like that
You and I, we have friendship...
Don't get me wrong.
I'm talking about Setsuko-san.
What? I was surprised.
Wait, Masai-kun, let's go together
No way
I'm all alone here
It's because you oversleep.
Oh you.
Even though I came,
you forced a nonchalant face
Hey, hey, Do not enter without permission
Why don't you come closer to us?
My partner is totally against it, you know
That person is very stubborn.
I wonder Why are you unattractive?
See how it goes
I'm still 18, you know
But your friends have a bit more charm, you know
Well, nobody wants to hang out with someone like you
What are you talking about?
I always flirt with the women I like.
But I'm not ready for that.
You are like a male lion
Oh, Do you do photo?
Of course
Are you taking a picture of me?
Sorry about that
I'm not like those amateurs around here
I don't want to waste film on things I'm not interested in.
Damn it.
Please just go home, okay?
I'm sleepy again
Then can you give this to me?
No, this is my life
Well then, let's play with one more
Please play it somewhere far away
I can smell Morio-san
She's trying to be sexy.
Is that so?
Yeah.
What are you thinking?
Just something about the future, I guess
What about you?
Since the day I were born until now
We were thinking about a lifetime.
Right,
life...
Help me.
Pull yourself together!
Setsuko!
Setsuko.
She is unconscious,
I have done something bad
Hey,
what's wrong?
Please, take Setsuko with you
Excuse me.
Are you okay already?
I caused a lot of worry last night
They say that once someone has nearly drowned, they tend to live a long life
You don't have to worry anymore
I actually have a hobby for something like this
What do you think? Just one picture would be fine, right?
Keiko, I was asked by Morio to be a model for a photo
I thought it would be something like that
He wants me to wear a swimsuit
Setsuko, I'll tell this
you have a weakness
because he could help you, right?
You never know
what might happen
Well, I don't think it's that exaggerated, you know
Photography is that person's hobby
Come on, that's a weakness.
If I were a man,I would try to seduce you
with this opportunity right now
You think too much.
Leave it to me, Keiko, okay?
Sayama?
Thank you for waiting.
Setsuko suddenly got a stomach ache
It was cold yesterday
So I came in place of you, is that okay?
both of us have two arms and two legs, not much difference, right?
That's true, but I...
are you saying my body isn't artistic?
No...
it's your skill to capture that artistically
Just turn that way for a moment, I'm going to change
Off-limits!
I'm ready.
So, where should we take the picture?
Since I all the way to wear this
It has to be in the water, right? You should get in
I'm fine here
Hey come on
I will
Stop complaining and hurry up and come in,
I got it
Hurry up.
You don't have to drag this out
Here's fine
I got wet.
Like this?
I think this is better.
Wait a minute
My profile looks
really artistic from this angle
Could you move a little further over there?
The background here is not great
Could you pass a bit further over there?
Just a little more, one more step,
one more step
Keiko really did change into her swimsuit there.
Is that really true? Something like that?
It's true, and she looked really happy about it
I have a weak heart, so I almost fainted.
If that's true,
That's unpleasant for us
So it's easy to get suspicious when a woman and a man are together.
Just look at that situation
I feel like I can imagine what happened after that,
but I think that kind of imagination is too terrible
Do you think what I'm saying is wrong?
Is that really the case?
Hey, San-chan,What do you think?
Yeah, She's growing up very precociously
It's a family problem for her
Don't say such a ridiculous thing.
Where has Setsuko gone, Hajikawa?
What's wrong?
Don't try to dodge the issue
Oh, for what?
What have you been up to until now?
I'm serious, I never thought you were that kind of person.
Wait a minute
Something happened to you since that day
Wow, that's terrible
You deceived me and betrayed me
Wait
Don't touch me.
Are you feeling okay?
I was lying
I was really worried
I'm sorry, even though I promised.
it's fine
What about you, Keiko?
she just went home a little while ago
Well then
Setsuko
I'm into jazz
You are definitely into
classical music, right?
I've been wanting to have a
good chat about music sometime
I'll be waiting for you tonight at the pine tree.
OK?
Keep secret to Keiko
Just wait, wait for me!
Kajikawa-san
Listen to me
Please, Kajikawa-san
Wait for me
Kajikawa-san
Please
Listen to me
Believe me
I believe in you.
Kajikawa-san
Keiko....I....
They are having festival there.
It's nice to have music coming across the lake
Do you remember what happened last night?
Setsuko
no! Let go! Let go!
You kissed me
please listen to me,Sayama
I suffered all night long
Even so, I still can't help but feel pain
When Setsuko-san lost consciousness
I kissed her.
I'm so bad
I really feel like a criminal
What the hell am I supposed to do?
I....
Moreover I like Setsuko-san
It's not about being engaged or anything like that
Sayama, do you think if I honestly apologize to Setsuko-san, she will forgive me?
I might be hated or despised
But still, I can't just stay silent
I'm going to go and apologize
Arai
Setsuko-san
Please forgive me
I did something terrible out of a sense of relief thinking I could help you
Please go home
Hey everyone! Setsuko has gone
somewhere with her bag?
Didn't she go home alone?
That can't be right
if she were going home, she should
have properly told me before leaving.
That's right, there's no way she would
go home alone.  we always act as a group.
That's right
I don't know
if she went home or not,
but she walked towards the lake
I wonder it's strange
what's wrong?
it's strange.
She was acting strange earlier
Was she?
Well, anyway, let's all look for her together
What should we do?
Where? Towards the lone pine?
And she's gone towards the hill
Let's go over there.
Setsuko!
Setsuko! Setsuko!
How was it? She's not over there,
what about here?
I have to take a call at this hotel
so everyone,please help her out, okay?
What should we do?
Then let's split up and search!
Hacchan,which way are you going?
let's go there.
Setsuko!
What's wrong with Setsuko?
We can't find her.
Setsuko!
Arai.
Do you know where Setsuko is?
What's wrong?
She's not here, she's disappeared
It must be my fault
Arai
I'm sorry
She thought I had helped her.
I took advantage of that,
so what did you do?
I have done something that cannot be undone.
Please forgive me
You.
You bastard!
I'm sorry, please forgive me
What good does it do for you to apologize to me!
Are you even human!
Someone like you deserves to die!
You might not die,
but Setsuko might have die
I did something really bad....
Hello? Was she definitely on that train?
Hello, what time is the next train to Tokyo?
Is that train available until tomorrow morning?
Hello?
Is there a train to Tokyo?
Hello, let's say the next match is tomorrow
No, this time it means I have to do it
Well then, excuse me
Hello, this is Aso
Ah, this is Setsuko's mother
Is Setsuko there? Hello?
She was supposed to arrive
alone on the last train at 10 o'clock?
Hello?
What's wrong?
It seems she arrived at the station on the last train.
What happened to her?
It's already been two hours
I wonder what happened.
Hello?
What's wrong, young lady?
Did you run out of the house
after being scolded by your father?
Do you have a place to stay?
If you don't have anywhere to go,
my sister's house is nearby
Wanna come?
Let's go, okay?
It's dangerous for a woman to walk alone,right?
Are you Setsuko?
What's wrong?
I understand
I can't take her out.
When did you come back? Alone?
Wasn't Keiko with you?
Let's go to my place.
Yes, I found her near the station.
Well, it was also late,
so She is staying at my house
Huh? What did you say?
Is that so?
Well then, I'll send someone to pick her up.
so what did she say?
Why can't she come back by herself?
Be silent.
No, no, oh dear
I see
Please don't worry about it anyway.
I will definitely bring her with me.
Did you find her?
Please tell me.
I want to meet Setsuko
I want to meet her as my own responsibility
I will make amends her for the rest of my life.
What do you plan to do for that ?
That won't erase your sins
So, as amends...
So, as amends?
Then please return Setsuko to her original state.
the love that started from mistake
And then, a marriage that was lazily.
please don't make a mockery of such a thing
So, No matter what Setsuko say
I oppose it
What our purity is like
How could someone like you ever understand it forever?
But if you're human, you should be able to understand. That's right, you're not even human
You're more barbaric, conflicted, and vile than dogs or cats
So, what kind of person is your partner?
What good does it do to ask that now?
He must be a bad guy.
Don't cry,do you think crying will solve anything?
Anyway, you should quit school right away and stay at home.
Um, I hope it's not too presumptuous of me, but...
Well, that would be quite sad for Setsuko
We are even more pitiful.
If this becomes known to the public,
she won't be able to marry into a respectable family
But it's a mistake, after all
Moreover, Setsuko-san is suffering this much as well
You may be judging from your business perspective,
but I cannot do the same
Well, that phone call this morning was like that, right?
It's nothing
Since you say there's no need to worry, so I was not worried
We are very embarrassed
It will ruin her whole life.
It may be nothing to you,
but I'm sorry
He's someone who speaks his mind without holding back
and I truly appreciate all that you've done for us.
It's fine
I feel embarrassed because I thought I
was being scolded while listening to you
I am also a woman who has made mistakes
But we don't have parents either
In such times, I wished someone would scold me thoroughly,
She is fortunate to have someone who scolds her.
Just because a young girl tripped over a stone and fell,
does that mean she can never live as a decent woman for the rest of her life?
Please, aunt, I ask you to apply on behalf of your daughter and teach me.
No matter how much I suffer or how much I reflect, will I never be forgiven?
Setsuko.
What's done is done,
so there's no helping it.
I will apologize to Dad properly later.
I...
Her teacher and her friend came to visit
Setsuko!
Setsuko-san!
that's enough
If you've cried that much, that's good
Now that we're here, you might listen to what I have to say, right?
There are many people living in this world, and you are one of them
I am one of them too, but how many of those people are truly without mistakes?
You have an abundance of future ahead of you
In that context, as humans, we can both progress and fall into depravity
We make progress but we also regress.
That is why there is hope, adventure, and beauty
But I can't take it anymore
I can't go to school where I can't join everyone
Setsuko, why do you say that?
My Dad....
I want to meet her father.
Please
Let's all ask her Dad together.
After all, Setsuko's situation
is our collective responsibility.
That's right.
even I teach students
while pretending to be a teacher
If I wash my heart, I'll find I also have a lot of mistakes
However, I believe the issue is not about having made a mistake,
but rather what happens after the mistake
Although people don't make mistakes,
Isn't the person who goes through life without ever realizing their own weaknesses and foolishness
the most unfortunate of all?
But, you know, teacher, at that age,
having something like this
I think that's definitely a wound.
But since it's a wound from her youth,
it will heal on its own if left alone
Those people have vitality
and are inherently clean, you know
Moreover, it's not just my father's responsibility;
we also sincerely apologize
Excuse me.
I came because I have a request
Please don't let Setsuko quit school
This is everyone's request
Just because a mistake was made
That's not Setsuko's intention
Moreover, the wounds that Setsuko
received are something we all vowed to heal
Please
Let's acknowledge this friendship of young people, shall we?
Let's heal this wound with the love of our parents and our friendship
Aunt, please
Dad, please say something...
Please
What are you dawdling about?
Aren't you cooling the watermelon or something?
I just can't compete with young people
Watermelon, watermelon!
I really love Ozaki teacher.
He never gets mad no matter what we do.
I wish there were more teachers like him
Hey.
it hurts, it hurts!
Even if you say something clever, your score isn't enough
Your score will not change this year.
THE END