Translation/Subtitle: jls001999 (jls001999@gmail.com)
Review/Proofreading: coralsundy (coralsundy@gmail.com)
(Paid by coralsundy for the translation, personal use only)
Zoku Judai no Seiten / Judai no Seiten 2
Dangerous Age (1953)
Eat it.
It's delicious.Here you go.
Here you go.
Here's your tea
They are fighting.
Come here
leave them alone.
They are annoying me
Don't look at them
Get hands off of me
You hit me
You are rooster
You are hen
Wait
Your math score is 50
Don't start a fight this early in the morning.
Stop play with her
She told me my math score was just 50
Take a lesson from Akiko.
Mom
I didn't know your were at home
I took the last train home.
aren't you sleepy after getting up so early?
I'm used to it.
Come in
You don't have to get up if you come home late.
I'll do it.
You don't have to worry about that.
I'm more concerned about my job as a hotel accountant,
I know it's a bit of a burden, but you'll have to put up with it.
In return, I'll do whatever it takes until you graduate from school, Aki-chan.
Everything until the day I graduate.
I'll do my best too
And when I finish school, I'll work hard and make you happy, too.
I wonder If I can
Oh,I don't know what I'm supposed to do for homework.
I wonder if he's awake.
You're always beautiful.
Stop saying it
You ask if it's okay to come in through the shoji.
I know.
Bros
Who? Aki?
Yes,May I come in?
Come in
You're not up yet.
Till 10 am
Sleeping in in the morning is good for my mental
That is not good idea
If you look at my shirt, you'll see filth.You see my socks, they're filthy. Now you think sleeping in is filthy?
If you want to be a doctor, you can't be filthy.
I see
You should brush your teeth first
Again
You know what?
Maybe I should stop calling you "brother" from now on.
Why?
Because we're cousins.
It's strange to call you brother
How do you call me?
Well
Mappe is fine
I'm sorry, I'm just calling you that behind your back.
I call you Mashita
Mashita?
It's kind of weird, but I'll get used to it.
Show me your homework
Yeah
Don't smoke it
What's this
It's hard
Get ready,Aki
You'll be late
Wait
That's good
Guess what is this
Please tell us
Look at this stat sheet
Yours?
This is Matsushita teacher's
She preaches to the girls roughly every twenty-seventh day according to this statistical table.
Oh yeah
SO it means
So from today?
Yes, we should be careful
We have to prepare for it
I can't believe you are about to find out a secret about someone like that.
You think so?
Every woman has secrets.
Because it's filthy.
I don't think so.
What do you think, Masako?
It's ok.
And it's not like this statistic hurts Matsushita's authority.
I'm just trying to "scientifically analyze" her hysteria.
You're right
I'm disgusted with you.
I'm her side
Such an investigation is perverse.
Who let me do my homework and then gets all smug with his theories?
But this stat is..
Hey
Teacher
How panicky are you?
You are like thieving cat
Okay, everyone, please turn in your homework from yesterday.
Imakura?
Thank you very much for earlier.
I'm so glad you were on my side.
Yeah, I was angry, too.
I mean, how would they feel if they did that to you?
I know.
I was on my way to catch the train and I picked this up this morning.
Men's watch?
He's a college student.
I tried to give it to him. I was going to give you the nest, but the train left.
So I think I'll wait at the stop tomorrow and give it to him.
Oh, that's so romantic.
Why?
You wait and the nobleman appears.
And he holds your hands
I hope so
He's going to be your wonderful boyfriend.
He's better than I am
Have you decided on a research topic for your senior thesis?
I've been working on it for a while.
I study eugenics in consanguineous marriages.
How is it going?
I'd like to affirm that if I could.
No personal feelings in academia
Why?
You're thinking of your cousin Akiko, the high-schooler.
How’s he?
It's good
Second class?
Your score is 7!
He's shy
He's so pure
Look at us
Your score is 4!
Your score is 2!
Hi
Yamakawa.
I've been waiting for you?
What are you waiting for?
You should go my home
Actually, Mr. Yoshizawa, one of my seniors, is getting transferred to Osaka.I was invited to his farewell party.
Yoshizawa is a member of the soccer team, right?
Isn't it an honor?
Actually, I have to go with my partner.
Will you go with me?
Don't tell your mom
I'll let your father know.
I will go with you
I'll give you one chance to do that, but you have to do what I say.
I'll do anything.
I'll be waiting for you at the Prince's, so just get here as soon as you can.
I'm home
Welcome home.
I promised my friend and I that we would go to a party.
How about this?
When?
From now
You can't
Why?
Your new tutor has come here
I don't wanna study
I made a promise
Can I start from tomorrow?
He has come here all the way
I'll go get you some tea.
Come with me.
What are you doing?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
She's Natsuko.
I'm Makito Miki
I know you.
You are Akiko's cousin
Oh you are
We are cousin
That's a coincidence.
Please have a seat
That's why Akiko's grade is good.
I hope Natsuko s grade will be better
It's not easy
My mom always tell me to learn from Akiko
She's the same as me when she's at home, isn't she?
I have no idea
That's what I thought
Forget it
What's wrong,Yamakawa?
Your partner has not come yet
She's coming soon
You were declined?
No
It's part of being in love.
What are you doing?
You're a bully.
Cheer up.
Have a drink
Here you go
Tangent line of the circumscribed circle at vertex A If we place...
It means 90 degree
Are you listening to me?
I've done something wrong.
Did you promise a party?
Because tonight is a very important part of my youth.
I wonder if life is more meaningful to you if you enjoy dancing or if you suffer through maths.
Well, let's discuss the meaning of life some other time, shall we?
Look at this
You're not romanticist
Have you ever been in love?
I've never been in love.
That's not good
You're already 27
Anyone can fall in love, even if they don't want to.
But not mathematics.
Look at this
Take your clothes off
Water
You're cute
I'm home
Welcome back.
You're back late.
What kind of house did you get a part-time job at?
That's your friend Natsuko's house.
Natsuko's?
She's got a little kid, but he's pretty cute.
Yeah
I bet you're hungry.
I ate there
Sorry I can't eat
Never mind.
Compared to the delicacies of a rich man's home, my cooking is nothing.
That's not what I meant.
It's okay.
You can't teach me about school anymore.
Why you say that?
You'll get a reward for teaching Natsuko.
This is my part time job
I'm fine with being alone.
You're stupid
You got better?
Where's here?
You're all drunk.
It was heavy, and I'm tired of coming all the way back here.
You have pretty eyes.
Is the door locked?
That door sometimes does that.
It's too late
Why don't you get the ashtray?
Take those matches, too.
Thank you.
You know what
Here's fine
Excuse me
You dropped this yesterday
I give up, thank you.
So you've been waiting for me all this time?
Also parabola ikokko situation and straight line overhead to find the intersection of the parabola and the line
You can see this when you think about how we solve quadratic equations and how we solve quadratic equations from the intersection of a hyperbola equal to one and a straight line plus.
We can also represent proportional and linear relationships with straight lines and we can read the relationship.
In this way, we can use our brains The calculations that are done by reading numerical values in this way are called diagrammatic calculations.
This watch is old-fashioned. But it's a precious memento of my father's.
So your father is dead too?
My father died when I was seven.
That's a coincidence.
I'm starting to miss my father
So do I
You'd have to be in the same situation to understand how I feel.
Go ahead.
I have a flat right here, why don't you come by?
But
It wouldn't be good to be found here with your friend.
I'm sorry to have to say goodbye, so why don't you come in?
Come in
Have a seat
Shall I make you some tea?
I will
Don't worry
Ok thanks
Akiko
You get angry?
Come again
This is so great
How's this?
it looks good
I'm glad you like it
Is this ok?
I've come on a sudden business trip  so tell AKIKO about us as soon as you can.
By the time you get back.
So I can't give you this until then?
She's a sensitive girl.
You've been struggling to raise her on your own for so long,I'm afraid to be her dad
She really needs a father from now on.
Yamakawa
You always sleep
Would you go into a man's room unannounced at any time?
Because even if I woke you up, you wouldn't wake up.
What are you doing here?
I came to apologise for breaking my promise yesterday.
You're angry.
I missed school because of it.
It's too late
Don't say that.
I bought your favourite chocolate.
I won't eat it.
Since when do you smoke?
I'm not kids
You've changed a lot, haven't you?
It's none of your business.
Stop it,Yamakawa.
If you do that, it'll be bad for your father who got transferred.
What the hell?
Stop it
I'm done with you.
Here you go
Bros
Are you alright?
I'm home.
Welcome home
Welcome home,math score 50
You are mean
I'm sorry I said that.
Let's get back on track and study.
No...
I have a flat right here, why don't you come by?
You get angry?
Come again
Why don't you just come in?
You get wet
I was hoping you might come by.
Go on, wipe up.
It's raining suddenly.
Take off your clothes and put this on for a while.
Try this.
It'll warm you up and give you energy.
You can't. Escape from here
Escape from here
I thought you were the one who came in.
Come again
Where have you been?
Aki
I'm enjoying my time here.
How is it with him who dropped watch?
How's he?
She's putting on her makeup.?
I'm disgusted with her
Is she insane?
Yes she is
What do you mean?
Ask your teacher
Open page 42
Shut up
Teacher
What do you mean about Ikamono?
Ikamono?
Person like me
Welcome home.
I'm home
I was just leaving.
I made your favourite oshiruko.
And, ...
I'd like to talk to you.
Natsuko
Has studying become more interesting since you've been tutored?
Yeah, I'm thinking about going to med school and becoming a doctor.
I'm like a second Madame Curie.
Madame Curie.?
But now we have penicillin.
I wonder if there's anything left for me to study.
It's not Treasure hunts.
Really
I'm taking the kids to a friend's ranch this holiday. I'm going hiking with the kids to a friend's ranch.
Why don't you come with us?
Yes, take Akiko with us
She's very depressed today.
Really?
I'm home
Are you studying?
Why don't we go hiking with Natsuko next Sun?
It would be better if it was just the two of you?
You’re stupid
Natsuko invites you
She's worried about you, too.
I worry about you, too.
I don't know what you're worried about.
If you have something to say to your mother, you can say it to me.
If it's wrong for me to go to Natsuko's, it's fine with me.
Yes, I've been naughty since I was little, and I used to make you cry.
But now I don't want to make you cry.
Girls are supposed to be crybabies.
You're a little too whiny.
I'll just forget about it.
I'll just pretend it was a bad dream.
You get used to riding.
Wanna run?
I can't.
I will fall down
I'm so nerves
What a nice view
I wanna go there
Let me see your technique
You can go first
Let's race
we are waiting there
Wait for me!
You're too fast
We are racing
I give up
Let's take a rest
Put me down.
Take me there.
You are too heavy
I'm 50kg
You're 55 kg
I’ll do like this
Hold on
The sky is nice
Oh, it's beautiful.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
I take a revenge
Stop it
I wish you were my brother.
I don't want to be such a naughty sister.
Am I?
I guess I am shy
Aki
Oh you are here
It felt so good, I flew too far.
Natsuko wait for you there.
Let's go
You're so stupid, like a child.
Something's worrying you, Aki-chan.
Maybe you're worried about Ueda-san.
We're all worried about you.
Don't worry about me.
Stupid
What's wrong?
Aki-chan has changed completely.
It's good you selected
Yes But
We've decided on the cast.
We'll rehearse for two hours each on Monday, Wednesday and Friday.
There's still a month to go, so please do your best.
If you have any comments, please let me know.
Teacher
Please let me know.
When it comes to our school's anniversary arts and crafts festival, we have a tradition that is so prestigious that even other schools have a reputation for it.
I'm sure there will be many senior guests in attendance.
That's exactly what I told you.
So?
Well
I'm not happy with the casting.
But this was decided by your vote.
I know but
I can't act...
You can't?
You're the only one in our class who can do Jeanne d'Arc.
We all agree on that.
Since she declined, there's no need to force a recommendation.
I thought you wanted to do it yourself.
You're mean.
I just think the role requires the purity of a beautiful virgin.
Then I don't have a problem with it.
That's why everyone recommended her
Ok. have a seat
I know you have some opinions. It was decided by your votes.
And I also think this is the best casting, so I'm going to go with it.
Please give them this
Makita?
Madam?
Come in
Graduation Thesis?
You need to get some rest. You're going to be exhausted.
Are you off today?
I'm not
I'm here to consult with you
What's going on?
Akiko seems to be getting further and further away from me.
I'm very worried
I think maybe it's a UEDA thing.
If she doesn't like us. I think it's okay if I decline his propose
After all, she's at an impressionable age.
But I don't think it's just about Ueda-san.
She doesn't even talk to me.
Please, somehow, listen to Akiko's feelings.
Yasutome
I thought you won't attend PE lesson
You know, you and I always had our periods together.
You're done?
She's getting weirder
Mary, I am an unspoiled maiden.
I disguise myself as a pure maiden
I have a heart stained with lewdness and wickedness
I am a sinful, dirty woman.
My soul is with you, Mary.
Mary's image is clasped to my breast
By me,Mary
I am the maiden who knows no dirt.
Well done.
There's only a week left, so we have to work a little harder.
Let's surprise the principals on the day of the show.
Listen
I wanna tell you
I think our upcoming play will be the last beautiful memory of our youth!
That's right
I think that those who participate in this play I think we should be proud of the purity of our uniforms.
She's talking about us as if we're not pure.
There are rumors that there is such a person, that's why I'm asking you for advice.
Who?
You have some kind of proof?
But I'm not at liberty to say.
If you can think of anyone who might have something to say, on our honor. I think you should tell us voluntarily.
Kumakura-san.
What?
we believed in each other!
I think it's terrible to say such a thing based on an irresponsible rumor.
I think so
She says it's a hoax.
I feel sorry
What if someone doesn't deserve to be in a play that is pure and innocent?
Just tell us what the rumors are.
Masako saw her checking out a book on pregnancy at the library.
not only one time
It's terrible to doubt someone over something as trivial as that.
Besides, anyone would read a book like that.
I've read it
Some people do more research.
I read matrimonial magazines too.
But there are more rumors about her
What kind of rumors?
Tell them
You can tell them
The owner of the local grocer's said her tits are weird.
Is such a terrible thing for us to say?
Because facts are facts.
This is our sacred classroom. We're not having a wellness meeting.
Then I'll tell you plainly
Yasutomi
Do you have the courage to make a vow of purity in front of everyone?
If you're so brave and confident, you should prove it even if you're naked.
I think she came to that conclusion on her own.
Shimakura
If someone said such a terrible thing to me, anyone would leave.
Getting naked in front of everyone is terrible!
You're the ones who hurt the class pride.
I know Akiko better than anyone.
Or do you think I'm less trustworthy than the landlady at the grocery store?
I hate you guys
To be honest,I love her.
But I'm not emotionally ready to do so until I know whether or not I can marry an inbred.
I'm not saying that inbreeding in general is wrong.
There are cases where both positive traits are dominant.
As a doctor, I'm sure you're right.
I'm not in favor of suppressing emotions either.
Someone is visiting you
Who?
She's a beautiful high school student.
That girl, right. go to see her
Oh Natsuko
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Well...
It's about Akiko-san.
Something unusual?
Akiko was bullied a lot at school today.
It's just not normal.
I don't want to believe that she's pregnant.
But Akiko doesn't say anything about it.
But that's terrible,
She's not such a girl
I believe in her too
But
You wanted to ask me?
No no
To be clear, I like her
But I believe a relationship between a man and a woman should be based on marriage.
Some people laugh at me for being old-fashioned.
I'm sorry, I doubt her
Do you wanna eat sweets?
Hold on
I'm home
Aki?
Why didn't you leave me alone?
You're stupid
I'm a doctor.
People who take life for granted are my enemies.
If you were alive, you'd have the pleasure of crying.
Sorry, I'm bad girl
My body is like this
Forget it
I'm a doctor.
For the sake of your friendship with NATSUKO and to restore your own hope, you will be a great heroine of the school play.
I won't tell your mother until then.
I don't know how much you suffered while you were wandering between life and death.
Do you know why you suffered?
I'm sorry.
Good night.
You are Jeanne d'Arc, nineteen years old.
Is that right?
Do you swear fidelity in the name of Jesus Christ?
Tell me why you have assumed the form of a man and why you have come to the battlefield.
Because I heard the voice of God in the forest.
Well, go to your genre, the bird of Orléans.
ONMI is the Son of God who will save France.
All God's voices are heard only by those in ministry
Don't tell lies
In fact, you are probably a demon who indulges in the lewd pleasures of foolhardy soldiers.
I am not
Wrath of God.
Mary
You are demon
High Priestess, please forgive Jeanne
Jeanne was never a witch.
Only God is the judge
please forgive Jeanne
Witch of Orléans, who bears the innocent maidens
Know thy God now.
Set fire on
You are demon
Mary, I send my soul to the high skies with fervent prayers.
Mary, I am a pure maiden.
That tone is the sound of a flock of angels
I feel the image of Mary in my heart
Please hold my hands
Mary, I am a pure maiden.
Take her
What should we do?
I'll go
She was a miscarriage after all.
Just as we thought.
She's ruined her reputation at school.
Who's the man she's with?
I don't know. You should ask Natsuko.
I think he's a college student from her hometown.
I wanna see him
What's the matter?
Leave me alone!
She betrayed me.
She cheated on me.
I understand.
But Akiko has to go to hospital now.
I'd like you to go with me.
She's so dirty lair
Say hi to Dr.Nakata
Please
What's the matter?
She's a patient you brought in yourself.
She's my future wife, the one I was telling you about.
So it's you then?
No, no.
No, it's just different, and it caused me a lot of pain.
I'd been thinking about it for a long time, and then I finally decided to marry her, and that was the day I found out...
she was pregnant.
Well, I didn't know that
Learning about life is even harder than learning to be a doctor.
I'll take care of the patient.
Thank you
Miki
you deceived me too.
You're the one who did this to Akiko.
What did you say here the other day?
What I said wasn't a lie.
I believed Akiko.
That's why I...
Suffer on your own. You deserve it.
What about me, who was betrayed by both you and Akiko?
It wasn't me who got Akiko-san pregnant.
It was an accidental mistake.
Akiko tried to clean up her mistake by dying.
And now she started practicing the role of Jeanne d'Arc as hard as she could.
She tried to regain her lost innocence.
Seeing that, I couldn't help hating Aki-chan.
I made up my mind that I could have a child of my own.
Blood pressure?
Sorry Natsuko
It was my fault
Akiko.
It's okay.
Sorry Natsuko
Akiko.
Kazuko
Natsuko-san, please forgive Akiko-san.
She keeps calling out to you now.
She doesn't say a word about the pain of the operation, she's gritting her teeth and enduring it.
Sorry,Kazuko
Natsuko.
We young people are still imperfect and prone to mistakes.
That's why we must cherish our purity even more.
Aki-chan is risking her life to regain her purity.
Teacher!
Akiko
I've been waiting for you.
Natsuko..I...
Let's go
Sorry,Natsuko
I wasn't going to come.
I don't deserve it.
I couldn't stay while I was thinking about you.
Natsuko.
Don't worry,Let's go
Here's fine
I'm listening here
That's fine with me.
Please go
Akiko
They're all waiting for you.
Look at that.
Come here,Akiko!
She's here
Akiko
I was sorry
I was sorry too
THE END